[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
YOO JAE-HA
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU
Oh. Do you wanna listen to it first?
That's okay. I'll do it after you.
Well, then.
So, I…
I'd like to apologize
if I crossed the line.
Don't worry about it.
It's in the past now.
Do you like Yoo Jae-ha?
YOO JAE-HA
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU
Yes.
"Because I Love You" is my favorite song.
Which one do you like the most?
That one's my favorite song too.
When I come here,
I always listen to it on vinyl.
The remastered CD version
feels oddly slower,
so it's not the same.
[inhales deeply]
I heard it was a technical error
from when it was transferred to CD.
Oh, so that's why.
It happened by pure coincidence,
but I do think the change suits
a breakup song better.
"I will give you everything I have
now that you've come back to me."
It's about breaking up
and getting back together, no?
It's more about his regret
and what he wishes he could do.
[Jae-ha] ♪ But now I realize ♪
♪ I belong to you only ♪
♪ Now that you have returned to me ♪
♪ I will give you everything… ♪
Now that I hear it that way,
it really does sound different.
I guess…
I haven't been able to let you go.
♪ We will never say goodbye ♪
YEONG-MOOK REPAIR SERVICES
♪ Because I love only you ♪
Oh. Hi, Mr. Kang!
♪ Because I love you ♪
[song ends]
Did you come here a lot as a kid?
Yeah. When I bombed a test
or didn't wanna go to tutoring,
I usually hid out here.
Oh, we might've even run
into each other here, don't you think?
Well, I think that
I ran into a schoolgirl
who looked like a complete handful.
And I think I remember seeing
an older guy who seemed incredibly boring.
That probably wasn't me.
People always said that
just being near me was pretty fun.
-[scoffs, chortles]
-[chuckles]
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
[mouthing]
That's just the store next door opening.
[sighs] That scared me.
I thought it was my dad.
Well, don't you think
we should tell your father, though?
He'll probably feel betrayed.
That's true, but…
He's a good kid.
And also a lonely one.
What would you think
if I dated someone like him?
[inhales deeply, sighs]
I don't know.
You said he's a good guy. Why hesitate?
That's a different story.
I don't think the time is right just yet.
Then let me know when the time is right.
Okay.
-It's all set. Wanna listen?
-Yes.
Wow.
[distorted music playing]
[classical song playing]
[gasps] It works!
[sighs]
It sounds just like it used to.
It sounds so beautiful.
[song continues]
I know a photo can't capture sound,
but let's take one as a keepsake.
[chuckles] Sure.
[camera shutter clicking]
EPISODE 10 - DON'T KNOW
THE ANSWER, STILL CLOCKING IN!
An in-store display?
Have you thought of any ideas?
Usually, products from different companies
are displayed in one space.
However, for Home-AI products,
it's the best that we show them
all together at the same time.
Then we may have to
create a separate space
for SAEUM Home-AI zone.
I'm not sure whether that will be possible
under the current agreement.
We understand that.
We wanted to speak to you first
about the possibility.
A Home-AI zone…
Well,
please send me a proposal,
and I'll discuss it internally.
Okay. I will send it to you right away.
You never take an easy route,
Mr. Kang, do you?
I'll take that as a compliment.
Uh, should I reach out to the domestic
stores with the same proposal?
Yes, let's do it on the condition
that we handle
the system integration
and content updates.
I'll take care of the overseas account.
Ms. Cha, Mr. Jeon,
please take care of the domestic side.
-Yes, sir.
Also, I have a business trip
out of town today.
-A business trip?
-Yes.
An international buyer who couldn't attend
the demo requested a meeting.
That's why I'll be in Pohang
today and tomorrow.
Please make sure things run smoothly
while I'm away.
Yes, sir.
-Yes, sir.
[sighs]
Hey, what is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Did something happen?
It's the Legal Team.
I wrote "world's first"
'cause that's exactly what it is,
but now they're demanding proof for it.
What kind of proof?
As far as we know, it's the world's first.
That's what I'm saying.
Get this, they asked if I had
combed through every tiny start-up
in Africa to double-check. [scoffs] Geez.
You know how conservative they are.
No explanation will ever convince them,
-so just change the wording.
-[sighs]
They're seriously the worst.
Hey, do you have a lead
for the web drama series?
[exhales sharply] It's Cho Ga-eul.
[Kee-tae] Who's this Ga-eul?
[Na-ri] It's Cho Ga-eul.
Cho Ga-eul?
[Na-ri] Well, he's the singer of that band
that's blowing up right now.
You know him, right?
Mmm. That's great.
Isn't it?
-[phone buzzing]
-[sighs]
If it weren't for that Legal Team,
everything would be fine.
Yay, I need to rewrite the PR material
from scratch. [laughs]
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
[Si-woo] Be the Clock-out Fairy today.
I'm clocking out right on the dot today.
Look at her bolt
the second Mr. Kang's gone.
Well, I'm out of here too.
Seriously?
-Later.
-For real?
Hope you wrap it up quickly
and go home too… too… too…
Wow, so much for loyalty.
How am I gonna rewrite all this?
[phone buzzing]
-Mr. Kang?
-[Si-woo] Have you left the office?
Yes, I'm on my way home now.
And what about you?
I'm in Busan right now.
You're not in Pohang?
No.
An old classmate reached out to me,
saying he was down in Busan.
I came right after my Pohang meeting.
He must be a pretty close friend
to rush all the way down to Busan.
He threatened me, saying he was debating
whether to sign with us.
Ah.
So it's just business?
I'm here doing sales for the team,
Sr. Associate Cha.
Hmm. Well, you keep up
the good work, Manager Kang.
I'll call you when I'm at the hotel.
Okay.
Who was that? Soo-jin?
No, my girlfriend.
Mmm.
Huh?
What the…
Choi Soo-jin and I divorced
a year after we got married.
Wow.
I had no idea.
I put my foot in my mouth
big time with Soo-jin.
I asked how she was liking
working with her husband.
She'll understand.
But why did you split up?
You two never fought once the entire time.
Everyone was so jealous
and called you a rare match.
Was that so?
[inhales deeply] So you two
are just colleagues now?
Mmm.
She actually got remarried recently.
And you?
Are you dating your current girlfriend
with marriage in mind too?
[chuckles]
[police siren blares]
Hmm?
Oh, you're back.
Is something going on?
A burglar broke into our building.
A burglar?
My unit got hit too.
You'd better go inside
and check your place.
Let's go on in, ma'am.
Sorry?
-Let's get some photos first.
-Sure.
[gasps]
[phone camera clicking]
[sighs]
[Ji-yoon] Someone broke into my place.
[Si-woo] Ji-yoon,
you should go over to my place.
When you get there,
have some warm tea first.
The light-blue container
is the one with chamomile.
CHAMOMILE
[soothing music playing]
[Si-woo] Then make yourself at home
and get some rest.
You'll be safe there.
[sighs deeply]
It's so warm.
[sighs]
CHA JI-YOON
SHE MAKES ME LAUGH
[Ji-yoon] What does…
that mean?
CHA JI-YOON
SHE MAKES ME LAUGH
[sighs deeply]
[door closes]
Ji-yoon?
KANG SI-WOO
MAKES ME LAUGH TOO!
[Ji-yoon] Kang Si-woo makes me laugh too!
-[door opens]
-[chuckles]
Oh, Mr. Kang.
How did you get here at this hour?
I almost missed the last train.
You must've been terrified.
Yes.
So you'll have to forgive me
for wearing your clothes.
I was so scared I forgot to pack mine.
As long as you're safe,
nothing else matters.
[chuckles] I feel very safe.
[chuckles]
Don't tell me you had to drop everything
because of me?
Do I look like someone who would do that?
[chuckles] You don't.
Thank you for coming so soon.
Ji-yoon,
stay here for the time being.
I'll be too worried if you don't.
While you're staying here,
we can look for a new place for you.
Am I moving in?
I'd like it if you did.
[chuckles] I was planning to move
once my lease is up anyway.
Even before the break-in?
Yes.
I wanted to start making new memories
in a new place.
Don't move too far away.
Of course not.
I plan on sticking right by your side.
[sighs]
Yeah. It'd be great to do it at my place,
but we have a patient here. [chuckling]
Oh, please.
Of course I'll prep the green onions
and garlic before bringing them over.
Yeah.
I'll have to call you back.
You're home early.
[bag thuds]
What is this?
What?
Am I a joke to you?
[sighs, grunts]
I told you to keep the cast on, didn't I?
You need to leave it on
if you want it to heal!
How else are we finally going to make it
to that lawyer's office?
[both sigh]
Let's see now,
were you trying to wrap this or unwrap it?
Unbelievable.
[sighs deeply]
I'm making kimchi over at
the laundromat lady's place tomorrow,
so you and Joon-su
can order noodles or something.
-Shouldn't I come along and help out?
-[laughs]
In this state? No way.
You can just take Ji-yoon some of
the kimchi once you're out of your cast.
[grunts]
[sighs] By the way,
is something going on with Ji-yoon?
Why?
I don't know.
She seems to have a lot on her mind.
Is she dating?
It was a bit weird when she asked me
what kind of guy I'd like her to…
Wait, what if she's dating some moron?
A moron?
What if he's a kid Joon-su's age?
Or a total slacker,
a divorcé, or the kind of…
guy she's too embarrassed to talk about?
[groans]
See what you can find out
when you drop off the kimchi.
-Should I?
-Uh-huh.
-Okay. Got it.
-Mm-hmm.
[grunts, sighs]
You can peel some garlic if you're bored.
Mmm.
This here is the absolute last one.
I wasn't going to show you this one
because it's way over your budget,
but since this gentleman here
is being incredibly particular,
I had no choice.
This place faces south,
the neighbors are good,
security cameras are everywhere,
and it has great water pressure.
If you can stretch your budget
to match the price, take it.
I just don't think I can walk anymore.
I'll just look around for myself.
Sure.
Gosh, your husband is so thorough,
isn't he?
[chuckles]
But, you know,
if a man like that is only lenient to you,
he's a keeper. [chuckles]
[door closes]
Great. The water pressure's fine,
and the soundproofing is good.
-However…
-What is it now?
There are many dummy cameras these days.
Are you sure the cameras here work?
I'll head to the management office
and check with them myself.
You two keep looking around. [sighs]
Geez.
Wow.
This place gets
really great natural light.
Yes. Of all the places we saw today,
this is the best one.
It's much more expensive, though.
Besides, it's a little too big
to live in alone.
Then, how about if we live together?
-What?
-We could live here,
or at my place.
Living together is an option.
You want me to move in with you?
You have a few different options
to consider right now.
You could take out a loan
and move in here,
or look for somewhere else
that fits your budget.
You could even stretch yourself thin
and look into buying your own place.
As another option,
you could also consider marriage.
Wait, is this a proposal, Mr. Kang?
I'm ready to do that
at any time, actually.
But today, I'm presenting it
as your housing option number four.
It never once crossed my mind…
that marriage
could be considered as a housing option.
Well, think it over
while you're staying at my place.
What? Do I look pretty?
-You do.
-[laughs]
Like I didn't know that.
[laughs]
[in French] Hello.
Do you speak French?
Yes.
[in English] Come on, help them.
You should try it.
[in French] Uh, can I help you?
Oh, yes. So…
[stammers] This place.
How do I get there?
Go straight. Uh…
At the roundabout. Go 50 meters.
You'll see the sign.
[stammers] I'm sorry,
could you repeat that?
Uh… [chuckles]
Straight.
-Roundabout.
-Mm-hmm.
See the sign.
Okay, I get it.
It was hard
because not many people here speak French.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
-Have a nice trip!
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Have a nice day.
-[No-ah chuckles]
[squeals]
[in English] My French
actually worked! [laughs]
Well done.
Even so, I don't think
they understood at first.
Your pronunciation was a bit shaky,
and you mixed up masculine
with feminine gender.
Did I?
Ugh.
French is so hard because of the genders.
This won't do.
I'll just have to teach you a lot more.
Like what?
Gender differences.
[Jae-in sighs]
FRENCH LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY TEST
So you're really just studying?
Let me quiz you.
Okay.
So, is "beard" masculine or feminine?
Well, it's masculine, of course.
Wrong. It's feminine.
[sighs] Really?
Then,
what about hair?
Hmm…
It's feminine?
No. It's masculine.
[groans]
French is so hard because of the genders.
And that's the reason why
you shouldn't try to use logic.
Memorize them.
-And this?
-I know this.
La bise. That's feminine.
What about what you and I are doing?
And what are we doing?
Embrasser.
It's actually a verb, not a noun.
["Ma Belle Additionelle" playing]
FRENCH LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY TEST
[song ends]
You can put your clothes in here.
I see that you have so much empty space.
Too big for one person, huh?
Once you're done unpacking,
I'll make us some tea.
Okay.
[soft music playing]
[Ji-yoon] I received a strange proposal.
A proposal completely different
from the one I had made.
Not something emotional and impulsive,
but a calm and rational offer.
That's right.
This is how marriages should really go.
-[sighs]
-So why…
do I feel this way?
I love Mr. Kang so much,
and I don't ever want us to break up.
So why…
So why am I hesitating about it?
Ms. Cha, congratulations.
Why? For what?
You're getting a promotion.
What do you mean?
It's not even promotion season.
It's a special one! [chuckles]
[sighs] Manager Cha Ji-yoon,
how on earth are you going
to be able to lead a team
-if you're so slow on the uptake?
-[chuckles]
Mr. Jeon is also a special candidate.
Really?
Finally! I'm finally making
senior associate. [chuckles]
President Han recommended you both,
and Mr. Kang even sent
your performance reports to HR.
I'm so jealous.
I should've applied to the task force too.
Well, it's not like everyone
who applies makes it, though.
[sighs]
And even if you did,
it doesn't mean you'll get a promotion.
Come on, I'm sure you're up next.
You're great at marketing.
I bet you'll get it after the launch.
Oh, uh, thank you.
Excuse me, folks, I'd appreciate it
if you'd focus on me for a sec.
It's only a recommendation.
Who knows what will happen
once HR starts the vetting process?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Too late.
I've already bragged to my wife about it.
-Don't… Don't you dare jinx me, all right?
-[chuckles]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Young-sam clears throat]
You better not. [chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[mouthing] Yes!
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] Don't let your guard down
until the final results are announced.
But still, congratulations.
[Ji-yoon] Hang on.
If I want to keep climbing
the corporate ladder,
wouldn't it be better not to get married?
-Ms. Cha.
-Yes?
Mr. Jeon wants us to join him.
Oh. I'll be right there.
[sighs]
[Ji-yoon] Oh, right.
President Han is married too, huh?
As for the Home-AI Zone,
we won't do it.
-Sorry?
-Pardon?
We concluded that it would create
an uneven playing field
for other companies.
-[sighs]
-I'm sorry.
Well, uh, do you think maybe you could
reconsider, perhaps? [chuckles] Uh.
We understand.
We'll follow up with
a more viable proposal for your store.
Sure.
-[sighs] This isn't easy.
-[sighs]
If they accepted our proposal,
it's obvious that our competitors
would be pushing back.
[customer] Look, honey,
investing in premium appliances
from the start is the way
to save money in the long run!
Let's wait until we move into
a bigger place and buy them then.
And when is that gonna be?
Forget it, I'm not marrying you.
That again?
So when are you going to marry me?
[groans]
-Where are you going?
-Classic.
Every marriage
always kicks off with a fight.
[sighs]
Do you really fight that much?
We fought over wanting
to watch different TV shows,
mmm, over eating out
versus cooking at home,
and over treating
our families differently.
We fought so much
when we were newlyweds. Ugh!
Then how do you make it work?
It's like riding an invisible seesaw.
Since I got my way on this,
I concede on that.
Since you let it slide last time,
I'll look away this time.
Rocking back and forth like that.
That's how you strike a balance.
[groans] Sounds exhausting
just hearing about it.
But, you know,
you eventually get the hang of it.
Yeah. When things feel tense,
you run and do some chores.
What if the seesaw tips too far?
Then it all explodes.
Fights between husband and wife
are inevitable.
What matters is how you make up after.
And how do you two make up?
We, uh, agree to keep our mouths shut
but to stay within view of each other.
-[sighs]
-The thing is,
neither of us are allowed to walk away.
-[chuckles]
-[sighs] Marriage is hard work.
Why? Mr. Kang ask you
to marry him? [laughing]
I need to hit the restroom.
My stomach hurts.
Be right back.
What did you just say now?
I said I'm going to the restroom.
Hey, Jeon Kee-tae.
Stop right there!
Hey!
I must've let my guard down.
Turns out Kee-tae already knows about us.
And the rumors haven't spread yet?
Thankfully, he hasn't told anyone.
And he said he never will.
Looks like Mr. Jeon's quite loyal.
By the way,
why do you keep your tea so far away?
If you just left them there,
it'd be easier to find and make a cup.
Oh. I just don't like
having things lying around.
Oh.
I need these to be in my view.
I'll put them back.
No.
Leave them here. Whatever works for you.
I guess you sleep well
only when it's completely dark.
Yes. It's not the case for you?
To be honest,
I can't sleep very well if it's too dark.
-[chuckles]
-Oh.
You should've told me sooner.
Mr. Kang,
are you always going to
change your ways for me?
-Of course I am.
-But for how long?
It's fine for now,
but you can't do that forever.
Would that be too hard?
Someone told me that marriage
is like riding a seesaw.
One person gives in this time,
and the other person
gives in the next time.
If only one side keeps giving in,
one day the seesaw won't move anymore.
All right, so let's find a way
that works for us.
[Ji-yoon] Will I ever be able to set aside
everything about myself for him too?
[phone buzzing]
6:00 A.M.
WAKE UP
[sighs]
[Si-woo humming]
[humming continues]
[humming stops]
[resumes humming]
[humming continues]
These moments feel like a gift,
which I never would've known
by living alone.
Did you sleep well?
Should've woken me up.
That way, I could've heard
more of your singing.
You'll hear plenty of it in the future.
I'm ready.
Let's go, Mr. Kang.
You're already incredibly beautiful, but…
[chuckles]
SI-WOO'S - JI-YOON'S
I know. Come on.
It's ridiculous that Ms. Cha
is going to hold the same rank as us!
We need to take collective action to block
this kind of reckless fast-tracking.
We can't sit back and watch.
Exactly. If she were under me,
I would've given the worst review.
[coworker 1] Did you all see
the Global Talent Development Program?
[Young-sam in distance] Right?
Yes. Duh, that's right.
GLOBAL TALENT
DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM
[coworker 2] What's the point of looking?
Married guys like me
can't go anywhere anyway.
[coworker 3] I'd even bolt right now
because of our boss,
but I don't meet the requirements.
[chuckles]
ASSIGNMENT COUNTRIES:
RUSSIA, DUBAI, SENEGAL, VIETNAM
[coworker 1] They pay your full salary
and all your living expenses?
What a sweet deal.
[coworker 3] You need
at least three years' experience
with good performance reviews,
Mr. First-year.
REGIONAL SPECIALIST RECRUITMENT
A regional specialist?
Okay, got it.
Wait, aren't you all supposed to be
in the design meeting?
Oh. But the meeting's next week.
The Design Team
is at an exhibition until today, sir.
How many times do I have to tell you
to give me a heads-up on stuff like that?!
-[groans]
-But I did tell you.
Geez.
[sighs] Goodness.
Goddamn it!
Ugh!
[sighs]
How much longer
do I have to put up with Mr. Ko?
Just wait a little while.
You delivered results this time,
so you should be able to transfer
to any team you want.
[sighs]
Ji-Yoon, have you ever been to Senegal?
Are you talking about
the Global Talent Development Program?
[chuckles] Yes.
I saw that Senegal was on the list,
and I just can't stop thinking about it.
It'd be great if you went.
Most people are scared to take the leap,
but you'll definitely level up
if you decide to go.
And it sets you up as an expat.
I'm scared, though. It's not like everyone
who applies gets accepted.
Have you never thought about it before?
I probably would have considered it
if I were still stuck under Mr. Ko,
but I can't go now.
Because of Mr. Kang?
Mmm. I don't really want
to leave him alone like that. [chuckles]
[scoffs]
[sighs] At this rate, you'll be saying
you're marrying him next.
I used to think
that marriage was the natural
next step after dating.
That as long as you loved each other,
then that was really enough.
But not anymore.
There's so much to consider.
And what are you considering, huh?
Whether marriage
will be getting in the way of my career,
whether I can truly live well
with this person,
and most of all,
whether I'm certain
that we will never break up.
Why are you being so intense?
People get married
and divorced all the time.
[sighs]
I can't do that.
[Ji-yoon] I can't let him
experience failure twice.
[coughs]
You're living together?
I believe I clearly said it's temporary.
Whether it's temporary or just for a day…
Well, have you lived with another person
in the last ten years?
I haven't.
So is it okay?
Especially for a picky guy like you?
At first, I was quite concerned too.
"Will I be able to live
with another person again?"
But, you know,
it's not as bad as I thought.
Actually, I love it. A lot.
Wow.
I guess love truly is the only thing
that can change a person.
[both chuckle]
Anyway, how could you
possibly propose to her
by giving her marriage
as another housing option?
You should buy flowers and a ring
and do it properly.
Then it would become hard
for her to say no.
I didn't want to make her feel pressured.
[sighs] But don't you think
she still felt a bit disappointed?
She might even be wondering
if you were being serious.
[playful music playing]
[clears throat]
[giggles]
Hmm…
Why do you keep following me?
-Because you're beautiful.
-[chuckles]
If you're just doing this
because of my beauty,
then I'll pass.
You see, I'm looking for a man
who can appreciate my inner beauty.
Therefore, just give it up, please.
You've got me all wrong.
All I've been seeing is your inner beauty.
Is that another wrong answer?
Yes.
You need to start thinking
outside the box, you know? [chuckles]
Then how about this?
Wait, what is this?
My feelings for you.
Not too heavy, but definitely not shallow.
You don't have to feel bad
about saying no.
I really want you to seriously think
about what's best for you.
I guess I like rings.
Almost forgot all I've been
contemplating over until now.
Contemplate a little more
until you finish that.
I'm going to really savor it.
[chuckles]
[gasps] This thing is huge, isn't it?
[chuckling]
[Young-sam] Mr. Noh,
could we at least grab dinner?
Please give me one more chance.
I'll make sure to deliver this time.
Mr. Noh!
I have discovered
some shocking news to share with you!
MANAGING DIRECTOR NOH
[sobbing]
Damn. Damn it!
[sighs]
[scoffs, breathes heavily]
You always ride
on other people's coattails,
and now you're just handing it over
to Ms. Cha?
Why? To screw me over?
Are you so afraid that
I'll make Managing Director before you?
I'm not afraid
of incompetent people at all,
or those who play dirty.
[sighs]
You still haven't come to your senses.
You're the one
who hasn't come to your senses.
Are you sure that lifeline of yours
is even a reliable one?
At this rate, you might
end up reporting to Ms. Cha.
You… You bastard!
I know I may not be able to pull you up,
but I can sure drag you
straight to the bottom!
[breathing shakily]
[rock music plays]
[grunting]
I can't wait.
[sighs] Damn it.
[breathing heavily]
Geez. Gosh…
[employee 1] Thank you.
[employee 2] Good luck
with the wedding planning.
[sighs] I'll get going now.
[Na-ri] I heard
she's getting married next month,
and she's already
transferring departments?
-See you.
-Bye. Stay in touch.
I will.
-I forgot about that.
-[employee 3] Goodbye.
-[employee 2] Take care.
-About what?
That married couples aren't allowed
to work in the same department.
It's not that they can't,
they choose not to.
It'd be so awkward to work together.
You think so?
But that means one of them might be forced
to give up the work they love.
That's true.
And let's face it,
it's usually the one who's more junior.
[scoffs] Yeah, office marriages
are a terrible idea.
Double-check that
before you show me, okay?
Okay.
Great work.
[sighs]
-Uh, Ms. Choi?
-Yes?
Ms. Choi, we'll get the proposal copied.
-[Soo-jin] That was good enough.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Ji-yoon.
Ms. Choi.
I already heard.
Thank you.
See you.
[sighs]
-A themed zone?
-Yes.
Instead of just building our Home-AI Zone,
we propose letting our competitors set up
their own themed zones as well.
Is it really necessary to go that far?
Well, if it means we can set up
our Home-AI Zone,
then why not?
It would be to our benefit.
And what's your reasoning behind that?
Given the current market,
I believe running ahead on our own
won't win us any applause.
We need to let our partners
and competitors grow with us.
In fact, we just need
to stay half a step ahead.
Frankly, I'm sure we'll win regardless
of what themed zone they bring in.
[chuckles] I knew it.
-I wasn't wrong about you.
-What?
Chasing you down to get you on this team
was totally worth it.
[inhales sharply] You see,
if we got married,
I would have to go to another department.
-Says who?
-Company policy.
Married couples can't work
in the same department.
Exactly, so why should you be
the one to move?
If anyone's moving, it'll be me.
Mr. Kang,
I'm going back to my place.
Why?
Well, the police called me this afternoon.
They caught the burglar.
Ah. That's a relief.
[sighs] But I'm still a little scared,
so could you stay with me tonight?
Of course.
So are you done contemplating?
Yes.
And did you find your answer?
In regards to the fourth housing option…
[keypad beeping]
Huh?
A… A burglar?
[keypad beeping]
Stay here.
No way.
Why aren't you going in?
[high-pitched ringing]
[tense music playing]
Dad.
Dad, please sit down first.
Let's sit down and--
Your daughter and I are dating, sir.
You…
Dad, I'm sorry.
I should've told you sooner.
Outside.
Wait, Dad.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
[sighs] Why didn't you tell me
that you were coming over?
I did.
I called, but you didn't answer.
We thought you weren't home,
so we were gonna leave the kimchi and go.
[sighs]
That guy. He's from the kiss cam, right?
[groans]
-How come Dad already knows him?
-For starters, don't say a word to Mom.
[sighs]
You should pace yourself.
When did you two start dating?
We met in the summer
and then started dating in the fall.
And now it's a snowy winter.
You're telling me
you lied this whole time.
I'm sorry, sir.
Come to think of it,
I've never asked you
what company you worked for anyway.
That's exactly why I liked you, sir.
You never asked what I did,
what school I went to,
or how much money I made.
You didn't ask any of those things.
You just
saw me for who I was.
Well, I'm regretting it now.
Let me ask you this straight up.
Are you dating my Ji-yoon
with the intention
of getting married to her?
You're going to get angry
no matter how I answer that.
You're damn right.
I am angry, kid.
You're laughing, punk?
See, I know what you're worried about
better than anyone else.
[gentle music playing]
But I want you to know this.
Mr. Cha, I care very deeply about Ji-yoon.
Fine.
It's not like you two are children.
You're both smart enough,
so you'll figure it out.
But still,
I'm against it for now.
And I don't care if that upsets you.
Okay.
[sighs]
Hey, punk,
why did it have to be my Ji-yoon?
[sighs]
-I'm home.
-Oh my.
Oh, my goodness. What is going on?
-Oh, gosh.
-Listen, I always side with my wife.
-[grunts]
-If she says yes, then it's a yes.
And if she says no, it's a no.
-Gosh.
-You got that?!
Why are you acting so strange?
-Where should I set him down?
-[Hye-gyeong] Here. Right here.
Yes. Over here.
Lie down for now. Lie down here.
-Geez.
-[grunts]
[sighs] Thank you.
He barely drinks. I don't understand
what made him drink so much.
And who are you?
Uh, my name is Kang Si-woo, ma'am.
Oh my, aren't you…
very handsome. [chuckles]
But, anyway, how do you know my husband?
I'm a regular at his store.
And what does our Mr. Regular do?
I work at the company SAEUM.
Oh! Oh my!
[stammers] My daughter works there too.
-Her name is Cha Ji-yoon. Oh.
-Mom, I'm home.
Huh?
Wh-What a surprise to see a…
a stranger here.
[chuckles]
I should probably get going now.
At least stay for a cup of tea, please.
[chuckles] That's all right.
I'll introduce myself properly next time.
Bye, Madam.
[romantic music playing]
All right.
Then, I hope we definitely
meet again next time.
My gosh. He called me "Madam."
You heard that, right?
Yes. But I call all the older ladies
"Madam" too.
My goodness.
He's polite and treats elders so well.
I wonder if he's married. [chuckling]
[sighs]
[sighs] My dad gave you an earful,
didn't he?
He bought me drinks, gave me advice,
and put his arms around my shoulder.
Yeah, right.
Just be honest.
What did he actually say to you?
That's a secret
between your father and me.
[chuckles]
[sighs] We should have told him
ahead of time like you said.
Then things would've gone
a bit better today.
No. I think today
was the perfect time for this.
We got caught without a second
to prepare or get nervous.
Shall we walk for a bit?
We first met in the summer,
and it's already winter now.
So we just need
to experience spring together.
Right?
The very first spring we welcome together.
How many more springs are there?
Assuming the average lifespan is 80 years,
about 40 more?
Wow.
[chuckles] Hearing that I'll be welcoming
40 springs with one person seems a bit…
Disappointing?
-[chuckles]
-Ah, I knew it.
I guess I played the marriage card
a little too early.
[chuckles]
Tell me, Mr. Kang,
aren't you afraid of marriage?
Yes, I am.
Especially since I've failed
at it already. How could I not be?
Is there a "but"?
But it's with you.
Because I want to see
40 seasons of cherry blossoms,
summer fireworks,
autumn leaves, and snowy winters with you.
Sure, marriage can cause pain,
but it has its fair share of benefits too.
Also, if you ever get sick
or need legal protection,
I can officially step in
as your protector.
And I can give you everything I own
if you need me to.
I didn't realize that,
but it's actually a very tempting offer.
What's more,
I'm older than you, as you know.
[chuckles]
Mr. Kang.
I really don't think
I can choose
option four, after all.
So I'll just look for a place
that's within my budget.
As for…
your marriage proposal,
I'll keep thinking about it.
Then my proposal's only on hold,
not rejected.
It's a 40-year, long-term project,
so take your time reviewing it.
Okay.
And when my love is overflowing,
I might just say yes
before you even have time
to get nervous or prepare for it.
I'll be waiting right here.
[chuckles]
[exhales]
This is it!
[exclaims]
[clears throat]
[breathing deeply]
[giggles]
[employee] Did you see this?
[suspicious music plays]
BLAH BLAH - ANONYMOUS ONLINE
COMMUNITY FOR PROFESSIONALS
OFFICE AFFAIR
[employee 1] Anyone want the scoop
on a massive affair going down at SAEUM?
Give me enough upvotes,
and I'll drop the details.
[typing]
[phone buzzes]
OFFICE AFFAIR
[employee 2] Hurry up and spill.
The suspense is killing me.
[employee 3] 100% agree. Who is it?
Someone's definitely sweating right now.
[employee 4] I have my popcorn.
Hurry and spill the tea.
[commenter] Wow. Cheating scandals from
other companies are the absolute best.
[employee 5] Agreed! The vibe on
the eighth floor is super tense right now.
-Maybe this is why.
-[commenter 2] SAEUM's wild.
[Ji-yoon] An affair?
Someone's probably
just spinning stories again.
[Kee-tae] Still, there's no smoke
without fire. I agree too.
[Na-ri] I'm super curious too.
Wish they'd hurry up and tell us.
[employee] Since everyone wants it,
here it is.
[Kee-tae] Hey, it's up!
SINCE EVERYONE WANTS IT,
HERE IT IS
[employee 1] Here's something no one knew.
SAEUM's male Manager K
and female Manager C from another team
used to be married!
They divorced, then crossed paths again
when Manager C got headhunted by SAEUM.
But get this,
Manager C just got married recently.
Since then, things between them
have been super sketchy.
Manager C joined K's project,
they meet privately,
and even outside of work.
And here's the smoking gun.
The day Manager C was in Busan
for a design expo,
Manager K was staying at the same hotel!
If you're suspicious, check if they were
actually married first. [chuckles]
RECEIPTS FROM THE SAME HOTEL
ON THE SAME DAY
[employee 6] Manager K is Kang Si-woo,
and Manager C is Choi Soo-jin, right?
[employee 7] Those two were
actually married?
[employee 8] So are you saying Mr. Kang
is a divorcé or a home-wrecker?
-Which one is it?
-[employee 9] He's both!
[employee 10] Holy crap.
I've seen them together in a car before.
[employee 11] The vibe was weird then too.
[employee 12] They're great at their jobs
and sleeping around too.
[employee 13] Don't tarnish the company's
reputation and just quit together already.
[TODAY'S HOT ISSUE]
OFFICE AFFAIR
[phone buzzes]
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Kang,
I think you should see this.
SINCE EVERYONE WANTS IT, HERE IT
IS! HERE'S SOMETHING NO ONE KNEW
SAEUM'S MALE MANAGER K
AND FEMALE MANAGER C
FROM ANOTHER TEAM
RECEIPTS FROM THE SAME HOTEL
ON THE SAME DAY
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
-Oh.
-Mr. Kang?
You just stay quiet. Don't do a thing.
[sighs]
[pants] What is all this?
Tell me, how did this happen?
[sighs]
I need you to take immediate action
to have that post removed.
Since it's a third-party app,
there's nothing we can do right now.
But with time…
[Soo-jin] Who wrote that post?
I am going to report them immediately
for defamation.
Let's all take a deep breath.
So, is it true that you were both
in Busan on the same night?
That's right. I was on a business trip
with my team for a design expo.
I submitted those hotel receipts, yes,
but I never once ran into Mr. Kang
while I was there.
I noticed your business trip
was scheduled for Pohang, Mr. Kang.
I went to Busan due to
a sudden request from a buyer.
I simply picked
one of our company's partner hotels.
I had no idea where Ms. Choi stayed.
That's the truth.
Then is it true
that the two of you used to be married?
-Yes.
[groans]
Honestly, our strict company policy
is not to intervene in personal matters.
So your only option is to file
for a police investigation or a lawsuit.
So we just have to sit back
while the entire company gossips about us?
The noise will die down eventually.
And what if someone
spread this rumor with ill intent?
Who would do that?
Well, that's for the company to find out.
Internal corporate receipts
have been leaked within the company.
Shouldn't the Audit Team
be investigating that?
All right. I'll look into that.
[Ji-yoon] Where are you?
[sighs]
[Kee-tae] Totally groundless!
You're all writing fiction.
Anyone who actually knows Manager K
knows he's a total workaholic
who wouldn't bleed if you pricked him.
So you already knew
that they used to be married?
Mmm.
Wow, you're so amazing, you know that?
No, not really.
I can't do anything about this right now.
[employee] You're K, aren't you?
[chuckles]
I'm not. And just believe it
when I say it's not true. Geez.
I don't think this will fade away easily.
[No-ah] I asked a friend on the HR team,
and they said it's hard
to take down Blah Blah posts.
You know…
I was actually with Mr. Kang that night.
The night they were supposedly together?
Mmm.
A burglar broke into my place,
so he rushed back to Seoul.
If I'm able to clear this up,
it'll prove they weren't having an affair.
You can't be serious!
Why would you get involved like that?
If you do, you'll just end up
throwing yourself under the bus.
She's right.
Uh, when you're up for a promotion,
you shouldn't even cough the wrong way.
Just close your eyes, cover your ears,
and wait for the storm to pass. Got it?
[sighs]
MR. KANG, I THINK YOU SHOULD
SEE THIS - WHERE ARE YOU?
[coworker clears throat]
So what happened?
-What do you mean?
-Mr. Kang and Ms. Choi.
You're all on the task force,
so you must know something.
Yeah, we do know.
We know Mr. Kang is way too busy
to have time for an affair.
Come on, you don't know that.
No matter how busy you are,
you can still find time to sleep together.
She's right. You can use a business trip
as an excuse to stay in the same hotel.
Then you two go ahead and do that.
And stop running your mouths
about other people's lives.
Let's just go order. Yeah?
Uh, you can only sit after you order.
It's that way.
-Hold back. Please.
-[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] I'm on my way in
after getting some fresh air.
So did you go to her room,
or did Ms. Choi come to yours instead?
[tense music playing]
I mean, why did you
even bother divorcing anyway?
What, you got a thing
for dangerous relationships, huh? [laughs]
Is this all you've got?
Is this how you planned to ruin me?
I have no idea what you mean, you know?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You wanna hit me? Do it.
Yeah, hit me in front
of all these people watching.
Do it. Yeah.
Ms. Choi and Mr. Kang
weren't together that night.
And how could you possibly know that?
Because I was the one who was with him.
What?
[romantic music playing]
Mr. Kang and I
are dating.
[gasps]
Is this your answer to my proposal?
Yes.
[music continues]
SPECIAL THANKS TO BAE YU-RAM
[Ji-yoon] I thought that
by telling the truth,
the lies would disappear.
You have to brace yourself.
[colleague] Do you think Cha Ji-yoon
actively threw herself at him?
[Soo-jin] People can be crueler
than you'd think.
But don't let them break you.
Well, I'm still the same.
Are you able to say
with absolute certainty
that no personal feelings
affected that decision?
[No-ah] How would you feel if
I got transferred to an overseas office?
[Na-ri] A complaint has been filed
against Mr. Kang.
[Young-sam] Have you really
lost your mind?
[U-jin] Why's there so much noise lately?
About Ms. Cha, let her go.