But if we reunite,
and I act like a stranger, that's your cue.
May I leave your order here,
ma'am?
- You sure?
- Huh?
Don't you share this space with your husband?
No.
This is my bedroom, where I sleep alone.
Things have gone unbelievably well
since we last spoke.
Ouji...
My husband has become kind,
and work has come pouring in.
But, I...
[For once you've opened a door...]
I want to see what lies beyond this.
The time...
We're still good.
My next delivery
isn't for another 25 minutes.
That feels amazing...
It was a mere 25 minutes of my life.
[Episode 10]
I feel so relieved.
That's a bit crude.
I can write.
I reckon I won't see that man again.
Nor will I ever tell my husband about this.
But I don't regret what I've done.
If I had to make a comparison...
[Ram3]
"It felt like you were finally relieved
of being constipated"?
Great comparison.
But that's really what it felt like!
Like, relieving yourself
after a long day of work.
Oh gosh...
Our resident author has a way with words.
- In any case, I'm happy for you.
- Huh?
I can tell the experience really helped you.
Yeah, it probably did.
Things were going well with Ouji,
and I was satisfied enough.
I assumed I didn't need sex in my life.
But I was only trying to delude myself.
And the relief I felt after sex
made that fact all the more obvious.
All this time, I've wondered why
I couldn't have these experiences.
It made me feel inferior to others.
But now I see it was no big deal after all.
I'm like, "that wasn't so hard", you know?
Haru, that means it was a big deal to you.
You think so?
I've actually come to a similar revelation.
About why I'm so attached to him.
What, is your fling good in bed?
Language, Akina.
That's not entirely it.
My husband is self-centered, even in bed.
Doing it with him was never enjoyable.
It always felt like an obligation of sorts.
That sounds difficult.
Which is why when I met my partner now,
I felt fulfilled.
Sexually?
I mean, yes, that too.
But I felt as though he saw me as a woman.
As a human being, even.
It was honestly comforting, in a way.
I get it.
I grew up with a low self-esteem,
but I finally feel like that's changing.
It's like I'm more confident now,
for some reason.
See? It was a big deal for you.
Meanwhile, mine's only tanking.
Huh?
My self-esteem.
It's about to hit rock bottom.
Even though I feel
plenty comforted and fulfilled.
Is this about the male "therapist"?
Yeah. The "therapist".
And I'm just a customer.
I can't deny that.
But you can't ask to meet in private, right?
Because you wouldn't want to be rude.
Nothing will happen
if you don't at least try.
I see a one-night stand
has made you confident.
It was a one-afternoon stand, mind you.
What's the difference?
I wonder if I'll be a customer forever.
I gotta go.
- Huh?
- I'm meeting him tonight.
I think I'm getting used to this loop.
I can't stop myself from wanting to see him.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. It's been three weeks
since the operation.
You worrywart.
Can I call you?
Sure.
Hello?
Hey there.
You're outside? Is everything okay?
I need to be outside to go out the house.
I guess...
I promise I'm fine, okay?
I can't help it, I worry about you.
Thanks.
Why did you want to call?
Big news.
I'm going to be on the cover of a magazine!
I'm counting on you to style me, Fuyumi.
Fuyumi?
Sorry, I was just so shocked.
Congratulations.
Will you come celebrate with me sometime?
Sure.
Thanks.
I'll reach out again once I'm home, okay?
Talk to you soon.
Good evening.
You ran here?
The train was running late.
Besides...
I wanted to see you.
I'll go ahead and take a shower.
Akina.
Would you mind letting me go?
Sorry.
No worries.
I'm just a bit sweaty now, is all.
But you're free to cling once I'm clean.
Has everything been alright since then?
Huh?
That stalker. Has he been bothering you?
Not at all. I'd forgotten about him.
That's good to hear.
I'll get our bath ready.
Go all the way with me.
I mean, what? Sorry.
I was just kidding.
Akina.
Jeez, I must be pent up or something.
I can't believe I just asked that.
A friend said she felt great
after doing it all the way.
She must've influenced me a bit.
I seriously can't believe myself.
Good night, see you next time.
What the heck am I even doing?
This color is beautiful.
[Love Survivors]
I had pink in mind, but this is wonderful.
It really is.
I wanted the cover
to have a lasting impression,
with the hopes that it'll become
a best-seller.
Exactly. Our goal is a volume two.
Really?
But I think it'll be doable.
Oh? You've been on a roll lately.
I'm exploring new avenues for myself.
Sounds potentially raunchy.
Why? I meant it as a change in heart.
I feel more confident in myself now.
I was always on this side of the border,
but I've finally stepped one foot
into the other side.
Sorry, I'm not exactly following.
No worries.
What do you think of this cover?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're early.
Yeah. Tomorrow and the day after
are full recording sessions.
- You're staying the night?
- Yeah.
Sorry I've been holed up at the studio.
Don't be. I'm looking forward to the album.
Thanks.
Mind if I join you for a drink?
- Cheers.
Yum!
Ouji knows something happened to me.
Do we have any of that expensive cheese left?
The one we got as a gift.
I think so.
I'll get it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
But he probably won't pry,
so long as it seems like I've calmed down.
We had a solid chunk left.
Great.
This side, and that side.
The border used to be so rigid, and yet...
I scare myself.
How so?
Before, I was so desperate to know
what he was thinking.
But now, I can read him like a book.
Sorry, what is this about?
Erm... a pet.
I don't remember you owning a pet.
I don't.
Then your next book will be about a pet?
Yeah, I'm considering it.
Can't wait to read it.
[Busi-CAFE]
Did something inspire you to change?
Huh?
You said you felt more confident.
Right. Yeah, you could say that.
So, what happened?
Nothing major or life-changing, really.
The protagonist of your book. Is she...
Sorry, I need to take this.
Hello?
Oh, yes. It's good to hear from you.
Next month?
[Secret]
Yum!
Question.
Do you guys prefer to know secrets?
I mean, some things are better kept
in the dark, right?
Yeah, I'd rather keep my secrets.
My phone is full of them.
Which is why I keep my phone screen down.
- Right.
- What?
You're keeping a secret from Haru?
That mysterious vibe is a no-no nowadays.
Other way around.
Other way around?
Haru's keeping something from you?
That stalker - I mean,
girl obsessed with you, keeping a secret?
Surprising.
How can you tell? Is she acting jumpy?
The opposite, actually.
She's become calm.
Like she's self-assured now.
So you suspect a secret?
Yeah.
I'm surprised.
Right? She's always been an open book.
No, I'm surprised by you.
You wouldn't notice something like that
if you weren't observing her.
Question is, do you want to know her secret?
Well...
Not an immediate answer, I see.
Things are going well,
so I thought I wouldn't pry.
Really?
We haven't fought or anything,
so it's been peaceful.
Then don't open Pandora's box.
You're probably just overthinking it.
- Exactly.
- Right?
No, I'm really not.
Heading out already?
Yeah. Ouji... My husband's out tonight,
so I thought I'd grab dinner on my way back.
Mind if I join you?
It's been a while
since we had dinner together.
Yeah. The last time was
when we were both rookies.
And now you're a full-fledged author.
I wouldn't say that.
Who would've thought
I'd publish a book, right?
I always had my faith in your writing.
You deserve the recognition.
Thanks.
I'm just speaking my mind.
Yikes. I can totally see his love for me.
This situation, it's a bit...
- Fun.
- Huh?
Sorry, I was just thinking
it's nice hanging out with you.
And I said it.
I can't believe I'm being so bold!
Haru.
Is your book really based on
a friend's story?
Huh?
It felt more like you were writing about
your own experiences.
Well...
If...
If everything you wrote about is true...
Then you should end that marriage
while you can.
No, but I...
The protagonist feels relieved now.
But what about your body?
Though you may feel fine now,
ultimately the issue remains.
Well...
I would give you both my body and heart.
Sorry.
I love you.
Will you stay with me tonight?
[Hotel PAL]
[Preview]