What about us?
Are we dating?
What should we call each other?
My number is saved as Orange.
Your number is saved as Orange’s owner.
Will Tle choose to attend med school like Ko Song?
Aren’t you worried about being apart from him?
Ko Song.
After we graduate from high school,
will you leave me?
Even though we like different things,
it doesn’t mean we will go separate ways.
Don’t argue with me.
If you do, I’ll kiss you.
(I always remember the atmosphere before we graduated high school.)
(It was the time when we were forced to grow up.)
(It was the time we began to fear)
(that if we didn’t study hard,)
(we might be the only ones who didn’t get into college.)
(Everything that used to be simple, it suddenly became hard.)
(The entrance exam was approaching.)
(We needed to stop playing around.)
You need to study.
The exam is coming soon.
Sorry.
What did you say?
(Even I, Boss Ko, had to give in to the educational system.)
You will take the entrance exam soon.
I want you to think about whether your interest is still the same.
If you’re still going to choose the same faculty,
show me your hand.
Okay, you can put your hand down.
Choosing the faculty is important.
Do you think universities in Bangkok are better?
I don’t think so.
You should choose a university based on
the curriculum and the living environment.
How about this? Close your eyes.
Imagine your college life.
Did you imagine you were living in Bangkok?
Yes.
The thought of living in the city already gives me chills.
Are you only considering schools close to home?
If I can choose, I want to be close to home.
If I live away,
my mom won’t be able to live.
Okay, open your eyes.
Do the test and see if the result matches
the faculty that you want to choose.
Do it.
Which university do you plan to attend?
I’m not sure.
I’ll attend any university that I get into.
Why didn’t you wake me up?
I saw you sleeping soundly. I didn’t want to wake you up.
Hey.
Today is Saturday.
Why don’t we buy a comic book to read?
You should be studying. You didn’t study last night.
But I’ve been studying with you for over a month.
Can I have a break?
You are smart.
I’m sure you can get into college.
Don’t be careless.
Students from other schools are also smart.
You’re so boring.
Can we go in the evening?
We can ask our friends to go have snacks.
It’s okay.
You should go back to your study.
I’ll ask August to go with me.
You’re so cold.
I feel lonely, but you refuse to hang out with me.
(So who would help my mom buy groceries?)
(Augar went to basketball practice since early this morning.)
Achi is definitely with Augar.
Why is no one free this weekend?
(What is Ko Song doing?)
(Let me guess.)
(He’s studying.)
Yeah.
All he does is study all day.
How can he do that?
(He wants to go to med school.)
(It’s not easy to get in.)
(You should be more understanding.)
You nag me just like my mom did.
I’m going to take a shower.
I’m hanging up.
Teenagers these days are unpredictable.
They can quickly go from having fun
to feeling lonely, hungry, or sleepy.
Uncle.
What?
What degree do you have?
Which college did you attend?
I didn’t even attend middle school.
I only attended elementary school.
My oldest brother was the only one who attended college.
Ko, you know what.
When I was in school, I…
Not attending college,
it’s not a big deal.
But it’s better to attend college.
What are you thinking?
Don’t make the wrong choices.
I warn you.
I’m not doing anything.
Of course, I will go to college.
I’m just curious why he has to work that hard.
Why does he want to study in a difficult field
and go to college far from home?
Uncle.
If I move away, will you be lonely?
I think my ears would feel more comfortable.
When are you going to leave?
I’m counting down to it.
Uncle.
I’m going to feel that something is missing.
We see each other every day.
But what can I do?
Everyone has to grow up.
You can’t expect them to be with you forever.
This is how life is, Ko.
Everyone has to go on their own path to grow up.
Go on their own path to grow up?
He’s been spacing out for a while.
Uncle.
What if we don’t go on our own path?
What are you doing here?
We just finished the warm-up.
I’ll let you take a break before we gather again.
Go take a break.
Thank you.
You forgot, didn’t you?
Forgot what?
We’re going to study for the exam together today.
That’s right.
I forgot to tell you that
my coach called a practice session today.
I’m going to go to a training camp soon.
I have many things to work on in the practice today.
The practice will probably wrap up in the evening.
I can’t study with you anymore.
I’m sorry, Achi.
Coach just told me yesterday evening.
When I got home, I fell asleep.
I forgot to call to tell you.
Aren’t you going to study?
The exam is coming soon.
Let me get through this period first;
I’ll find time to study with you.
I promise that I will study at home too.
You have to keep your promise.
Of course.
I don’t mean to be pushy.
I’m just worried about you.
I want you to get into a university.
I don’t think that you are pushy.
I like it when you’re worried about me.
I’ve got to go back to the practice.
Bye.
You can do it.
I’m worried about Augar.
All he does is practice basketball.
He probably secretly studies.
He’s studying when he’s at home, right?
Yeah.
He’s on the national youth team now.
He’s still excited about it.
So he wants to put all his focus on it.
Can you try to understand him?
Yeah, I understand him.
I know that we all have different interests and goals.
But…
Doesn’t Augar want to grow up with us?
Everyone has to go on their own path to grow up.
This is how life is.
We all have to go on our own path to grow up.
What are you thinking?
Can you tell me?
Why do we have to grow up?
We are humans.
We have to grow up.
No, I mean…
why do we have to go on our own path?
Why do we have to go on our own path to grow up?
Why did you say that so casually?
Why are you acting like going our separate ways is not a big deal?
Because it’s an inevitable reality.
We can’t be together forever.
We have to move forward.
We can’t stay in the same place forever.
That’s why we have to go on our own path to grow up.
But…
don’t you want to grow up together?
Don’t you want to be together?
Damn. I’m so sore.
You are studying for less than ten minutes.
But you already complain.
For me, studying for ten minutes is a lot.
Damn.
What is that?
An mp3 player?
Yeah.
Damn. I really want one.
My mom’s friend bought it for me.
I still don’t know how to put songs into it.
You need to connect it to a computer.
Then you copy songs to the device.
Teach me how to do it.
Augar, what are you studying?
Augar.
Augar, wake up.
Huh?
Wake up. You need to study.
It’s late. Can I go back to sleep?
I will study tomorrow.
You always say that.
But you wake up late every morning.
Not every morning.
Yesterday, I woke up at 5 a.m.
It’s because you had basketball practice.
What’s up with your tone?
Do you know that you are sulking?
No, I’m not sulking
You are not sulking?
I’m not sulking.
You’re so sulky.
I’m not sulky.
Huh?
Why is this baby so sulky?
What?
Are you leaving?
Aren’t you going to sleep over here?
I can’t concentrate.
I’d better go home to study.
Calm down.
Just think of this as spending time with friends.
Can’t we do that later?
We are having an exam in a few days.
Do you want to leave that much?
Orange.
Don’t get upset.
I just want to try my best.
I want to know whether I can do it.
I…
I don’t want to regret it when I look back.
After the exam, everything will go back to normal.
I will have time to play with you.
Which university will you attend?
Is it far away?
I’m not sure.
In your future,
will I be a part of it?
Of course.
That’s why I told you not to feel upset.
Don’t overthink it.
I’m not moving away.
Can you try to understand me?
I’ll take a break.
Achi, what are you doing here?
I should be the one who asks you that.
What are you doing here?
Don’t you know we have an exam today?
Why didn’t you take the exam?
Did you hear what I asked you?
Yes.
But I told you I don’t need the exam to get into college.
There’s no point in taking it.
I would have failed it anyway.
Do you really not care about it?
Don’t you care about your future?
Yes, I do. That’s why I’m practicing basketball.
I love basketball. You know it.
Can’t you let me seriously pursue this?
Why are you pressuring me to do those things?
Pressuring you?
No, I mean…
I feel pressured.
I’m not saying what you are doing is wrong.
I just want you to understand me.
Have you ever told me that?
If you don’t want to do it, just say it.
Then why did you promise me?
You want me to do it, and I want to do it for you.
It doesn’t make me happy.
I just wanted you to prepare
for the entrance exam like everyone else.
I want us to attend the same university.
I want us to be together just like now.
I want that too. Do you think I don’t want it?
But university is not my place.
Then we won’t be together.
I do understand him, August.
I don’t like myself being pushy like this.
Augar doesn’t think of you that way.
Don’t be so hard on yourself.
But I meddled in his life.
I know that’s what he loves.
I just don’t like this feeling.
I feel like I’m the only one who tries to do everything so we can be together.
I get it.
I think Augar keeps you in his mind in everything he does.
But right now, he’s really into what he loves.
He just got an opportunity to do it.
He likes playing basketball, but that doesn’t mean I like you any less.
He may act stupid sometimes, but he really likes you.
Can you try to understand him?
If basketball is his pride,
you are his best support.
Okay?
Stop overthinking it.
Why don’t you go see Achi?
Why did you come to see me?
He doesn’t understand me.
I don’t understand you either.
You should leave. I’m going to study.
Even you are studying for the exam?
Why is everyone so serious about getting into a university?
I can’t believe it.
Don’t you think you need to study too,
even if you want to be an athlete?
You can’t just neglect it.
What if you break your arm or leg?
Then how are you going to make a living?
I know that.
But what do you want me to do?
Do you want me to throw this chance away
and go back to studying?
I got into the national team.
Not everyone can do it.
What can I do to make him understand me?
Are you two also fighting?
What?
Are you fighting with Ko Song?
♪ All I can do is keep them inside an old picture ♪
♪ And pray that we will again meet each other ♪
♪ Wanna say "I love you" ♪
♪ Wanna say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ No more watching from afar, letting chances go ♪
Ko Song. Write a message for me.
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
♪ “I love you” I never said ♪
Hey.
Huh?
It’s our last day in high school. Smile.
I’ll write you a message.
Sure.
♪ But you left without a word ♪
♪ Kept thinking, if I’d said them first ♪
♪ Things might've turned out better ♪
♪ Distance only makes me think it over ♪
Ko.
♪ What should be said if we again meet each other ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ No more watching from afar, letting chances go ♪
GOOD LUCK, ORANGE’S OWNER
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
I LOVE YOU, ORANGE.
When you were studying for the exam,
I thought you were sucked into a book.
You are talking nonsense.
Everyone was doing that too.
Can I ask you for real?
If you attend med school,
will you have to study this hard every day?
Probably harder than this.
It’s understandable.
You want to save lives. You need to be very smart.
All the cures are written in books.
If you don’t read them, you won’t know.
Ouch.
Right now, you need to help me first.
Orange juice got into my eye.
So revealing.
Don’t touch it.
The exam result will be announced tomorrow.
Are you nervous?
Very much.
You know that I really like you, right?
No matter what our exam results are, I still like you.
I will find the best way so we can meet often.
Don’t worry.
Do you get it?
See you.
Yes.
I want to cancel the set-top box.
I’m going to move.
I don't need it anymore.
I can’t take it with me.
I’m going to move to another province.
Yes, my whole family is moving.
Damn.
I got in. Augar, I got in.
You really did it.
Call Achi.
Yeah, I’ll call and tell him.
No, you call to ask him where he got in.
Okay, sure.
Hello, Achi. Did you check the result?
Damn, the faculty of medical technology.
Which university?
So it means you and Augar
will attend different universities.
Congratulations.
Yes, I got into the university that I want.
I’m going to become a Bangkokian.
I will buy a cool pair of jeans to wear.
Sure. See you.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I got in, Dad.
Really?
Well done, my son.
I’d better call your mom.
Honey.
Aren’t you with Ko Song?
He left the house in the afternoon.
He didn’t take his bike.
Really?
Hello.
August, is Ko Neung with you?
What about Augar?
I called Achi.
He said Ko Neung wasn’t with him.
Alright.
I’ll check his house again.
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
What’s up?
Why do you look like that?
Where have you been?
I should be the one who asks you that.
Are you avoiding me?
Why couldn’t I find you?
Do you know I’m really worried?
When you move away,
we won’t be seeing each other anyway.
Why do you have to worry?
Let’s go talk somewhere else.
You took me here.
What do you want to talk about?
Are you mad
that I didn’t tell you about moving?
Weren’t you going to tell me?
You are moving away.
Why didn’t you tell me
so I could prepare myself?
I didn’t mean to not tell you.
But it happened so fast.
It happened during the exam.
I didn’t want to fight with you then.
You didn’t want to fight?
I needed time to prepare myself too.
It was not easy to tell you.
So you chose not to tell me.
How could you do this to me?
I didn’t mean to not tell you.
It was still uncertain back then.
If I didn’t get into the school,
I would continue to live here.
If that was the case,
I didn’t want to say anything to worry you.
I got into a university in Bangkok.
My mom wants me to move back to study there.
Is this the reason you studied so hard?
Have you ever thought about me?
You can’t just move here
and move away as you want.
I want you to try to understand my reason.
You can’t just see it
only from your perspective.
Why don’t you just say I’m selfish?
I just want you to try to understand me.
I can’t make this decision alone.
Have you ever tried to understand me?
How will I live, Ko Song?
How will I live when you are gone?
Do you think I’m okay with this?
Do you think I’m happy
to know that we will be apart?
Do you think this is what I want?
But you still chose it.
You want to leave.
Am I wrong to choose my dream?
This is my future.
Didn’t you say
I would be a part of your future?
I told you.
Nothing will change between us.
So which university did you get in?
You don’t need to know.
No need to be sarcastic.
I’m just doing what you did to me.
We keep arguing the same thing.
Do you really want me to leave, don’t you?
You are the one
who wants to leave.
Fine.
Go.
If you want to leave, then leave.
Don’t come back if you leave.
Fine, I’m leaving.
Don’t ever come back.
Go away.
Go!
Ko.
Are you alright?
What’s wrong?
Are you okay?
If I were him, I would leave too.
You were crying and whining.
I told you everything.
But why didn’t you take my side?
How can I take your side?
From what I hear,
Ko Song didn’t do anything wrong.
His only fault is not telling you about moving.
You should have seen what I saw.
My boyfriend was studying so hard,
barely taking any rest.
So he can go on his path to grow up.
He’s happy that he got in, though we will be apart.
Am I supposed to be happy for him?
Yes.
Do you expect him to be with you forever?
You want him  to throw his dream and future away.
So he could be with you forever.
You two would make a living from fishing.
Is that what you want?
I understand that you are sad
about being apart from him.
But this is normal.
You don’t need to live next door
to each other.
You don’t need to have a meal
or go to school together.
You can still be important people
in each other’s lives.
Which drama did you learn this from?
I’m practicing it to tell Achi.
I knew it.
I want you to think about it carefully.
When you calm down,
you should go talk to him.
He must feel hurt to hear you say that.
Achi
I’m going to go to Tong’s shop
to get what I ordered.
Okay, Mom.
Augar, what are you doing here?
Why? Do you own the market?
Stop joking around.
Don’t you have basketball practice?
I can’t focus on the practice
if you are still mad at me.
I’m not mad at you.
Augar.
Are you still mad at me?
I told you I’m not mad at you.
Then why are you making that sour face?
What’s wrong?
I think I was being a jerk to you.
I was being too pushy.
Instead of trying to understand you,
I was acting like that toward you.
No, I know you mean well.
I’m still worried about you.
I know you want to be an athlete.
But you still need to attend university.
Who said I wouldn’t?
Achi.
I got accepted to the Faculty of Sport Science
through the athlete quota.
Really?
Yes.
I was going to wait until the results came out
before telling you.
But you were mad at me.
So I didn’t have a chance to tell you.
And…
you are going to attend a university far away.
I’ll go to Bangkok to visit you often.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
And…
Let’s make up.
Why are you here alone?
My mom said she would go get something
and hasn’t come back.
(Now, he is on cloud nine and smiling all day.)
(Now, it becomes annoying.)
It’s good that they reconciled.
He was practicing what he was going to say with me.
It was so cheesy.
(Anyway, are you going to see the fireworks
celebrating the MP’s birthday?)
No, I don’t want to be in the crowd.
I’d rather stay home.
(It’s up to you.)
(If you change your mind, you can call me.)
Okay. I’m hanging up.
What’s wrong, Ko?
Aren’t you happy
that you got into the university?
Huh?
Are you okay
with me going to study in Bangkok?
Of course.
You got into a good university.
Of course, I’m happy.
Won’t you be lonely?
But I need to adjust to it.
I will think that you have a great opportunity
and live in a good place.
I can endure the loneliness for it.
Ko.
Change is a normal part of life.
Nothing can stay the same forever.
You need to learn to adjust to changes.
I’ve got to go.
Ko Song came to see you this morning
when you were still sleeping.
Ko.
Your friend is here to see you.
He’s waiting downstairs.
We need to talk.
I…
I’m sorry.
I was being selfish.
I was acting like a child.
I forgot that we couldn’t ride a bike
and play around forever.
Orange.
I should have congratulated you that day.
Instead, I told you to go away.
In the end, I came back to you.
I’m such a loser.
I heard that
you also got into a university in Bangkok.
Congratulations.
Aren’t you mad at me?
Do you want to scold me back?
Scold you about what?
What you said was right.
I deserved to be called selfish.
I should have thought about your feelings.
I’m sorry.
I don’t like this.
I can fight with anyone in the province.
But your few words can hurt me badly.
Are you that sad that
one of your gang members will be away?
You are my favorite member.
Yes, I know I was wrong.
I regret what I did.
So…
you are not mad at me anymore, right?
What? What do you mean?
Do you want to get mad again?
You’re going to be a college boy soon.
Why are you still acting like a child?
Hey, how could you say that to me?
I’ll teach you a lesson.
I’ll tickle you because you can’t stand it.
Don’t tickle me.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Can we not be apart?
No matter where we are,
we will never be apart.
Can you do that, Ko Song?
We will never be apart.
I promise.
(Many things happened
before we graduated high school.)
(The thing we were most sensitive about  was changes.)
(Changes made us anxious and scared.)
(It led to a misunderstanding between us.)
(But changes helped us learn and love each other more.)
(Hello?)
(Honey, did you fall asleep?)
(We stop guessing, focusing,
or worrying about what will happen in the future.)
(It’s useless to worry about things that haven’t happened yet.)
(It’s wasting our time together.)
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls, hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand
as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
(We should be focusing on the present
that is beautiful and shining.)
(It’s the most precious moment in the 18 years of our lives.)