The sun needs rest too.
If it shone all the time,
the plants
would wither,
and the rivers
would dry up.
We all carry fear inside us.
Fear can keep us from moving forward.
That's when
we have to find our strength again
and take that first brave step.
When I'm with you,
I feel recharged.
Then,
why don't we write down that feeling
while it's still fresh?
Here?
The truest feelings
are the ones you have right now.
This time,
I don't want to write about
what I've lost.
I want to
write about what I still have to give.
[Smile After Tears]
[Chapter Eleven: A Chorus of Courage]
This time really is different.
The music finally feels right.
You guys were amazing!
That's wonderful.
I'll submit the demo later today.
[Learning Knows No Bounds.
Education Is for All.]
Sir,
this is the class assignment.
Okay.
Junjia, come here.
Come.
[Manhattan School of Music]
What is this?
The school has received
a notice about an exchange program
with the Manhattan School of Music.
I think you're an excellent fit.
Your English is strong,
your grades are outstanding,
and you're fully qualified.
It's a rare opportunity,
so give it some serious thought.
That's it.
[Exchange Student]
This one's on me.
And
thanks
for helping me the other day.
You don't have to.
Welcome.
Don't come over!
Well,
sorry for scaring you.
I'm Junjia's classmate.
My name is Zheng Diaoqin.
You should've said you were human!
Don't creep around like that!
No wonder Junjia said
you're hilarious to talk to.
I guess I am pretty funny.
That didn't sound like
a compliment.
The tricks I taught you
worked pretty well, didn't they?
Well...
they did help Junjia.
Help Junjia,
or help the two of you?
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Is this
where Junjia works?
Junjia, time to eat.
Diaoqin!
Our demo got through.
We advanced.
Seriously?
Yes.
The organizers just texted us.
That's great!
You did it!
I have to thank you for this.
Let me see what other groups there are.
By the way,
I heard about the exchange program.
How did you know?
Well,
people in class have been
talking about it.
So,
he's been staying at your place?
Yes.
It's good that he's with a classmate.
Has he been eating well?
I'm just asking.
Junjia
is stubborn,
but he's a good kid.
And here I am, a grown-up,
too embarrassed to call him
after our argument.
I'm not sure
if he even wants to hear my voice.
The school called.
They said there's an
exchange program
with the Manhattan School of Music.
But Junjia turned it down.
An exchange program?
To the U.S.?
Yes.
Didn't Junjia tell you?
I just
turned my professor down.
It just doesn't
feel like the right time.
There's still too much
I can't leave behind.
I have to work,
rehearse with the band,
and keep making music.
And if I leave,
what will happen to my aunt?
I want him to have a better life.
I don't want him struggling like I do—
constantly worrying about money
and wondering how we're going to get by.
I can't give him that.
Now that this opportunity
is right in front of him,
he still won't take it.
I know he has things he's worried about.
You're his good friend.
I hope you can talk to him.
I just want
him to have a better life.
-If you could try to persuade him...
-Auntie,
I don't think
I can promise you that.
If it's not what he truly wants,
he'll only
end up miserable.
But I know you're doing this
because you want what's best for Junjia.
My parents often tell me the same thing.
But,
they also tell me
that instead of pushing me down
a path that only looks better,
they'd rather have someone
walk with me and help me
find the path I truly want.
Taking that first step
is never easy.
Actually,
I'm also very scared.
If I take that step forward,
what if I end up losing something
along the way?
By the way, Junjia,
there's something
I need to tell you.
I met with your aunt.
She's really worried about you.
Thank you.
Hey.
Um...
You first.
You go first.
It's okay.
Diaoqin,
thank you.
You're thanking me again?
Ever since the beginning,
you've taken me in.
And when
my aunt went to see you,
she told me
how much you cared about me
and how you said so many things to her,
right?
I just want you to know
that no matter what difficulties you face,
no matter what happens,
I will always be there.
I know.
Do you know
that I like you?
It's just
that I don't know
if my answer
is the one you're hoping for.
How would you know
what kind of answer I'm hoping for?
After talking with you for so long,
the one thing I expect the least
is an answer.
Sometimes,
happiness
is having someone
who will always love you,
and having someone
you can love with all your heart.
Actually,
I think both of us
really need courage.
So,
I want to be the strength you can lean on
when you don't have enough courage.
But
I don't know how long
it will take me to move on.
I will wait for you.
From now on, we're friends.
Time has separated us for so long.
My love for you
has never changed.
What are you doing here?
It's dangerous.
Whatever's troubling you,
tell me
when you're ready.
So
stay
as long as you want.
Junjia!
Auntie,
don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I'll stay by Junjia's side
and accompany him.
Junjia,
do you
really want to go abroad?
Even if you truly lose something
along the way,
I'll be the person
you can turn around and see
whenever you need me most.
It doesn't matter
if you're not by my side.
At least
when I need them,
they are the ones
that I can see when I turn back.
They are in my heart.
That's enough.
I'd forgotten
I'd once said those very same words.
It turns out
that when we're consumed by fear,
we forget that we once had courage too.
Maybe
courage isn't something
we're meant to carry alone.
Maybe it's something
that slowly awakens
when someone is by our side.
Everyone.
Come on!
Gather around.
Come on.
The competition is this weekend.
No matter what the result is,
I just want us
to remember one thing:
We're walking onto that stage together.
So whatever happens,
don't panic.
All it takes is one look at each other,
and we'll know exactly what to do next.
I believe
that's our chemistry.
No problem.
Let's do our team cheer.
Come on.
BACKSPACE!
Go, go, go!
Our band's performing
this weekend.
You have to come.
Okay.
I will.
Diaoqin,
you're right.
The sun
needs to rest too.
Even though it looks the same every day,
it's still beautiful.
[To Junjia]
All these years,
I haven't been able to give you much.
I could only save a little at a time.
I know it's not much,
but at least it'll help you go abroad
and see the world.
And don't think you can get away
without paying me back.
When you make it big someday,
you'd better pay me back.
You've failed so many times.
Are you still going to keep going?
Yes.
This is our last chance.
Are you ready?
[High School Hot Music Club]
♪ It's a beautiful day ♪
♪ When I looking your eyes ♪
[High School Hot Music Club]
♪ Like a dream ♪
♪ Can I call you baby ♪
♪ Thinking of last night ♪
♪ Oh replay the tape ♪
♪ Woke up in morning ♪
[High School Hot Music Club]
♪ Looking at your profile ♪
♪ Oh baby don't worry ♪
♪ You can't get a word in edgewise ♪
Where is Junjia?
I don't know.
Call him.
Any news?
The number you're calling is unavailable.
-Please leave a message after the tone.
-Everyone, are you ready?
Where is Junjia?
I just called him.
He didn't answer,
and he didn't reply to my messages either.
Have you heard anything from him?
No.
Could something
have happened to him?
Hello?
Is that Diaoqin?
Yes, speaking.
Are you with Junjia?
He hasn't arrived backstage yet.
I can't get through to him.
I'll go find him right now!
You can stop here.
Junjia!
Please don't let anything happen to him.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
Jiayi.
He.
I finally get to see you.