[OVERDO]
[Episode 14]
Ren Susu?
Why is it her?
I want her.
Who is he?
So full of himself.
So it's Mr. No. 9.
You truly have a good eye.
So he's the legendary No. 9.
Why's he so unreasonable?
He just outright asked for her.
Why the rush, sir?
In front of everyone,
you could swap out a living person.
Who knows if the one I take home
will still be her?
So...
I want to inspect her.
Qingyi?
Restore it.
No. 9 sure lives up to his name.
Very experienced.
First time seeing
a woman being inspected on site!
Get her out.
Why are you here?
If you can act independently
and come here to save others,
can't I come
to save the one I want to save?
Have you found Ms. Ye?
She was supposed to be on stage now.
I'm standing in for her.
You're mine now.
I'll take you out.
No.
Ye Zhihong and the other girls
are trapped inside.
I can't just abandon them.
I need to stall for time,
so Yinwei and the rest
have a chance to rescue them.
What's your plan?
Muddy the waters, of course.
It's easier to make a move amid chaos.
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪
♪ Stop bowing to the crowd ♪
Light it up!
♪ Conquer to be free ♪
Hai,
you sure
we don't have to go to the vault?
You're needed more here.
If we assassinate that darn old Huo here,
we can draw away the Huos' main forces.
Then Susu will have a better chance
to save those inside.
Do you think
Susu will be in danger?
In our journey,
which step hasn't been dangerous?
To save others,
Susu's risking it all.
Look at these animals.
What now?
The show's over.
We can't stall any longer.
Who says the show's over?
I can buy more time
with just a superficial wound.
It's all in my plans.
Do it.
Hurry up, No. 9!
You can't do it, can you?
You wimp!
Replace him!
-Replace him!
Ren Susu,
you're really going all out.
♪ Fantasies reduced to ash ♪
♪ In a raging fire ♪
When you grow up in hell,
you naturally
understand that
♪ Those caught in the wake ♪
only by being ruthless
♪ Now tell only gray lies ♪
and decisive
can you drag the evil
into the darkness with you.
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
♪ Of the past ♪
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
You're as ruthless to others as ever,
♪ Wandering beneath a pitch-black sky ♪
♪ I smell no sorrow ♪
and even more so to yourself.
Forgotten the lesson
of the bloody wedding dress already?
♪ Let the story start over ♪
You really never learn.
♪ With a new beginning ♪
Innocent people?
♪ Willingly ♪
She's innocent?
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
You're always like this,
♪ Of the past ♪
being soft-hearted at the critical moment.
That's why you get fooled.
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
Then I have to be more ruthless
than you just once,
to beat you once.
She can only be mine!
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪
♪ Just you and me, all else fades away ♪
Inspector Li,
it's so late.
I can just
patrol with the others.
Go back and rest early.
It's fine.
Hasn't there been a crime wave lately?
It's good to have an extra pair of hands.
But as for you,
hasn't your mother
fallen sick recently?
These few days,
go home early.
Is this batch of goods from the vault
all sent out?
Yes, Grandfather.
They're all sent out.
That girl I sent over
must not be left alive.
Rest assured.
I'll make sure she
wishes she were dead,
before I kill her.
[Hong Fang Bank]
Here they come.
What's going on?
Grandfather, get down!
Don't let them get away!
Let's go.
We can't kill him now.
That'd be letting him off too easily.
Go!
After them!
Let's split up!
Yes!
I saw the inspector Li Boze
coming for us too.
You go that way.
I'll deal with Li Boze.
I'll draw away the Huos.
This way!
Stop running.
You again?
I should ask you that.
What happened over there?
Shouldn't you go take a look?
The loud noise scared me.
I had to run for my life
and even sprained my ankle.
Carry me.
Why should I?
Why should you?
Tell me:
what are the duties of the police?
Enforce the law justly
and protect the people.
Am I not part of the people?
Are you not part of the police?
I was just passing by after rehearsal,
when I heard a loud bang.
I thought
a sprained ankle was bad enough,
but then I bumped into you, Inspector Li.
Boss Hai,
what are the odds?
Wherever there's unrest,
there you are.
How about this?
Go back to the station with me
and make a statement.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Anyway, like the moon
revolving around the earth,
you're always revolving around me.
Are you the moon incarnate?
Boss Hai...
don't you love playing pretend?
So why
is your mask
starting to slip?
Looking so fierce,
this is the real you, huh?
What do you want?
I can't do anything.
I don't have evidence right now.
But I'll keep my eye on you
until I uncover the truth.
Do you detest me this much?
Then why'd you blush
every time you saw me?
Boss Hai,
I won't beat around the bush.
I'll be straight with you.
Although we
haven't known each other for long,
I admit that since I first saw you,
I became unspeakably curious about you.
It's a curiosity that's
indescribable.
I want to know
who you really are.
But I also know
you're hiding a lot of secrets.
So...
So you want me to
throw myself at you
because of your vague feelings,
before you'll let me go?
I have no such intention.
I just...
I just hope you can
voluntarily come back
to the station with me
to make a statement.
Inspector Li,
you and I are from different worlds.
Don't waste your time on me.
[Hong Fang Bank]
Is anyone there? Help!
She's not breathing! Somebody help!
Is anyone there?
Somebody help!
She's not breathing!
Where's everyone?
Help! Somebody!
-What's wrong? Stop yelling!
-Help!
Please save her!
She's not breathing!
She's dead?
Is she dead?
Drag her out.
Shouldn't she be on stage right now?
Help! Open the door!
Thanks to the plan you and Miss Fang made,
we're free.
How are you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can they go out
the way you came in?
Yes.
Don't worry.
I'm here to take everyone out.
What about Miss Fang?
Where is she?
Once you reach safety,
she'll find a way to leave.
You take them out first.
I'll go back her up.
Let's not go out with a whimper.
We want revenge.
We want to save others!
Yes!
We'd rather die
than let those bastards go!
Sisters, let's fight them to the death!
Okay.
Let's fight our way out together!
Okay!
Ms. Wang,
bad news.
Guards,
lock the door!
What's this about?
You're not No. 9.
Not No. 9?
Then who is he?
You're quite the actor!
Who on earth are you?
Who I am isn't important.
But if you dare to
mess with me and her today,
neither you nor the Huos
will end well.
The vault matter must not be exposed!
No matter who it is,
leave no one alive.
Kill him.
Go! Go! Go!
-The power's out!
Miss Fang.
-Miss Fang!
-The power's out!
We're here!
Susu!
We're here.
What can a bunch of women do?
Oh dear, they escaped!
I'll beat you animals to death!
Let me go!
Spare me!
Leave!
Bastard!
I'll kill you!
Oh no.
That auctioneer's gone.
How dare you hit me.
You wretch.
I'll kill you!
Susu!
Ms. Ye,
I'll leave this to you.
I'll go find that auctioneer.
It's okay.
Turn off your flashlights.
That guy's in the dark.
With the flashlights on,
we become living targets.
Even pigs and dogs
don't harm their own kind.
Aren't you afraid of going to hell?
I don't want to do such dirty work either.
I-I was forced into it by Master Huo.
Being an accomplice to a villain
is a choice you made.
Wait, Miss.
I have the key to the front door.
I'll help you get them out.
Please, let me go.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Where's Miss Fang?
She's still inside.
Miss Fang!
We fought our way in,
but the way in is blocked.
The Huos didn't shoot just now, in case
the guests got hurt.
Looks like anything goes now.
I got the key to another door.
We'll fight our way out from there.
Hurry!
Why are you so slow? Go faster!
Go, go!
Hurry up!
Let's go.
Hurry!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Turn on the lights!
Hurry!
They can't escape!
The power's back on!
They're catching up!
Let's go! Hurry!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Go!
What are you doing?
You go ahead.
I'll cover you.
Are you crazy?
It's not the time to play hero.
Come on!
We're bogged down by our many casualties.
I'll hold them off.
Didn't you often warn me to
just mind my own business?
Now, I'm on a suicide mission.
Ren Susu,
you'd better
do as you told me
and mind your own business.
-Go!
-No!
Murong Qingyi!
Watch out!
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
♪ The more icy ♪
♪ Our present clash ♪
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
Hurry!
That fellow's a handful!
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
Bring your guns!
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
No matter dead or alive!
Hurry!
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Young Master Murong Qingyi,
today,
you must die here!
If you have the guts...
♪ How much love ♪
kill me.
♪ Is enough to be wasted? ♪
♪ I haven't forgiven you ♪
♪ So don't you forgive me ♪
♪ Let the wildfire ♪
♪ Consume us and burn us to ashes ♪
♪ Still, we choose to be moths ♪
♪ Flying into the flames ♪
Qingyi!
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
I finally won.
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
Hang in there.
I'll take you out.
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
You've...
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
made your choice.
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
From now on,
♪ We ♪
you have to give
♪ Must be together ♪
every single second...
♪ Forevermore ♪
of the 96.4 million seconds...
back to me.
Qingyi?
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
Qingyi!
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪