[OVERDO]
[Episode 15]
Starting today,
you owe me
96.4
million seconds.
You have to give
every single second
back to me.
Qingyi.
Qingyi!
Move, hurry.
-Move.
-Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Move.
-Hurry up.
-Move.
Hurry up!
Take them to the hospital. Hurry.
According to regulations, we have to take
them to the police station for questioning.
Can't you see how badly they're hurt?
I'll take responsibility
if anything happens.
Go!
Open the door.
Get in the car in an orderly manner.
Come on.
Careful.
Come.
The Huo family is finally finished.
For these rescued girls,
we will cover their travel
and medical expenses.
Make sure they are settled down properly.
Don't worry.
Take care of yourself!
What's the patient's condition?
Repeated high fever.
Repeated high fever?
Yes.
Doctor,
how is he?
The bullet has been removed.
His life is not in danger,
but he's badly injured.
He will be in a coma for a while.
Even if you want to leave,
you should wait until the snow melts.
In snowy weather,
the roads are hard to travel.
I'm leaving.
You keep complaining that I lie to you.
But you are the most gullible person
in the world.
Before I even spun a web,
you dove right in,
and I couldn't even drive you away.
Dad, Mom.
Xiaolan.
I have long been trapped in the dark,
and I'm used to moving alone.
But now, surprisingly,
I can occasionally bask in the sun.
Are you the patient's family?
I am...
His sister-in-law.
The patient won't wake up for a while.
You can go back and pack up first.
Take care of the wound
on your shoulder too.
Keep it away from water.
Qingyu.
The Huo family incident this time
involves too many people.
Someone will definitely
try to cause trouble.
So we have to trouble Ms. Ye and keep her
at the police station for a few more days.
I will take good care of them.
Alright.
I'll leave this matter
in your hands.
If you encounter any difficulties,
just let me know.
Understood.
Brother.
[File]
This is...
These are the confessions of
some of the Huo family's subordinates.
Some of the contents
are about sister-in-law.
What do you mean?
Some of the Huo family's subordinates said
the reason why sister-in-law
appeared in the vault
was that she was wandering
outside the vault alone.
She was noticed
and accidentally dragged in.
Sister-in-law has long
had her eyes on
the Huo family's trafficking of orphans.
Okay.
I got it.
Go back to your work.
By the way.
Boze.
About this matter,
it's best not to let a third person know.
Don't worry, Qingyu.
When have I ever let you down?
[File]
[Hong Fang Bank raided at night]
Are you reading
news on the Hong Fang Bank?
You're here.
You seem to
pay extra attention
to the Huo family's affairs.
Do I?
From the very beginning, you knew
something was wrong
with the Huo family's vault,
and what they were up to, didn't you?
And coincidentally,
you appeared at the vault first.
To save my fiancé's girlfriend for him.
I was more anxious than you.
Your brother
was seriously injured by the Huo family,
yet you still have the mood
to talk in riddles with me here.
You ought to seek justice
for him sooner instead.
The police
have intervened in this matter.
It's not convenient for
the Murong family to come forward.
Boze is
always fair in doing things.
There will be results soon.
I hope so.
I'm a little tired.
I'd like to rest now.
[Hong Fang Bank]
Pay back! Pay back! Pay back!
Did something happen to the Huo family?
We all saw the police coming.
Won't anyone give
the depositors an explanation?
Quiet, everyone!
Quiet, quiet!
Quiet, everyone.
Listen to me.
Hong Fang Bank
is a long-established brand,
isn't it?
The Huo family
is also a top-tier family in Nancheng.
This small trouble
will definitely pass in the end.
Trust me, okay?
Words are cheap!
Why should we believe you?
We just want our money!
Pay back!
Give me the money!
No, wait.
Calm down.
Calm down, calm down!
-Calm down. Calm down.
-Pay us back!
Pay us back! Pay us back!
What are you doing?
Pay us back!
It's perfectly justified
to demand a debt payment,
am I right?
Pay us back! Pay us back!
-Pay us back!
-It’s him! Take him away!
-Stop it!
-Take him away.
[Huo Residence]
I left the bank in your care
because you were reliable.
Now that such a big mistake has occurred,
what do you have to say for yourself?
Young Master.
The vault operations
had always been secretive
and heavily guarded.
Nothing had ever gone wrong before.
Besides,
in Nancheng,
no one dared to target our Huo family.
I just really didn't expect
that Murong Qing...
Trash!
Brainless fool!
You kidnapped Murong Qingyu's fiancée
and tied her up in the vault.
And you expected
the Murong family not to retaliate?
No, Young Master...
-I think you’ve become too complacent
-Young Master.
as the manager, haven't you?
Haven't you?
-Haven't you?
-Enough.
Why are you yelling at your elder?
Master.
Please, for the sake of my many years
of loyalty and hard work
for the Huo family,
spare my life.
I was at fault this time.
It was my mistake.
I didn't manage the vault well.
Master.
Please spare my life, Master.
Over the years,
I believe I have treated you well.
Ma... Master.
Master.
For making such a huge mistake,
breaking both your arms
isn't going too far, is it?
Master...
Master!
Please spare my life!
For the sake of my many years of service,
please spare my life!
Master!
Grandfather.
Don't be angry.
It's a small matter.
Have a seat.
Grandfather.
Right now at the bank,
depositors are causing a run,
and major clients are withdrawing funds.
What should we do next?
The lifeblood of the Huo family
is not just the bank.
As long as the South
still needs our imported arms,
the Huo family won't fall.
What do you want to say?
Grandfather.
I...
I previously embezzled
some funds from the South
and put it in the stock market.
I thought it was a sure-fire profit.
Unexpectedly,
I lost it all.
You bastard!
How dare you embezzle the money
and lose it all?
Are you trying to ruin the Huo family?
Do you know that
once the arms supply
to the south is cut off,
our Huo family will really be finished?
Grandfather,
I was wrong.
I know I was wrong.
I will never dare to do it again.
Please tell me
what to do next.
It seems
we can only go to that family now.
Who?
Nanny Sun's case
has been classified as a missing case,
and temporarily closed.
The most troublesome one is Murong Qingyu.
You just said that
he's suspecting you now?
He seems to know
about my early involvement
with the Hong Fang Bank.
How did he know?
Maybe Li Boze suspects me.
But he doesn't have much evidence.
At least he hasn't found out
about my real identity yet.
Li Boze and I have crossed paths
several times.
He is also suspicious of me.
You caused a scene at the vault.
I'm afraid the Huo family
is already targeting you.
Going head-to-head with the Huo family...
Isn't that what we want?
I didn't expect you
to have such a history with them.
Their old master and I
did great things together back then.
They wouldn't dare stand by
and watch us go down.
I'll leave this matter
to you.
Okay.
Don't worry, Grandfather.
I'll definitely get it done.
Nanny Sun disappeared for no reason,
and there are still no leads on the case.
Let's not blame it on that girl for now.
But...
As for the aircraft explosion
at the aviation school opening
and the bank being raided this time...
That girl
from the Fang family
is involved in all of them.
I'll send someone to investigate
that bitch Fang Mulan right away.
Investigate?
Too slow.
I just want her dead.
Grandfather,
she is, after all,
the fiancée of the Murong family.
Shouldn't we consider
the collateral damage?
[Ji'an Hospital]
Haven't left yet?
You're awake.
I'm thirsty.
No, no.
I have no strength.
Why are you so quiet today?
You're pulling on my wound.
Ow, it hurts so much.
Lie down.
I'll go get the nurse.
♪ I forgot when it started ♪
I was lying.
♪ You're always behind me ♪
♪ Silently accompanying me ♪
♪ My heart belongs only to you ♪
Susu.
♪ Am I out of my mind? ♪
It hurts here.
♪ It's too late to turn back ♪
It really hurts.
♪ I'll be lonely without you ♪
It started 3 years ago,
and remains hurting now.
♪ Our hearts are close ♪
♪ But our distance is widening ♪
♪ While silently waiting for your reply ♪
♪ I frantically hide the fear
in my heart ♪
♪ I can't confess ♪
♪ The bitterness in my heart ♪
I'm sleepy.
♪ As long as you live happily ♪
♪ It's worth it ♪
♪ I can't help falling ♪
When I wake up again,
♪ It's a sudden whirlpool ♪
will you still be here?
♪ You don't know I've been here ♪'
♪ Waiting ♪
♪ I can't help falling ♪
I'm not leaving.
♪ It's a sudden whirlpool ♪
♪ You don't know I've been here ♪
♪ Waiting ♪
Young Master Qingyi,
you brought my butler
from Feng'an to Nancheng
to identify someone.
Who did he identify?
I now suspect that
you're shielding your accomplice
who killed my father.
Check on the person
Huo Minxian brought to the ancestral hall
that day.
Yes.
Any move
from the Huo family?
The people in the vault that day
were either silenced by the Huo family
or bribed by them.
Even the newspapers in Nancheng
have been spoken to.
As for the police station...
What's happening on Boze's side?
Can't hold on anymore?
As far as I know,
the inspectors with real power
at the police station
have also been heavily bribed
by the Huo family.
They intend to frame Ms. Ye
and the girls who were arrested
for intentional injury.
How did Boze handle it?
Fortunately, Inspector Li was there.
He argued back based on reason
and rejected the accusations.
Get the car ready.
To the police station.
Yes, sir.
What should we do?
Will the Huo family let us go?
They hold all the power in Nancheng.
I'm afraid the police
are all working for them.
Do you want some water?
All right.
Don't be so down.
Everything will be fine.
How about this?
I'll give you a math problem.
Whoever solves it first
will get a reward.
-A reward?
-A reward.
What kind of reward?
A reward!
times 2
minus
56.
How much is it?
178.
That was fast.
You deserve a reward.
But it's incorrect.
168.
Correct.
You are...
Liu Amei.
Ms. Ye.
You remember my name?
Over the past few days,
I've memorized everyone's name.
Ms. Ye, do you remember my name?
What about mine?
-Ms. Ye.
-Do you remember mine?
What's your reward?
Do you know how to write your name?
No, I don't.
Then I'll teach you.
Go on.
Liu...
-Liu...
Ah...
Mei.
[Liu Amei]
Ms. Ye,
I can write my name now!
Ms. Ye, I want to learn
to write my name too.
-Ms. Ye. Me too.
-Me too.
I want to learn too, Ms. Ye.
I'm Mao Xiaowa.
Please teach me too.
Ms. Ye,
I'm Niu Abao. I want to learn too.
Ms. Ye, I'm Liu Amei.
I want to learn too.
Okay.
I'll teach all of you to write your names.
-We can write our names.
-Great.
That's great!
Ms. Ye.
But I hate my name.
Why?
I know.
You're worried about
the safety of Ms. Ye
from the aviation school.
Rest assured.
With me here,
no one can harm her.
Can she leave now?
Yes.
If you want, she can leave right now.
What about the rest of the girls?
The Huo family is stirring up trouble
in the police force
just to silence people.
As for these girls,
I have no way
to have them acquitted immediately.
But I can fight
for a lighter sentence for them.
As long as they are under my nose,
their lives won't be in danger.
After the storm has passed,
it won't be too late to send them away.
So,
how has Ms. Ye been?
Ms. Ye from your school
is indeed a remarkable person.
What did you say?
Your name is Wang Zhaodi?
I have
8 older sisters.
I'm the 9th child.
My father really wanted a son,
so he gave me this name.
But after my mother gave birth to me,
she never had another child.
My father
cursed me for bringing
bad luck to his son.
He cursed my mother
for not being able to bear a son.
But the truth is,
he made my mother work in the fields
before she even recovered from childbirth.
It caused her health to decline.
And then,
my mother passed away.
Not long after she died,
my father
sold me.
I don't want the name
given by that old bastard.
So,
what was your mother's name?
I don't know.
I only know that
on her grave,
it says, "Lady Liu of Wang Family."
I remember
when we escaped from the vault,
you were the first to pick up a weapon.
You were like the first ray of light
shining in the night.
From now on,
we'll call you Liu Jiming,
okay?
Jiming.
That's a beautiful name.
I think so too.
Thank you, Ms. Ye.
I like this name.
From now on,
you will all have your own names,
be able to write them,
and no longer be numbers 1, 2, 3, 4,
or A, B, C, D in a ledger.
Nor will you be called cats and dogs,
or Zhaodi and Pandi by your families.
In this world,
the more people look down on you
and bully you,
the more you must hold your heads high
and loudly say to them
your own names.
Got it?
-Yes.
-We got it.
I can leave,
but can those girls be released?
Can I leave
because I'm from the aviation school?
because of you, Principal?
Then I'm not leaving.
This is no time for willfulness.
If I leave,
those girls must leave with me.
Teaching Assistant Ye.
You've always been rational.
Let me be irrational just this once, okay?
Principal.
Brother.
Growing up,
this is the first time I've seen you
ask for a favor
for a group of strangers.
I've put you
in a difficult position this time.
But those girls are indeed innocent.
After this incident,
I will share the pressure
from the police
and the Huo family with you.
Alright.
Since you say so,
if they pursue this matter later on,
I'll use your name
and borrow your authority.
You may leave now.
Let's go.
Those who have relatives
or friends to rely on
can leave on your own.
Those who don't,
come with me.
Principal Murong has promised
to make arrangements for you.
Don't worry, everyone.
You can go with this gentleman.
Then, follow me.
Did they remind you of your past self?
I'm luckier than them.
My parents treated me very well.
It's just that
they passed away early.
My uncles at home
were eager to sell me
to an old man as his second wife.
If I hadn't risked my life to escape,
I wouldn't have
joined the aviation school.
And met...
I'm sorry, Principal.
Just now,
I shouldn't have threatened you.
You did the right thing.
To help the world
instead of just taking care of oneself
is exactly the responsibility
the teachers of our aviation school
should shoulder.
♪ I happened to ♪
♪ Hear your name ♪
Then, do you know
why you were able to threaten me?
♪ And all the memories ♪
♪ Came flooding back ♪
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
I know.
♪ My heart pounding ♪
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
♪ In the misty train car ♪
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
Let's go.
I'll give you a lift.
♪ If you have any ♪
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
♪ Memories are like falling into a trap ♪
♪ Full of mud ♪
♪ The more I struggle,
the more suffocated I become ♪
♪ But I couldn't resist collecting them ♪
♪ I keep collecting ♪
♪ Every word and comment ♪
♪ They speak of you ♪
♪ You are so clear ♪
♪ So close and so clear ♪
♪ If you possibly ♪
♪ Still have the courage ♪
♪ Then take me away from here ♪
♪ Please stop doubting ♪
♪ My determination to run away with you ♪
[Two months later]
What are you doing, my lord?
Be careful,
your wound might tear open again.
I was just sitting here for a while,
and my ring is missing again.
Go back to your room and rest.
I'll help you look for it.
It's right around here.
I'll do it myself.
Get out of the way.
Miss Fang,
why are you here again?
Where?
You lied to me again.
Go run 2 laps.
This isn't the aviation school;
there's no track here.
Isn't this hospital
big enough for you to run?
I don't have time to run.
I have to help you find your ring.
Look at you,
how lucky you are.
Where else can you find
such a considerate subordinate?
Found it.
Miss Fang will come visit tomorrow.
Just give it to her then.
If you wait any longer,
I'm afraid you'll rub it flat.
What do you know?
A ring is such a precious thing.
Of course I have to
pick a good day to give it.
How could I not know?
I've followed you for so many years,
I've seen it all.
Ever since you came out
of the Huo family's vault,
you've been covered in injuries
but constantly smiling.
It's really creepy to see.
Isn't it just that she
went through life and death with you?
Is it worth being this happy?
Easy for you to say.
The danger was real.
The flying bullets were real.
And her heart for me is also real.
Yeah, yeah.
Hurry up and pledge yourself to her.
But,
with her current status...
What will you say
to Young Master Qingyu?
♪ The more passionate ♪
[Luggage Storage]
♪ Our past embrace ♪
♪ The more icy ♪
Is there any clue?
♪ Our present clash ♪
No.
Sir,
should we check the train
Butler Li took?
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
Keep investigating.
Yes.
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
[Luggage Storage]
A few months ago,
a Mr. Li did indeed
deposit this here.
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
Qingyu.
♪ Forevermore ♪
I...
Met a girl.
Ren Susu?