Please.
Your results are in, Ms. Monou.
According to our diagnosis,
you are infertile.
A natural pregnancy
will be near impossible for your body.
Even if you undergo a corrective procedure,
you would only be 10% more likely
to become pregnant.
I'm... infertile?
Ms. Monou.
Though your chances are low,
they are not zero.
I advise you to discuss solutions
with your fiancé as soon as possible,
and come visit our clinic again.
I'm...
Infertile.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to stay with you forever, Sui.
But when my parents saw your records...
[Diagnosis]
They told me the marriage was off.
I want to marry you, Sui.
I don't care about your status or family.
Don't worry, I'll get my parents to understand.
Satoshi...
But to help put my parents at ease,
could I ask you to get a check-up first?
I couldn't do anything more for you, okay?
I mean, infertile? After seven years together?
Damn it!
- Congratulations!
- You're next!
I wanted the bouquet...
Thank you.
Here.
Flowers for my dear older sister.
- For me?
- Yup.
A little happiness, from me to you.
Next it's your turn, okay?
Thanks.
Sui, thank you for raising me
in place of our parents.
Rin...
I was surprised to hear
you broke up with your fiancé.
But...
I know you'll find someone better, and fast.
I'll always be rooting for you.
Thanks.
Let's make sure our kids
become best friends, okay?
I'm going to inherit this company.
Of course I had to break up
with someone infertile.
What? Sui is infertile?
No wonder you ended things
with the girl you were crazy for.
Guess it can't be helped if she's infertile.
She wouldn't get you an heir.
But you didn't have to fire her, did you?
I didn't fire her.
Mom said...
I mean.
My parents said she was better off elsewhere.
Sui's probably awkward here anyway.
But hey, if she's infertile,
doesn't that mean you two can do it raw?
That's a big win!
Sui.
Honestly, Sui.
Don't listen to their vile words.
Takizawa...
They're practically saying
you've failed as a woman.
- What?
- Unforgivable.
Failed, as a woman.
Did you say something?
No, not at all.
I'm planning your farewell party,
so look forward to it, okay?
Thank you.
Aw, this is nothing.
Especially given how much you've done for me.
I'll make sure we send you off with a blast.
Thanks.
Let's enjoy these last few days together!
[Monou]
To Rin's marriage,
and your graduation from parent status.
Cheers!
I seriously have to give it to you.
Not everyone can put themselves second,
and send their sister to college
after their parents passed.
To think a crybaby like her
is now going to become a mother.
You won't have to look after Rin anymore.
So, you'd better start focusing on yourself.
Erika...
So, what's the plan now?
You're quitting the job,
and letting your sister have the house.
Yeah. Rin's family will only grow,
so a single house is far too much for me.
And I'll find a new job,
as long as I'm not choosy.
Want me to introduce you
to my father's company?
It's a similar sort of real estate job,
and they have employee housing, too.
Thanks, but I assume positions
will be scarce anyway.
I suppose you're right.
Maybe this was for the better.
What do you mean?
Finding out about my infertility
after marriage would've been worse.
So, in a way,
I think his rejection was in good faith.
It was not.
Himukai's a scumbag.
Don't listen to that bastard.
You dummy. Goody-two-shoes.
- Erika, that's enough about him.
- Oh, I'm not done.
He's pathetic. A momma's boy.
A rich guy with no spine.
I promise, I'm fine now.
- There you go again.
- Huh?
It's a bad habit of yours.
You tend to hold back on yourself.
You're allowed to complain
and rely on others, okay?
Your friends and loved ones
will always be happy to listen.
Then could I say just one thing?
Lay it on me.
When my marriage was called off,
rumors about my body circulated the office.
- What?
- That's one thing.
That was a shocker in it of itself.
But then, a junior of mine said...
They're practically saying
you've failed as a woman.
Unforgivable.
Those words really shook me.
Who the hell said that about you?
- I won't forgive her.
- No, I swear she's a nice girl.
She just happened to make a biting remark.
Still, that's nothing to say to...
Hold on.
[Misaki Takizawa]
[How does this restaurant sound?]
What's up?
My department's holding
a farewell party for me next Friday.
[Palace of Versailles]
Do you have any more?
I'm so glad we could have dinner
at one of your favorite restaurants, Sui.
I've never been somewhere so fancy.
You've got great taste.
Great restaurant choice, Takizawa.
Thank you.
I wanted Sui to have one last
great memory with us here.
What dish would you recommend?
Huh?
The tripe's great here.
It's one of their specialties.
"Tripe"? I've never had it before.
You haven't?
Score! A first for me!
Then tripe will be a memorable dish for us.
Yeah.
Looks like this place specializes in tripe.
Let's definitely order some of that.
I'd recommend their other dishes as well.
Like what?
The escargot, and potatoes are great, too.
- Everyone have a glass?
- Yes, sir.
Here's to Monou's bright future. Cheers!
Cheers!
Thank you.
That's good.
Have you already found another job?
Not yet.
I'm sure you'll find a place
to utilize your CAD skills.
Thanks.
I did always love looking at architecture.
Is there anything else
you've dreamt of doing?
Not really.
Taking it easy isn't so bad either.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Do you have any dreams yourself, Nakano?
I'm too busy dealing with my newborn kid.
Can you believe my wife wants two more?
- Kids are cute, so I understand.
- I suppose.
Though kids aren't a necessity, of course.
Right.
Exactly!
No kids, no marriage,
it's all up to the individual!
Great point.
Your glass is looking empty there, Sui.
Sorry I didn't notice.
Yes, drink up, Monou. It's your party.
Don't be shy, eat your fill!
How's that?
Tastes great.
Really?
Thank you for all your hard work.
- No, thank you.
- Take care.
You sure you're not joining for round two?
Yes.
What a shame.
Keep in touch, okay?
Then let's mosey on to the next bar.
- All right.
- See you, Monou.
- Good night.
- Good luck.
Get home safe.
All right guys, drinks are on me!
Yes!
How about a drink on me?
- No thank you.
- Aw, but you look free.
Did you need something from my girlfriend?
So, the uggo's got a boyfriend.
Are you allright?
Yes, thank you.
You're drunk stupid.
Where do you live?
I don't wanna go home.
Here, water. Drink up.
Wait.
Why?
We're not doing anything?
Don't try something you're not used to.
Sui is infertile?
They're practically saying
you've failed as a woman.
Don't go.
I don't care what happens anymore.
Please.
I know this won't sound convincing, but...
You ought to be more wary. You're a woman.
A woman...
Don't bother putting one on.
You won't need to.
I'll be fine.
So...
What are you talking about?
These are for protecting your body.
Morning.
I'm so sorry. I was out of it yesterday.
Feeling better?
Yup.
Thank you.
That's all for us.
Good bye.
It's fine.
I'll stay until you sleep.
Hey! How was the party yesterday?
It was complicated.
But it gave me the motivation to move on.
As you should.
So, here's the thing.
Could you introduce me to that job after all?
The one at your father's workplace.
Yeah, I want to give it a shot.
Thanks.
What, really?
[Monou]
So, the new hire is coming in next week?
Yup. It seems she's an old friend of Erika's.
Hopefully your spartan work ethic
won't scare her off.
Hey!
Although, I am a bit worried...
Don't be, she'll warm up to you.
That doesn't sound reassuring.
How do you read her name?
It's read, "Monou".
"Monou".
Unusual name, isn't it?
- You could read it?
- Not at first.
Glad I wasn't alone.
I didn't think you'd move out so quick.
Erika says I'm better off not dawdling.
I'll miss having you around.
But that's just me being selfish.
Don't worry, I'll come back to help often.
Thanks.
Still, I can't help but worry
about a lady living alone...
I'll be fine.
The apartment's a company dormitory,
so my neighbor is a fellow coworker.
Then I guess no weirdos will be around.
Call me immediately
if you face any trouble, okay?
And you take care of your body.
Okay.
- They have gotten big.
- Yeah.
Your door is now locked.
Guess that wasn't all for us, huh?
What do you think of the night we shared?
He's being extra kind to her.
Good night.
You haven't given up
on your own happiness, right?
Why are you...
I can't give up on you, Sui.