How did we run into a funeral procession?
Li Yiran, you can't get away!
Zhuang Qiang
Have you come to save me?
Yiran
I've come to kill you.
Had another nightmare.
That Linda...
She's a total Dragon Lady.
Last night,
she made me pull an all-nighter.
And this morning she drags me to some team building.
Sicko.
We need the code to get out
Where's the code?
Where could it be?
Is it here?
These young folks
have no sense of when it's appropriate
Zhuang Qiang
You're so naughty!
I've missed you so much!
You bad boy
I can't wait any longer
What is it?
Don't be so impatient every time
Didn't you say
you're gonna break up with Li Yiran?
I'll break up with her the moment I'm back
I haven't wanted to see her for a long time
She's got no figure to speak of
and no money either
She can't give you what you want
I really don't know
why you're even with her
Well, that's only because I was
Too young too naive
and just didn't know any better
You're the only one in my heart
Such a smooth talker, you are
Holy shit
Don't stop
Ugh, the stench of love
This is clearly an affair!
Run!
Linda, we should've shaken them off by now, right?
Shaken... yeah, we lost them
Oh my God!
I'm so scared
It's okay
I'll protect you
You bastard
You've got a mommy complex and never told me
Guess you've never had anything good in life
Boss
The show for this team building turned out great
And you performed in it yourself
The plot's a real treat to watch
May the cheating couple live happily ever after.
Didn't you say you'd break up with Li Yiran?
I'll break up with her the moment I get back.
I never want to see her again.
Yiran, let me explain.
Zhuang Qiang, I'm telling you,
what I despise most is a social climber from the country.
If you want to take shortcuts, I won't stop you.
But
please don't ever bother me again.
What... what's going on here?
That's a lot of pressure.
Zhuang Qiang, are you done yet?
Is this Li Yiran?
Who is this?
I'm Director Ma from the Lecang Chunguang Subdistrict Office.
Is something the matter?
Well, it's like this.
About your mother...
She...
What happened to her?
Don't be nervous.
It's nothing bad.
It's good news.
Your mother
in three days
is getting out of prison.
We just received the notice ourselves.
I'm calling just to let you know.
All of you, get the hell out of my way!
What do you think you're doing?!
Son of a bitch!
That'll teach you to bully my wife!
Pops!
Yiran!
Son of a bitch!
Pops
Long is the road to the Yellow Springs, walk slowly.
Half awake, half drunk, let your sorrows fade
Filial children kneel before the spirit
Loose shoes step steady through Yangping Pass
Cross the Bridge of Helplessness in peace
Ascend to the immortal realm
Return to your rightful place
Bless your children and grandchildren with fortune
Filial sons, bow your heads
Pops
After Pops passed away
I never went to visit Wu Huilian
Eight years now
She and I became strangers
I don't know how to face her
Or how to face
that past that tore my family apart
Hello? Hello?
Li Yiran, are you listening?
Yes, I'm listening
If you don't come back,
then how about
you bring her to Shanghai?
In a situation like hers
she's been locked up for too long
Some people just can't adjust
and end up killing themselves
or they reoffend and get locked up again
With you by her side
we at the office can breathe a little easier
Thank you, Director Ma
I understand
Zhuang Qiang sure knows how to put on an act.
Who knew?
Putting on a fancy act.
He's just a total player.
Only good-looking guys
get to be called players.
Him?
He's more like pond scum.
Then don't waste your tears on a scumbag.
He's not worth it.
You're right.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm putting the past completely behind me.
I'll find myself a new job.
Yiran.
I'm not just saying this,
but don't push yourself so hard.
Sometimes it's good to take a break.
Xiaofang.
What is it?
Forget it.
It's nothing.
I'm off to send out resumes.
I'll hang up now.
Hold on.
Like I don't know you.
I know you inside out.
I can read you like a book.
Come on, out with it.
Whatever's bothering you, just say it.
Give me a good laugh.
The subdistrict office called me today.
They said
Wu Huilian is getting out of prison.
Really?
That's great!
You quit your job anyway,
so why don't you just come back?
Think about how long it's been since we last met.
Go back?
No way.
It took me eight years to move past all this.
Yiran.
The past
is best left in the past.
All these years,
Auntie Huilian's been all alone in prison.
It's been really tough on her.
Listen to me.
That's enough, Chen Xiaofang.
Why are you so preachy?
I'm hanging up.
Don't!
The nerve of her.
Go home and wait to hear from us.
Sorry, Miss Li.
You're probably not a good fit for the position.
Goodbye.
Miss Li,
why did you leave your last company?
It's because
my ex-boyfriend cheated on me with my boss.
So can I take that to mean
you don't handle pressure very well?
They cheated,
so why are you the one who quit?
Are you out of your mind?
What's so funny?
Sorry, you're not a good fit.
Next.
Hey, Director Ma
Something terrible happened
Your mom's been taken to the police station
Hurry up, get back here now
Thief!
Who is it?
Son of a bitch!
What do you think you're doing?
Stealing in broad daylight!
And you almost made me
end the family line!
I'll kill you!
What do you think you're doing?!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you trying to kill me?
You want to murder me!
You...
You're trying to kill someone!
You hag!
See you at the police station!
Officer
I've been wronged
Wu Huilian
Here
Li Ermao
You don't have to stand. Sit down and talk
How were you wronged?
I'm more used to standing
Here's what happened
I was going back to my own home
I couldn't get the door open
Then he shoved that basket over my head
He attacked me first
In broad daylight,
she was hacking at the door with a hammer
How was I to know she wasn't a thief?
I was going into my own home
Why do you care how I open my door?
I wanted to get in
None of your damn business!
Let me tell you, Officer
How many times have I told you?
We're in the service industry
What's wrong with letting a customer touch a little?
Am I right?
So unprofessional
No dinner for you tonight as punishment
Wu Huilian
Let me tell you
If you don't pay my medical bills today,
I'll take you to court
Go ahead, sue me
This was self-defense
Why the hell should I pay?
Pay up
You have to pay
The kid's clothes were brand new
Officer
That alpaca peed all over the kid
Look
Look at this
If you don't believe me, smell it
Officer
That's not pee
It's because this kid
was hitting our alpaca
so it just spat on him, that's all
Smell it ten thousand times, it's still pee
Your zoo
has to pay
These clothes don't cost much
It's a minor dispute. Just pay and be done
No way
Officer, look
My...
This almost made me end the family line!
This is a first-degree disability
Don't be so dramatic
Is this some kind of harassment?
She's a woman
What are you staring at?
What is wrong with you?
You're the one who started it
You hag!
You're completely unreasonable
You stinking man
You're the unreasonable one
You started it
Wu Huilian
Here
Is this a market?
Settle down, will you?
He started it
Officer
I'm...
Wu Huilian's daughter
Are you the one in a dispute with her?
I'm sorry
We can pay the medical bills
Can we settle this privately?
See how sensible your daughter is?
Just my rotten luck
Eight hundred. Forget it.
Eight hundred? You're extorting me!
It nearly made me end the family line!
Eight hundred. I'm going easy on you
Fine then
Let's settle it privately
Settle it privately, fine
Forget it
Seventy-eight, just my rotten luck
Alright
Since you're both willing to make peace
Here, sign this
You can go now
Next time, don't get physical
Got it?
Come on, you sign one too
Why'd you hit my alpaca?
My suitcase
Come on
Come on, hurry up
Officer, sorry about that
I haven't signed yet
Here, here
Thank you
Come on, let's go home.
Yiran
Driver
Could you turn on the radio?
Alright
According to our station's report,
this day next month,
we'll welcome a new solar term,
the Start of Autumn,
marking the arrival of Early Autumn.
The grain begins to ripen,
and all the waiting finally bears fruit.
This farce after Wu Huilian's release from prison
ended with me losing 800 yuan.
This farce was just like our lives,
with no way to begin,
and no way to fix it.
But eight years later,
I still ended up back here,
the place I once desperately tried to escape.
When I got home today,
the door lock had been changed.
That's the only reason I...
You don't need to explain to me.
I wasn't the one who threw the first punch.
What's gotten into you today, Ermao?
That Wu Huilian...
Fresh out of prison and already so hot-tempered.
She nearly made me end the family line!
You have no idea what she went in for.
Murder!
I won!
Pay up, pay up, pay up!
You're never gonna quit, are you?
Your luck is really terrible.
That bastard Zhang Lijuan
Couldn't even bother to come welcome me
Forget it
Every dog has its day
You coming or not?
Welcome home, Godmother
Sister Lan
Yiran
Auntie Juan
You're finally back
I saw the door was closed just now
I thought...
that even you were fed up with me
How could that be?
I just wanted to surprise you, you know?
Thank you
Sister Yiran
Yangyang, hurry up
Say hi to Godmother.
Welcome home, Godmother
Yangyang
Godmother
You've grown up so much!
Wait a second
Wait
Huilian
Yiran
Uncle Daren
You're all back
Wang's aunt passed away
He went over to help
Otherwise
For something as big as your return,
there's no way he'd miss it
Huilian
Step through the door once more
The auspicious hour is here
Fire cleansing
Burn away the gloom
Let the past drift away like smoke
And welcome a brand new start
Go on, step over
May everything go smoothly from now on
Good luck and good fortune
There we go
Come here, Yangyang
Thank you, Sister Yiran
Come on, sit for a while
Have a seat, Sister Lan
Last time I saw you, you didn't have this much gray hair.
How'd you get so many gray hairs?
Well, I'm getting old.
Getting on in years, you know.
Bound to go gray.
Not like you.
You haven't changed a bit.
Me?
I just don't have a care in the world.
You, careless?
You're the most caring one there is.
Otherwise,
how'd you raise Yangyang so well?
Yangyang.
And Yiran turned out just as well, didn't she?
All grown up into a young lady now.
Time really flies
Uncle Daren
All these years
Thank you
You're back now, that's what matters
You're all back, that's what matters
You must be hungry
Let's get ready to eat
Yangyang
Huilian
Lijuan
Time to eat
Come on, Sister Lan
Come here, Yangyang
Bring that chair over
Have a seat, Yangyang
Yangyang
Thank you
You're all back
No more crying
Let's eat
Come on, eat
Today's a happy day
We should be happy, right?
Right
Here
Take it
Uncle Daren
Yangyang, eat up.
Here, Sister Lan.
Eat up.
Come on, come on.
I'm finally back
Come on
Let's have a drink
Hey
I've got something to tell you
I said I have something to tell you
Can't you hear me?
It's just the two of us in this room
Why are you yelling so loud?
Once I clean up your mess, I'm heading back to Shanghai
Before that
Let's agree on three rules
First
Don't cause trouble
Second
Third
Still, don't cause trouble
Did you hear me?
What are you trying to do?!
A little stool trying to climb on the table now?
So disrespectful.
You haven't greeted me once since you saw me.
Don't you know how to address people?
Yiran
You need to pay more attention to how your mom's feeling
She'll be very fragile after getting out of prison
Encourage her to keep a positive mindset
And reach out to us if you ever need help
A brand new day
A brand new start
Gotta be happy every single day
Right, old Li?
Li Yiran, wake up!
It's eight already and you're still not up.
Get out.
Can't a person sleep this early in the morning?
I steamed you some buns and made soy milk.
Don't want it, don't want it! Get out.
Get your ass up right now!
I'm going to see your Pops today.
You're coming with me.
Ugh, you're so annoying!
Who says I'm going with you?
Whatever you say goes, huh?
I just do whatever you tell me?
Get out!
Leave me alone!
In a situation like hers
she's been locked up way too long.
Some people can't adjust,
so they kill themselves.
Or they slip up and end up back inside.
Wu Huilian!
She wouldn't really do something drastic, would she?
I'm her mother, damn it!
We'll perish together!
No!