2026 MAY
TAXI
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Today, I made your favorite
hamburger steak.
Thank you, as always.
It's nothing, really.
I have to say, my cooking skills lately
have been improving rapidly.
By any chance,
did you get fired from school again?
What?
You're making hamburger steak
just to butter me up.
Get your act together already!
Even now, you ride around
on that huge motorcycle,
acting cool in front of students,
saying "It's great,"
yet every single school
you go to, you get fired.
You're already 52.
Normally, this is the age people
become vice principals!
Or is it that, since I still bring
money home, you aren't worried?
No, sorry, I don't think like that.
It looks like I'm just getting
mad at you, but that's not it.
It's because no matter how many times
I say it, you just don't listen!
The last time you got fired,
you said, "I didn't do anything wrong."
Then let me ask you,
what on earth even is this
"Great Teacher" thing you talk about?
What kind of teacher is it?
Well, that's, you know…
Someone who cares about the students…
I can't hear you.
What it means is, as a teacher, I…
Oh, enough already.
Just find a new job
as quickly as possible.
Promise me that you won't
quit that school.
And come up with a proper answer
for what a "Great Teacher" is.
If you can't do that…
What?
DIVORCE FORM
Hey! You're joking, right?
I am serious.
I'll be going back to my parents' house.
What?
By the way,
your hamburger steak is burning!
Oh, crap!
Wait!
It's hot!
Azusa! Hold on…
Oh, no! I have to turn the fire down.
It's hot!
CV - EIKICHI ONIZUKA
It seems you have resigned
from quite a number of schools.
That was because…
my educational philosophy
did not align with the schools.
Rumors say the reason is
that you once occupied a school,
were violent to colleagues,
verbally abusive toward parents,
and even sexually harassed students?
No, I did all of that
for the students' sake.
Even if that was the case,
I don't think any school would hire
someone over 50 with such a background.
No matter how severe
the teacher shortage is right now.
All right, please open your mouth.
Mr. Onizuka.
The only option left for this tooth
is to extract it and get an implant.
ISABE DENTAL
One, ten, one hundred, one thousand,
ten thousand, one hundred thousand…
What?
Are implants really that expensive?
299,800 yen… I…
Woah! Stop!
OSARU DELIVERY
It hurts!
Do you want to die, idiot?
Shut up, bastard!
Is that you, Onicchi?
Oh, it's you, Masaru!
Why were you spacing out like that?
That's dangerous.
-I have a lot going on.
-A lot?
Come on, don't look so pathetic.
It's not like Ms. Fuyutsuki
will divorce you, right?
What?
Wait, seriously?
Uh…
I need to find a job
or I'm in deep trouble.
No one will hire me.
We've been married for 25 years,
and I thought we'd be together
until our hair turned white,
but at this rate, it's truly over.
Oh, I know.
Why don't you try
for my daughter's high school?
Wait, you have a daughter in high school?
Didn't I tell you last time we met?
I'm already 43, you know.
To earn money for my daughter's tuition,
I started working as a delivery driver.
A hopeless delinquent like you
is now the father of a high school girl.
Quit getting all sentimental over
your former student's happy life, and go.
I'll email you the details.
Oh, right, that school
is run by a large corporation,
and they are looking
for a teacher right now.
Got it? They are a big corporation.
Wear a suit and tie when you go. Got it?
Yes.
Let's do this.
Excuse me…
I would like to meet with the person
in charge of teacher recruitment
for the school your company runs…
We've been waiting for you.
I will guide you.
What a magnificent building.
Students who attend a school
run by a fine company like yours
must be truly happy.
Mr. Onizuka.
Yes?
You've passed.
What?
Would you come to our high school?
No way? Are you sure?
Come on, don't you remember me?
What?
Back in Kairei High School,
Class 2-C, I was in your class.
Oh! Yes!
Um, I remember. You're…
You tried to cheat just now.
No, I would never do that!
I totally remember you.
But could you just tell me the first part?
Today, you see…
My tooth hurts, and I'm not feeling well.
It's "Mi."
By the way, what's next?
"Ya."
A bit more.
"Za."
Could it be, the next part is…
"Wa?"
It's Miyazawa.
Ryunosuke Miyazawa. Ryunosuke!
Yes.
What the heck?
You're a big shot now,
I didn't recognize you.
Besides, you see…
I only remember first names anyway.
That's right.
What the heck, you're working
at such a great company.
You're amazing, Ryunosuke.
Quite the opposite, you saved me.
It's only May, yet a teacher just quit,
so the higher-ups told me
to fill the vacancy. I was panicking.
And I was looking for a passionate teacher
who could ignite a passion
in the current students.
So, meeting you must be fate…
Well…
Will you really come to our high school?
I'm not sure…
I've actually received pretty good offers
from other schools too, you know.
All right.
Let's do this!
Good morning.
Our school's slogan is
"Nurturing Future Leaders."
We have classes using
state-of-the-art technology,
and classes on investing
for when they get a job in the future.
-I also teach those classes.
-Good morning.
We also accept students
who were truant or have issues
as part of our efforts
to contribute to society.
Good morning.
Hey, what is everyone holding?
Those are tablets provided by the school.
Various data and information is entered,
and students and teachers
can easily interact via chat.
It helps create an environment
for a comfortable school life.
Somehow this place…
Yes?
It feels more like a company
than a school.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
This is Principal Ohkubo.
PRINCIPAL
I'm Eikichi Onizuka.
I will dedicate my life to working here!
Well, thank you.
Over there is the Vice Principal…
Hello, nice to meet you. I will be…
Onizuka?
Why are you here?
Oh, long time, no see!
What was it again?
You were there, weren't you?
Back at Seirin Academy,
you were one of the two people
who gave me a hard time.
I remember now.
Uchiyamada!
It's Nakamaru.
Oh, that one.
Principal, let's pass on this guy.
He's bound to cause catastrophic trouble.
Even if you say so, I don't have
authority over personnel matters.
Mr. Miyazawa, why did you hire
someone like this?
I was his student, and when all's said
and done, he's a really good teacher.
Even so,
look at this terrible work history.
This man is a former biker gang member.
What?
Is that so?
Come on, Mr. Nakamaru.
I'm 52 now, so I won't
do reckless things like I used to.
How can anything you say be trusted?
After 30 years of hardships, in the year
I finally became Vice Principal,
why does an unqualified teacher
like you have to come along?
To my school!
What's with that look?
No, if I recall…
Back then, you stepped aside to let
another teacher become Vice Principal,
so I thought you had become
a better teacher.
But you've reverted to an unpleasant guy.
-What did you say?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
If I get fired this time, it will be truly
disastrous, so I'll take it seriously.
I'm happy to be able to teach
at such a wonderful school.
The future of Japan is right here! Yes!
STAFF ROOM
Good morning.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
Ms. Kashiwabara, you're cutting it
pretty close today too.
I'm sorry, my horoscope wasn't good today
so I thought about not coming. Then I
thought that wouldn't be right either.
And besides, I'm not late.
Going at your own pace as always.
Your generation really dislikes
wasting effort, right?
In our time, such a thing was unthinkable.
And your clothing is also
a bit much for a teacher…
Mr. Murayama.
What you're saying
is harassment, you know.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it that way…
It's fine, isn't it?
Ms. Kashiwabara does her job properly,
and I've never heard complaints
from students, right?
I'm still lacking
compared to you, Ms. Koizumi.
Hold on!
Everyone.
Allow me to introduce him.
He will be taking over Class 1-B,
from its previous teacher,
teaching Japanese History…
I'm Eikichi Onizuka!
If anyone among you
knows the answer to
what a "Great Teacher" is…
Ms. Kashiwabara,
please mentor him, since you're
the assistant teacher of Class 1-B.
Sure.
Mr. Nakamaru,
I'm not done with my greeting yet.
-If nothing changes, my wife will--
-Everyone, have a good day.
You can have this.
What?
I've put together necessary info, like
what lessons were already done in April.
Right.
Thank you, this helps a lot.
It's nothing, it was easier
to write it down than to explain it.
By the way, why did
the previous teacher quit?
It seems he was struggling
with his mental health.
What?
Does that mean
there was some problem with the class?
No, nothing like that.
Right.
Is there anything
I should be careful about?
Maybe it's my age, but I don't really get
high school students these days.
Just do as you like.
You're the homeroom teacher, after all.
All right.
CLASS 1-B
-Good morning.
-Let's go!
Good morning.
Before we start homeroom,
let me introduce him.
-Starting today, he will be your home--
-Excuse me.
I'll take it from here.
Right, please go ahead.
EIKICHI ONIZUKA
I'm Eikichi Onizuka,
your homeroom teacher starting today.
Nice to meet you.
Let's see…
I have been teaching for 27 years.
My motto is…
Oh, we've already looked you up,
so we're good.
-What?
-You seem to be quite a unique teacher.
Interesting.
-Woah.
-He's funny!
Then…
I'm taking attendance.
Ayano Ashida.
What?
Is Ashida absent?
Oh, if you're here, speak up!
I'm sorry.
The rule here is to address
both boys and girls with honorifics,
so I was a bit startled.
Is that so?
It was in the memo I gave you.
Oh, right.
But…
Isn't that a bit too distant?
Let's give you a nickname, come on.
Since it's Ashida…
Something like Asshi.
Why is there a need to do such a thing?
That way we can get closer faster,
you guys can call me Onicchi too.
I'm sorry.
I don't really get it.
High school life
will be more fun that way.
I don't think school is meant to be
enjoyed, it's a step toward the future.
Hold on, kid.
You have to enjoy your youth!
What is "youth"?
Running toward the sunset,
getting excited at mixer parties,
eating mystery hotpots,
doing tests of courage.
Mixer parties, mystery hotpots,
tests of courage…
I don't know what they mean,
so I'll look them up.
Hey…
Hey, are you kidding me?
What?
Is that guy absent?
He hasn't come for a while.
How long is "a while"?
Who knows?
What's their name? Someone tell me.
What was that guy's name again?
Don't ask me.
It's Kenta Katayama.
Ah, there was a guy like that.
What was he like?
I can't even remember his face.
It's kind of a mystery.
You…
Aren't you worried?
What are we supposed to do?
Isn't that your job, Mr. Onizuka?
STAFF ROOM
Kenta Katayama did come
for about two weeks after April,
but he has been absent ever since.
The reason?
We don't really know, but at least
it doesn't seem to be bullying.
By the way, that was also
in the memo I gave you earlier.
What?
I'm sorry.
Lately, I can't read small print.
Didn't anyone try to persuade Kenta
to come to school?
The previous homeroom teacher
went to his house once,
but it seems Kenta said
he "doesn't need to go to school."
And then?
That's all that happened.
FOR FIREFIGHTING
Kenta Katayama.
Wait a minute.
This device, can it also
be used to watch "that stuff"?
PORN VIDEOS
What are you doing?
Mr. Onizuka.
Nothing really.
By the way, you can't view
adult sites on that tablet.
You idiot, no way I'd do that.
How old do you think I am?
Can I have one too?
That's it.
Thank you.
You used to scold me a lot back then.
For smoking cigarettes on the rooftop.
Right.
How nostalgic. I did do that.
How are the kids in the class?
Well, they're detached,
always looking at their tablets.
They don't look at me when I talk,
which is frustrating.
I understand how you feel,
but please be careful.
Our school has a teacher feedback system.
Feed…
What is that?
Students anonymously evaluate teachers
on a ten-point scale
from plus five to minus five.
This is the current ranking…
By the way, who is number one?
It's Ms. Koizumi, the English teacher.
KOIZUMI - 810 POINTS
RANKING (WEEKLY)
She uses a projector
to conduct classes in a game-like format,
so the students love her.
Give explanations for interior
and exterior angles…
Also, Mr. Abe, the math teacher,
is quite popular too.
He cuts out waste and prides himself
on cutting-edge classes
using generative AI.
The length of EF can be found to be two.
Are there any unpopular teachers?
In the year 1789, August 26…
I shouldn't say this out loud,
but maybe Mr. Murayama,
the world history teacher?
He just reads from the textbook,
and never scolds students,
so everyone does other stuff in his class.
Mr. Onizuka,
if low evaluations continue for too long,
you'll be removed
as homeroom teacher, face a pay cut,
and eventually be dismissed,
so please be careful.
Well, I do want to avoid that.
But if you reach
number one, you get a bonus.
What? Really?
Mr. Onizuka.
You've always loved money, haven't you?
No, you see…
I've caused my wife trouble
for so long, so…
Right.
Does anyone have any questions?
We’re good.
Come on, don't be shy,
you can ask me anything.
Why are you smiling so much?
This is just how my face is…
Oh.
Great work today.
If you ever have any problems,
don't hesitate to reach out to me.
I'm Onizuka.
Eikichi Onizuka, nice to meet you.
You can call me Onicchi.
Mr. Onizuka.
Yes?
I'll be leaving now.
What? Are you heading home already?
Yes, I’ve done everything I needed to do.
Bye then.
That's a pretty nice house.
Yes?
Is Kenta Katayama here?
Who is it?
My name is Eikichi Onizuka,
Kenta's new homeroom teacher.
Are you Kenta?
You need something?
Isn't it obvious?
Why aren't you coming to school?
No point telling you.
-Why?
-Because I'll die soon.
No way! Are you sick?
I'm not. There's just no point in living.
What are you talking about?
If you come to school,
there are lots of fun things.
Like what?
For example, making lots of friends.
I went for a little bit in April,
but everyone was looking at their tablets,
they barely even talked to me.
Aren't your parents worried about you?
My father
has no interest in me whatsoever.
That's not true. What about your mother…
I don't have one.
What?
My mother died five years ago.
An accident? Illness?
That's enough already!
I'm not going to school anymore.
Don't say that.
Come on, please come.
And give me feedback, Kenta!
Kenta?
Therefore,
tomorrow, why don't we all
go encourage Kenta to come to school?
All of us.
Excuse me.
Why do we have to do that?
Tomorrow is a day off,
and aren't you classmates?
If you ask me,
I don't think many people here
think those around them
will become important lifelong friends.
What?
It just so happened
that we ended up in the same class…
Or rather, we're just sharing
the same space.
Are you guys saying you don't care
what happens to Kenta?
Don't say it like that…
We were in the same middle school,
but he was also always absent back then.
Don't force your way of thinking on us.
And calling each other by nicknames,
that's just extrovert logic.
It can lead to bullying,
so the school decided
everyone should use honorifics.
Right, Ms. Kashiwabara?
That's right.
Are you serious?
Besides, when you state an opinion,
how about you look up
and look the other person in the eye?
-Mr. Onizuka.
-Yes?
That was risky.
What?
If you keep this up,
it will affect your feedback score.
What?
The previous homeroom teacher
also snapped, his score kept
dropping, so he ended up quitting.
Oh, right.
-I see.
-Yes.
I wasn't angry, you know.
-Come on, Ms. Kashiwabara. Say something.
-What?
You're the assistant teacher, right?
-Do you know what a perfect number is?
-What?
What is that?
A number where, if you add up all
its divisors, it equals the number itself.
To be precise, it's the proper divisors,
excluding the number itself.
I've no idea what you're talking about.
For example,
the divisors of six are one, two…
and three.
When you add them all up, they equal six.
Making six the smallest perfect number.
But what does that have to do
with what we're talking about?
The next smallest
perfect number has divisors of four,
seven, and fourteen.
It's 28.
So?
I was just thinking, the number
of students in this class is 28.
What?
For reference, on a certain
famous watch brand's website,
the date display is apparently
always unified to 28.
Because it looks the most beautiful.
Which means,
Class 1-B has to have 28 people,
isn't that what you mean?
Right.
If Kenta isn't here,
this class isn't complete.
Tomorrow, let's gather
in front of his house
and convince him to come to school.
Right? I'm sure Kenta will be happy too.
Not a single person came, huh.
What? Is he not home?
What are you doing, Kenta?
What? Hey!
Kenta!
Are you okay?
What?
What is this?
What are you doing?
That's my line. What is this?
I was experimenting to see
if I would die if I jumped from here.
What?
And the landing spot seemed pretty good,
my dad would find me right away
when he gets home.
I've decided on jumping from here.
Stop saying such stupid things.
No matter what happens,
I won't let you die.
Then what would you do
if I jumped right now?
I'll catch you.
No matter what happens,
I will protect you.
Then can I test it?
What?
To check if you'll really protect me,
I'm going to drop this doll, so catch it.
Oh, it's the same weight as me,
so I think it's pretty heavy.
Are you sure?
All right.
Then bring that thing over.
Here I go.
All right, come on.
See, you failed.
No, that was unfair!
You have to say,
"Ready, set, go" or something.
I need to get mentally prepared too.
I'll give you one more chance.
With a different method.
Different method?
What?
I'm going to drop it into the river
from here. Will you save it?
Yeah, all right.
Here I go!
This time, I saved this thing!
Be careful, the current is fast here.
Hey, help me.
Wait, hey…
Hey, hold on…
You failed.
In the end, the doll washed away.
You can't blame me, it absorbs water,
so it got incredibly heavy.
Why don't you just give up?
There's no point
in protecting someone like me.
No way that is true.
Please, one more chance. One more chance.
Fine. Then take out your phone.
What?
Your phone.
Sure.
What? You're still using a flip phone?
Idiot. It's a low-spec smartphone.
It can even do video calls.
Then tell me your number.
Wait here.
I'll call right away.
Hey, wait, what are you planning on doing?
KATAYAMA
My mother died five years ago.
Hello?
Mr. Onizuka, can you see me?
What? Yeah.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm going to hang myself now.
Will you come save me?
The door has a sturdy lock on it,
so getting inside is going to be tough.
Wait, you! You're joking, right?
Well, here I go.
You've got to be kidding!
Kenta! Stop messing around!
Hurry up, I'm going to die!
Kenta!
Mr. Onizuka! Hurry up! It hurts!
I'm going in!
Wait for me!
My students…
I won't let…
any of them die!
Kenta!
Are you okay?
Hey!
-Anything but that.
-What?
I'm okay!
This is a harness
used for shooting films and such.
This is a rehearsal too.
You can't prank people like this!
What's going on?
What are you doing, Kenta?
I am terribly sorry!
We were fooling around a bit,
but I broke your door.
I'll pay you back for it!
That won't be necessary.
Please leave us alone.
Wait, please!
I have one request.
What is it?
Could you, as his father,
help convince him to come to school?
Okay?
He can do whatever he wants.
What?
It doesn't seem like
he has anything he wants to do.
And even if his grades are bad,
the school will let him graduate anyway.
Huh? What?
What do you mean?
My father is an executive of the company
that runs the school.
What? No way!
I'm sorry,
but please stop involving
yourself with my son.
Goodbye, sir.
Kenta,
are you really okay with this?
My mom…
died of COVID.
I see.
Because I passed it to her.
What?
That's why I couldn't see her body,
or even say farewell.
During the funeral,
I saw my father crying
and tried to hold his hand, but…
It was like he was saying,
"This is all your fault."
"You should have been the one to die."
That's how it felt.
No, there's no way…
Since then, I haven't touched my father,
not even once.
What?
Actually,
I haven't touched anyone
since the fifth grade.
I will…
hug you tight.
What?
Come on.
Don't be shy! Come at me!
Come on!
-Here!
-Cut it out!
What is wrong with you?
Just leave me alone already!
Thanks for the meal.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
But the housekeeper said earlier…
"I can tell by the closet,
your mother was a wonderful person."
I see.
I'll contact the housekeeping agency
to ask for a replacement.
Wait a minute! I didn't mean it that way!
Yes. Okay.
Just leave a message.
I'm at the staff room,
so I'm hanging up. Bye.
Good morning.
Leisurely as ever, Ms. Kashiwabara.
I'm sorry, my mother called
and she just wouldn't hang up.
Onizuka! What on earth
were you thinking? At your age!
What's going on there?
It seems Mr. Onizuka
caused some trouble at a student's house.
I wonder why they hired
a person like that.
Apparently, he used to be in a biker gang.
Oh, really?
Let's try to stay away from him.
What are biker gangs? Please tell me.
You're already this old!
What were you thinking?
Barging into Mr. Katayama's house,
breaking the door…
That was because Kenta was trying to die.
He was obviously just messing around.
This is a big mess for us.
His father filed a complaint, asking why
we hired a violent teacher like you.
Vice Principal, I will explain that matter
to Director Katayama myself.
Miyazawa, you should never have hired him!
I'm sorry.
But I'm sure Mr. Onizuka
was just worried about Kenta.
That's right.
The school needs to take action too,
or it'll be a disaster.
People who make a big fuss
about dying don't go through with it.
Right, Principal?
Yeah, besides,
the school can't take responsibility
for a student's family issues…
There are limits, you know.
So you're just going
to leave him like that?
You know that in this era,
not going to school
is also a valid choice, right?
-We teachers can't be saying that!
-Mr. Onizuka, wait a moment!
Ryunosuke, you tell him something too!
I'm sorry.
I'll leave these matters
for the two of you to decide.
What the heck?
Excuse me.
What is it, Ms. Kashiwabara?
I need to tell Mr. Onizuka something.
Okay.
What's the matter?
I found something really bad.
Something bad?
It's Kenta Katayama's social media.
It looks like he's trying to do something…
Kenta.
Yes.
Everyone is already gathered.
Hello, everyone.
It's time, so we'll depart.
We are going to a quiet, remote place,
then we'll fill the car with exhaust gas
so we can all die together,
that's the plan.
Let's do this.
It hurts!
What are you doing? It's dangerous!
Kenta,
do you know what a teacher's job is?
What?
It's to protect
the future of their students.
I heard that from someone.
-What's with you?
-Shut up!
My wife went back to her parents' house,
my tooth hurts,
and my dental implants cost money.
I'm in a bad mood!
You idiots.
Every one of you!
Go home already!
You,
how long do you plan
on keeping up with this boring stuff?
Ah, my tooth.
Just now, it hit my lower back too,
so I have to go to the hospital.
Which means more medical bills.
It doesn't matter anyway.
No one in the world cares about me.
Right now, with social division
and global warming,
it doesn't seem like
anything good will happen.
Even so, we have to keep going.
Because we're human.
What, you're quoting Mitsuo Aida?
What?
You actually know Mitsuo?
Because my mother liked him.
Your mother will be sad too,
if you do something stupid.
If you're going to say that, then tell me…
Why shouldn't I die?
What?
Why do I have to stay alive?
Well…
I mean…
So there is no reason.
Nothing matters.
Because…
I would be sad.
What?
If you die, I would be sad.
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean,
we just met and I still don't know
anything about you,
but we managed to do
things together and it was fun.
And besides, look…
I haven't decided
on a nickname for you yet.
"Troublemaker Kid?"
Or "Lonely Boy?"
I want to do lots of fun things with you.
With you and everyone in the class.
My class has 28 people.
Not a single one can be missing.
Are you stupid?
It's enough.
Forgive yourself, Kenta.
It was all COVID's fault.
Not yours.
I'm sure your mother thinks so too.
The only one who can forgive you
is you.
Let's go home.
Get on.
Hold on tight.
Tighter.
Do it right.
Dammit.
Why is it so warm?
Why?
Let's go.
Idiots!
Morning.
What is it?
Nothing.
I was just wondering if you would ask,
"Did something happen?"
I'm sure something happened between you
and Kenta Katayama yesterday.
Well, yes, you could say that.
That happy face of yours…
Does that mean he's coming back?
Yes.
I'm sure.
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone!
What? No way.
Has anyone seen Kenta?
Seems he's absent today too.
That's strange.
Excuse me, could you start homeroom?
Ah, sorry.
Right.
I need you all to decide
whether you're going
to major in science or humanities,
so I'll hand the forms out.
Good morning, everyone!
I'm sure you don't remember me,
so I'll introduce myself again.
Kenta Katayama, Cancer, blood type O.
My future dreams…
I have none.
Wait, that's not right,
I plan to find them
during my three years in high school.
Yesterday, I declared that to my father.
I…
I don't plan to work at your company.
But don't worry.
I will never do anything
to cause trouble for you.
So…
won't you shake my hand?
I remembered
what my mother told me a long time ago.
She said that when foreigners shake hands,
it's to declare that they want
to know more
about the other person.
Can't I?
So that's how it is.
I hope we can get along!
Sorry, I forgot something important.
After talking to Onicchi,
I was thinking about
a nickname for myself.
My mom always called me this
when I was little…
Ken-Ken. So call me that!
All right.
Ken-Ken is here too,
our class has become a perfect number.
Everyone.
Let's make today a good day too.
And give me good feedback scores…
Help me get those numbers up! Thank you!
-HE NEVER USES TABLETS AT ALL, WHAT A PAIN
-TOTALLY
LET'S GET RID OF ONIZUKA
MR. ONIZUKA GOT A LOW SCORE
If anything,
you can even call me Great Teacher.
It's like this class has
a hidden mastermind, like on TV…
The reason he confessed his love
was because he wanted
to make the person he loves happy!
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.