12th Century, China.
The Northern Song Dynasty was in disarray.
The emperor had no interest in governing,
and officials indulged
in bribery and corruption.
Those who advocated for change
were deemed rebels,
and all who revolted were quelled instantly.
The citizens,
faced with taxation and poverty,
became village-plundering bandits,
perpetuating a cycle of robbery and terror.
Yet the militia,
who were to protect their people,
choose instead to act
as accomplice to these thieves,
and helped transport
their stolen loot-turned-bribes.
These tributes are for Sir Gao Qiu.
Carry them with utmost caution!
Yes, sir!
[Imperial Guard]
[Yuncheng, Northern Song]
Ready?
Halt.
Who goes there? Move aside.
Pardon us, sir.
But our wagon has lost a wheel.
The three of us alone cannot carry it aside.
Assist them at once.
Yes, sir.
Move.
Get this wagon aside.
Retreat!
Fire!
Fight!
It's the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
Villain, you dare plunder our people's taxes?
Your soldiers are not the cowards.
They run, because you are the coward.
Cowards lose their men, and their money.
We found them!
They're right here, sir!
The year cursed us with barely any rain.
Our people suffer from taxation as well.
[Song Jiang, Yuncheng Clerk]
Yet bandits steal whatever foods remain.
Perhaps the heavens themselves
have forsaken us.
Are you alright?
You'd best look where you're going, lass.
No, she cannot see.
Would you like to buy a flower, sir?
What?
A flower, you say?
Smell that.
[Lu Zhi Shen, Monk]
These are sprigs of mint.
She has mistaken the scent
for that of a flower.
I see.
I prefer these herbs
over any beautiful flower.
Here.
They smell quite refined, no?
I shall buy your entire stock, lass.
- Everything she has, Song Jiang?
- That's right.
Thank you.
Sir... Song Jiang?
Yes.
There.
Careful now.
[Yuncheng]
[Yuncheng Administrative Office]
Remember, bright smile!
Bring us the booze!
Apologies for the wait, sirs.
You damned slowpoke!
Song Jiang, you must entertain our guests.
These soldiers act as though
this were a tavern.
They carry our people's taxes with them.
We must be grateful for their hard work.
Any child could tell you
they carry bribes, not taxes.
That is the role of the militia.
They'll demand booze and meat at every stop,
and those who refuse them will only perish!
Hey! Where's the alcohol?
Forgive us, sir. We'll bring it right over.
Emergency! Emergency!
Sir, it's an emergency!
What is it?
A neighboring village has fallen to bandits.
What's the commotion?
Sir, I plead your assistance.
A neighboring village is being plundered.
Would you please lend us your assistance?
How utterly ridiculous.
We're busy transporting these precious taxes.
We have no orders to protect any villages.
These are lives we can save, sir.
Song Jiang, these men are busy.
Yuncheng has its share of warriors, no?
They are currently on their rounds,
and will not return in time.
- Sir, please!
- Silence!
We are duty-bound to transport these taxes!
Sir, do you truly transport
our people's taxes with you?
You're ruining the taste of my booze.
Get him out of my sight!
Take him away!
Go on, go on.
Where is this village you speak of?
It is the very one we visited days ago.
Sir?
Hello?
Is there anyone left alive?
Lass!
She's still breathing!
Pull through, lass. Can you see us?
She's suffered a fatal injury.
What is it?
I can't hear you. Speak up!
Flowers...
Sir Song Jiang...
Lass!
[The people are suffering...]
The people are suffering.
And all turn a blind eye to this fact.
I was once the very same.
Yet when I felt the warmth of a child's life
fade away in my arms,
something within me finally snapped.
Our government and militia
refuse to acknowledge our citizens.
Our citizens,
who are dying to bandits and poverty.
We have none to blame for this fate,
but this very country.
This rotten country of ours
killed that very child.
I must question my very purpose
by complying to this corruption
through my ignorance.
Humans who die accomplishing nothing
have served no better purpose
than the trees that surround us.
No, even trodden mint leaves
emit a refined scent,
in all their stubbornness.
No longer will I
rely on the heavens to strike.
I will take action myself.
For if heaven refuses to send aid,
then we, the people must act.
And I will fight with like-minded individuals
till this country changes itself anew.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
I pray this will be the beacon
to illuminate the dark of this land.
Friend, won't you deliver my message
to our comrades of the light?
[Five Years Later]
[Dongjing Kaifeng, Capital of Northern Song]
[Imperial Guard]
[Imperial Guard, Parade Ground]
[Wang Jin, Martial Arts Instructor]
[Militia]
[Imperial Guard]
[Episode 1]
Do you grow bored?
Come at me with whatever you desire.
[Lin Chong, Spearman Instructor]
Stand!
And you call yourself an Imperial Guard?
These are simple exercises.
[Imperial Guard: The emperor's own soldiers]
Remember your duty to protect our emperor.
Hey!
Protect him, from what?
You submitted another request, sir?
Don't look so dissatisfied, Lin Chong.
While I think it fine to test our trainees,
if we impose such a trial,
none will join the Guard.
Why so?
Because all will fail.
And that is fine.
The Imperial Guard must remain strong.
We cannot humor such coddled individuals.
Then we shall garner the resentment
from those such people.
You make a fair point.
Someone will eventually see
the merit to my ways.
"Someone"?
You cannot mean Gao Qiu, do you?
He is the very definition of "coddled".
Enough.
It is my nature to be uptight.
I cannot change that.
They're here. Pull over.
[Cargo]
Is this all you are carrying?
Yes, sir.
Then you may pass.
[Ruan Xiao Wu, Fisherman]
[Ruan Xiao Er, Fisherman]
[Ruan Xiao Qi, Fisherman]
Brother, what are you doing?
Nothing tastes better than smuggled salt.
Do we meet in a bamboo glade
so I am less capable of defending myself?
You may be at ease, good sir.
I am one known as Lu Zhi Shen.
A mere test will not change the country.
You, a stranger,
will complain about my methods as well?
Though you can reignite an unlit candle,
you cannot gather its ashes
to make a candle anew.
I'm afraid I don't follow.
Reforming the Imperial Guard
will not change this country.
I wish to revolutionize this country,
with a like-minded fellow such as yourself.
And what do you suggest I do?
I have come to hand you this.
"Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name"?
If heaven has forsaken us,
then we must take action ourselves.
"We".
You have others recruited to your cause?
I cannot accept these writings of yours.
Carry that in, carefully.
Don't you dare drop our load!
[Chao Gai, Bandit King]
If it touches water, it's gone forever!
I'm surprised you can read
in such darkness, sir.
Why do you continue to reread these writings?
Find me the man who wrote this, Wu Yong.
If I may ask, why?
[Wu Yong, Private Tutor]
Because he is a dangerous man.
So you will kill him?
Go, find him.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
Song Jiang continued to play
the incompetent official,
all while gathering comrades
to one day strike against the country.
Would you like to buy a flower?
Sir... Song Jiang?
Song Jiang.
You called, Xu Li?
You've used the wrong character here.
My apologies, sir. I'll fix it right away.
You've misspelled a name as well, how rude.
I shall fix that as well.
And please, fix your attire.
My attire?
Your sleeves, they have ink on them!
I am a clumsy fellow, sir.
How do you get ink on your sleeves?
Even children know to keep tidy.
Sir, about these villages here...
They've all been plundered
by the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King, no?
Yes, what of it?
I'm simply perplexed.
Not a single villager
was killed in the attack.
What are you getting at?
Why did his troop not attack
the surrounding villages as well?
All the other bandits show no mercy.
And it's far easier to loot villages
than attack the Imperial Guard.
Who cares what a bandit is thinking?
You must fix your attire at once!
Yes, sir.
I shall handle the rest of our work.
Folks, please. Feel free to head on home.
- I better not see another mistake.
- Yes, sir.
It takes double the time to fix them.
I understand, sir.
- Now don't keep Lian Lian waiting.
- Right.
I mean, enough!
- You'd best do well, you understand?
- Yes, sir.
[Look into the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King]
I am the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
Leave your carriages and wagons here!
We'll capture you today, villain!
- I'm next.
- No, it's my turn!
I am the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
- No, I am!
- I am!
No, I am!
[Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King]
- I'm the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
- No, me!
I am the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
What do you mean, "harsh treatment"?
It is my duty to cultivate capable soldiers.
Yet you ignore those who pay you a bribe.
[Gao Qiu, General of the Imperial Guard]
A bribe?
I heard about your proposal.
Mandate a test to join the Guard, is it?
What a clever way to fill your own pockets.
You misunderstand my intentions, sir.
As a martial instructor,
it is my duty to test our guards.
So your one word will decide
whether they can join or not?
As general of the Imperial Guard,
it is my duty to worry
about the potential of corruption.
Though you may be general,
you have disrespected me so, sir.
Rescind your proposal of a test.
- General Gao Qiu...
- Return to your assigned duties!
Am I clear, Master Wang Jin?
My apologies, sir.
Not to worry.
I take no offense.
If you shall excuse me.
Yes, of course.
Welcome home, Dear.
Yeah.
Will you be having dinner tonight?
I already ate.
Then how about some tea?
My wife.
Please, leave me be.
[Zhang Lan, Lin Chong's wife]
[General Lv Rong has been captured.
Master Wang Jin is in danger]
Master Wang Jin...
Master, you must run.
Run, you say?
Prepare to leave at once.
Take your mother with you.
I do not understand.
Your close friend, General Lv Rong,
has been captured as a suspected rebel.
He is to serve as an example
to the rest of the rebels.
Master, you will be next.
How do you suggest
I escape with my elderly mother?
I shall make all necessary arrangements.
I've already taken your stead
outside our walls.
Lin Chong...
Master, you must knock me out.
Our every movement is being monitored now.
I only see apprentices around.
A spy is hidden among them.
Now, hurry!
You have my gratitude, Lin Chong.
Take this as a token of appreciation,
from one martial artist to another.
This is where we part ways.
It will only be temporary.
I pray that you remain well.
I won't hear our staffs cross again.
Farewell.
Farewells are always a difficult endeavor.
No.
He has reminded me
good friends are a blessing.
That is why I shed tears for our parting.
You must thank life for those bonds.
[Madame Wang, Wang Jin's mother]
The reason why you cry
for a friend you must part with,
is because you lived a fulfilling life,
Jin.
He is a man I am proud to call a friend.
Welcome home.
You waited all night?
You were never one to return at dawn...
Well, I am now home safe.
Rest. A night without sleep is taxing.
What are you doing?
I am mimicking my wet nurse.
She used to comfort me in this way.
Why?
Because you looked quite lonely, my dear.
You smell of winter daphne's.
[Yan Po Xi, traveling entertainer]
Yan Xin!
[Ma Gui, Song Jiang's Spy]
Ma Gui?
I see Bai Lan is here as well.
But where is Yan Xin?
Come, this way.
Bai Lan.
My husband has died.
This is what he left for you.
Yan Xin was an excellent spy.
I will not ask how he passed.
But I shall keep his spirit close to heart.
As well as this memento he has left me.
Master Wang Jin has safely escaped
the Imperial Guard.
Ma Gui?
I shall take over my husband's mantle.
[Li Fu]
[Qinglian Temple, Intelligence Organization]
Your instruction is on par with Wang Jin.
How does it feel to sit
in your mentor's throne?
You are?
First, I would like to ask one thing.
Do you know where Wang Jin has gone?
No. I have denied this countless times.
Then one more question.
Have you heard word of a monk
Wang Jin met in a bamboo grove?
I will take anything you know.
No, I cannot say I have.
I hear a competent soldier was slain
outside these very walls.
All while carrying his elderly mother
on his back.
What a stunt, I say.
Excuse me, sir.
I come bearing news about this author.
Oh? So you found him?
No, sir.
But a mysterious monk handed
the same writings to one of our subordinates.
The very same script.
Let us keep an eye on this monk.
Sir, you are
the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King.
Why bother with the author of this text?
Read it, and you will understand.
Why have you come?
You must leave at once.
What?
Sir Song Jiang insists you are in danger.
Alright.
When?
Tonight.
I've stationed my men outside these walls.
I cannot leave so easily. I rather stand out.
When night falls, come to the barrack walls
as you did with Wang Jin.
You shall be safe there.
And bring your wife with you.
Zhang Lan?
She is equally in danger.
What danger?
Our marriage was a cover,
to make it look as though I've settled down.
As things stand, Zhang Lan will...
Things aren't going well between you two?
The very opposite.
Zhang Lan...
She has surrendered her heart to me.
Who is this man?
He was a messenger for Sir Gao Qiu.
An invitation to a meal.
Did this man make any note of that?
No, he declared he came to have his fun.
A damn trap!
I will be charged
for murdering Gao Qiu's messenger.
Let us claim he violated me.
That is why you cut him down.
But imagine the looks people would give you!
You killed a man for my sake.
And I must reciprocate
that love you've shown me.
Zhang Lan...
Listen to me.
I only masquerade as a spearman instructor.
In truth, I work for a man named Song Jiang.
To change this country for the better.
Change this country?
I will now escape this place.
You will stay here as a woman
abandoned by her husband.
You are my home, Dear.
I do not care who you truly are.
Why?
Why love a man like myself?
You act like you know it all,
yet you know nothing.
Love does not need a reason, my dear.
Zhang Lan...
I...
Song Jiang!
Lin Chong has been apprehended.
You must leave this village at once!
That, I cannot do.
If I escape,
Lin Chong will have no place to return home.
I will remain right here.
Lin Chong knows your name.
He would never give that intel away.
I understand your conviction,
but if we lose you,
what will become of our movement?
If my death ends this movement,
then that is all my ambitions
ever amounted to.
You can avoid death,
yet choose to face it willingly.
Is that not betraying
those very ambitions of yours?
Lu Zhi Shen.
You are also betraying your comrades!
How can I preach a great cause
without even trusting my own men?
I will choose to believe in Lin Chong.
Lin Chong.
I see you have received quite the beating.
Your wife, Zhang Lan, was it?
She continues to plead your innocence.
I did not know he was a messenger
of General Gao Qiu's.
I am well aware.
No fool would knowingly murder
a messenger of the general.
You believe my words?
But of course.
Sir Li Fu...
I am the one who sent that messenger
to be slain by your hands.
What?
Locusts are dangerous pests to keep around.
Two will immediately propagate,
and become a plantation-killing drove.
These writings light a fire
in people's hearts.
It has even inspired
a loyal countryman as myself.
I...
I am only a spearsmanship instructor.
You share Wang Jin's eyes.
The eyes of a locust.
Who wrote these scriptures?
Tell me.
Or else we shall torture Zhang Lan.
That woman...
She knows nothing!
Come, this way.
So you are Zhang Lan.
You are indeed quite the beauty.
Do you wish to save Lin Chong's life?
Yes, sir.
No matter the method?
Then you know what you must do.
Do you not?
If I am able to save my husband...
Then I fear nothing.
Undo your garments.
Keep going.
Guards!
General Gao Qiu!
What a cowardly man.
Do you think a woman like myself...
would be able to kill a man like you?
What?
Lin Chong is innocent!
You have taken my husband's life hostage,
in hopes of violating me.
Where is the justice
in this capital of Kaifeng?
I only masquerade as a spearman instructor.
In truth, I work for a man named Song Jiang.
To change this country for the better.
If I had known sooner...
I would have been able to support you.
What are you doing?
My dear...
Do I...
still smell of winter daphne's?
Stop!
Enough.
Terrible news, Lin Chong.
Your woman has died.
What?
Why does that bother you?
How did she die?
She killed herself.
Put a knife to her neck, and sliced.
You succumbed to lust,
and attempted to violate her.
So what if I did?
Did you not check her belongings beforehand?
Or perhaps you never thought
his wife would be wielding a knife.
Does the Qinglian Temple underestimate me
after gaining Cai Jing's favor?
What were her...
What were Zhang Lan's last words?
Come again?
Her last words.
I don't know.
She asked if she still smelled
of winter daphne's.
- If memory serves correctly, that is.
- Silence!
Now that his beloved has died,
no amount of torture will get him to speak.
Even death turns a beauty
into a hunk of meat.
No, I...
I failed to notice...
her love for me.
This was to be the start of our future.
Gao Qiu! You bastard!
Gao Qiu!
You bastard!
"If you seek birds,
then why not offer a perch?"
"Birds cannot fly forever, else they'll die."
"If you seek a perch,
come to Liangshan Marsh."
Pardon me.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
Where are you headed to?
Liangshan Marsh.
Why the marsh?
The Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King
calls for me.
It is too dangerous.
These are bandits who pillage
every last village they come across.
The Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King
only aims for dirty money.
He's not murdered a single villager.
But why go to see him yourself?
The one who left this note
is telling me two things.
One, they have more intel than us.
And two...
They see the fault in my writings.
If I seek answers,
I am to go to Liangshan Marsh.
There it stands.
Like a stronghold that floats above water.
There are around 2,000 to 3,000 bandits
over yonder.
They are ruled by the man known as Wang Lun.
No, do you intend to storm the place?
Even the militia
struggle to overcome that fortress!
That is the perch
the Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King refers to.
If our comrades have no base,
then we are doomed to repeat
a tragedy like Lin Chong's.
I will start by building a country there.
Song Jiang...
Though it will be quite the small country,
it will be inhabited
by those with large ambitions.
Yes.
That small country of yours
will one day overtake this rotten one.
I read your writings extensively.
Those who have strong ambitions...
would have their hearts set ablaze by it.
Yet ideals alone cannot shape a country.
When starting a fire,
one must first collect the branches.
Go on.
This is a magnificent text
that will spark inspiration in our men.
Though your ideology is grand,
there is one component that is lacking.
And what may that be,
Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King?
Myself.
You, sir?
Call me Chao Gai.
I shall become your first branch.
I will give you your country.
Chao Gai.
For starters, a small country will do.
Indeed.
I want that fortress for our cause.
No, Lin Chong will be murdered.
We cannot lose Lin Chong.
Though it is a gamble,
it is not an impossible one.
Enough!
What have you done
aside from write, Song Jiang?
All you've given us is abstract theories.
We of Qinglian Temple will take action.
We shall rebuild this country
from the shadows.
You have grown drunk on your own strength.
You are doomed to die on the battlefield.
A spy like myself
could never become a normal woman.
"Yang Zhi, the Blue-faced Beast"? Not bad.
You order me to abandon a child
who has much in his future?
I do not fear your face.
It is blood I fear the most.
You must save something bigger.
That is to say, this country of ours.
Live!
This is how I create a country.
That is no way to be a king!
Then why else do countries fall to ruin?
Song Jiang!
[Episode 1- FIN]