Wu Huilian
She wouldn't really try to kill herself, would she?
It's so ugly
When did you get
such a scruffy little black bird?
Godmother
Its name is Yaya
Yaya
Yaya, Yaya
And one more thing
Don't call me Godmother
Call me Sister Lan
Call me Sister Lan, come on.
Sister Lan.
That's more like it. Here.
Does Sister Lan look
glamorous today or what?
Shameless.
You stupid bird.
Spouting nonsense here.
Watch me glue that beak of yours shut.
Pretty, so pretty.
Sister Lan is pretty.
Yangyang's such a sweet girl.
Not like the one at our house.
The egg lecturing the hen.
Outrageous.
I really underestimated Wu Huilian's nerve.
I thought she'd be trying to kill herself.
Turns out she's here badmouthing me.
All that worry for nothing.
Forget it.
Yiran.
Morning, Yangyang.
Your outfit's so pretty.
Thanks.
Here's a bun for you.
Why did you come down dressed like that?
None of your business.
Worry about yourself.
Go change your clothes.
Why should I change?
Celebrating your eight years in prison?
All dolled up like that,
scared people won't notice you?
We're visiting Pops' grave soon,
and you plan to wear this?
I'm dressing up nice,
so he knows we're doing well up here.
Then he'll rest easy down there.
I swear.
Making me dress up like this.
Pops would leap right out of his grave.
Let him leap out, then.
Let him take a good look.
See how gorgeous the two of us are.
All dolled up so glamorous.
And how great our lives are.
Great, my ass.
Liangliang.
Next year, let's come see Grandpa Li again, okay?
Okay.
Now who's been here?
Someone still thinks of your Pops.
That's nice.
Old Li
I haven't seen you in ages
Are you doing okay over there?
I brought you some liquor
I know it's your favorite.
Hello?
Is something wrong?
Oh, Old Li
Look at you
You couldn't even bear to kill a chicken
Why'd you play the hero, huh?
Well, isn't this just great.
It's all over for you now
Leaving us a widow and orphan behind.
Old Li
Have a drink
Honestly, all these years
locked up in there
I just drifted through in a daze
I don't even know how
but the time just flew right by
Come on
I'll drink first, out of respect
Come on, you have one too
If I hadn't been so reckless
I wouldn't have torn this family apart
I'm sorry
Yiran's all grown up now
She's turned out so pretty
Everything about her is great
It's just that temper of hers
Stubborn as a mule
But that's okay
She's my own flesh and blood
I won't stoop to her level
Don't you worry
Are you done yet, Wu Huilian?
Come on
It's been eight years.
Three cups for each year
I'm drinking 24 cups
Old Li, come on
Have another cup
I'll have another cup
You have another one too
I'll drink one more as a penalty
I'll have another cup
Wu Huilian
Just look at the state you're in now
Get down
I can't be bothered dealing with you
Fine, fine, fine
I'll look after her, okay?
You're just playing favorites
Old Li
Yiran
Mommy misses you
I don't miss you
Look at how this is written
The two of you, take a look
What the heck is this?
And you two call yourselves college students
Can't even write a eulogy
Pops
Junior college
I went to junior college
He's the one from a top university
I studied acting
Not script writing
Acting, my ass
What good does that do?
In the end you still got no real job
You're so proper, then you write it
Me?
Wrote it a dozen times and you're still not happy
This eulogy
is meant to let the living
remember and mourn
and let the departed rest in peace
Get it?
Whatever, I don't want to do this anymore
Bro, we can't just refuse the client
Boss Zhang really is paying a lot
So what if he's paying a lot?
Can it bring his wife back to life?
He just wants to show off
You're just a kid, you don't get it.
You
You shut your mouth
Honor the dead above all
With this eulogy
if you get one word wrong
or use one wrong punctuation mark
that's disrespectful to the dead
In our line of work
we have our own rules
Rules, rules
It's rules all day long
What era are we even in?
Still the same old routine
Bullshit
I quit
I'm off to the zoo
You, you get back here
If I could write it myself
what would I need you for?
You brat
Uncle Chen
Yiran, you're here.
Long time no see, Uncle Chen
Quite a special welcome ceremony
Sorry about that
Have a seat, have a seat
I'll go teach that brat a lesson
Xiaofang
Yiran, I missed you so much
I missed you too
You horrible woman
You came back and didn't call me right away
I came to find you right away, didn't I?
And Uncle Chen? What's up with him?
Why is he so angry?
It's my useless brother, who else
You know how it is
Chen Baixi?
Yeah
That was him just now?
Forget about him
Your timing's perfect
I need a huge favor.
Do me a favor
Look at this.
I've got so many gray hairs now.
Juanzi.
Can my head get a fresh start?
It's all up to you.
Well, you've come to the right place.
Sister Lan.
I'm top-notch these days.
My skills are seriously good.
This is all my work.
I want...
that perm.
She was my idol when I was young.
Alright.
Sister Lan.
Today, Curly and I will be taking care of you.
Who's Curly?
Let me give you a grand introduction.
This one.
Come on.
Once we finish this hairstyle, you'll step out
and blow them away.
If we could be as one, I'd not fear death;
with our love, I'd envy no immortal's breath.
That's so beautifully written.
You don't know this,
but Lili and I were childhood sweethearts.
Who would've thought...
Every ordinary moment I spent with you
was a kind of brilliance
So heartfelt
So moving
It expressed my exact feelings.
Thank you
It's the least we could do
My condolences
Oh, right
My wife left behind some personal effects
Could you help sort them out for her?
Not a problem
Leave it all to us
Let's head to the ceremony site
Okay
Boss Chen
The cremation has to be the first cremation
Just as you requested
We've got it booked
Thanks to Master Li for lending a hand
But let's go the whole hog
How about you come with me on one more job?
Brother Min
Cheng Weimin, our mortician
He's the ace of Paradise Funeral Home
Hello, Brother Min
Come on
Let's go, get in
Yiran, I knew it
It's so great you're back
You're back and already doing me a huge favor
Chen Xiaofang
I really fell for your trick.
Dumping every rotten job on me
Sister Lan, it's all set
Zhang Lijuan
You permed my hair into this hideous mess
How is this anything like Marilyn Monroe?
Look at her
Now look at me
Come on, don't be mad
A mistake
This
It's all its fault
Curly
It must be in a bad mood today
Well, I'm in an even worse mood now
Let me tell you
For this godawful hair
I'm not paying you a cent
My perm special is 158
I wouldn't even give you 5.8
You're trying to cheat me!
5.8 wouldn't even cover the electricity
Don't insult me like that
You're the one insulting me
Just look at what you did to my hair
Permed it into this hideous mess
Have some herbal tea, cool down
Why would I drink that?
Just cool down
Look at my hair
It's so ugly
It's not that ugly
Yeah, exactly
Wang Daren, what's that supposed to mean?
I mean, the hairstyle's ugly
What do you mean, Wang Daren?
No, no, that's not what I meant either
It's not your fault
Not her fault, it's mine
It's my fault for being ugly
No, no, no
The perm's ugly, the perm's ugly
Who permed it ugly?
Curly
Curly permed it ugly
That's right, it's all Curly's fault
Well, since Curly ruined it
Then you're responsible
So the money
I won't charge you
In your dreams
Shameless
Hey, I didn't say that
You stupid bird
Open that beak and talk nonsense again
And I'll turn you into...
Troublemaker! Troublemaker!
158 for the perm special!
Fine
I'll go ask Li Yiran
And see if she'll pay you
It's fine. Sorting of personal effects is easy.
Just relax.
The deceased today...
Jiang Lili.
Diagnosed with stomach cancer a year ago.
Doctors gave her three months at most.
But she toughed it out with chemo,
and hung on until just two days ago.
Sometimes you have to wonder,
the will to survive against a deadly illness,
even Death himself gives it some respect.
We're here.
Ms. Jiang Lili
Sorry to disturb you
I'm Chen Xiaofang from Paradise Funeral Home
Cheng Weimin
Li Yiran
Now, we'll begin the sorting of personal effects
Here, put these on
Heaven really envies lovers in love
What a perfect couple they were
There's even more under the pillow
It's such a terrible shame
What's wrong?
Felt like something just pricked me.
Let me see.
There's nothing there.
You're just imagining it.
Get to work.
You've got some nerve.
She's still lying right there.
What's there to fear? She just had chemo.
She won't wake up anytime soon.
Did you two hear that?
Hear what?
A woman and a man talking.
Watch your improper words.
Speak no ill-omened words.
Didn't I tell you to loosen up?
Don't be so jumpy.
Fair enough, it's your first time.
Do it a few more times and you'll get used to it.
Let's go.
Off to the funeral home.
There's no time left.
Li Yiran
Yiran
Use this phone for now
My number's in there
Hey, Yiran
Where are you?
Sir, ma'am
My condolences
Mr. Zhang
Everyone, pay your respects.
First bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Water... water.
Zhang Wei, aren't you scared?
She's only got a couple days left.
Then you and I can be together forever.
Yiran.
I looked everywhere for you.
Why did you run off out here alone?
You're all spaced out.
What's wrong?
Tell me...
Can you fake loving someone?
Why?
Forgot how Zhuang Qiang acted so soon?
It's got nothing to do with him.
I just feel like...
Zhang Wei's acting a little strange.
How is he strange?
Come with me.
Come on down
They saw me, they saw me
I told you to come down earlier
It's way too obvious
Did they see or not?
Nobody noticed, right?
Don't worry.
Those two old fools
are crying their eyes out.
No way they'd notice this stuff.
Damn it!
Your wife just got buried,
and you're already this eager?
Holy crap.
Li Yiran.
Are you the Monkey King or what?
Wait, how'd you know about this filthy pair?
This... this is a bit complicated.
I'll tell you later.
I've been looking all over the funeral home for you.
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
Are those two the adulterers?
What does it have to do with you whether they are or not?
Don't move.
I'm going over there. So shame...
So shameless!
It's got nothing to do with you.
Xiaofang, hold her back!
Auntie Huilian.
Let go of me!
Listen to me.
What they're doing is against the law.
This is adultery, you know?
Come back!
So it's adultery, so what?
Is it any of your business?
I'm gonna go teach those two a lesson.
How can you let this stand?
Oh my God
What?
Go take a look, quick!
Dad, Dad!
Dad, Dad, let me explain!
No, no, no!
Easy, easy!
Dad, Dad, I was wrong!
I really messed up!
You bastard, you tore my clothes!
It's a misunderstanding!
You hit way too hard!
I won't, I won't do it again!
Dad, Dad, hear me out!
Dad!
The filthy pair always gets what's coming to them.
He totally deserves it.
Mind your own business.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Forget it, forget it.
At least someone stands up for justice.
My phone!
Go, go, go!
Everyone passing by, come take a look!
Paradise Funeral Home, you rotten bastards!
Ruined my name, cut off my livelihood!
If you don't apologize to me today,
this isn't over!
Paradise Funeral Home, you rotten bastards!
Ruined my name, cut off my livelihood!
If you don't apologize to me today,
and pay me for emotional damages,
What's he doing?
this isn't over!
Zhang Wei's got nothing left to lose now.
He's making a scene here.
You rotten bastards!
Isn't this his own problem?
Why is he blaming you guys?
If you don't apologize to me today,
this isn't over!
What the hell are you pulling here, kid?
Get out of here right now!
Boss Chen, are you blind?
Take a look yourself!
Give me that.
What are you doing?
Listen, this is disorderly conduct.
I'll call the cops on you.
Fine, go ahead and call them.
Let the cops haul me away.
My woman's gone now.
My job's gone.
I've got nothing left.
Like hell I'm scared.
Enough.
Whose fault is it, huh?
You brought this on yourself, didn't you?
Stop making a scene here. Get going.
Exactly. Don't you know?
Heaven is watching.
You're just getting what you deserve.
You think I won't beat you to death?
Come on, come on.
What are you doing? Go on, hit me!
He's hitting people! He's hitting people!
He's hitting people!
Let me tell you.
I've got a heart condition.
Just touch me.
Just try touching me.
Touch me and you're done for.
What heart condition?
Who knows if your records are even real?
Unbelievable.
Fine.
Never mind if my records are real or fake.
You people.
Letting a killer's daughter write the eulogy.
That's true, right?
That's no lie, is it? Am I right?
So what if I'm a killer's daughter?
What business is my eulogy to you?
Well, aren't you proud of it.
The daughter of a murderer.
Carrying a life on her hands.
This is so disrespectful to the dead.
It's her.
The killer's daughter.
The killer's daughter. It's her.
Quit yelling. What are you doing?
The killer's daughter.
Boss Chen, this is such bad luck.
Hurry up and refund my money.
So I can book with someone else.
Alright, alright, alright.
Refund it now, refund it now.
Fine, I'll refund it then.
The killer's daughter.
It's her.
I heard her mom killed someone.
Stay away from her from now on.
Keep it down, don't let her hear.
Criminal genes are hereditary.
Right, watch out or she'll off you.
Off you, just like that.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Refund the money.
Got it.
Let me tell you all.
If I don't get an explanation today,
this isn't over.
I'll give you an explanation.
Who are you?
I'm her mother.
What are you doing?
What's this? I'm recording.
Trying to hit someone again, huh?
I'm recording.
Think I'd pick a time to hit you?
Move.
Everyone's watching.
Calm down.
Calm down like hell.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
She's crazy, she's crazy!
Let me introduce someone.
This is the murderer herself.
Your husband was murdered.
Isn't it all your fault?
It's payback, isn't it?
Payback.
Payback my ass.
That's right.
I am the murderer.
You hear that clearly?
But if you bully my daughter,
I'll take you down with me.
No!
Oh my God!
Someone's been killed!
Murder!
There's so much blood!
Wu Huilian.
Here.
Sit.
How come it's you again?
Yeah.
Quite a coincidence.
So what's it about this time?
She... she tried to kill me!
This is the weapon.
Have you no shame?
You bastard, open your eyes and take a good look.
It's my head that got hurt.
Your fingerprints are all over this weapon.
Officer, that's not it.
She hit herself.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Officer.
This guy stirred up a mob outside our shop.
Lock him up.
Don't you talk nonsense.
You invaded my privacy first.
What nonsense am I talking?
You? Invade your privacy?
You two.
Stop arguing.
What privacy did we invade?
Spell it out clearly.
Go on.
Say it.
Actually, it's nothing really.
Just a small family matter.
How about we settle privately? Okay?
You want to settle privately?
You change your tune faster than flipping a page.
You think this is a small matter?
Have you no shame at all?
What kind of scumbag are you?
Officer, let me tell you what happened.
This man's wife was bedridden and sick,
and he was out committing adultery.
Then his wife passed away,
and he put on a fake show, throwing a big banquet.
And at his own wife's funeral,
he was flirting with that harlot.
Aren't you afraid of being struck by lightning?
Scumbag.
Wait, this has nothing to do with you, right?
Shameless, absolutely shameless!
You bastard, you're truly shameless!
Your shady dealings
have nothing to do with me.
But you bullied my daughter,
and that I won't allow.
Wu Huilian, will you ever stop?
Since when is it your job to dish out justice at a police station?
Li Yiran, I don't care.
He bullied you,
so I'll fight him to the very end.
How are you going to fight?
A life for a life again?
My life's already ruined anyway.
But no one gets to bully you.
I'm not scared of going back to prison.
I'll kill you!
Enough!
I don't care whether you go in or not.
Wu Huilian, I don't care.
Stop getting all sentimental about yourself.
You think you're protecting me?
You're hurting me.
I don't want to face people pointing at me every day.
I don't want people saying my mom's a murderer.
I just want...
What do you want?
It's always about what you want.
You do whatever you please.
You're always this selfish.
You're always so full of yourself.
You do whatever you want.
You vent your anger whenever you feel like it.
What, stabbing one to death wasn't enough?
Fine, I'll give you what you want.
Don't go for him. Here, stab me.
Come on, stab me!
Stop fighting, stop it!
He's right.
You're the one who got Pops killed.
Did I get your Pops killed?
Is that so? Say that again.
Yeah
I'm the one who got your Pops killed
You're absolutely right
Are you satisfied now?
Wu Huilian
You don't deserve to be a mother at all
I...
Li Yiran
Auntie Huilian
Please don't be upset
Yiran only said that because she's furious
It's fine
I know
She's as stubborn as a mule
It's fine
Officer
Do it his way
Let's settle it privately
Fine
A gentleman doesn't fight with a woman
Let's settle it privately
Here, sign this
It's agreed
Your injuries have nothing to do with me
Here, you sign too
Miss Li, it's been almost a week now.
When are you gonna pay this month's rent?
Sorry about that, landlady.
Some family stuff came up and I forgot.
Yiran
I really did like you back then.
Yeah, cheating was my fault, I admit.
And yeah, Linda is older than me.
But you've got to understand,
being with Linda
saves me at least ten years of grinding.
Ten years, you get that?
I came from the countryside.
I clawed my way out with everything I had.
You want me slaving away half my life
just to end up farming back home?
Yiran, I did the math.
This is two years of our dinners, dates,
and shopping bills.
Just to be fair about it,
let's split it down the middle.
I'll knock off the loose change for you.
Just send it to me on Alipay.
social climber from the country
Hope you stay a city dog your whole life
What's up with her?
Bad breakup or something?
It's fine, keep eating.
I can tell you just got back.
You picked the wrong hot pot spot.
But I didn't think it'd be so bad you'd cry.
It's... it's just too spicy.
Yeah, I can see that.
So spicy it brought tears to your eyes.
What are you doing here?
My dad's blood pressure spiked today.
I went to the hospital to get his meds.
About what happened today...
I'm sorry.
Barely back and already causing you trouble.
In the funeral business,
there's always trouble.
That guy from today,
he'll get what's coming to him.
But don't take it to heart.
The way I see it,
this is Xiaofang's fault.
I mean, this should've been her job, right?
Why'd she make you write it? Am I right?
Worst case, just look it up online, you know.
Why haven't you left yet?
Aren't you taking your dad his meds?
It's still raining.
And I see you didn't bring an umbrella.
I'll take you home in a bit.
Eat, just keep eating.
Don't mind me.
Pretend I'm not even here.
Mommy, thank you for today,
for swimming with Yangyang.
I wanna go again tomorrow.
If you like it, Mommy will take you every day.
Mommy, didn't you say water means wealth?
I'm gonna catch all the wealth
Hurry up!
and bring it all home to us!
Yangyang!
You'll catch a cold in the rain, Yangyang!
Come inside, quick!
This child...
I'm gonna earn lots and lots of money for Mommy!
He was right.
You're the one who got Pops killed.
Yiran.
Pops.
You don't deserve to be a mother at all.
Catching the fortune
Slow down, Yangyang
Slow down
I want to catch
Yangyang
all the fortune and bring it home
Come on
Get inside
You silly kid
You'll catch a cold, Yangyang
Hurry inside
I want to earn tons of money for you, Mom
So you won't have to take on so much work
Alright, Mom knows
You're soaking wet all over
Come on, let's go
Let's go home, let's go home
Hello
Yiran
I heard about what happened with you two today
Don't think I'm nagging you
Your mom, she means well for you
Don't say such hurtful things from now on
Her heart's not made of stone, you know
Uncle Daren
Stop trying to talk me into it
I know how to handle this
It's raining pretty hard
You're out working, so stay safe
I'll hang up now
Alright, alright