These are lives we can save.
Flowers...
Sir Song Jiang...
No longer will I rely
on the heavens to strike.
I will take action myself.
For if heaven refuses to send aid,
then we, the people must act.
Locusts are dangerous pests to keep around.
You share Wang Jin's eyes.
The eyes of a locust.
I shall become your first branch.
For starters, a small country will do.
Indeed.
What was your impression of him?
[Song Jiang, Yuncheng Clerk]
Ah, Chao Gai.
Was he as you expected?
His face certainly was not.
His face?
I had imagined many sorts of faces
before our meeting.
But none matched the one
who appeared before me.
If I had to say...
[Chao Gai, Bandit King]
His face left me excited for the future.
I feel my blood...
[Lu Zhi Shen, Monk]
being set ablaze.
What's wrong?
Does he irk you?
[Ruan Xiao Wu, Fisherman]
You always mull in silence
when you're bothered, Brother.
Tell our comrades across the land
of this development.
We shall set this country in motion.
[Dongjing Kaifeng, Capital of Northern Song]
[Episode 2]
Where is Sir Yuan Ming?
[Li Fu, Insurgence Advisor]
He has yet to arrive.
Is that so.
How are the Imperial Guards?
Is it terrible, Li Fu.
[Cang Ying, Military Advisor]
Marshall Tong Guan
insists on re-training the guards.
He only wishes to have strong warriors
at his beck and call.
As a eunuch, I suppose
nothing else pleasures him.
This is no place for sharing complaints.
Tong Guan has always been an odd fellow
when it comes to his men and affection.
We must remember to align our ambitions
[Qinglian Temple, Intelligence Organization]
with that of the ruling chancellor, Cai Jing,
while gripping the reigns from the shadows.
Gao Qiu is garnering the emperor's favor.
[Wu Da, Local Militia Advisor]
He may prove to be a nuisance to us.
That will not happen.
Sir Yuan Ming.
Gao Qiu is but a weed sprouted
by the emperor's foot.
We can do away with him at any moment.
Now cease the idle chatter.
Make your reports.
[Yuan Ming, Leader of Qinglian Temple]
Over 3,000 bandits occupy Liangshan Marsh.
[He Gong, Civil Affairs Advisor]
Even regional militia
refuse to deal with them.
However, these bandits target merchants,
rather than revolt against the country.
It is not logic,
but your spine
which shall alert you to danger.
I have my eyes on many potential rebels, sir.
Not because they are logically
a source of danger,
but because they send shivers down my spine.
That is the sort of intel I wish to hear.
Then I shall start
by presenting these writings.
"Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name", is it?
You are aware of these scripts, sir?
"If heaven refuses to send aid,
then we, the people must act."
I agree with the sentiment entirely.
However!
One must not destroy the country
in the process.
We shall be the ones to take action.
We shall rebuild this nation
from the shadows.
I believe those who are moved by this text
will one day become a dangerous ensemble.
Then we must quickly extinguish these embers.
Let them smolder.
To strengthen the earth,
one must first await a storm.
The presence of a common enemy
will reinvigorate our citizens.
I suspect it will be
a rather bloody storm, at that.
Send our envoys to keep an eye
on these rebels.
Yes, sir.
- Li Fu.
- Sir?
I must ask about this salt.
Is it possible these bandits use salt
as the source of their funds?
Yes, sir.
Though the number of bandits only rise,
the amount of smuggled salt remains steady.
[Salt, cannot be traded...]
Why do you suspect that is?
[without the country's permission]
This salt is smuggled in
through various, ingenious methods.
I believe they trade with utmost caution.
Precisely so.
And what does that suggest, Li Fu?
The one organizing these trade routes
must have a substantial amount of influence.
An individual, like the Pagoda-Shifting
Heavenly King, for example.
What truly sends chills down my spine,
is not one anticipated danger.
But two surprising elements merging together,
to bring about unprecedented change.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
You are as stubborn as they say, Lin Chong.
How do you not see your efforts are in vain?
We already have a country.
What purpose is there
in tearing this nation apart?
[Lin Chong, Spearman Instructor]
You people can only break.
- Continue.
- Yes, sir.
[Huazhou]
Mother, are you alright?
I am fine, my son.
[Wang Jin, Martial Arts Instructor]
The further we trek,
[Madam Wang, Wang Jin's mother]
the further you escape from death's grip.
As your mother, that is my utmost priority.
Mother!
I thank you for your help.
Of course.
But Wang Jin,
you must let your mother rest here.
Pardon?
I can tell her organs are growing weak.
Her expression betrays herself.
I suppose my mother always
was a stubborn woman.
If you will allow us,
then I shall take up your kind offer.
I wish my son could meet you both.
[Shi Li, Chief of Shi Family Village]
Your son?
He lost his mother when he was only six,
and has since dedicated his life
to honing his strength.
Is that not a respectable path to take?
Perhaps, if my son was not such a ruffian,
seeking only to grow ever stronger.
[Shi Jin, Shi Li's son]
Why must we bury Father here?
Your father worked under Song Jiang.
His death cannot be made known.
We cannot even give him a grave?
You need not know any more.
[Ma Gui, Song Jiang's spy]
Mother...
[Yan Po Xi, Yan Xin's daughter]
Po Xi.
We must survive.
Steel your heart for what is to come.
I am sending you away...
to be Song Jiang's mistress.
Mother?
Pardon me, sir.
You have a visitor.
[Tang Niu Er, Song Jiang's assistant]
Yan Po Xi?
My, you've grown.
What brings you here at this hour?
Po Xi? What are you doing?
Tang Niu Er.
- Tang Niu Er!
- Y-Yes, sir!
Why do you cry?
My father has died.
And my mother, she told me to steel myself.
Is that why you have come here?
What a fool.
Your father was a loyal subordinate of mine.
Did you think
I would so easily abandon his family?
My mother said we must survive.
Po Xi.
I desire to create a world
where no such tragedies
are expected to occur.
Create... a world?
I know. You will become my attendant.
Surely that will put you at ease.
Do not worry any more.
Give me pork, veggies,
[Wang Lun, Head of Liangshan Marsh]
and some buns, Pops.
[Zhu Gui, Eatery Proprietor]
You've returned.
You look displeased to see me.
We once fought side-by-side
to change this country, did we not?
And now we've both lost such ambitions.
I ask for food, not harassment.
That looks delicious.
Zhu Gui, give me what he is having.
You damned perverted man.
You once pledged to rid this country
of corruption.
Where has that man gone?
My ambitions have grown, old friend.
Zhu Gui.
Only you are allowed to wield a weapon...
in my presence.
A gift, you say?
Yes. I would never visit empty-handed.
Is this eatery as good as you claim?
Indeed. It is a recent favorite of mine.
Still, why must you go to visit them?
They ought to come to you.
You are not Chao Gai's subordinate.
He is a wanted man,
while I am a countryside clerk.
Which of us would draw less attention
in the streets?
The answer is an obvious one.
Thank you for always visiting.
Of course.
[Chen Li, Zhu Gui's wife]
I'll be back.
Apologies, sir.
Good afternoon.
Welcome, Song Jiang. Do you require a seat?
No, I have come to purchase a gift.
May I have some of your delicious
seafood buns?
Of course.
How many are we feeding?
I would not know.
I will take as many as you can offer.
Coming right up.
My wife has been ill for some time now.
I have heard.
The fishermen in this area
sing high praises of her.
She is a kind woman.
I know a bit about medicinal herbs.
I will bring some next time I visit.
I appreciate your concern, Sir Song Jiang.
But a number of doctors
have already visited my wife.
Is that so.
I, too, wish I could do more.
I apologize for making an unnecessary remark.
No, not at all.
Will this suffice to feed your crowd?
- Yes, thank you.
- It is my pleasure.
Chief! Chief!
What is this commotion about?
He brings trouble!
What do scum like you
want from my villa?
I'll break your legs till you can't walk.
Come at me all at once.
What is this commotion?
Unhand me!
Foolish.
You there.
Did you call me a fool?
It is unhanding your weapon
that I find foolish.
As if you could best me.
You have grown drunk on your own strength.
You belittle, and look down on your foes.
An utter fool.
You are fated to die on the battlefield.
Me?
The Nine Tattooed Dragons, dying in battle?
Come, fight me.
I only gave an explanation
because I was asked.
I would never injure
the son of a village chief.
I will humbly decline your duel.
I do not mind.
Chief Shi Li.
If my son breaks a bone or two,
that is his own fault to bear.
Please humble this arrogant brat.
Are you certain, sir?
He must learn a lesson, through combat.
Then I shall do my part,
to repay your generosity.
Enough slander.
I will keep his injuries to a minimum.
Wait.
If you're facing me, use a proper staff.
Or do you intend to disrespect
the Nine Tattooed Dragons further?
This piece of firewood
will more than suffice against you.
If you are dissatisfied,
then prove yourself by besting me once.
You are Ruan Xiao Wu, yes?
Where might Chao Gai be?
Thank you very much.
[Wu Yong, Private Tutor]
My name is Wu Yong. Please, follow me.
"Timely Rain".
That's your nickname, right?
[Timely Rain]
Indeed, some call me that.
"Timely Rain".
Rain that falls when most inopportune.
What of it?
Nothing.
When it rains, I reckon you use an umbrella.
While we cling to our boats for dear life.
I'm afraid I do not follow.
Even something like rain is different
for you clerks, versus us fishermen.
Is that not true, "Timely Rain"?
On rainy days,
I rush around the village,
worrying for our crops.
On stormy days,
I worry for the integrity of our homes.
On rainy days following a drought,
I feel relief.
It is true, we all perceive rain
in different ways.
And you have just taught me
the dangers of rain atop a boat.
I will continue to learn
from these differences,
and gather the hearts of many within me.
Will that not suffice, Ruan Xiao Wu?
A daytime shower? How mysterious.
Wu Da.
What is on your mind?
I was simply recalling
a sentiment expressed by Yuan Ming.
What sentiment, if I may ask?
When two surprising elements merge together,
they bring about unprecedented change.
Just like this daytime shower here.
Master Lin Chong.
You are Master Lin Chong, are you not?
Who...
I am not surprised you have forgotten.
I am one of your many disciples.
Disciples?
You trained me rough.
Enough to have me pass out.
To see you reduced to scraps...
What a pity.
You must be parched, no?
They've starved you for three days now.
Here. Have some water.
Water?
Here, here.
Drink up.
Water.
Why do you retch? I added plenty of salt.
Why...
Why?
I do not even need this firewood.
My bare hands will be plenty.
Those drunk on their own strength
are fated to lose their lives.
Has our spar sobered you?
I had a feeling you were no ordinary fellow,
yet you have far exceeded my expectations.
I suppose I am obligated to speak the truth.
I formerly trained the Imperial Guard.
I am currently on the run
for reasons I must not disclose.
The Imperial Guard...
No wonder you are so strong.
Rest assured, I did nothing to be ashamed of.
Still, I cannot impose on you any longer.
My mother and I shall leave tonight.
Please, make me your disciple!
Say what?
You, my disciple?
I would like to discuss our plan
to seize Liangshan Marsh.
- I see.
- What do you think we most require?
Soldiers, weapons, and a commander, yes?
Indeed. But I am asking a simpler question.
Eat. We will speak shortly.
You're here.
This is Song Jiang.
I am Lu Jun Yi.
[Lu Jun Yi, Distributor of smuggled salt]
This is Yan Qing.
[Yan Qing, Lu Jun Yi's attendant]
"Lu Jun Yi"?
The greatest merchant of Da Ming, Beijing?
You have heard my name?
Of course!
Your accolades speak for themselves!
Your high praise honors me, good sir.
I have called Lu Jun Yi
to help solidify our plans.
We must talk money.
Money?
Money. Coins. Gold.
Call it what you will.
Lu Jun Yi.
Song Jiang, do you know what this is?
I believe that is salt.
- And wonderful salt, at that.
- Indeed.
Yet to the eyes of us merchants,
each granule here is a speck of gold.
Human beings cannot thrive without salt.
Salt is the embodiment of money.
Precisely.
Every dish known to man uses salt.
These buns use salt.
Preserved foods use salt.
Rations use salt.
Salt is a necessity for survival!
We use salt to preserve
the heads of our enemies.
We use salt to keep our horses running.
Salt. Salt. Salt!
Salt makes this world go round.
Yet we cannot acquire salt so freely.
Indeed. The nation keeps a monopoly on salt.
I see now. This salt has been smuggled in.
Correct.
Chao Gai, you have been
circulating this salt?
No. It is Lu Jun Yi
who controls the salt roads.
So this is where the master merchant
comes into play.
How exactly do you transport this salt?
Every route has an official who checks cargo.
Do you come in by sea?
No, even then, there are checkpoints.
Ships utilize bags of dirt
to remain steady in rough waters.
Otherwise, they would all easily capsize.
Strangely enough, these foolish officials...
Apologies.
I do not mind.
Plenty of us officials are fools.
These officials will check our cargo,
but not the anchoring dirt bags below.
Impossible. Are those bags filled
not with dirt, but with salt?
The human brain works in mysterious ways.
If they think it is dirt,
then it cannot be salt.
If they do not think it is salt...
Then they would never know it to be money.
Lu Jun Yi has routed several paths
and methods for his salt to be carried.
Those who transport my salt
do not realize they are accomplices.
Even if this salt is somehow confiscated,
it cannot be traced back to myself.
All routes and inventory of salt
remain solely inside of Lu Jun Yi's head.
He has written no note of it anywhere.
Chao Gai, you are a brilliant man.
Wang Lun, the head of Liangshan Marsh,
once hoped to change this corrupted nation.
Yet it is because they struggled financially
that they turned to thievery.
But you are different.
You see the future.
With salt alone, you rally soldiers,
purchase provisions,
and will seize Liangshan Marsh itself.
Chao Gai, you are indeed a brilliant man!
Enough praising, I say.
Here.
Eat.
Go on.
Do I pique your curiosity?
I just wondered what you were doing.
I am transcribing Song Jiang's writings.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
"Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name", huh?
Here. You may have a copy.
I don't need anything from a cowardly clerk,
nor a hulking monk.
Is that so?
Then I shan't push.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
I see you do not admonish him.
When searching for Song Jiang,
he was always seen with a suspicious giant.
Yes, I do tend to stand out.
I must admit,
you are nothing like the tales I heard.
How so?
For one, you would not forgive
Ruan Xiao Wu's insolence just now.
Perhaps back when I was a ruffian, yes.
But I have changed, thanks to Song Jiang.
Humans change, time and time again.
Is that not right?
I can only hope so.
And now that you've reformed,
you copy writings all day.
What is it you are doing?
What do you mean?
I am transcribing these writings
for the greater good of this nation.
What are you doing?
- I transport salt.
- Salt.
I cannot understand why Sir Chao Gai
is so partial towards that clerk.
- Do you dislike officials?
- Huh?
- Song Jiang is different.
- All officials are the same.
Then is Chao Gai the same as other bandits?
No!
You will come to understand.
Spend days, months with him,
and you will understand.
Like hell I will.
I wish to learn from you.
True strength will come
at the risk of your life.
I do not mind.
You will need to overcome death's limits.
[Death's limits]
A practical impossibility
for a man like yourself.
"Death's limits"?
It is to go beyond your very limits.
To experience what lies ahead...
when you feel as though you will collapse.
Past these limits, movements come with ease.
Your body moves exactly as you will it.
That is the reward
for overcoming death's limit.
Then please, guide me to that limit.
I will overcome whatever it imposes on me.
You said you were named "Jin", yes?
We share a name.
The road ahead will be excruciating, Shi Jin.
You will curse our encounter every day.
I am prepared for the consequences.
Then I shall impart to you...
the technique of my arts.
Good morning, Tang Niu Er.
Yan Po Xi!
Good morning, Sir Song Jiang!
Po Xi? Good morning.
Are you heading out?
Yes, I have some fishing to do.
Fishing?
When will you return?
I believe I may be late.
You are free to leave before I return.
Please, take me with you.
That, I cannot do. I am meeting a friend.
Is that "friend" a woman?
No, no.
Is that so. I hope you manage to fish lots.
I will.
Not a bite to be had.
Perhaps you chose a poor spot?
That can't be. This is the season for fish.
So tell me, how do you intend
to fish up that catch?
Springing an attack on the unknown
is suicide.
Across the marsh is a natural fortress,
guarded by cliffs on every side.
A fortress, home to 3,000 bandits.
We cannot rely on a frontal assault.
We will need to attack from within.
You plan on making connections with Wang Lun?
Indeed. But I hear Wang Lun
is a cautious man.
None claim to even know his face.
There is one man who does.
Who?
The proprietor of an eatery
next to Liangshan Marsh.
You may know him,
seeing as you bought buns from his place.
Zhu Gui?
He once worked alongside Wang Lun.
I hear they still meet from time to time.
Song Jiang, will you convince Zhu Gui
to aid us in reaching Wang Lun?
Me?
If Wang Lun shares our ambitions,
then we can recruit him to our cause.
If he is but a bandit king,
then we can kill Wang Lun,
and take his fortress for ourselves.
Will it really be so simple?
It will.
For us, it will.
I would like a symbol for our cause.
Song Jiang, do us the honors.
What shall I write?
Fresh catch!
No wonder I had no bites.
I must decline.
Zhu Gui...
I do not wish to associate
with Liangshan Marsh any further.
Song Jiang, I thought
you were an upstanding man.
Will you turn to thievery as well?
Zhu Gui, I have a dream.
I wish to rid this nation of its corruption.
Rid it of corruption.
That man once had the same ambitions.
His words had a certain truth to them.
That is why I lent Wang Lun a hand.
Yet as his numbers and troops grew,
he began to plunder
rich travelers and merchants.
Eventually,
his frustration at failing the civil exam
began to overtake him.
All at once, his motives changed
from his old ambitions, to seeking revenge.
Wang Lun is no longer the man I once knew.
We will not tread the same path as he did.
I can hear it.
Another voice within me.
What does it say?
It suspects you are cut
from the same cloth as he.
My wife is now my sole priority.
I wish to dedicate my life to her,
and her alone.
I understand.
I shall push no further.
What? Lin Chong is still alive?
[Gao Qiu, General of the Imperial Guard]
Yes, sir. Sir Li Fu's orders.
And I ordered you to kill him!
A man who aims for my neck
is being kept alive? Unacceptable!
Transfer Lin Chong to another prison.
Pardon?
He will die in an "accident" along the way.
Am I clear?
An "accident", is it?
Unbelievable.
The moves of an utter fool
cannot be anticipated.
Why not simply play ball with the Emperor?
Damned Gao Qiu!
Hey. Hey!
Did you hear?
Lin Chong is being sent to Cangzhou.
- Why?
- Beats me.
But I hear General Gao Qiu despises him.
Then he will be killed during the transfer?
It's entirely possible.
Great work.
I hope you are not pushing yourself.
Not at all.
Your husband was an excellent subordinate
who gathered intel from all over.
But that is no reason for you
to carry his mantel.
This job is befitting of me, sir.
My daughter... Is Po Xi well?
Indeed. I promised to take her fishing.
She is still a child, that one.
I apologize for the trouble she may cause.
[Lin Chong will be murdered
while being transferred to Cangzhou]
[Lin Chong]
Lin Chong... He will be killed.
Lin Chong will be killed?
Yes.
What to do...
According to our report,
he will be escorted
by ten or so capable guards.
We cannot lose Lin Chong.
Chao Gai, will you lend me some of your men?
Why do we have to save this Lin Chong?
Because all lives are inherently connected.
That's nonsense.
It is not nonsense.
If we save Lin Chong,
we can save a man named An Dao Quan.
If we save An Dao Quan,
we can save Chen Li, and Zhu Gui.
This man is crazy in the head.
Song Jiang, you must make yourself clear.
My apologies.
Lin Chong will be transferred to a prison
where a doctor named An Dao Quan is held.
I can personally attest to his skills.
He is able to cure any disease I've seen.
What's so important about this doctor?
That man will be able to cure Zhu Gui's wife.
You will have Zhu Gui repay the favor
by allowing us to see Wang Lun?
No, I earnestly wish to save her life.
Zhu Gui has lost faith in this world of ours.
That is why I wish to remind him.
This world still has
its share of hopeless fools.
Fools, who will risk it all
to save our people.
You're asking me to believe you?
Ruan Xiao Wu. I understand
you respect Chao Gai, and despise me.
While it is true we aim for the same goals,
our methods differ slightly from each other.
Even so, I think that is perfectly fine.
Then allow me to ask you this.
What exactly is this "method" of yours?
To fight, by encroaching on the heart.
Rather...
To fight, by saving hearts.
That is my way.
Bullshit!
What have you done
aside from write this text?
You've only crafted impractical theories.
It's all talk, no action.
Ruan Xiao Wu! You have stepped out of line!
Lin Chong is the only one
who can help that doctor escape.
You still insist on saving this man?
Please, help me in saving Lin Chong.
I wish to rescue Lin Chong, and An Dao Quan.
To cure Chen Li, and help Zhu Gui.
And to save you as well.
Lives are all connected, Ruan Xiao Wu.
This is how you fight, Song Jiang?
Wu Yong.
How do we save Lin Chong?
Ruan Xiao Wu...
[Da Ming, Beijing]
[Cangzhou]
Do not think death will bring peace to you.
Though there are several routes
the guards could take,
I believe they will avoid the valley.
Why?
The valley has no natural guard
against attacks.
They will likely hug the river instead.
Ruan Xiao Wu, depart ahead of time
to keep watch.
Prepare to give a signal
once the guards are in sight.
But do not have your subordinates with you.
We shall strike with a small team.
Chao Gai, Ruan Xiao Wu,
Lu Zhi Shen, and myself will go.
Really, it will be a strike team of three.
Wu Yong is a tactician more than a fighter.
You four will go alone?
No, I shall join you.
Song Jiang, you cannot be seen with Chao Gai.
You must remain an innocent clerk for now.
Leave this sort of dirty work to us.
I promise to return with him, Song Jiang.
Trust in us.
Thank you.
Lu Zhi Shen,
you will lie in wait at the front.
Chao Gai, we shall await
Ruan Xiao Wu's signal.
They really came this way.
At Ruan Xiao Wu's signal,
we will all take action at once.
While the guards are distracted
by Lu Zhi Shen,
Chao Gai will spring an attack from behind.
Understood.
What was that sound?
Perhaps it was a signal?
There! Someone is blocking the way!
What are you doing here?
I have come to take that man away!
Lu Zhi Shen...
- Apprehend him!
- Yes, sir!
A pincer with two men?
They underestimate us!
Stay hidden in the fronds, Wu Yong.
Do not waste your lives!
Ruan Xiao Wu! I hear you do better in water?
You're damn right I do!
Please, save Lin Chong.
I have the captain's head!
Lin Chong!
You're late.
Lu Zhi Shen.
I'm sorry, my friend!
[Yuncheng Administrative Office]
Song Jiang.
Your head is in the clouds.
If we could expose
just one fault of the government,
it would quickly spread like wildfire.
I came to see you, An Dao Quan.
"Yang Zhi, the Blue-faced Beast"?
Not bad.
I am alive within you.
I believe it to be true.
Saving Bai Sheng?
We're breaking out.
Do not cower! They will realize your lies.
I would never lose.
Has this invisible enemy of ours
noticed our presence?
[Episode 2 - FIN]