What did you say to Phil?
Why'd he bail
all of a sudden?
Hey,
can I at least
finish breakfast?
Lisa's getting in early today.
Oh, crap! Lisa's here!
I'm so dead!
Morning, Lisa.
Your coffee,
75 degrees as usual?
Is this your first day?
Okay! On it.
These are the cast bios
for the show.
This is the title.
Then the profile
starts below.
Why the paper airplane?
Is there a story
behind it?
It looks great.
This cover
tells me nothing.
Neither do these
pointless effects.
You just wasted
10 seconds.
I review at least
40 decks a day.
If every deck
has five things like this,
that's over
33 minutes a day.
I could write
all your resignation letters
in that time.
When's Phil coming in?
He turned us down.
I've got a few
stronger candidates.
I told you
he was our best shot.
He's stubborn.
If he's not interested,
you can't change his mind.
Or did you just
not try hard enough?
He's not interested
in dating shows.
Who says I'm not?
How'd you get in here?
Through the door.
Now that you're here,
let's talk.
I'm interested
in your dating show.
But I have one condition.
Let's hear it.
Everything's negotiable.
I want Cole
as my producer.
Easy enough.
Every cast member
gets a producer.
And Cole's yours.
Let's start with
a quick interview.
Just so we can
get to know each other.
Sure.
Have you ever been
in a relationship?
Not really.
But I almost had one once.
He knows.
Wow! What happened
between you two in high school?
Let's switch gears.
What's your type?
Wait.
Let Phil finish.
I just follow my heart.
When I fall for someone,
I don't give up easily.
Unless...
their heart belongs
to someone else.
You've dated a lot,
haven't you?
I'm not the one
on the show.
Why would I tell you
about my love life?
You're the scriptwriter.
You're writing
my storyline.
I need to know
how you see love.
Makes it easier
to work with you.
You don't.
Let's do a quick
personality quiz.
Get a feel for you.
Hey, guys! I'm Jan.
Check out this outfit.
I've got a secret mission.
I'll be working undercover
as a server
at The Coach.
In a minute,
I'll mask up
and serve tables.
Hopefully
I can pull it off
without anyone
recognizing me.
Here's your
ricotta toast, sir.
And your hot chocolate.
For your hot chocolate,
I'd recommend adding this.
Sorry! Sorry!
I'm so sorry.
What's your name?
Oops.
Busted.
I was asking your name.
I didn't ask
to see your face.
I'm Jan. January.
Excuse me.
Your employee damaged
my MIDI keyboard.
Somebody's
gonna pay for it.
I don't care
if it's the café
or your employee...
February.
March? April?
May.
Stop filming.
I'm so sorry.
Henry.
Still working?
Lisa wants me to find
a new angle on the cast.
You're worried
about your probation, huh?
You'll be fine.
Lisa can be
pretty demanding.
But
she'll give you a shot.
Phil comes off
like a jerk.
But
he's actually
very thoughtful.
He's always there.
Once you get to know him,
you'll realize
he's got a soft side.
He can be vulnerable.
It makes you
want to look out for him.
You really know him.
Let me grab you a coffee.
We can keep talking.
I'm good.
Coffee keeps me up.
I'd better get going.
Yaowei!
Jing Tong,
have you seen Phil?
Nope.
Let's split up
and meet by the stairs.
Okay?
Wait.
There's something
I need to tell you.
The party's about to start.
Can it wait?
Chen Yaowei!
That's exactly why.
Can you just hear me out?
Please don't reject me.
You can fool
everyone else.
But not me.
You only have eyes
for Phil.
You're wrong.