Because Natsuki, you don't really love me.
Wait!
"Getting dumped" means,
being told by someone you like
that they don't like you.
This is Souta Kobayakawa. My boyfriend.
He really is such an unlikable guy.
That's unacceptable!
If you get an E rating on the next mock exam,
you can just give up on
the college entrance exam.
I've been asked to tutor.
But university could still be a catalyst
for some kind of change.
You did well.
[Genuinely falling in love]
This will be my good luck charm, okay?
So, the tutoring,
we'll continue with it like this, right?
Together in the summer,
love and storminess came to our home.
[Episode 2]
A tutor, huh?
You got dumped, so you've got nothing to do
during summer vacation but study.
[Natsuki's friend, Ryo Konno]
Shut up.
[Natsuki's friend, Kazuharu Sanada]
I guess I should start getting serious too.
Come with me, Ryo.
- Darn it!
- Whoa, whoa, watch the watermelons!
Students studying to get into college
sure have it rough.
What about you, Kazu?
Have you decided to go to culinary school?
- Yeah.
- You're taking over your dad's restaurant?
I'm going to become a chef
at a three-star restaurant.
- Isn't that cool?
- I prefer your dad's restaurant.
- Why's that?
- Well, me too.
- Your dad's ramen and dumplings are divine!
- I prefer the fried chicken!
- I want the fried chicken!
- I'll have the soy sauce ramen.
Got it.
So you both love fried chicken,
huh, you and your brother Natsuki?
Because it's super delicious.
[Owner of Ryuunken Sanada]
I'm so happy to hear you say that.
- Wait just a moment.
- Sure.
- Soy sauce ramen, fried chicken...
- And then what happened?
[Riyo's friend, Yui Kagami]
What kind of person is Souta?
He's a really nice guy!
So your tutor is Riyo's boyfriend?
Yeah.
What kind of guy is he?
He's insufferable.
"Getting dumped" means,
being told by someone you like
that they don't like you.
He doesn't consider people's feelings.
I guess you could say he lacks delicacy?
He's very kind and considerate.
Is he one of those people who seems to
exude calm intelligence and good upbringing?
The high schooler crying
at the convenience store was Natsuki?
He talks nonstop
about everything all the time.
He has a super charming
killer smile that everybody likes.
But he's also an opportunist
who is good at manipulating people.
- Really? What an insufferable guy.
- Yeah, he really is insufferable.
Right?
- That's just perfect!
- Isn't it?
Why is Riyo with such an insufferable guy?
Is he handsome?
Not really...
But he's good at teaching math.
You did well.
- I'm curious about what kind of guy he is...
- Really?
Calm down.
Oh, looks like there are some rain clouds.
- Rain?
- Yeah, it looks like it'll start raining soon.
- Oh no! Maybe we should head home.
- Yeah.
Natsuki's weather predictions
are always right.
No, I'm not making a forecast.
More like a message from the clouds.
- So cool!
- You guys are making fun of me, aren't you?
- See you.
I'm home.
Natsuki? Souta is here.
Huh? Already?
- It's delicious!
- I know, right?
I'll be teaching you again today.
Thank you in advance.
We ran into each other
at the convenience store.
You're often at the convenience store.
Souta bought me some ice cream. Want some?
- Not right now.
- Oh, okay.
Then I'll take all of it.
I just said not right now.
What a troublesome guy.
So you like ice cream, huh, young Natsuki?
You don't need to address him
like that, Souta.
- Why not?
- Because it's a waste.
But suddenly calling someone
just by first name might sound a bit harsh.
You think so?
We aren't that close yet.
I don't like being called that either.
Addressing each other
just by the names will bring you closer.
How you address someone is important.
Yeah, but...
Then how about calling him
'Nat' as a middle ground?
What middle ground?
I guess that might be easier to say
than addressing him just by his first name.
All right, then it's decided.
And how will you address him, Natsuki?
It's fine. I won't call him anything special.
You're younger than him, so calling him
just by his first name feels too forward.
- As for 'Mr.' Souta, that's also...
- That's why I won't call him that.
- How about 'Sou'?
- 'Sou'?
People tend to call me that in my hometown.
Really? Then it's 'Sou' and 'Nat'.
Okay, repeat after me.
Yes, Nat.
Well...
Yes, Sou.
No way.
You two are such buzzkills!
We'll be doing tutoring here today?
Because my sister and parents are around.
I see.
Don't stare, it's really messy in here.
Not at all.
I think it's clean.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Nat...
Natsu...
It's fine, you can call me whatever.
But, as Riyo says, it might bring us closer.
My sister is always so pushy.
How do you even deal with that?
But Riyo is super nice, isn't she?
Is she?
- Natsu...
- What about me?
She was really worried
and came to me for advice.
She wanted me to push you to get started,
saying you have potential.
Really?
All done.
You were close, but just a bit off.
Guess I'm no good at this.
Let's try thinking about this again.
Come in.
All right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
How's it going?
Sorry, sir.
Hasn't Mom come back from shopping yet?
She's probably chatting
with the neighbors again.
I wonder if she took an umbrella?
There are nimbostratus clouds,
so I think it might rain.
I see...
All right. Please continue with your lesson.
Okay.
You seem to know a lot about weather, huh?
Why?
Well, the term "nimbostratus clouds"
doesn't exactly roll off the tongue.
But you just said it too.
I'm taking meteorology classes.
Oh? Classes?
Do you want to become
a weather forecaster or something?
I haven't thought that far ahead,
but I'm interested.
- I'll be going out for a bit.
- Okay.
Sounds like he's taking an umbrella
and going to pick her up.
Your mom?
That's so sweet of him.
He's a classic Showa era dad,
though he'd never say that out loud.
I see.
This one's tough.
It's cool after it rains, Rock.
You seem to know a lot about weather, huh?
He might be sharper than he looks.
What's up?
You're so cute, Rock.
[You have a new message from Souta]
Did we exchange contacts?
Hold on.
Feel free to let me know
if you have any questions.
Okay. I probably won't, though.
I did.
Good morning.
Today, let's go on a field trip.
A field trip?
Hello.
It's nice being outside.
Why do you seem so fresh
when it's scorching hot out?
Thanks.
I wasn't complimenting you.
I don't believe in genuinely pleasant people.
Why not?
I just think it's an act.
An act, huh?
You're not denying it.
- Hey, Natsuki!
- Hey, Riku.
Did you get dumped again, Natsuki?
What? No, I didn't.
- You're not crying, right?
- I'm actually quite popular, you know.
Oh! It's that teacher from the other day!
Well, I'm not actually a teacher.
- Hello.
- Teacher, what does it mean to be popular?
Hey. You can ask me that, you know.
But this teacher explains things clearly.
- Huh?
- Well...
It means someone whom lots of people like.
- Then Natsuki isn't popular.
- Why not?
Because you got dumped.
"Getting dumped" means,
being told by someone you like
that they don't like you, right?
You remembered that very well.
Good job.
You did well.
More, more.
You're great.
Riku isn't fazed by it at all.
Am I weird for being startled by it?
You like clouds, don't you?
- What?
- Even your strap looks like a cloud.
Not really.
What? Really?
This is a Samoyed.
I see.
I thought it was a cloud with a face.
It's a Samoyed, but I guess it does
kind of look similar to a cloud.
Yeah.
Look, doesn't that cloud over there
look just like a Samoyed?
What? Which cloud?
That one.
Ah... now that you mention it,
it does kind of look like a Samoyed.
Right?
Do you know what they call that?
What do you mean, "that"?
When clouds look like people or animals.
There's a name for that?
Yeah.
It's called pareidolia.
Pai... Pai?
Pareidolia.
Like seeing a rabbit in the moon.
Or seeing a human face in rocks.
That's the same phenomenon.
Even though we know it's something different,
it's a psychological phenomenon
where we see it as something familiar.
Pa... Pa... Pareidolia?
Pareidolia, huh?
That's it.
What?
- Let's call it a day for math.
- What?
Let's switch this to
a meteorology class from here.
Huh?
- Here's your fried chicken.
- Hey, hey.
I heard that Souta is smart,
kind, and just the best guy.
Huh? But isn't he really insensitive?
Yeah, yeah. He's good at teaching math,
but he's kind of an unpleasant guy.
Huh? That's totally different
from what Riyo said.
Here you go, your fried rice.
- Here you go, your fried rice.
- Thank you.
People can seem completely different
depending on your perspective.
Can I write that down, sir?
Sure! Everyone, write that down! Copy it!
- Engrave it...
- Engrave it in your heart.
I'll do that!
What kind of guy is Riyo's boyfriend?
What about this one?
- Cumulonimbus clouds.
- Correct!
These clouds grow quickly
and cause sudden thunderstorms.
They're quite the opposite
of nimbostratus clouds.
Correct.
Give me something more challenging.
Wow, you're motivated.
What about this one?
Well... what's that one again?
Well...
Can I have a hint?
It starts with an 'a'.
A... A...
- Anvil cloud!
- Correct!
- That's impressive.
- Next one.
How do you count clouds?
- One cloud, two clouds?
- No.
It differs depending on the type of cloud.
- Really?
- Yeah.
For example... one spot of cloud.
One streak of cloud.
One piece of cloud.
Wow, I didn't know that.
The more you learn about clouds,
the deeper it gets.
That sparkling must be due to the light.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Thank you.
[Great job]
You did well today too.
Huh? But I didn't really do anything today.
You studied.
What?
Learning new things and things
you didn't know before, counts as studying.
But it's not math.
That's okay.
If you can find the joy in studying,
it leads to the next step.
When I was trying to do that,
I thought I'd start with something you like.
Is that why you're taking
that extracurricular class?
[Introduction to Meteorology]
I'm glad you like clouds.
It would've been rough if I got it wrong.
Is there a reason why you like clouds?
Are you listening?
Wh... What was that again?
I asked you, why do you like clouds?
I'm not feeling nervous or anything.
Well...
Definitely not.
This is the place where
I first started liking clouds.
I see.
When I was a kid, I used to come here with
my sister and dad to watch planes take off.
I wonder if your plane is here yet, Dad.
It's not my plane,
it's the plane I worked on.
So doesn't that make it your plane, Dad?
- Oh, there it is!
- You're right!
I wonder where it's going.
At this time of day,
it must be the flight to Fukuoka.
It goes to the other side
of the sea, very far away.
Cool!
Those clouds are interesting!
- Those are contrails, right?
- Yeah.
Today they're lingering without disappearing.
Which means it might rain later.
Why?
Because it's proof that
the humidity in the sky is high.
- Wow, so the clouds are telling us that?
- Exactly.
It's a message from the sky.
- Amazing!
- Cool!
Yeah, it's really cool!
That's when I thought that
clouds are really something.
That's a good story.
It's nothing special.
You have a great dad, and a great family too.
What about you? Something happened, right?
Something that makes studying fun,
or something you like.
Is it okay if I talk about myself?
Yeah, of course.
Then would you mind
spending a little time with me?
Sure.
[Ryuunken Sanada]
All right, please take care of this.
Looks tasty.
- Sorry, my dad can be demanding.
- It's fine, it's on my way home anyway.
Oh, Natsuki.
Oh, is that the rumored tutor?
Is that Riyo's boyfriend?
Natsuki doesn't seem to mind him.
- True, it seems like they're having fun.
- Yeah.
Another lie...
Here we are.
Huh? Here?
Yeah, the bridge.
What about the bridge?
It's something I like.
- This bridge?
- No, not just this bridge.
From small bridges to big bridges...
all bridges, actually.
Why do you like bridges?
Bridges span rivers, seas, valleys, roads,
connecting places that are otherwise divided.
Okay, stay right there!
Huh? Okay.
What?
Nat!
If this bridge didn't exist,
we might still be able to see each other,
but we wouldn't be able to get closer, right?
But...
Huh? What?
Thanks to this bridge, we can meet like this.
Bridges connect people.
Maybe hundreds of years from now,
all of Japan... no,
maybe even the whole world
might be connected by bridges.
It sounds like a dream,
but wouldn't that be amazing?
I wonder where that bridge is.
- Huh?
- Do you know what that bridge is?
Yeah, it's the Sokolullu Mehmet Pasha Bridge.
Sokolullu Mehmet Pasha.
A World Heritage Site of the Ottoman Empire.
Wow, I didn't know that. Thanks.
- Well... I...
- Oh. My surname is Kobayakawa.
I'm in the same class as you.
- Huh? The same class?
- Yeah.
Sorry, I'm not that good
at remembering faces.
No problem.
You like bridges?
Yeah, I really love them.
- Okay, do you want to have lunch together?
- Huh?
I'm a World Heritage enthusiast.
We may have some interesting conversations.
Yeah, I agree.
I want to go to
Sokolullu Mehmet Pasha Bridge with Souta.
Once I start talking about bridges,
I can't see anything else and just go crazy.
I'm sorry.
No, I think it's really great.
What?
I didn't really think much
about bridges before,
but now I'm pretty interested.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Having something you love so much,
and being able to talk passionately
about it is really great.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
That simply makes me very happy.
Something was starting to stir within me.
So you want to build bridges?
Is that why you're studying at university?
Yeah, that's my dream.
That's awesome.
I'm happy!
Only you and Riyo ever say things
like that to me.
But this person is my sister's boyfriend.
For a moment, I almost forgot.