[Episode 31]
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed is turned off.
Sorry, the subscriber...
Look what you did!
- Mr. Tao.
- At the dock,
if Mr. Liu checks the goods
and they're wrong, who takes the blame?
- Sorry.
- Don't just stand there! Pick them up.
Enough, Mr. Tao.
Everyone is watching.
Once it's on the ship,
then it's your responsibility.
Until then, you don't get to bark orders here.
Got it.
Just get the goods to Mr. Liu's dock safely,
and make sure the cops don't catch you.
Load the cargo.
Thanks, Yi.
Hurry up. Once this last batch is loaded,
we leave.
Before we board the ship,
isn't Mr. Tao in charge of the convoy?
Today's different.
With you driving alone, I'll feel safe.
Phone.
- You don't trust me.
- I have rules. You know how it is.
Of course.
Once this run is done,
I want to find a place with some sunlight
and get some real rest.
Once you're making more and more money,
you won't even want a single day off.
Let's go.
Yi.
Do you remember when we first met?
In 2003. In District Seven.
If you hadn't put me in that pool match,
I couldn't have supported my family.
No.
The first time we met was under that bridge.
If you hadn't helped me back then,
there might not be the me you see today.
You saved my life.
I gave you a job in return.
Wouldn't you call that fate?
Absolutely.
- I owe you a thank-you, Mr. Zhang.
- No need to thank me.
I started out on the street, too.
I had a roast goose stall back then.
I worked until four or five every morning
for an extra 40 or 50 yuan.
Now.
This car you're driving
is worth over a million.
No one in Teng City can afford it.
But don't worry.
You'll drive something even better.
In life, it all comes down to one word: gamble.
Cheers.
When will this hellish life end?
These days, seeing geese makes me sick.
Feel good?
A few days ago,
my mom took me to see a fortune teller.
He read my bone structure
and said that in the next few years,
I'd be rich and powerful
and reach the peak of my life.
What kind of fortune teller?
A blind man.
You believe a blind man?
Fine. I believe him.
I'm betting the blind man wins.
Later, my bet paid off.
It wasn't the blind man I trusted.
It was Zhai Feng Mao's prized brotherhood.
He listened to me and trusted me in everything.
We started committing tax fraud.
The stakes kept getting higher,
and the money kept pouring in.
Then, later,
the whole thing came crashing down.
With just a few words, I got Zhai Feng Mao
to take the fall. He did it willingly.
As for me, I stayed completely clean.
Over the years,
I became a Teng City entrepreneur
and a great philanthropist.
That's why I dare to gamble.
Everything I have came from gambling.
This time, we have to win this bet.
Yi, remember this.
As long as you can win,
you can give up everything.
Come on. This way.
What's going on?
- Over here.
- Keep driving forward.
[Drunk Driving Checkpoint]
Hello, sir. Please cooperate.
Blow into this.
What's going on?
Why another drunk-driving checkpoint?
I don't know.
They never check this road.
Yet now...
- This is so annoying.
- We're running out of time.
Come on, pull forward.
- Hello?
- Mr. Zhang.
Looks like there's a checkpoint up ahead.
A checkpoint?
Traffic police or regular police?
Looks like a drunk-driving checkpoint.
We're about to pass through.
Tell everyone to stay calm.
If they panic, they'll give themselves away.
Okay, got it.
Okay. No problem.
Drive safely at night.
Okay. Drive safely at night.
Routine inspection. Let me check your vehicle.
Mr. Zhang, something's wrong.
I saw Zhou Kang An.
Switch to the backup plan.
Stop him! Get out!
Get out. Get out of the car.
Out. Get out of the car.
Hurry up.
Turn right. Take the side road.
Get out of the car.
That sly old fox.
Teams One and Two,
retrace his route and find him.
Teams Three and Four, secure the scene
and contact the Coast Guard detachment.
We can't pinpoint the suspect's location.
- Hands on your head. Down.
- But he may well
try to escape by sea.
Once he's spotted, intercept him immediately.
Yes.
Don't move.
Don't make it about belief.
It's just for peace of mind.
I didn't say I'd throw it away.
We don't need divine protection.
From now on, we'll be safe and sound.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Hello, Uncle Zhou.
- Jing.
- I saw Zhang Bin's car.
- What?
- It turned right at the highway entrance
and took a side road.
The plate number is Teng SQ7583.
Did you follow them here?
Chen Yi is in the car too.
This is reckless.
Send out the suspect vehicle's details.
Teng SQ7583.
Keep an eye on that car!
You set me up.
What do you mean, Bin?
No way.
They caught up this fast?
Turn left onto the main road.
Turn left.
It's not a police car.
You siblings make a pretty good team.
Come on, then.
Speed up.
Chen Yi.
[Luomei Pier, Fishing Harbor Pier]
Hello, Uncle Zhou.
Jing, don't do anything rash.
Where are you?
I'm at the junction of Luomei Pier
and Fishing Harbor Pier.
I lost them.
But judging by their route,
they're probably headed to Fishing Harbor Pier.
They're going out to sea.
Near Fishing Harbor Pier,
there's a cluster of abandoned warehouses.
If Zhang Bin is running,
going by sea is the safest option.
Jing, stay where you are.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
Captain Wu, Tech says
the roads near the fishing harbor
aren't covered by the traffic cameras
on the national highway.
Captain Zhou, there are no cameras
near the fishing harbor.
Take Team Three and search the fishing harbor.
Zhang, take Team One to Luomei.
Everyone, stay in contact
with the tech team at all times.
Be careful.
- Keep your comms open.
- Yes, sir.
- Understood.
- Kai, get in the car.
Let's go.
[Unknown Number]
Hello? Sorry. We're closed.
It's for you.
Hello?
You've got a chance to get back at Zhang Bin.
Do you want it?
Where is he?
Only you would know that.
You know him.
If he was going to run, where would he go?
Zhai, where are you going?
To see an old friend.
Go to bed early.
Don't wait up.
Come back soon.
Jing.
Hurry.
Search the area. Move.
Okay.
You're back late.
Where's Miao Jing?
Your girlfriend was worried about you.
She went to buy medicine.
Give me the ledger.
You want it?
I said give me the ledger.
Fine.
500,000 yuan.
I need to set up a life for my family and me.
A deal works for both of us.
Cash, then.
Wait for my call.
If you lay a finger on her,
you'll never get the other half
of that case file.
Young man.
We're pretty much the same now.
You know how to negotiate.
Before you said that,
I thought you were an undercover cop.
Hello.
Zhai Feng Mao came to see me.
You can move in now.
I applied to Teng City Normal University.
What gave you the right to change it?
There's 80,000 yuan inside.
It should be enough for you.
Didn't you say everything was fine?
Why are you sending me away now?
I'm just tired of all this.
We're not on the same path. You can't help me.
Chen Yi, are you out of your mind?
Do you hear what you're saying?
Of course, I know what I'm doing.
Miao Jing.
You'd better wake up soon, too.
Do you see it now?
Chen Yi.
Don't regret this.
Yi.
A couple of days won't make a difference.
Why rush to kick her out?
If she doesn't leave, I can't rest easy.
Chen Yi.
Yi.
I know this has been hard on you.
Listen.
I've thought it over.
This place isn't safe.
I'll take you somewhere new to start over.
Once we make it big,
we'll come home in style, okay?
- What are you trying to say?
- Where are you taking me?
Country Jin.
It's close.
Just a few hours away.
Bin.
I did everything you asked.
Right.
This whole thing is between the three of us.
It's too risky to leave him here.
I'll take him with me.
You're right.
I don't feel good
about you going to Country Jin alone.
I'll handle the case file.
Once things blow over,
I'll come get you myself.
Okay.
Take care.
Go on.
Chen Yi.
I just want to ask you one thing.
What exactly did Zhou Kang An promise you?
Money, power, status. I can give you all of it.
What are you really after?
Why team up with Zhou Kang An to betray me?
Because you and I were never on the same path.
You know nothing!
The best path is the one that pays.
So, for money,
you can make
the brother who built all this with you
from the ground up take the fall?
Since you know everything,
things finally add up.
You've been avoiding me
since you came back to Teng City.
So that's what it was all for.
I used to follow Zhai Feng Mao.
He was just a roast-goose-selling nobody.
We made it this far.
People used to call me Roast Goose Kid,
then Bin,
then Mr. Zhang.
And now,
the people
who know my past are pretty much dead.
You're the only one left.
Yi.
If you die here today, will you regret it?
You got He Wen Jie killed.
You destroyed countless families in Teng City.
You've been a villain half your life.
What do you have besides money?
Zhang Bin.
Do you regret it?
I told you before.
I won everything I have now by gambling.
What do I have to regret?
Since you're so eager to suffer,
look at me.
Look at me.
Come on.
Go down there and take your time.
What are you staring at?
Go wash your hands. Dinner's ready.
It's Mom.
Zhang Bin is a cunning old fox.
He must have left himself a way out.
He's still stalling here,
so he must be waiting for Liu Bin Bo's men.
We must find him soon.
We're racing the clock.
When people are about to die,
every last one of them gets scared.
I thought you were tougher, Chen Yi.
When you kill someone yourself,
there's no way your hands don't shake.
Not scared, are we?
Good.
We were brothers once.
This day next year,
I'll burn three bundles of joss paper for you.
Goodbye, Chen Yi.
Chen Yi.
- Chen Yi!
- Miao Jing!
Go.
Miao Jing.
Chen Yi.
Get up here.
Stop.
Lucky you.
This is really goodbye.
Did you miss me?
We still have a score to settle.
You!
Zhai.
Before they took me to Country Jin,
Zhai Feng Mao tied me up at the docks.
Honestly, I wasn't that scared.
I just kept thinking
I never got to say goodbye properly.
I never got to hold your hand the way I am now.
Chen Yi.
You're mine.
Zhai! Zhai!
Stop, please.
Zhai.
- Stop.
- Don't move.
- Drop the knife.
You can't kill me.
Jing.
Yi, are you okay?
Hurry. Call for backup.
Hurry. Call an ambulance.
I...
love...
you.
I love you, too.
[One day ago]
[We'll meet in the light,
where there's no darkness.]