Don't worry.
Making up is the easiest part.
Get off.
Don't touch me!
Ouch!
You're the one who let me into your room.
- Stop!
- Quit resisting already.
Stop, please!
Sui.
Get off of her.
You, again?
This is between me and Sui. Get out!
You get out.
Shut up!
Quit getting in my way!
Woah, hey, ouch!
Let me go! Stop!
You broke something!
I'm telling my mom!
Ow, ouch!
Get lost. If you don't, I'm calling the cops.
What? But Sui was my fiancée!
Why?
Open up!
I said, open the door!
O-Oops, I left my phone in there.
I need it for work! Please?
Are you hurt?
No.
You've saved me, again.
I'm sorry for roping you into my trouble.
You don't need to apologize.
No, I...
That man, he was...
Don't force yourself to speak.
Take it easy for the night.
If you're anxious, I can stay here with you.
Thank you.
I'll be fine.
Huh?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
If you're going to ignore me...
Let's just die together!
Takizawa?
Good morning.
Could I ask a work related question?
Morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Morning.
Have some tea.
What happened? Is everything okay?
Why did you turn him down?
Huh?
Himukai came to make amends, didn't he?
How do you know about that?
Because I convinced him to.
What?
Wh-What the...
I have the perfect plan.
Whether you go through with it or not is up to you.
I'll do anything to get Sui back.
Great. Then let's get married.
What?
I won't ask for love.
I just want the status as your wife.
And how would that help me?
Let me finish.
If we get married,
I'll turn a blind eye to all your affairs.
You can keep Sui as a mistress,
and stay with her forever.
I see your point now.
Not many wives are so allowing of mistresses.
It's not a bad deal for you at all.
Sui would prefer to stay with me, right?
Of course.
One more thing.
Here.
Huh?
[Check-up diagnosis]
No issues, whatsoever?
I promise to bear a healthy heir for you.
Just guarantee me the money
and position as your wife.
Is this how all three of us can be happy?
I didn't even think of this solution.
You're so smart, Takizawa!
Thank you!
Once I'm pregnant with an heir,
your parents will have to accept me.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm all in on your plan!
This is all for Sui's sake.
Everything is for Sui, right?
That's right.
Takizawa...
This is all for Sui.
We had sex with no love, just for you.
With this plan of mine,
the three of us can all get what we want.
To not agree to such ingenuity...
Sui, are you sure you're feeling all right?
Takizawa...
You're crazy.
I am doing this for your sake.
- But you're suggesting we...
- Sui. You are infertile.
Quit dreaming,
and become Himukai's mistress already.
It's the only way you'll find happiness.
Contact Himukai, now.
Excuse me.
We are not seeing clients
with no appointments today.
I've come here for Sui's sake.
Otherwise, she'll never be happy.
That has nothing to do with our business.
What?
Excuse me, we'll be needing
this meeting room soon.
Yes, I was just on my way out.
Sui.
Charming them with your pity act, again?
What?
I remember when your parents passed,
you played the "pathetic girl"
to get everyone on your side.
Monou would never do such a thing.
You'll come to understand soon enough.
Anyone who stands in my way will see hell.
I'll see you all again soon.
Are you both all right?
I'm fine.
I'll brew you a cup of hot tea.
Have I been blind this whole time?
What?
I had a fiancé.
The man you saw the other day.
Oh, him.
Our engagement was called off
because of my... circumstances.
But he wanted to do things over again.
What?
Of course, I turned him down.
I couldn't forgive him.
I must be so narrow-minded.
Dear, stop this.
Stop it!
You don't have to forgive him.
What?
If it hurts you to try and forgive,
then don't.
You don't have to ignore your resentment.
Even if you despise him...
Even if you feel you're weak...
Protecting your heart is your priority.
Thank you.
You've saved me once again.
I did exactly as you said,
and nothing worked out!
I'm calling off our marriage.
Don't panic, Himukai.
Everything will work out just fine.
Besides, a bright future awaits us.
Wh-What?
It's the heir you so desperately yearned for.
I've granted one of your wishes, haven't I?
No way...
I'm on my way to the gynecologist now.
So, don't worry about Sui, okay?
I've made sure she'll contact you.
And I can trust you on this one?
Of course. Just leave it all to me.
Hang on tight.
I will!
We're veering starboard.
Takizawa, the winds! They're strong!
I thought Himukai only had
his riches going for him.
His obsession for you has made him crazy.
He's a dumb, nasty scumbag.
What'd you ever see in him?
Huh?
Sorry. I forget you're weak to pushy guys.
Still, glad you broke it off with him.
Dinner's ready.
Thanks.
I'm partially to blame
for never seeing his faults either.
There you go again.
You're such an earnest gal, Sui.
You think so?
But enough about him.
Here's to someone better.
- Cheers.
With the new job under your belt,
I know you'll find someone new.
Someone new...
What, found one already?
No.
Even if I did,
I don't think I'd take the initiative.
I see.
How's Mao?
I was asking about his work ethic, but...
Right, of course.
Yeah, he's really dependable.
Looks like you have found someone.
Have not.
What?
So, there's nothing between you and Mao?
Of course not.
I think you're just his type, though.
He's six years my junior.
And my husband is four.
It works for you because you're mature.
Younger guys are great.
There's really no arguing, for one.
And if he pisses you off,
it's easy to shrug off.
When he's reliable,
you can't help but be impressed
since he's younger.
It's all great stuff.
Thanks for sharing.
Any time.
Mao, want some coffee?
Sure, thanks.
I hope Monou will be all right...
If anything crops up, I'll back her.
Are you currently dating Monou?
What?
I'm sorry, never mind.
It was an inappropriate question.
It's fine.
But why make that assumption?
I'll be honest with you.
I happened to see you two the other night.
I see. Didn't realize someone was watching.
I was just acting as a guardian of sorts.
A guardian?
She was self-destructing,
due to incidents at her previous workplace.
I only helped her up
because she was blackout drunk.
I see.
Sounds like something you'd do.
But for her to drink to her limits...
Things must have been rough.
It might take a while
for her to fully recover.
Nana, a coffee for me too, please.
Shall we get to work?
Aw, you always give Mao special treatment.
I mean, I get it.
Of course he's popular. He's so nice.
Mizuno is also kind.
She has a strong sense of justice.
Not to mention incredibly capable.
She's actually taking the exam
to become a certified architect.
She's a hard worker, that one.
Considerate, too.
She's a good girl, through and through.
- See you all tomorrow.
- See you.
Let's hold a welcome party
for Monou this Friday.
Great idea.
A party, for me?
Yeah. Should we go to Vente?
Great choice. Everything tastes great there.
We might not get a reservation though.
Fair point.
It is a popular spot.
Should we order take out instead?
Sounds good to me.
But where to eat it all?
How about my place?
We're neighbors, so it's convenient for us.
What? You're neighbors?
I'm staying in one of the company dorms.
Oh yeah, they did mention an open room.
Yes. I moved in there.
I see.
All right, I'm looking forward to it. See you.
- See you tomorrow.
- Good bye.
- Nana, you coming?
- Right.
- See you both tomorrow.
- Bye.
See you.
What's the matter?
I'm here about the child.
Oh! I have it handled.
I'll send you my diagnosis some other day.
Don't lie.
- What?
- There is no child.
I had Mom look into your medical records.
You didn't have a file
with this gynecologist.
That pregnancy test
must've been someone else's.
Why did you tell such an obvious lie?
You really can't tell?
It's because I love you, why else?
Enough stupid lies!
You said you only wanted money and status.
I'm calling off this deal, marriage and all.
Please, wait!
I promise to birth your child.
I'll handle Sui as well, so please!
Please don't call off our marriage!
How?
What?
I understand Sui better than anyone.
We were together for seven years, after all.
Sui won't agree to the schemes
of a dirty woman like you.
"Dirty"?
If Sui won't return to me,
then I'd much rather marry
someone Mom chooses, over you.
Unbelievable...
It's all her fault.
I won't let my plan be ruined so easily.
I felt like someone was following me home.
- Following you?
- It's my first time presenting an idea.
I think we can create a wonderful event.
It's like when we first met.
Except, now we're reversed.
Want to pick up where we left off that night?