Water
Zhang Wei
Aren't you scared at all?
Water
What's there to be scared of?
She won't last more than a couple days.
In a couple days,
you and I can finally be together forever.
Oh, you're terrible.
Xiaofang
Let's not have our next date at the shop, okay?
This place of yours...
It's pretty creepy.
What?
Just like your dad,
you look down on our line of work?
Of course not!
My sweetie,
just say the word,
and I'll come work here with you right away.
I'll be at your beck and call.
Forget it.
You're too high-maintenance for me.
How did I get so high-maintenance?
Oh, right.
Next week, why don't we
go register our marriage first? How about it?
Can you keep your word?
Has your dad agreed?
Of course my word counts.
Auntie Huilan,
what are you doing here?
This is my boyfriend, Zhou Fang.
This is Yiran's mom.
Hello, Auntie Huilan.
My name is...
Your name is Zhou Fang.
Didn't she just say it?
I need to cut in line.
I need to talk to Xiaofang about something.
Tonight, I need an answer, no matter what.
An answer to what?
Can't you take a hint?
Auntie Huilan means she wants you to get lost.
Now scram!
Fine.
Then go ahead and cut in line.
Get your answer first.
Xiaofang
I came to see you today
because I wanted you to tell me
about what Yiran's been through all these years
Where do I even start?
Well, anyway...
Right after you went in
Yiran and I were both bullied constantly
Everyone called her
a little murderer
One makes a living off the dead,
the other's a murderer
You two are really
a match made in heaven
Look at the state of her!
Later on
she went off to college in Shanghai
For years she refused to come back to Lecang
I keep thinking
maybe it's this place
that hurt her so deeply
During those years
she worked several jobs to support herself
Mom, this is Shanghai
Five thousand a month is nowhere near enough
Li Yiran, working her way through school
Hello
Here are your coffees
Yiran
We're heading to a bar in a bit
You coming?
I'll pass
Enjoy your drinks
Working stiff
Why bother asking her?
Country bumpkin
Get out of the way
Forget it
Let's not invite her next time
Such a buzzkill
Auntie Huilan
All the years you were gone
she's really had it rough
It's my fault
I wasn't a good mother
I didn't protect her
Auntie Huilan, don't say that
So it's normal she ignores me now
All that was so long ago
What happened next?
Well, later on
she graduated, right?
And she was about to settle in Shanghai
But recently that jerk cheated on her
What happened?
She's got no figure
and no money
The moment I got back, I dumped her
I hadn't wanted to see her for ages
And then after that
she just quit her job
If you ask me
That scumbag cheated with her boss
so why on earth should she quit?
She just can't stand any wrongdoing
Do you have that scumbag's phone number?
His address?
Tell me. This mama's going to Shanghai to fix him
Auntie Huilan, don't worry
Yiran sorted them out right on the spot
It was so satisfying
Really?
Really
Well done
Just like her mama
Otherwise this mama would've been furious
You can rest completely easy, Auntie Huilan
Yiran's just stubborn with her words
Deep down she cares about you a lot
Really?
Really
She really cares about me?
She absolutely cares about you
Then if...
Auntie Huilan
Did you get your answer?
How about
you let me cut in line first
I want an answer too
Your name's Zhou Fang
You'll never get your answer in this lifetime
You'll never hold on to Xiaofang
Auntie Huilan, why are you cursing me?
Xiaofang
Then let's go get our marriage license next week
Yiran
What made you come wash your hair here today?
Our water's cut off at home
Had hot pot yesterday, my hair reeks of it
It's driving me crazy
Mom
Yaya got loose, I can't catch her
Yaya got loose
That darn bird
Yiran, wait a sec, I'll be right back
Honestly
Where is it now?
Auntie Juan
Yangyang
I totally forgot about this
Auntie Juan
I'm back, Auntie Juan
Did you catch Yaya?
What are you doing here?
So many bubbles.
Sleep well, sleep well.
Just close your eyes.
How's the pressure?
Fine, just hurry up and wash it.
Just rinse it off for me.
Okay, okay, okay.
Peanuts and beer, coming right up!
Here.
Here's your glass.
This one I'm grilling here,
it's called Hearts Connected.
There's no hurdle we can't get over.
We're always a family with hearts connected.
Exactly.
Yiran, Lan, eat while it's hot.
Daren's treating today.
I run a small business, you know.
I really can't afford to treat.
My treat, my treat, my treat.
I'm not eating.
Yiran, Yiran, Yiran.
My treat, my treat.
Everything on the table tonight,
it's my treat.
Don't be shy.
Sit, sit, sit.
Okay, I'll go grill some more.
Weren't you not eating?
So why'd you sit back down?
Uncle Daren's the one treating.
Am I eating your food?
Is it any of your business?
You're the egg I hatched.
If I didn't look out for you,
you'd have been smashed to bits long ago.
Um...
Auntie Huilan meant well, after all.
At least she got us some payback, right?
Yiran, cut her some slack too.
Cut her slack for what?
Does cutting her slack even help?
She still won't listen either way.
Troublemaker.
I was wrong, okay?
I admit I was wrong, isn't that enough?
They'll be my witnesses today.
I'll never cause trouble again.
I mean it.
Yeah right, like I'd believe you.
Zhang Lijuan.
Scam call.
Go on, go on.
Talk is cheap, you know.
So what do you want, then?
Let's put it in writing.
So you came prepared, huh.
Then I'll have to think it over carefully.
Are you signing or not?
Forget it if you won't.
I knew you never meant to change.
I'll sign, I'll sign.
I don't have a pen.
Look, here's a pen for you.
Here's your pen.
This mama's stuck being Party B.
There, you satisfied now?
No, I'm not.
What else could you possibly want?
This mama, all her life,
has never written a single guarantee.
Do you even have a job right now?
Being jobless isn't the problem, Huilan.
The problem is you never keep one.
I know. I'll find a job.
Don't you worry.
I won't make you support me in old age.
I can earn my own money.
You'd better.
Let's make a toast
Come on
Come on, come on
Here we go
Have a drink, have a drink
Come on, Yiran
Normally
I'd be drinking till I drop tonight
But
since I promised Li Yiran
that I'd cut back on drinking
I'll only have one glass
Just one, just one
Alright
Just one glass then
Won't you have a drink?
This one's for you.
Are you crazy, Wu Huilan?
Your wounds aren't even healed and you're drinking?
What do you know?
This is called drowning my sorrows.
Fighting poison with poison.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
And to celebrate Yiran coming back, right?
Come on, come on.
Cheers, cheers!
Zhang Lijuan.
You have no idea.
I was so badass that day.
What happened?
That scumbag
came to Paradise Funeral Home to hassle Yiran.
This mama grabbed a brick and charged right at him.
And then?
Then she ran over and blocked me.
But I found my second chance.
This mama grabbed the brick and smacked again.
And then?
And I smacked it right on my own head.
But only a little blood came out.
Not that much blood.
The key thing is,
I turned that brick around
and put it in that scumbag's hand.
So when we got to the police station,
the cops couldn't do a thing to me.
Because that brick
was covered in his fingerprints.
So tell me, isn't this head of mine clever?
So clever!
Sis Lan.
To your cleverness,
let's have one.
Have one.
A couple of drinks and she's bragging again.
I can't take it anymore
Why did you drink it all?
I promised you
Just one glass
I keep my word
Come on, let's hit the restroom
Come on
Wu Huilan
No more overthinking
When your heart is big
your problems become small
It's really no big deal
Right, Lao Li?
Don't you worry
I'll never do anything foolish
I still want to be there for our Yiran
I'll listen to her
Find myself a good job
Not be a burden to her
I've got to stay strong
Stay strong
Here.
Yiran.
There's actually something I've wanted to ask you.
Go ahead and ask.
How could you tell those two were having an affair?
You don't even know them.
I...
I've always been a
materialist who doesn't believe in ghosts or gods.
I figured in this world,
there's no such thing as all that mystical stuff.
But the day of the old man's funeral,
the moment I touched his belongings,
I got Sensory Resonance.
I could see and hear
things that happened while he was alive.
Just like a dream.
Yiran
This is your dad's phone
The police finished their exam and sent it over
Ever since I hit my head that night
I've been having nightmares all the time
Maybe it's from too much grief
causing hallucinations and after-effects
Hey, hey
I'm talking to you
Zoning out again, are you?
Didn't you say it yourself?
I'm the Reincarnation of Sun Wukong
I've got the Eyes of truth
And you actually believed me?
If you ask me, that was just Blind luck
Pure Dumb luck
If This mama had any dumb luck
I'd be in Shanghai right now
making a name for myself
Yiran
There's something I'm not sure
whether I should say or not
If you shouldn't, then don't
Life, you know
just forget about the past
What truly matters
is only the present
We don't offer a base salary here
And no social security either
It's commission per item
You sell one, you earn on that one
Can you accept that?
Yes, I can accept that
I can accept it
So when can I start work?
This is my ID card
Born in '78
Year of the Horse
I'm Year of the Rat
Our birth signs clash
Off you go, now
Go on, hurry
Don't hold up my business, all right?
We sometimes do unpaid overtime here
Is that okay?
Unpaid, mind you
Sure, overtime's no problem
But isn't Yiwu a bit far for overtime?
Is there travel pay? Overtime pay?
I said unpaid overtime
Not that you fly to Yiwu
This one's not right in the head
Off you go, go on, go
Go, go, go, I don't dare hire you
You've killed someone
It was excessive self-defense
Excessive self-defense is still killing
Go, go, go
I don't dare hire you
Don't come any closer!
You... you're thirty-three?
Yeah, I'm thirty-three.
I'm from the countryside, so I look older.
Alright, everyone, listen up.
We've got way too many people
here today.
Anyone over thirty-five,
you can head home now.
Also, for the women here,
if you're married with kids,
you can step out and go home too.
Come on, keep up back there.
Don't break the line.
Pick up the pace, come on.
We're keeping things strict over here.
Just like I said before.
We're not short on people today.
We're mainly filtering, okay?
Right, we want quality.
How'd it go?
I'm exhausted.
I knew it.
This mama definitely didn't check the almanac today.
Inauspicious day for everything.
You blame the heavens, the earth, the almanac.
Didn't I teach you some interview lines?
How could it not work?
What are you so anxious about?
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you itching to get back to Shanghai?
Then go on back.
I don't need you keeping me company.
This mama will stay and take her time job-hunting.
Fine, I'll go! I'm heading back to Shanghai tomorrow.
I get along just fine on my own in Shanghai.
This mama gets along just fine too.
Who wants to be around you anyway?
Heavenly spirits turn,
earthly demons hide.
Fortune and misfortune,
set by yin and yang.
The compass points,
the aura rises.
Evil spirits and bad luck
have nowhere to hide.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Hired a master to clear your mom's bad luck.
Right, so don't cause any trouble.
The master is reading our feng shui.
Master, how's the feng shui in our home?
The stove faces west.
Fire overcomes metal.
A sign of financial loss.
Wu Huilan,
you're someone who has to sneak
onto the bus with someone's senior card,
and you believe this con man's garbage?
Watch your mouth.
That master is really accurate, you know.
One yin, two yang,
Three Pure Ones, Four Emperors,
disasters and calamities,
all shaped by human effort.
By divine command!
Master, why are you sighing like that?
What's wrong?
Patron Wu,
this hexagram signals an Industry Jinx.
Disaster is coming.
When it does,
your home will be in chaos, all lost.
So what do we do?
Pay up.
The master will cast a spell.
Thank you, Master.
Patron Wu,
this curse is hard to break.
Spend money to avert disaster.
Give it all.
Give it all!
I've got some more here.
This is all of it, Master.
Nothing left.
Sincerity is arriving.
Look, look, he's casting the spell!
One yin, two yang, Three Pure Ones, Four Emperors,
disasters and calamities,
all shaped by human effort.
Wind, fire, thunder, lightning,
break!
What's he doing?
Casting the spell, casting the spell!
Wind, fire, thunder, lightning,
break!
Look, look, he's casting the spell!
The candle lit up!
That's amazing!
Patron Wu,
in the southeast corner of the room,
I've lit a candle
and set up a formation.
When the candle dies on its own,
the disaster breaks by itself.
So "the candle dies on its own" means
we wait for it to go out by itself, right?
Heaven's secrets cannot be revealed.
Farewell.
Can't, can't let it go out.
Thank you, Master.
Here, Master, let me see you out.
Master, thank you for your hard work.
Master, here, let me get the door for you.
You know what?
Now that the spell's been cast,
I'll find a job in no time.
Keep laughing at me, then.
Master.
Coming, coming, let me see you out.
Lighting a candle in the southeast corner?
Watched too much Ghost Blows Out the Light?
It can't break on its own?
Then I'll break it myself.
Plus 36 equals
Plus
Eight equals 207
Yiran
Do me a favor, would you?
If there are any job openings,
keep an eye out for me.
Have you thought this through?
You want to stay?
Not me, it's Wu Huilan.
She's going crazy looking for a job.
She went to some fortune-teller, you know?
Once she finds a stable job,
I can go back to Shanghai.
If I keep hanging around here,
my social security will lapse.
Go back to Shanghai? What for?
Just stay and work with me.
Let me tell you,
with the silver economy now,
funeral services is a sunrise industry.
Sisters united
are unstoppable.
Let's grow Paradise Funeral Home together!
I'm not joking with you.
I'm definitely going back to Shanghai.
Anyway, you've got so many connections.
If there's a job, look out for her, okay?
What a heavy rain!
A job? Here one comes.
This Chen Xiaofang is so unreliable.
What is there to do at a zoo?
I think working here is pretty nice, actually.
The air is fresh,
and you get to be with the little animals.
Plus there are so many cypress leaves.
Grab a few to roast sausages, so tasty!
Not bad.
Run!
Big bear! Big bear!
Li Yiran
Do you really not remember me,
or are you just pretending?
Of course I remember you,
Miss Fan.