Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Your father may be gone,
but his debt isn’t.
You gotta pay for it.
I think Kaye is Mr. Kill.
The murderer is trying to communicate
by leaving clues in the crime scenes
in a way that no one else would notice.
I think the next victim is going to be
a rule-bending defense attorney.
According to the first two cases…
His theory might be right.
You must stay where I can see you 24/7.
At least until we find that lawyer.
You haven’t eaten anything
since this morning.
Eat.
What?
Can you only stomach instant noodles?
2 a.m. is hardly a good time for dinner.
As a cop,
I never know what’s going to happen next.
Maybe I have to chase after
a criminal in five minutes.
If I don’t eat now when I can,
how will I be able to catch bad guys?
I’m not a manga artist like you.
You can get up whenever you want,
go to bed whenever you want.
Like… Why are you throwing shade?
What was that for?
My coffee’s spilled now, don’t you see?
Sorry.
I forgot I’m cuffed.
I’m not used to this yet.
Please.
Are you messing with me?
Of course not.
I just don’t want you spilling
your coffee again.
Please have a sip.
It’s not him.
And what about this guy?
No, sir.
-Him?
-No, sir.
Yes.
Sir.
It’s not him either.
Alright. Let’s keep looking.
(Inspector.)
(The missing lawyers are,
one by one, making contact.)
(Except for Attorney Komkrit.)
Okay.
I’ll check up on him.
Inspector.
I…
I need to pee.
What? What was that?
I said I need to pee.
Ugh… Bad timing.
Thank you.
Hold on.
What?
Inspector.
I’m literally just going to the toilet.
Do you need to have me cuffed?
Just come on.
Hurry up. I don’t have all day.
Hey.
Hey!
If you’re in such a rush,
why not just uncuff me?
Hey.
You seriously expect me
to just pee like this?
Well, then, let’s go.
Wait.
Are you out of your mind?
Who the hell would be able to pee
with his hand cuffed
to someone else like this?
So you’re not gonna pee?
Then let’s just go.
Wait, wait.
I’ll pee.
Inspector.
What if I have to go number two?
What do we do?
We’ll think about that when that happens.
Just do your business.
If you’re just messing with me,
I won’t let you off the hook.
Listen.
If I really wanted to do that,
I wouldn’t waste my time
coming along with you.
But honestly, I wouldn’t mind
waiting in the car.
If we have another body
because you’re stalling for time,
It’ll be on you.
What?
What do you want me to do?
Climb inside?
Wait, hold up.
Just now, don’t you think
that was too convenient for you
to just blame me?
You think I’m okay my manga is used
as death sentences for these victims?
You should know that way better than me.
The door’s unlocked.
Don’t touch anything.
I know that.
The lights and the AC are left on.
Who would leave them running
during the day?
Well, that’s not always true.
Rich people…
They wouldn't be above paying
for their comfort, you know?
It’s not like they’re bothered
paying extra on their electricity bill.
Maybe he was taken while having dinner.
His secretary hasn’t been able
to reach him since Friday, that means…
He’s been missing three days.
Yeah?
A single lawyer
living alone in a big house.
If he had been missing for three days,
no one would suspect anything.
Wait…
Hold on.
What if the murderer didn’t just mean to
set up the bodies like in my manga?
We forgot something important.
The locations might not be
the exact locations in the manga.
But they look the same.
For example…
The first murder happens
in an abandoned warehouse.
In Nekros, the crime scene
is also an abandoned warehouse.
The second murder,
in Nekros,
happens in an empty field.
(Chapter 14 of Nekros
is about a famous lawyer.)
I get it now.
Where does the murder
take place in Chapter 14?
Warehouse…
In Chapter 14 of Nekros,
the crime scene is…
A warehouse by the pier.
Nop.
Send me all locations of warehouses
by the pier near Komkrit’s house.
I’ll check the first one.
Get some local police offices
to check out the other two.
Hang on tight.
Stay behind me.
Yes.
Hey.
You alright?
He’s likely been dead
for no less than a couple hours.
His blood hasn’t fully coagulated,
but rigor mortis has begun to set in.
The murderer likely hasn’t left
the crime scene that long ago.
What about him?
Kaye?
Is he still a suspect?
No.
He didn’t do it.
He was with me the entire time.
Drink some water.
What are you thinking?
I just…
I just want to go home and clean up.
We’re almost done here.
I’ll give you a ride home.
I’m sorry.
Sorry? For what?
For what I said at Komkrit’s house.
But you…
You might be right.
I drew those panels.
I even came up with the methods.
Abandoned warehouse.
Empty field.
Because I…
I… drew—
Hey. Take it easy.
Where’s your pill?
Swallow.
Take it easy.
Take a deep breath.
Focus, Kaye.
Focus.
Listen to me.
You didn’t kill anyone.
It’s the murderer who imitates your work.
You didn’t do it.
And everything that happens
isn’t your fault.
But if your guilt makes you want
to take responsibility for it…
Work with me.
Work–work with you?
You mean…
From now on,
you’re no longer a suspect.
You’re going to be a special consultant
to my Nekros Investigation Team.
Right now,
you’re the only person who knows
what’s going on in the murderer’s head.
If you want your guilt to fade away,
work with me.
Let’s catch this guy.
You should go on and take a rest.
I’ll call you if anything comes up.
Oh, you’re here.
Hello, Aunt Sri.
I’m sorry I’m late.
Something came up.
I’ll wire you your salary
first thing tomorrow morning.
I’m sorry I can’t pay you on time
this month.
It’s alright. I understand.
I’m going home,
but you know you can ring me up anytime.
Thank you.
Dad.
I’m sorry I’ve been away for so many days.
I was kind of busy.
How are you doing, Dad?
Do you sleep well?
Let’s get you cleaned up, shall we?
PAID
K-CUPID = MR. KILL
(NEKROS CREATOR)
My God.
Hey.
How many times did I tell you
not to barge in?
Wait, is this true?
K-Cupid is Mr. Kill?
What is he like in real life?
(Editor, I’ll send you the manuscript
of the new chapter tonight.)
You told me Kaye draws
the saddest look in his characters’ eyes.
His own eyes… are
about a hundred times sadder.
Come on and go away already.
Wait.
I have one more question.
Does he have anything to do
with the murderer?
K-Cupid’s Love in the Wind?
I like this manga, too.
You do?
I love this manga.
If I were to tell you
that K-Cupid is the same artist
who writes Nekros,
would you believe me?
Huh?
Are you saying Kaye is Mr. Kill, Praew?
Boss.
Hmm?
Yeah?
We’ve just been informed
Nekros killed a third victim.
The victim is…
Attorney Komkrit Nopparakkul.
What?
Attorney Komkrit?
Yes.
Guys.
That’s our scoop now.
Stop whatever you’re doing.
Let’s make a graphic for this news.
Attorney Komkrit…
Isn’t he the lawyer
who only took on high-profile cases?
Girls.
If you have any ideas,
feel free to let me know.
Of course.
In Nekros, the murderer chooses
to kill only bad guys.
Like in the previous two cases.
That means this lawyer
could be dirty, too.
Oh.
Attorney Komkrit.
The lawyer defending the rich kid charged
with manslaughter while drunk driving.
Komkrit. Komkrit…
They really are untouchable, huh.
That’s why a monster like Nekros exists.
A monster who will rebalance
the tipped scale.
Oh, that was nice.
Write it down! I bet Thun’s gonna love it.
-You think?
-Yes.
We have a tag line!
There’s been a third victim
of the serial murder case, Nekros.
The latest victim is none other than
the famous lawyer, Mr. Komkrit,
the man who’s been lauded
as ‘the wizard of the legal world.’
(Netizens are digging up dirt
on all three victims.)
(The underground manga turned murderer
Nekros is being praised for its vigilante.)
(In a world where justice is too costly
for normal people to afford,)
(many people have been waiting
for someone, or some monster,)
(to tip the balance back
on the scale of justice.)
(One thing is certain:)
(As long as the police fail
to catch this murderer,)
(many people will have to sleep
with one eye open.)
(In a world where justice is too costly
for normal people to afford…)
You’re finally here, tiger.
Hello, Uncle.
Here.
Have coffee with me.
Thank you.
(As long as the police fail
to catch this murderer,)
(many people will have to sleep—)
So it’s confirmed
to be a serial murder case.
Forensics just came back with the report.
So, yes.
This is a big case.
The press is shining a spotlight on it.
And there will be a lot of pressure
from the public, too.
You sure you got this?
You know what people think of me, Uncle.
I’m just…
The son of a dirty cop.
I want to prove
that I’m not like my father.
I promise, Uncle,
I’ll see this case through.
If there’s anything you need my help with,
just let me know.
I’m always on your side.
Yes, sir.
I’ve looked through it three times, sir,
and I don’t see any clues.
Maybe he didn’t leave any this time?
A serial killer like him is
always obsessed with patterns.
There’s no way he didn’t leave his M.O.
Sir.
The lab report on the pen stuck on
the victim’s chest just came back.
His relative insists the pen
didn’t belong to Komkrit.
But there are also no fingerprints.
I’m sorry I’m late.
We’re waiting for you. Come on in.
Do you know what this message means?
"ENEMIES FOR STRENGTH, FRIENDS FOR HEART"
I think it is said by one of the victims
in Nekros.
But I don’t remember which one.
Nop.
Dig up the Nekros files we recovered
and show them to Kaye.
Yes, sir.
I found it.
The victim in Chapter 18 of Nekros
is a dirty politician.
He’s a two-faced man.
“Enemies give us strength.”
“Real friends give us courage.”
It’s something
the victim of this chapter says a lot.
And…
That’s not everything.
The files are broken.
This is all we could recover.
Do you remember
how the rest of Chapter 18 goes?
I might need to reread
the beginning again.
Maybe it’ll jog my memory.
At least we might be able to find out
who the next victim is going to be.
Read through their profiles
and you just know they’re rotten.
Of course, our country is going nowhere
if these scums are sitting in our parliament.
Sir.
I’ve checked.
No politicians have been reported missing
these past few days.
This could mean two things:
First,
the killer hasn’t started.
Second, we’re on the wrong path.
Whoa, Inspector.
This guy tops the list.
Look.
He was recently involved with
the Chinese syndicate.
But the moment his charges were dropped,
he immediately builds his image back up
by turning to religion.
(As long as we believe in
doing the right thing,)
(our good deeds will protect us.)
Who is he?
That’s MP Jaratphong.
If I was Nekros, he would be
the top name on my list.
(Politicians have allies and enemies.)
(But I believe that…)
(My enemies give me strength.)
(And real friends give me courage.)
From his criminal record,
he was involved in drug cases,
bid rigging of state enterprises,
and money laundering.
There are nearly 10 cases in total.
You’re right.
There are also rumors that he’s involved
in scamming and human trafficking.
All charges against him were dropped.
All of them?
Yes, sir.
He made it through all that
because of his saintly image.
(Hello. How adorable.)
(Here.)
I think he’s the most perfect candidate
for Nekros’s victim in Chapter 18.
I agree with him.
Listen to this.
The MP is recently taking
a meditation retreat
at a temple in the suburbs.
This footage was posted on
the temple’s PR page just hours ago.
Contact him.
Immediately.
Ugh, you’re giving me headaches.
I’m telling you. Leave me alone.
Don’t you get my name involved in
that stupid cartoon.
And most importantly,
if you stain my name in the press,
I’ll sue the whole police department.
Ugh, what the hell?
Sir.
I heard that the killer
has claimed three victims.
Each victim was all high profile.
You heard, you said?
Yes.
What the fuck are you waiting for, then?
Crank up my security.
Go!
Idiot.
Freaking idiot.
Tell me if you find something suspicious.
Yes, sir.
You don’t have to go to work
tomorrow, do you?
No.
But I’m not pulling an all-nighter
with you, Inspector.
If nothing comes up, you can go home soon.
I’ll have another team relieve us.
You hungry?
I’m good.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Why did you write Nekros?
Is that question off limits?
Would it be alright
if I refused to answer?
It’s up to you.
I wrote Nekros…
From my life.
My family was ruined
because of the Thai Investment Bank case.
My father
was forced to take the blame.
He spent his life calling for justice.
But no one gave a damn.
Even the law itself
couldn’t save him, Inspector.
In the end,
GIVE ME BACK MY MONEY / SCUM FAMILY
he was left with a massive debt.
He was cornered,
helpless,
and chose to end his problem by…
Killing himself.
Along with his whole family.
Dad?
Where are you?
Mom!
Dad!
Help me!
I created Nekros because of
my own despair in the justice system.
Because a nobody like me
can’t make a difference.
But I’m serious, Inspector,
if the justice system could have helped
my family even a little…
My life wouldn’t have turned out this way.
I understand why you’d think that way.
But listen to me.
I’ll prove to you
that this world
doesn’t need a monster like Nekros.
Someone’s trying to break in.
Get ready to seize him!
Inspector.
Why are you moving closer…?
Are you going to put me
in handcuffs again?
No, I’m not.
Turn this way.
Thank you.
I’ll give you a ride home after we eat.
You’ve got good eyes.
You remember all the details.
No wonder your manga is famous.
Lies end up being truths
because the person who knows the truth
chooses to stay silent.
If we’re successful in catching him,
the rest of the manga
won’t be necessary anymore.