Lin Chong... He will be killed.
What have you done
aside from craft impractical theories?
It's all talk, no action.
One must not destroy the country
in the process.
We shall rebuild this nation
from the shadows.
We cannot even give him a grave?
You need not know any more.
I know. You will become my attendant.
Salt makes this world go round.
Salt is the embodiment of money.
You will need to overcome death's limits.
I do not wish to associate
with Liangshan Marsh.
When two surprising elements merge together,
they bring about unprecedented change.
I promise to return with him.
Lin Chong!
What? What seems to be the issue?
[Song Jiang, Yuncheng Clerk]
I wonder.
[Lin Chong, Former Spearman Instructor]
I am one who shares Song Jiang's ambitions.
[Chao Gai, Bandit King]
It's an honor to meet you, Chao Gai.
[Episode 3]
Song Jiang did not evacuate from Yuncheng.
He said he could not preach a great cause
if he did not even trust his own men.
That does not surprise me.
There is something I must tell you.
Gao Qiu is but a foolish man
who only knows to play ball.
The one manipulating his strings,
is a man named Li Fu.
[Enforcing the Way in Heaven's Name]
Li Fu? That is a name I do not know.
Is he with the Imperial Guard?
No.
He is merely another civil official.
[Lu Zhi Shen, Monk]
Yet he did not flinch in Gao Qiu's presence.
He was especially curious about you,
and Song Jiang's writings.
How much does this Li Fu know?
[Ruan Xiao Wu, Fisherman]
[Wu Yong, Private Tutor]
I am not sure.
Now, what is my next mission?
Lin Chong, you will be escorted
to the Cangzhou prison as intended.
Why?
To seize the stronghold at Liangshan Marsh.
But this will come in due time.
You must first find the doctor, An Dao Quan,
who is currently held in Cangzhou.
I do not see the connection between the two.
The wife of the individual
who is our key to Liangshan Marsh,
is afflicted with a serious illness.
Only An Dao Quan can cure her.
I understand.
It is a welcome challenge.
Are you certain?
Before I go, I must ask a favor.
Ask away, old friend.
Please deliver this to Song Jiang.
Is there anything you wish to tell him?
Tell him...
"Lin Chong is alive".
Listen well, foolish guards.
You two will escort this man to Cangzhou.
When asked where your squad has gone,
this shall be your answer.
"We were ambushed by bandits."
"Though we do not know their intentions,
our squad fought valiantly."
Now repeat.
Do not cower!
They will realize your lies.
We... We were ambushed by bandits.
- Our squad...
- Wrong!
"Though we do not know their intentions".
Repeat this as you march.
We will be watching.
Harm Lin Chong, and you will see hell.
You hear me?
Chao Gai!
What is your report?
Lin Chong is headed to Cangzhou.
I guarantee his safe journey.
Thank you.
Song Jiang.
Lin Chong requested
I deliver his prisoner tag to you.
[Lin Chong]
I also have a message from him.
He says, "Lin Chong is alive".
My son grows more endearing by the day.
[Shi Li, Chief of Shi Family Village]
All children one day leave the nest.
[Madam Wang, Wang Jin's mother]
Yet my own selfishness prays
he will stay a moment longer.
[Shi Jin, Shi Li's son]
Stand, Shi Jin.
[Wang Jin, Former Martial Arts Instructor]
The dragons on your back
are at death's door,
Shi Jin, the Nine Tattooed Dragons.
My son can only converse through combat.
He is happy to have found
a fellow fighting spirit.
"We were ambushed by bandits."
"Though we do not know their intentions,"
"our squad..."
"they fought valiantly."
"We were ambushed by bandits."
[Cangzhou Prison]
Only two escorts?
Where is the rest of your squad?
Your captain is nowhere to be seen.
We were ambushed by bandits.
Though we do not know their intentions...
- Our squad...
- Enough. Go.
Lin Chong was safely escorted to prison?
I ordered his death!
[Gao Qiu, General of the Imperial Guard]
The squad was ambushed by bandits,
and valiantly drove them away...
"Valiantly"? What rubbish.
No matter.
Jailed prisoners die often,
for one reason or another.
Send in our best men.
Yes, sir.
You have returned.
Commander Wang He, reporting.
I hear Gao Qiu raised quite a commotion?
[Li Fu, Qinglian Temple]
Yes, sir. He failed to assassinate Lin Chong.
I see. Lin Chong stands out.
Let him roam. See where he lands.
Gao Qiu has already sent his men to Cangzhou.
Gao Qiu has failed once before.
He will not succeed by repeating his methods.
And the smuggled salt?
We have yet to discover its origins, sir.
[Wang He, Commander of the Qinglian Spies]
Is that so.
How goes this search?
We are capturing wanted bandits,
but none lead to their ensemble.
However, there have been witness reports,
here, here,
here, and here...
Of this hulking monk.
The man known both by Lin Chong,
and Wang Jin.
Yes, sir.
Perhaps our search was misguided.
Pardon?
We only assumed
this was written by a bandit.
In other words?
Like the moon, hidden while the sun rises,
perhaps he is a man invisible to our eyes.
Search not only the dark depths,
but the sunlit paths as well.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir.
Pagoda-Shifting Heavenly King!
Charge!
Perhaps we ought to deploy an envoy
as Sir Yuan Ming suggested.
Our militia only bother to demand bribes
from local officials.
They will investigate nothing.
I cannot have that.
We have objectives to fulfill.
Is there no honorable man within our forces?
Perhaps Yang Zhi, of the Imperial Guard.
Interesting. Tell me about this Yang Zhi.
He is a man who holds pride in his lineage,
being a descendant of the hero, Yang Ye.
He is a skilled warrior,
who wouldn't dare betray the nation.
Fire!
[Yang Zhi, Imperial Guard]
Focus your aim!
Yang Zhi, the Blue-faced Beast.
A legendary name
that will be spoken of for ages.
Now that is a good tale.
Yang Zhi.
- Yes, sir?
- May I have a moment?
A brief one, sir. I am busy,
as I have been appointed to be an envoy.
I am the one who recommended you
to General Gao Qiu.
Pardon?
Yang Zhi.
I will bestow a special mission onto you.
Amend your ways
when you have realized your mistake.
Yes, ma'am.
[Know your mistakes, and correct them]
You must concentrate till the last stroke.
Yes, ma'am.
What? Is that all?
Not at all.
This is nothing
compared to your mother's lessons.
I struggled with her teachings as well.
Master Wang Jin! Bandits!
Bandits have arrived!
Bandits?
Shi Jin, this is another lesson.
Yes, Master.
Shi Jin, the Nine Tattooed Dragons!
You face us alone?
Has your village finally abandoned you?
I will strike your tattooed body,
till your nine dragons
are beaten beyond recognition!
[Cangzhou]
Bai Sheng, bring a support.
- Yes, sir.
- No crying.
- Next.
- There's been another cave-in.
Ready yourself, An Dao Quan.
The labor here is too grueling.
They're practically working us to death.
Lie down.
- The support.
- You patch him, Bai Sheng.
- What?
- Show me your injury.
Yes, I will sew you up later.
Use this rag to stop the bleeding.
Let me see him.
Here, he won't stop making a fuss.
It's nothing serious.
[An Dao Quan, Prisoner, Doctor]
- Are you in pain?
- No.
It did at first, but not at all now.
I see.
There's no hope for this one.
- Next.
- What?
How so? He's perked up.
[Bai Sheng, Prisoner, Thief]
- Don't ignore me!
- Move.
Out of the way.
He will lose his life
once I've fixed this man.
Ridiculous.
Take this.
Use this ointment,
it will mend in a few days.
Next. Out of the way.
You, wake up.
Open your mouth.
Your eyes, too.
- Hey!
- He is already dead.
Why?
He said he felt no pain.
Pain is what keeps us alive.
- Alright, lie down.
- Doctor, we got an emergency!
Get him up here.
Lie down.
Toss him out once he's dead.
I won't kill the man.
- Bai Sheng, boil the water.
- Yes, sir.
So, what is this?
Can you not tell? I was stabbed.
Stabbed?
This was clearly self-inflicted.
Why do something so foolish?
To come see you.
An Dao Quan.
To come see me?
What if you die?
You're a master doctor.
And since you only entertain your patients,
I turned myself into one.
Why?
To help you escape.
Dead men and their lies.
I am no liar.
I have my patients. I will not leave.
Wait.
You are fated to save something bigger.
You must save this very country.
- Wait!
- Hey!
[Ma Gui, Song Jiang's spy]
What are you doing?
You there!
Please, run!
Gao Lian, Follow her.
Yes, sir.
[Gao Lian, Qinglian Spy]
I shall lend a hand.
Sir, we could never...
Please, I only wish to help.
I shall lift this side.
- Ready?
- Yes, sir.
Ready, and...
This won't do...
It seems you all are struggling.
Is it so unusual to see an envoy around?
No, sir.
Allow me to lend a hand.
- Men, go assist them.
- What?
- Ready?
- Yes, sir.
Now lift.
That should do it.
Thank you, sirs. I am in your debt.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
- Safe travels.
Pardon me, but I must hurry along.
Wait.
Yes, sir?
I have never seen
an official assist a peddler.
What is your name?
I apologize for the lack of introductions.
My name is Song Jiang. I am a local clerk.
Song Jiang.
Traveling this nation, I had simply assumed
officials and their pups
required incentive to do good.
And you are?
Right, my apologies.
I am named Yang Zhi.
I have never met an envoy
who did not demand bribery, either.
Let our paths cross again.
Song Jiang.
Lu Zhi Shen, what brings you here?
Chao Gai awaits your company.
Understood.
You seem jovial. Why is that?
I met a rather interesting fellow.
A refreshing man indeed.
Have you fallen for him?
- Is that so wrong?
- Not at all.
You excel at seeing the good in people.
As do you, old friend.
Meeting new people
is truly a mysterious thing.
Chao Gai, for example,
fills in for what I am missing.
You are two hearts, beating as one.
Of course, we still have our differences.
Yet our goals are, miraculously,
one and the same.
How will Chao Gai change this rotten country?
He will have the citizens revolt,
and overthrow our government.
If they can find just one fault
in our current regime,
their rebellion will spread like wildfire.
To make a country,
one must centralize that flame,
to then burn down the old,
and make way for the new.
Is that so strange a sentiment to make?
- Or perhaps you are hungry?
- That, I am.
[Shi Qian, Zhu Tong]
Might I ask what those are?
[Lin Chong]
Tags. Lin Chong's helps me feel his presence.
Thus I decided to immortalize
our other comrades as well.
Though our numbers are small,
we are not alone.
I hope to meet them all soon.
Zhu Tong and Lei Heng are soldiers.
They protect Song Jiang from the shadows.
Wu Song wanders the land,
searching for more comrades like myself.
Ma Gui works as a spy, and gathers intel.
Shi Qian is a fellow spy.
While Dai Zong is a courier.
I will introduce you to them all in due time.
You treat those tags
as though they are treasures.
Right.
Someone may have caught wind
of our Salt Roads.
- Lu Jun Yi.
- Yes, sir.
Though the Salt Road is a complex system,
[Lu Jun Yi, Distributor of Salt]
one of our many pathways
was nearly discovered.
It is only thanks to Wu Yong's premonition
that we avoided any danger.
He predicted we ought to close the route.
A sharp official amongst the fools
must have noticed our presence.
Indeed.
When I am in Kaifeng,
I feel as though I am being observed.
What sort of official comes to mind?
Lin Chong had made note of one.
A suspicious man, named Li Fu.
Li Fu.
Song Jiang, can you use your network
to look into this man?
I will have Ma Gui investigate him.
Ma Gui alone will not suffice, no?
I hear she was nearly found in Kaifeng,
and led one of her allies to death.
Perhaps she is not suited to be a spy.
Then I shall ask Shi Qian as well.
He is a spy I can confidently send anywhere.
Excellent.
However, if our Salt Road is compromised,
that would be the end for us.
How do we combat this?
Let us lead our enemies astray.
Though they know of our presence,
they do not know our numbers.
This is to our advantage.
We will rob the country of its salt.
Rob the country?
I have already sent Ruan Xiao Wu
to the treasury.
They will steal bags of salt,
only for it to disappear without a trace.
What a wasteful plan.
Do they realize how heavy these bags are?
I am more bothered
by this excessively villainous garb.
We play the part of a fake gang of bandits,
the "Shadow Thieves".
Let our enemies chase an illusion
for a while.
"Disappear"? How?
Where will we hide all the salt?
We will not hide it.
We will get rid of it.
The sea will simply regain what it has lost.
This is the most wasteful thing I've done.
Less talking, more pouring.
- Ready, and...
- Good.
- Keep it up.
- This feels utterly wrong.
7,000 granules, lost?
Yes. They've disappeared without a trace.
We may be dealing with a larger ensemble
than we first assumed.
What else have you learned?
The band calls themselves
the "Shadow Thieves".
The citizens rally with them
as chivalrous bandits,
as they have stolen from the country.
Chivalry, as bandits?
Continue to look into their whereabouts.
Yes, sir.
A larger ensemble, or so they claim.
Never have we heard
of these "Shadow Thieves".
How did this salt disappear under our watch?
Nothing is adding up.
A bad feeling such as this,
is usually on the mark.
- Li Fu.
- Sir?
Raise the price of salt across the nation.
[Yuan Ming, Leader of Qinglian Temple]
Immediately.
Raise the price?
We shall drag those chivalrous thieves
through the mud.
[Notice: The price of salt will rise]
They've outdone us.
The Shadow Thieves are now
an enemy of the people.
To think they could change
the market price of salt.
This is unprecedented.
I cannot think of anyone in Kaifeng
who can influence the price so quickly.
What do you think, Wu Yong?
I agree with Song Jiang.
Regardless, now we can be certain.
This invisible enemy
is aware of our presence.
Sir! Sir!
What?
Give me a hand.
Thank you.
Do you truly plan to break An Dao Quan free?
If he would allow himself to be, yes.
You stand out.
You'll never be able to escape.
I'm already a dead man.
Escaping would be trivial.
Take a look around this area.
What?
Every guard has his eyes on you.
Now that you mention it.
Help me carry this, would you?
You're known as the Panther Head, aren't you?
To think that nickname
would spread even here.
You're also a former instructor
for the Imperial Guard.
All the guards fear you,
Panther Head, Lin Chong.
I see.
Ouch...
Hey.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Just my stomach.
Say.
If you take me along,
I'll convince An Dao Quan to leave.
I thought I will never be able to escape?
Come visit An Dao Quan later.
I'll explain the plan then.
Hey, what are you two doing?
My deepest apologies.
Get back to work.
Sir, you can't be standing out like that!
Sorry.
One more thing.
Be especially wary of those two.
My hunch as a thief is telling me
those two aren't like the other prisoners.
They never take their eyes off you.
I know.
Where is Bai Sheng?
What did you need from him?
We planned to plot our escape.
Bai Sheng is stealing a sharp tool
for me to use.
He should return soon.
And I will repeat,
I have no interest in escaping.
Don't be so stubborn.
Bai Sheng wants to break you free.
I have returned.
Bai Sheng.
There you are.
Now then, let's get down to business.
Help me lift this.
Heave-ho.
Take a look.
It's a map of this prison.
How did you acquire this?
I stole it, how else?
Not even a rat
can sneak out of these walls.
Then how do we escape?
There may be no path for a rat,
but there is always a way for a thief.
The unexpected route. That is our path.
We will escape, like so.
Are you a fool?
That is right out the front gates.
Exactly. You will shout it out,
loud and proud,
and slay your way out the front gates.
Why shout my name?
You don't understand how weaklings feel, sir.
The guards will hear your name,
and cower in fear.
No one here can best you
in a one-on-one fight.
Ain't that right?
I may very well die.
What a thrill.
You speak of your own death
with such excitement.
You were listening?
Why do you rush to death's arms?
All people are fated to die.
I am simply accepting that outcome.
No.
You are ill.
You crave death at every moment.
Love does not need a reason, my dear.
Can I be cured?
A wound of the heart can only be mended
by the one who afflicted it.
Then I am beyond saving.
She...
has already died.
You certainly have it rough.
Bai Sheng, what's wrong?
What are you doing?
He has a sharp object!
You thief.
Apprehend him!
Stand!
Yes, take him away!
Wait! Bai Sheng!
- Silence!
- He needs to be treated!
Master Wang Jin!
Please, wait!
You are being far too cruel.
I have taught you all I know.
The rest, you must learn on your own.
I still wish to learn under you, Master.
You cannot leave now.
Master Wang Jin.
I wish to travel alongside you.
Is that what I taught you, Shi Jin?
I taught you the importance of gratitude.
Abandoning your father,
all to follow your Master.
Is that your way of being filial?
Please, leave me one last lesson
before you part.
This is no farewell.
I will be alive within you.
I know it to be true.
Excellent work.
Do not ever forget that sound.
Let us be off.
Was this moment all a dream, Father?
It certainly felt like one.
But you have undoubtedly
grown into a strong man.
Lin Chong, you're late.
Where are the herbs?
I have them here.
There.
Useless junk, again.
Bai Sheng would have...
I am no doctor, nor am I Bai Sheng.
Your anger is becoming obvious, An Dao Quan.
It is my fault Bai Sheng was sent
to the discipline chamber.
I had him steal many things for me.
We can only wait for his return.
Bai Sheng has an infection
within his stomach.
If it breaks through his tissue,
the infection will spread,
and kill Bai Sheng.
Why do you obsess over Bai Sheng?
I do not know.
But I hate to imagine him in pain.
Then he is your friend?
I have never had a friend.
Nor do I know what it means to be a friend.
I simply cannot help but worry for Bai Sheng.
That is because he is a friend, An Dao Quan.
I, too, have my share of friends.
This is a prison.
All transactions are to be a trade.
If I save your friend, Bai Sheng,
will you come and save mine?
Save Bai Sheng?
How?
We will escape.
Hey! What are you doing?
Lin Chong!
You will shout it out, loud and proud,
and slay your way out the front gates.
Perhaps it is time Lin Chong revives.
I, Lin Chong the Panther Head,
will now be breaking free!
Bai Sheng!
This is no good.
I must treat you.
Start with the chains, they hurt.
How can a thief not escape some chains?
Can you stand?
We have to go.
Found them!
Your movements tell me
you're no ordinary soldiers.
Allow me a guess.
Assassins hired by Gao Qiu?
Let your bodies rot within the fodder.
Sir!
Are you alright, Bai Sheng?
I'm sorry, Bai Sheng.
Bai Sheng, pull through!
[Lin Chong]
Lin Chong...
Are you alright?
Bai Sheng, stay with us.
Bai Sheng, stay steady!
Lin Chong!
Bai Sheng is at his limit.
I must operate on him here.
What?
You are attempting the impossible.
Bai Sheng.
Bai Sheng, we will operate here.
Hurry.
Wait...
Leave me behind.
Do you know what I despise most of all?
It is people who die without my permission.
I will fight alongside you. So fight!
Show me your stomach.
Lin Chong, Bai Sheng will start flailing.
Hold him down.
You must live!
I will escort you to safety.
I will take you to my comrades!
Song Jiang did not evacuate from Yuncheng.
He said he could not preach a great cause,
if he did not even trust his own men.
I will choose to believe in Lin Chong.
You must come out of this alive!
Bai Sheng! Live!
Bai Sheng!
Lin Chong has broken out of prison.
Song Jiang.
How long will you stand there?
I will join you.
Sir Song Jiang!
Song Jiang!
Lin Chong?
Lin Chong!
An Dao Quan...
[Lin Chong]
Lin Chong!
- An Dao Quan...
- Are you alright?
Hey, are you alright?
- Stay with us!
- Wake up.
Wake up, I say!
Lin Chong...
has returned.
Welcome home, Lin Chong.
If he feels misplaced in the Imperial Guard,
then I would like him for myself.
Song Jiang is no ordinary clerk.
Will you create a moment
for them to smile?
I wish to have a lethal brigade.
One that chooses to fight as a group.
It is an impenetrable fortress.
We cannot break in from the front gates.
A monster resides within that fortress.
A monster, known as "authority".
A spy like myself
could never become a normal woman.
Some suspicious civil officials
work under Cai Jing.
Li Fu. The man Lin Chong feared?
Chao Gai, I want you to strike me down.
[Episode 3 - FIN]