Excuse me.
The interviewer was the older guy
who hit on you. That's just insane.
I really look like a kid, don't I?
Making people worry and
needing to be comforted.
- Excuse me.
- Ai-chan.
This guy is a real catch.
Please take good care of him.
He likes you, doesn't he?
I won't join Okumi-san's company.
So please reject my application.
I got the job offer.
- Huh?
- How did that happen?
He's just too cute.
Even though he's a cute boy,
he shouldn't be looking at dating sites
so openly.
Hmm?
You don't look so well.
Are you okay?
From the very beginning, I...
I never thought I'd fall in
love at first sight at this age.
That cake from last time was so good.
- It really was.
- I want to go again.
- You want to go again?
- Yeah.
Let's go next week.
So young.
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 3)
You got a job offer from
that older guy's company?
But I didn't know he was the president
until the final interview.
I got the job offer.
- Huh?
- How did that happen?
Hiring in our company
is decided by the HR department.
Are you serious?
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to take it?
I am.
The president, huh...
(Words from my late wife)
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Come on, what is it?
No, really, it's nothing.
- Let me see.
- Ah.
(Words from my late wife)
See?
Just because he was married
doesn't mean he only likes women.
Plus, it confirms he's single.
Isn't that a good thing?
I don't even know if he likes me.
(Maybe he actually prefers women.)
Why don't you just ask him directly?
No way.
Asking something like
that feels so childish.
(He was married, right?)
(A divorced older guy
with someone so young...)
(If he really likes women...)
(Things are great now,
but what about later?)
(What if he doesn't
actually like me that much?)
(He might not always like me.)
Wait.
- We're outside.
- Sorry.
You're just too cute.
(I thought you were adorable the first time
we met. I couldn't bear to let you go.)
Come in.
Excuse me.
It's so spacious.
It's been a while, Ai-chan.
It's only been a week.
You should praise me
for holding back until now.
Stop joking around, old man.
- Come here.
- No, no.
(But an older guy's true feelings must be
a burden for someone as young as you.)
(Even so, right now...)
Are you busy, Mr. President?
Huh? Well, I wouldn't say
I have a lot of free time.
What's wrong?
Doing this takes a lot of energy.
I was wondering if you'd be too tired.
Then,
Can I get a reward
for working so hard just to see you?
Ah.
What kind of reward?
Let me see more of your face
when you feel good, Ai-chan.
Ah.
You actually have a mole here.
Probably only my parents know about that.
Then you absolutely can't
let anyone else see it.
What do you like about me?
Am I not showing you enough love?
It's more than enough.
It's just that,
I sometimes wonder if I'm
really good enough for you.
Ai-chan.
You know,
- I was actually married once.
- Yeah.
Huh, you don't seem very surprised.
I read an interview online.
Right. I am a second-generation
successor, after all.
Back then, I didn't have the luxury
to figure out if I was gay or bisexual.
I didn't have anyone I
liked at the time, either.
I just thought that was
how life was supposed to be.
Fortunately, she was a good person.
As we lived together, gradually,
we developed feelings similar to love.
Then she got sick.
She passed away very suddenly.
So I thought I'd never fall in love again
and just die alone.
I never expected
that I would meet you.
Ah, sorry.
That got too heavy.
I'll go change the sheets.
(How could I put him in a tough spot?)
(I really didn't want him
to make that kind of face.)
Ai-chan.
Lone...
Lone?
If you're lonely, I'm still here.
Listen,
Can we cancel the promise
about dating until you get bored of me?
I want to be with you forever.
Not just until I get bored.
I'd cry if you ever got bored of me.
Give me a break.
You'd dump me without hesitation
if you got bored, wouldn't you?
That's impossible.
Is that a no?
Whether it's nursing care or whatever, I'll
take care of you for the rest of my life.
I'll do everything I can
to extend my healthy lifespan.
Okumi-san.
Ai-chan.
Can we do it one more time?
Hmm?
I already took a shower.
A shower?
We can just take another one.
(Next Episode) This is my
first time having an office romance.
You're starting to want to be happy.
Isn't that a good thing?
Ah!
I'm completely useless at the
company. Why did they even hire me?
If you feel bad about it,
then make it up to me.