Himukai's lucky he found out before marriage.
- Yeah, he dodged a bullet.
- I mean, he's the CEO's son.
He can't be marrying a girl
who can't provide him an heir.
Hey!
How's the dreaded farewell party going?
Sui?
Hello?
It's definitely dreadful.
I think I had too much to drink.
Jeez...
Don't get dragged to an afterparty, okay?
Go straight home after this one.
I will. Thanks.
Maybe I'll deploy him, just in case.
Can I ask you something
I've been wondering about?
Sure.
That night...
Which night?
You know.
The night you helped me.
Are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
You're drunk stupid.
Was it a coincidence you were there?
I wonder.
Erika didn't ask you to check on me, did she?
She technically told me not to tell you.
It's a coincidence a dude hit on you, though.
Honestly, I was surprised to see you
actually in trouble.
Sorry.
But thanks to him,
we shared a nice night together.
Hey!
Mao.
Thanks for always helping out.
It's no big deal.
[Idea Construction Office]
Monou, will you join us for our appointment
with the Hayashi's at 11 today?
Sure thing.
Then I'll see you there.
Is this what you're looking for?
Yeah.
The Hayashi's are coming
to ask about kitchen renovations.
I've marked some designs I'd recommend.
Thanks.
Hurry, they're arriving soon.
Right. See you around.
I felt like someone was following me home
yesterday night.
What? Following you?
I technically didn't see anyone though...
Is everything all right?
Nana says someone might've been
following her home last night.
Following you?
Any ideas on who it could've been?
I thought maybe it was the woman
who visited you, Monou.
Takizawa?
I'm only speculating, of course.
Still...
Anyone who stands in my way will see hell.
- What the...
- I'm so sorry!
It's not your fault.
No, it absolutely is.
I can't believe I've implicated you into this.
I am so sorry.
Don't apologize, please.
Sui.
For the time being,
I'll walk Mizuno home until this is settled.
You wouldn't mind?
Better to be cautious now,
then when it's too late.
Thank you.
That would put you at ease too, right, Sui?
What?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
Please take care of her.
Monou. I'll be heading out a bit,
then straight home.
All right.
Please take care.
Thank you.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
We'll be heading to do a deal with...
Wait! I haven't said my piece yet!
Leave me alone. This plan is over!
I want nothing to do with you anymore,
so please, don't bother me again!
Don't end things on your own terms!
I said I'd figure this out!
Damn you...
Sui?
Sui! Sui, Sui, Sui!
I knew you'd come back for me.
- What? No!
- Sui.
I'll always love you. I still do.
So, rest easy, okay?
You've clearly misunderstood.
I have no lingering attachments to you.
I don't plan on ever seeing you again.
No, but...
I'm here...
because I have business with Takizawa.
Really now.
Come to laugh at my pathetic fate?
Or have you changed your mind about my plan?
Neither.
Then what exactly do you want?
You're free to harass me as you wish.
But don't drag irrelevant parties
like Mizuno into our troubles.
Please.
What are you talking about?
Who the heck is Mizuno?
- You saw her when you visited.
- What?
- You went all the way to Sui's office?
- Oh!
That dreary woman who chased me out the door?
I don't have time to bother people like her.
The only one I have a grudge on
is the person who ruined my plan - you.
Oh, I know that irritating look.
Always standing up for others,
but never yourself.
Why would you even do such a thing?
First of all.
The only reason why this man chose you
was because he pitied you
after you lost your parents.
Huh?
You think you're so special.
Even I clawed my way
through my own struggles.
And just when I thought
I'd finally reached the top...
You had to use your cowardly pity tactics.
How dare you get a head start on me?
What are you talking about?
You should be thankful I'm so kind.
I couldn't stand to see you rejected
because of your infertility.
That's why I extended a helping hand!
I had the perfect plan
to make us all happy.
But you.
Both of you.
Why turn down such a genius idea?
Why not choose the path
that makes us all happy?
I won't let my plan be ruined so easily.
Sui?
Good bye.
Hey, a striped mullet.
I have to do what I ought to do.
[MIREVO DESIGN]
[Interior Design Coordinator]
[Hirose Architects]
Excuse me.
We're going to be using this room soon.
Sorry. Lunch break must already be over.
I admire your intense concentration.
You seem really motivated to study.
You think so?
It's like you're absorbed in your work.
All I can do now is my best.
There's plenty I'm still not used to,
so I'm causing trouble to the team.
Don't worry about that.
What?
We're all here for you, all right?
Thank you.
Would you like some coffee?
I'll get some myself, thanks.
[Idea Construction Office]
A proposal for an event?
Yeah.
Since it's being held by a partner of ours,
we were asked to lend a hand.
I see.
Do you know Takaomi Hirose,
of Hirose Architects?
Yes, of course.
I've known the kid since he was a student.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We've always wanted to work together,
but never found the opportunity.
So, I'm hoping to rope him in
to help us with this event.
Monou, want to be our representative?
I'd be honored to have the opportunity.
All right, I'll put in a word for you.
Draft a proposal
and go visit him in the coming days.
I'll have Mao support you.
- What?
- He's Hirose's junior.
They attended the same seminar.
That's amazing.
I'll try not to disappoint, Mr. Hoshina.
Sorry to drag you out. I know you're busy.
It's fine.
Can't defy the boss's orders, you know?
I didn't realize you attended
a seminar with Hirose.
That's really amazing.
We never attended at the same time, though.
I know him, but he certainly doesn't know me.
Still, I feel better having you come with me.
Glad I could help.
This is my first time
presenting an idea of mine.
I'm getting a bit nervous...
You'll be fine.
Remember, you're not alone.
Thanks.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
[Hirose Architects]
Did I keep you waiting?
Not at all. Thank you for seeing us today.
My name is Monou
of Idea Construction Office.
I'm Hirose. Let Mr. Hoshina know
I send my regards.
- My business card.
- Thank you, and mine.
My name is Tsukidome.
We actually graduated from the same seminar.
Really?
What a fun coincidence.
- For you.
- Thank you. And mine as well.
To start,
I've summarized our vision for this event.
Please, take a look.
Thank you.
[Contents]
[Event Specifications]
Mr. Hirose.
I know you must receive
plenty of offers like this.
That I do, yes.
However, I must let you know
your designs are special to me.
Before I moved, there was a cafe
I was quite fond of in the neighborhood.
I never felt uncomfortable there.
Being there motivated me to face the day.
It was sort of like a power spot of mine.
I see.
I discovered the place was your design
after entering this line of work.
Is that so?
I'm sure the cafe felt so comforting
because of your kindness
and careful planning.
That is why...
Monou.
Yes?
I do receive quite a few offers like yours.
But most clients could care less
whether it was my work or not.
I see.
However, seeing how passionate
you are about my work,
I think we can create a wonderful event.
What?
Next time, I would love to see an idea
that is wholly your own.
Yes, I'll be sure to bring one.
Since we've ended early,
how about we grab a meal together?
You wouldn't mind?
I'm sorry, but I have prior plans.
That's too bad.
Then how about the two of us, Monou?
I'd love to join you.
There's a place we've designed right nearby.
How about we go there?
That sounds wonderful.
I can't wait to see it.
Actually, this is that very store.
I've been here before.
- Really?
- Yes.
The terrace was especially beautiful.
I'm honored, thank you.
You're drinking fast tonight.
- Am not.
- And you're in a bad mood.
Am not.
Did you fight with a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Then you have someone
you're guarding, but not dating.
Again? You haven't changed since college.
I'm telling you, that's not it.
Mao just can't ignore people in need.
When will you learn the difference
between romance and compassion?
Helping someone does not equal dating them.
I know that already.
You definitely don't.
Yeah, whatever.
By the way, do you all know Hirose?
The one who also attended our seminar.
Takaomi Hirose?
The legendary architect?
- Winner of the Goro Nomura award?
- Yeah.
I've got a job with him coming up.
- Really?
- That's amazing.
He must be a real ladies man.
That's what you're focused on?
But he's married, right?
Is he?
See, look.
His wife's a beauty.
- Woah, she is.
- Married, huh?
You look happy.
What? I don't.
Now he's back to sulking.
Yikes.
What a complicated fella.
Why're not opening?
Mao?
What're you doing?
I was taking out the trash.
You were drinking, at this hour?
Are you drunk?
Let me see that.
Are you okay?
Water.
Oh, jeez...
Can you walk?
Here. Drink up.
Thanks for today.
I appreciated you being there with me.
The meal with Hirose was quite fun.
He gave me plenty of hints
for my next proposal.
You should join us next time...
Mao?
Do you feel ill?
It's like when we first met.
Except, now we're reversed.
Sui.
Want to pick up where we left off that night?
What do you think of Mao?
You seem angry.
I'd rather focus on making do on my own.
I'm worried about you too, Sui.
Mao, I love you.
I've always loved you.