[This drama is fictional
and bears no resemblance to reality]
[Some scenes feature AI technology]
[All child and animal scenes
followed strict safety guidelines]
[Episode 4]
♪ Why am I standing on this road? ♪
♪ Is this really my path? ♪
♪ At the end of this road ♪
♪ Will my dream come true? ♪
♪ I want to say with confidence
that this is my path ♪
- Hey, hey.
- ♪ Never regret it... ♪
You think you're walking straight?
What's that supposed to mean?
Because I got fired?
No, that's not it.
Where are you going? What road is this?
Same road as you.
What?
I'm making movies with you.
- ♪ What am I dreaming of... ♪
- Hey, hey! Wait!
♪ Who is that dream really for? ♪
♪ If I make it come true,
will I finally smile... ♪
Gosh.
What the...
You're insane, Ju Yi Jae!
Ian.
What?
- Someone's here.
- Ian?
Let's go get some breakfast.
In Uk.
It's freezing.
Huh?
Are you in there?
What are you doing?
Yeah, I'm in the shower.
Okay.
Sounds like a rough shower.
It'd be a problem if you died in there alone.
For me, for the hotel...
You too, probably. Going out like that.
Or maybe...
You'd be proud.
You're hot.
Come to the lounge.
What were you thinking?
I didn't know where to look.
Your eyes?
They're puffy.
Hey!
You should've told me you had a roommate.
I did.
He's next door, not my roommate.
Wait outside.
We need to talk about last night.
Don't go.
Normally, this is where the girl runs.
But I'm different.
Sounds rehearsed.
How did I get here?
I remember saying I'd make movies with you.
Fill me in after that.
So that's where you blacked out?
I didn't know you were that bold.
"Bold?"
Me?
What exactly did I do?
Ju Yi Jae.
You listed your place.
What?
It's a bit old, but the layout is great.
It faces south, so it gets great light.
You're the tenant, right?
- Hello.
- The landlord called me.
You even gave us the door code.
Thank you so much.
I did?
I've been running around all morning
just to show this place.
I really am... my own regret.
- I really like this place.
- Right?
Look over here too.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
[Film Screenplay and Directing Agreement]
- Yi Jae.
- Yeah?
Is that seal heavy?
A little.
Mine felt heavy too on my first contract.
Maybe try thinking of it another way.
This isn't a world
where no one notices if you disappear.
This story is yours.
You started it, so you get to finish it.
That means you write it and direct it.
And I'll be with you the whole way.
To the end.
[Sealed by Ju Yi Jae]
Finally.
Now it really begins.
Hello, I'm Seo In Uk.
Hello.
I'll do everything I can
so you can focus on the script.
Thank you.
What about the studio?
She doesn't have a place right now.
Why would you say that?
So that's why you were at the hotel.
- Sorry?
- I saw a pair of unfamiliar shoes.
We just met but...
I've seen your shoes.
- I'm sorry.
- No need.
We're looking for a quiet house nearby.
He insisted on that area.
Please stay at the hotel
just until the studio is set up.
I can stay with a friend.
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
You need to write.
The hotel will be better.
- Yes, sir.
- I look forward to working with you.
Same here.
Ta-da! Here Comes Dong Hyun!
He's better.
Welcome.
You've got a good eye.
Perfect.
- Producer Kyung?
- Yes?
I'm Seo In Uk.
It says Jaden.
I'm Jaden too.
I see.
What does a film company want with me?
Ju Yi Jae is still owed payment.
Ju Yi Jae?
What?
How do you know her?
She signed with us.
In a way, I guess we owe you.
We'd been dying to sign her.
- But loose ends still need tying up.
- Wait...
What did she sign?
And tie up what?
There must've been some mix-up.
I'll look into it first...
No, no.
You'd handle that yourself?
Even your own work was too much trouble.
What are you talking about?
Is that what Yi Jae said?
She's spreading lies because she's bitter.
I'm not like that. You've got me wrong.
No standard contract.
Driving for you. Editing for you.
Clock-ins. Meetings.
You gave unfair work to a contract worker,
then wrongfully fired her.
Our legal team is good.
They made it simple...
so you won't be bothered.
Take a look.
What's that paper?
Yeah?
Think of this as a warm-up
until the studio is ready.
- Don't push yourself.
- No.
This amazing work setup
is bringing my creative soul back to life.
[One Hour Later]
It has been dead for a while.
Even old sparks can come back.
Why don't you start by watching some movies?
References. Very important.
[Lead Actor, Go Sang Yeon]
Is he ever on time?
There he is.
He's not ready yet. Could you wait?
He's already late.
- Now you want more time?
- Sorry.
It's my fault.
You always cut Oh Ha Na slack.
Why so hard on me?
Just get me ready during rehearsal.
Use someone close enough.
Hey!
Hey! You. White shirt.
- Come here.
- Go on.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Here. Scene 26.
Rehearse for me.
Good luck, Oh Ha Na.
Cut!
Okay!
You're really good.
It was just rehearsal, but I want to use that.
How long have you acted?
- I'd love to see you in my next project.
- Thank you.
You've got the look and the emotion.
Hey!
Follow me.
There he goes again.
Beats me.
He's been on edge lately.
It's not his first time.
Why take it out on him?
What's with you?
- You laughed at me earlier.
- I didn't.
They call me box-office poison,
so I'm a joke to you too?
- I didn't.
- I can see it in your eyes.
Saw your chance?
Eyeing my spot?
I didn't.
- You told me to, senior.
- "Senior?"
Since when am I your senior?
That's enough, Mr. Go.
"Mr. Go?"
You've got guts.
Show some respect.
I'll leave if you're done.
Look at this punk.
You're nothing.
So why are you standing so tall?
Who's behind you?
Got some rich lady backing you?
Any problem?
- Have you lost it?
- You have.
What...
You two a thing?
Yeah, we're close.
- Who are you to touch my friend?
- "Friend?"
You don't have friends.
You barely went to school.
Why wouldn't I?
- Didn't you watch "Ha Na's High School?"
- You only clocked in on shoot days.
- It's called "going to school," idiot.
- With cameras?
I heard some great stories
from your high school days.
Your friends must've hated you.
- What?
- Oh, right.
Not your friends. Your bullying victims.
I apologized for that!
People don't change.
You should've outgrown the bully act back then.
I dropped out after middle school.
Real classy, asshole.
Come on, friend. Let's go.
Where are you going?
Get back here!
That's hot!
She didn't put it out!
Where's my manager? Report her!
Hot!
Why did I close my eyes?
What?
You want me to keep going?
No, I don't.
But...
Gosh.
Good night.
Yeah. Good night.
Yeah. Bye.
Bye.
Wait.
Why is he sleeping here?
[In Uk]
Coming back?
Not coming back.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Looks like you didn't sleep well.
Yeah...
Eat up.
No coffee?
Think.
[Nan Young's gaze turns toward Moo Gyeom]
[Nothing's coming to me... Nothing]
[Woo Soo Bin]
Did you eat?
[Want to have lunch later?]
[Don't push yourself too hard]
[Are you eating properly?]
[You worked hard today. Sleep well]
Come on...
Retirement feels so empty.
I'm still perfectly fine.
Why kick me out?
Tell me about it.
Young guys move up,
and suddenly we're old news.
Those young punks...
Well, not always.
Youth unemployment is terrible too.
Plenty of them just goof off all day.
Kids these days have it too easy.
- Enough. Stop.
- Why?
I'm not just goofing off.
I'm struggling, sir.
Yu Geon.
That event you mentioned.
Did they find someone?
You said you were busy writing.
Yu Geon.
Will you be in my movie?
Come on. You know I hate that.
Please don't give me even a tiny role.
[Staff Only]
- Hello.
- Yeah...
I figured.
Don't worry.
Tiny role or not, I can't even do my own job.
I can't write a single word,
so I'm here to make some cash.
What does Soo Bin say?
I'm dodging him.
What am I going to do?
I tell myself it's fine, but I can't calm down.
That blinking cursor makes my heart race.
And most of all...
I'm scared Soo Bin will be disappointed.
You must want to impress him.
Good luck.
Ju Yi Jae.
Ju Yi Jae!
Get in.
Do you read the comments?
[Something's off]
[They freeze when they lock eyes]
You think viewers are stupid?
Everyone can tell you two hate each other!
You kicked his shin?
Burned him with a cigarette?
Why should I hear that crap from Hyeon Gu?
Who's Hyeon Gu?
Sang Yeon's CEO!
Stop picking fights with him.
Handling your costar is part of the job.
Why do you clash with every rom-com lead?
They start it. They try to put me in my place.
- What?
- They all think they're kings.
But you know what's worse?
To everyone else,
I probably look just like them.
So what? Just stay with your own kind.
Don't come down and get your feet dirty.
And...
Isn't that a little hypocritical
on your way to a luxury event?
- Director Kang!
- Yes.
- Drop me at the next intersection!
- The next intersection?
- Over there...
- Yeah.
We're in the left lane, but I'll try.
Hello. Please try this scent.
Thank you.
Hello. Try this...
Why'd you skip me?
- At least act happy to see me.
- I'm not.
Ever heard of manners?
Depends on you.
There's someone I'm happy to see.
What's with you two?
Is he your manager?
Are you... my manager?
No. I meant you.
- Me?
- You're pretty casual.
So are you.
Your Korean is perfect.
Why only speak English at the audition?
Because it was in America. And this is Korea.
Are you close with him?
No. He's obviously older than me.
We were just neighbors for a bit as kids.
"Neighbors?"
"For a bit?"
Never be his friend.
How do you know her?
- Curious?
- Yes.
I'm a director.
She's an actress.
That's it.
At least we're not neighbors.
That's not the way.
You know where I'm going?
Aren't you buying anything?
- Will you give me a discount?
- Fine.
- You like Rouvee, right?
- Yes!
- You like it, right?
Raise your hand if you do!
If you love Rouvee, make some noise!
Next up is the moment
you've all been waiting for.
It's time for the lucky draw!
This lucky draw will be picked
by our brand model,
actress Oh Ha Na herself.
Please welcome actress Oh Ha Na to the stage!
Actress Oh Ha Na!
I don't often get to meet fans this close.
Let's have fun today.
Who will be our lucky winner?
- Number 38.
- Number 38!
It's me! It's me!
- Next is number 4.
- Number 4!
Who is it?
Number 4! Congrats!
Please pick the last number.
Last one! Last one!
- Last one!
Raise your hand if you want it!
Sorry!
Who are you?
- Do you know me?
- This one's for you.
The other one, I got bullied into buying.
I get why now.
Do you know me or not?
I know who you are.
And I know why you're here.
Aren't you even mad?
You finally made up your mind,
but it didn't go the way you wanted. Right?
You must've been scared.
But that's normal.
I'm scared too, that I'm just being selfish.
What if I'm only making things harder for you?
But we're trying to do something great.
Yi Jae.
Greatness isn't about making something amazing.
Going all the way together,
that's what makes it great.
Studio tomorrow, right?
Think hard about
whether you're with me to the end.
I should go.
Greatness isn't about making something amazing.
Going all the way together,
that's what makes it great.
Okay.
Woo Soo Bin?
It's you, right?
Thank God.
I've been looking everywhere.
You're late.
Trunk!
Yeah.
I'll load it.
Let's go. To do something great.
This is so nice, huh?
- Yeah.
- The ocean is wonderful.
Right.
- What should we eat?
- Anything's fine.
I know a great bibimbap place.
Bibimbap?
Not bibimbap.
- Something else.
- What do you even like?
- Remember this place?
- Where?
- There.
- Oh, there.
- You don't remember, huh?
- Of course I do.
I'm excited.
Come on.
Mom.
What?
What do you want me to be?
A decent human being.
Agreed.
Stop joking.
Anything.
I'm not asking what's for dinner.
At least I can choose dinner.
Kids never turn out the way you want.
Treasure them? Adore them?
What a joke.
That's harsh to your fired daughter.
You were always working yourself to death.
It's for the best.
Just find something else.
You could work festivals nationwide
and still make a living.
Just buy a car.
Stop taking the bus.
Mom.
I came here to write.
What?
A movie.
I want to try again.
Here we go again.
I told you so many times.
That's for rich kids
with nothing to worry about.
So Woo Soo Bin can, but I can't?
Right.
He went all the way to America and made it.
His dad was against it, so he cut him off.
That courage comes from
having something to fall back on.
No wonder I live like this.
Fine. I'll live my own life.
Don't tell me this is because of him.
I already signed.
I'm doing it with him.
You little...
Are you out of your mind?
Anyone but him!
Look what he did to you!
Why?
Because he's rich and I'm poor.
It's not his fault.
If you're right, I should've left home.
Family or not, I should've lived my life!
What is that supposed to mean?
Ju Yi Jae, come out.
Hey.
Eat breakfast!
[Interbank Transfer: Security Deposit]
Gosh! You scared me.
- When did you get here?
- At dawn.
Why?
I ran away.
What?
We're adapting the original draft.
Updating a ten-year-old draft won't be easy.
So let's start with the structure.
So I broke it down by chapter and scene.
When did you do all that?
Whenever I could.
You called that warming up?
Even if we change lines or move scenes,
the framework will hold.
Are we really doing this every time?
Sharing every word, comma, and period?
Yes.
Seriously?
I'm so embarrassed.
It shows too much.
It's not a diary.
This is efficient. We can sync in real time.
I wanted to clean it up before showing you.
Ju Yi Jae.
We're co-writing this.
We need to write as one.
Until even we can't tell who wrote which scene.
Okay, I'll catch up fast.
Let's meet whenever we need to.
And eat together.
Share schedules too.
Want to work out together?
For efficiency.
No, thank you.
Let's skip the workouts.
- Let's start.
- Yeah.
- I'll share the file first.
- Okay.
"Nan Young."
"Graceful and proud."
"Noble Young Master."
"You are quite impatient."
"Nan Young."
"She tries to pull away."
"Just then, Moo Gyeom pulls her by the waist."
"Moo Gyeom."
"Why shouldn't I be?"
"When your eyes are so full of love for me."
I like it.
What? You only worked?
How do you only work?
Weren't you nervous?
Nervous, my ass.
Hey.
I'm Ju Yi Jae.
I'm not that easy.
This isn't about being easy.
A grown man and woman under one roof?
What genre is that?
Usually, romance.
Wait.
I need to be careful.
It's not about feelings. It's the setup.
Live together all day,
and feelings just happen.
You start looking.
Then your heart follows.
Exactly!
And it turns into a hot, R-rated romance.
It started with a simple contract.
She only meant to take off his glasses.
But after that night, there was no...
Stop! Stop!
Hey.
Come back to reality.
And don't show it on your date.
Show what?
My pretty side?
Forget it.
I look like the lead
in an office romance today.
This should be enough for a smart, sexy man.
I can do this.
Is anyone around you?
You're saying some crazy stuff.
People?
- Someone's here.
- Yes.
I got your email.
Thank you for your help.
I'll call again if anything comes up.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
Doors opening.
After you.
Thank you.
Doors opening.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Could you wait a second?
Thank you.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Nice brand.
What are you doing?
Don't worry.
Laundry service!
- Laundry service?
- Oh wow!
You speak Korean?
Yes.
Call me. I'll cover the cleaning.
Sorry.
I heard your parents are traveling the world.
That's my ideal marriage.
After I retire, I want to travel with my wife,
just the two of us.
I see.
You must like traveling.
When wanderlust hits, I just take off.
What are your hobbies?
Soccer.
"Soccer?"
Not many women are into soccer.
I like it too. Who do you like?
Son Heung Min? Lee Kang In?
- Hwang Hee Chan?
- I like playing it more than watching it.
You play soccer? Why?
- Sorry?
- I mean...
What if you get hurt?
I'd be upset if your legs got scarred.
In the army, they called me Bomber.
Because I bombed the goal.
I scored 486 goals
in 128 international matches...
- After you.
- Smart.
And sexy.
Anything else you like besides soccer?
- Flower arranging?
- Men.
- Sorry?
- I really like men.
I like women too.
I'm sorry, but I should go.
I'll pay for the meal.
Where are you going?
To find a man.
I thought we had a vibe...
Sorry, Mom.
- Hello.
I'm looking for someone in this hotel.
I'm sorry, but for our guests' privacy...
I know, but please just hear me out.
He's about this tall.
Slicked-back hair,
thick eyebrows, a straight nose.
And a very sexy, sharp jawline.
Great forearms too.
Most of all, his English voice
is low and so sexy.
Have you seen him?
Could that be him?
- Thank you.
- Yes!
That's him! Thank you.
Excuse me.
Would you go out with me?
Yes, baby?
"Baby?"
I'm sorry.
Please pretend you didn't hear that.
What baby?
Are you crazy?
Why?
Is the casting list ready?
I'm on it. How's the first draft?
Two weeks.
She's working herself ragged.
I can tell just from your voice.
You sound just fine
after leaving me here alone.
You're still at the hotel?
You were looking for a rental.
Seoul rent is insane.
I added a month. On your card.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
What?
They let you do that?
I made them.
Check your phone.
[Card payment approved, lump sum]
11,000,000 won?
This is insane.
[Event Team Lead, Kim Ah Hyun]
I'm sorry. I have work right now...
It's only three hours.
Fine. Triple pay.
I'm only paying this much because it's you.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it this time.
Sorry.
Darn it.
Ju Yi Jae.
Stuck on something?
Let me see.
"The distance between them slowly closes."
"Their eyes meet..."
"Their breaths mingle..."
What are you stuck on?
Obviously, they kiss.
This feels like the moment.
- Now?
- Yes, now.
Nan Young confessed...
It started with a simple contract.
She only meant to take off his glasses.
Moo Gyeom...
What...
What's wrong?
This is dangerous.
Way too dangerous.
Darn it.
Ju Yi Jae!
Where are you going?
[Moo Gyeom pulls her by the waist]
[Their breaths mingle...]
What are you stuck on?
Obviously, they kiss.
[Their breaths mingle. Then they...]
[Then they kiss...]
Don't get confused.
This is just the setup.
The setup.
[Yi Jae]
The phone is off.
You'll be connected to voicemail.
A charge will apply after the beep.
Yi Jae!
Ju Yi Jae!
Hello, Ju Yi Jae.
I'm Ian Woo.
Because it stays with you forever.
Yi Jae!
Ju Yi Jae!
This feels like the moment.
Yes.
Now.
[Then they kiss]
[Special thanks to Lee Sang Jin
for the special appearance]
You were always right there,
so my eyes kept going to you...
Go home.
I'm here, Soo Bin.
She looks like she'd ruin a man's life.
You meddle in my life so well.
Why run from your own?
Want to come?
Should I keep you company
or get drunk with you?
Get drunk.
If you want to see your son,
you need to heal fast.
If you meant to cut blood ties,
you should've gone farther.