I hear she lives alone in that run-down house.
Not scared of ghosts knocking at midnight?
What ghosts, though?
The short-lived wretch her mom stabbed.
Hey!
Little murderer.
You bumped into me.
Apologize to me, damn it.
The nerve of you, still eating here.
You've gone and dirtied the stool.
Exactly.
Why are so many dogs barking today?
So noisy.
You...
Who are you calling a dog?
Boss, the usual.
Alright.
Sit.
Chen Baixi, mind your own business.
And if I don't, what then?
Li Yiran is family to us.
When it comes to family,
of course I'll step in.
You...
Forget it, forget it.
What bad luck.
Lately, I read a line in a book
that really made a lot of sense
A lion does not turn back at the barking of dogs
Just think about it
If a lion beats a pack of mad dogs,
is that glorious?
No, it's not
It's beneath its dignity
Thank you
Exactly
Yiran, have you ever heard a saying?
Life is a tragedy when seen in close-up,
but a comedy in long-shot.
It all depends on how you look at it.
Here
Grab a bun
Run!
Big bear! Big bear!
Let's go, hurry!
Run! Run! Run!
Run, run!
Yiran! Yiran!
Hello, Auntie Lan.
Hello.
Why'd you run off so fast?
I still wanted to say hi to you.
You scared me to death!
So the acting you studied in Beijing,
it was animal acting?
So? Did I look convincing?
Wasn't it super realistic?
Way too realistic!
You scared us both half to death.
She even took a tumble, you know.
I gotta say,
I really thought
this bear had escaped from the zoo.
It's so lifelike.
Are these teeth real or fake?
Feel them for yourself.
The tongue's even soft.
Oh my, it's got drool too!
So realistic!
It nipped my hand red, damn it!
Chen Xiaofang, are you nuts?
What kind of job is this you found?
Coming to the zoo to play an animal!
Well, my brother couldn't find anyone,
and your mom couldn't find work,
so you hit the jackpot.
What a coincidence, right?
Get lost.
Coincidence my ass.
You and your brother are both unreliable.
Blood is thicker than water, I guess.
Bro,
you've looked so miserable lately.
Is the zoo short on people?
I recently set up
a Cute Pet Paradise to make some money.
I wanted someone to dress up as a bear,
but nobody's willing to do it.
So I've had to do it myself.
It's stressful, exhausting, and miserable.
Then this is perfect!
I've got two unemployed talents right here.
Who?
My bestie and her mom.
You mean Li Yiran and Auntie Lan?
Exactly.
No, no, no.
This job's grueling,
and you have to play it convincingly.
How could those two ever pull this off?
Aren't you the acting master?
Just teach them, problem solved.
Come on, bro,
just help me out.
They can't find work,
you can't find anyone,
it's fate.
Fine, I'll give it a shot.
Auntie Lan, I never expected you to be this good.
What did I do to deserve this?
Getting to play a bear in this lifetime.
Fur Softener.
You spray this on, right?
Yeah, once you spray it,
the fur gets smoother.
I've got a question.
You said it's got drool,
so does it have tears too?
That, we don't have yet.
Didn't you study acting?
Are you the type
who can cry on command?
Let me tell you,
the second the director yells "three, two, one, action,"
my tears just come right out.
Really?
Really.
Then cry for me right now.
Right now?
Actually, we've got something else.
What's that?
If you can't cry,
you can use this.
What is it?
Don't keep me in suspense.
A tear stick
Whenever you can't cry
you just take this tear stick
and rub it under your eyelids
Rub it right here
just like a lip balm
Let me try it
Go ahead
So cold, so cold, so cold
On the eyelids
So cold, so cold
Then you keep your eyes open, staring at one spot
I can't, I can't
This feels awful
But this thing
It looks like lipstick, pretty cute actually
It's yours now
Really?
Really
You're so generous
Then I'll take it
Go on, take it
Thank you
You're welcome
Lend me this to play around with
You ready?
Yiran.
Jobs are hard to find these days.
You'll work alongside Auntie Lan for a while.
Once she settles in,
I'll have my brother keep an eye on her for you.
This job's simple and stable.
So you won't have to worry when you go back to Shanghai.
Simple.
Stable.
Yeah.
What are you doing? You scared me!
Why'd you hang up?
See? I'm the one who's good to you.
I'd never hang up on you.
Isn't it cute? Isn't it cute?
Cute my ass.
Take that head off right now.
I just wanted to get used to it early.
You don't need to get used to it.
Dressing as a bear to fool kids.
You can't do this job. Let's go.
Who says this is fooling kids?
How can you call this fooling anyone?
Our Here Comes Baby Bear program
is all about creating a dream for children.
We want kids to spend a magical, wonderful day
here in our paradise.
Right, Baixi?
Right.
Director Ding.
Yeah.
After hearing you describe this job,
I feel so excited!
Right?
It's so much fun!
This job is so sacred!
You just can't afford real animals, that's all.
Making it sound so noble.
You're deceiving your visitors, you know that?
Now, young lady,
you can't put it that way.
Think about it. If a real bear
interacted with kids, how dangerous would that be?
Besides,
feeding and caring for one costs money.
Our current income
isn't even enough to buy its feed.
That's really how it is.
When she was little, she ate and drank a ton,
and needed diapers too.
The little money I earned
was never enough for her.
Right?
Who asked you, Wu Huilan?
If you can't make comparisons, don't.
Why compare me to an animal?
So you see,
this brings joy to the kids,
brings in money for the park,
and pays your wages.
That's three birds with one stone!
Thanks, Director Ding.
But we won't be considering this job.
Give the stuff back to him.
Actually, this is a plan to save animals.
Save what animals?
Oh my god.
These animals are so pitiful!
Yeah.
The vast majority of animals here
are malnourished.
Some are sick, some are dying.
And nobody takes care of them?
The director only cares about making money.
Why would he care whether the animals live or die?
You mean that Director Ding just now?
That heartless devil, why won't he help?
The economy's been bad these past two years.
Tickets are ten yuan each,
and fewer than ten visitors come each day.
We've been losing money the whole time.
Large animals cost money in every way.
We can't even afford to keep them.
But you still can't just
stand by and watch
these animals wait to die!
Look at this tiger.
It's old,
and it's sick.
The director says treating it is pointless.
He plans to put it down.
That's just inhumane.
They want to euthanize it.
An animal's life is a life too.
Am I right or what?
So recently,
I made a Here Comes Baby Bear rescue plan.
I set up a new Cute Pet Paradise.
To draw kids in for a hands-on experience.
That way, once we make money,
we can buy them food,
and afford to treat them, too.
Another busybody sticking their nose in.
How is this being a busybody?
I don't think I'm meddling at all.
Now I get it.
You want us to dress up as bears,
really just to save them.
Right?
Exactly.
It's a last-ditch effort, that's all.
Save one if we can, one at a time.
Nobody's dying here!
A bad life is better than a good death.
We've got to live on properly.
And let them live on properly too.
Yiran and I are both caring people.
Aren't we?
She didn't say no, so that's a yes.
This job,
we'll take it.
That's really wonderful!
Auntie Lan,
base pay of four thousand,
plus a full benefits package.
Don't worry, I'll treat you both right.
When do we start?
Tomorrow. You can start tomorrow.
Before you officially start,
I'll give you training on animal performance.
Chen, you know me,
I'm a little out of touch these days,
but I'm not stupid.
I'm a quick learner too.
You teach it, I'll master it.
Alright.
Happy to work together.
From now on I'll call you Teacher Chen!
Sure thing, Auntie Lan.
Teacher Chen.
Auntie Lan.
This is a special feature all about bears.
In short,
playing an animal is really just acting.
Just like the performers at Disney.
Once you're in costume, from a distance,
nobody can tell who you are.
To become a true performer,
you must have conviction in your heart.
You must truly listen,
truly see,
truly feel.
Fully immerse yourself in the role.
Become a real animal.
Hypnotize yourself.
I'm a bear, I'm a bear.
I'm a bear.
I'm a big bear.
I'm a bear
Right?
Right
Come on, say it
The teacher told you to say it
You're a bear
You're a big brown bear
Teacher, I kind of want to laugh
You have to hold the belief in your heart
Okay
Teacher
Is there any real teaching coming up?
Are you just having us watch Animal World?
This is just the warm-up
Focus your attention
You need to settle down
Say it out loud
I'm a bear
I'm a bear, I'm a bear
I'm a big brown bear
Li Yiran and I are both big brown bears
Li Yiran
Do you really not remember me,
or are you just pretending?
Of course I remember you,
Miss Fan.
It really is you, Shiqi.
I thought it looked like you over there.
If you hadn't called out, I wouldn't have been sure.
Aren't you in Shanghai?
What, lost your job?
Come back to play a bear?
How do you know I'm in Shanghai?
Keeping such close tabs on me.
I...
I saw it by chance in our high school group chat.
But you don't seem to be in the group.
Right.
I came back on vacation.
Heading back at the end of the month.
And you?
Me?
Let me introduce myself properly.
I'm a director at Lecang TV.
Lately, the station's been working on
a program about the Return of Urban Youth.
I've been filming Chen Baixi for a while now.
No wonder.
No wonder you kept filming him with that camera.
Who would've thought.
Chen Baixi couldn't make it out there,
and now he's back as the star of your show.
Don't worry.
The fact that you played a bear,
I'll never breathe a word about it.
Well, thanks then,
old classmate.
I won't be needing this card.
I'm not coming back for good.
Let's begin today's lesson
Why did we set up here, you ask?
Because bears basically live in forests
Every animal is a living,
one-of-a-kind book
They have their own emotions, habits,
and instinctive needs
Just as complex as people
Bears, you know, sway their heads,
swing their paws, and roar
These are all their body language
So we must keep observing and imitating
Alright
Now let's start the horse stance
Come on
A bear's limbs, you see,
are very powerful
So we need to hold the horse stance
to strengthen our leg muscles
so our performance is more solid
Place your hands on both sides of your waist
Horse stance for three minutes
Is that Teacher Chen's girlfriend?
They make a pretty good couple, actually.
Oh boy.
Think they're in some romance drama.
You... you okay?
I'm fine.
Is your foot okay?
My foot's fine too.
You know what, though...
That girl's at least 1.7 meters.
Their heights match up well.
If you'd eaten more as a kid,
you'd be way taller now, you know?
Can you move over a bit?
My legs are so sore.
Just leaning on you a bit.
Let me lean here a sec.
Horse stance!
It's all about the core.
Deep breath.
Exhale.
These three minutes are way too long.
The three minutes are almost up.
Just hold on a bit longer.
Deep breath.
Exhale.
After a week of training,
you can officially start on the job.
Starting today,
Auntie Lan, you're Bear One.
Yiran, you're Bear Two.
There's a walkie-talkie inside the head.
If there's any issue, talk to me directly.
Try to move as little as possible.
Got it.
That way you won't blow the cover.
If you move, make it look real.
I want you both to be good performers.
Always remember:
Truly listen, truly see,
truly feel.
Enjoy the performance.
Don't worry, Teacher Chen.
You got this!
Bear Two.
Why is this zoo so boring?
There's not a single person here.
Come on, say something to me, Yiran.
This Bear Two has such a bad temper.
Auntie Lan, bears don't put their paws behind their backs.
Let's be a bit more professional.
Just because you've never seen a bear do it
doesn't mean a bear can't do it.
This bear of mine,
it's just really bored.
It just wants to put its paws behind its back.
Didn't you tell me
to truly listen, truly see, truly feel?
Well, right now what I feel is,
it wants to put its paws behind its back.
Yiran, don't just stand there frozen!
Didn't you tell me to move less?
I'm dying of heat.
Give me a sip.
Go buy your own.
Just one sip.
Yiran, the visitors will be here any minute.
Hurry up and put the head on.
I can't take it.
I need to pee.
Well, who told you to drink so much just now?
Hurry up and get the head on right.
The visitors are almost here.
Hurry, put the head on!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Come on, sweetie, look at the bears
Look
These bears even have manners
Life's so comfortable these days
Even the bears have gotten lazy
Exactly
Yiran, lift your head, look at them
Do a roll
You roll if you want to
Come on, move a little!
People finally showed up
I've got to put on a good show
Wu Huilan, do you have to be this awful?
Don't touch me
I told you not to touch me, Wu Huilan
Mommy, I want to see the bears
Look at that bear.
Look.
Go dance! Go dance!
I'm not dancing, Wu Huilan.
Don't touch me! You're driving me nuts.
Get up, damn it.
Do your duty while you're here.
You got that?
I'm sick of it, dressing up as a bear.
I really can't take this anymore.
It's okay.
It's okay, Li Yiran.
Looks like Wu Huilan's adjusting just fine.
I'll be shedding this bear suit soon.
And heading back to Shanghai.
Come on!
Dance already!
Hey
Bear One, Bear Two, don't overdo it
Or you'll blow the cover later
Just let loose and go all out
Don't be scared
I'll take responsibility for anything that happens
Alright
Is what they're doing right?
You taught them
Me?
Did I teach them?
Bear One, Bear Two, you're gonna blow the cover
You're gonna blow the cover!
Teacher Chen, don't worry
I'm acting so well
There's no way we'll blow the cover
Lately, thanks to everyone's hard work
Our ticket sales have tripled
We've gotta ride this wave of traffic
And take it to the next level
It wasn't easy
You've all worked so hard
Yeah
This big bear is really hard to play
After playing this
My head hurts, my neck hurts, my shoulders hurt
My back, butt, legs, and feet all hurt
There's not a spot on me that doesn't hurt
Director Ding
How about giving us a little raise?
The raise thing is a separate matter
Can you make us permanent soon?
Don't be in such a rush now
I promise you, by the end of the month
Raises and permanent positions
How's that?
Then
You'd better keep your word
I... I swear on the moon
Really
Alright, hurry up and clock out
The exhaustion's on you
But the pain's in my heart
Thanks, Director Ding
Rest up, rest up
Oh my god
My poor old back
I can't take it
There's no moon at all
And he swears on the moon
Tell me, is he lying to us?
Son of a bitch
Come on, we're off work
Let's go
In a sec
Just wait for me
Who threw an apple in here?
Wouldn't it be nicer if he threw some money in every day?
Get promoted and rich
Healthy and happy
Ace your studies
Wish for a child, get one
Find love right away
Getting rich! Getting rich! Getting rich!
Make a wish to the bears
It really works!
Come toss in your coins
Wealth from all sides! Wealth from all sides! Wealth from all sides!
Money, money, money!
I'm gonna be rich!
Rolling in cash!
Come to me, money!
Rich, I'm getting rich!
Rolling in cash!
Mine, mine, all my money!
It's all my money!
Wu Huilan!
Get back here!
My money, my money!
This Wu Huilan...
Does she not want her job anymore?
I'm a rich lady!
I'm loaded, I'm a filthy-rich lady!
Wu Huilan, if someone sees, we'll blow the cover!
None of your damn business!
Get the hell out of my way, damn it!
If you've got something to say, just say it.
You've been glaring at me the whole way.
What's that supposed to mean?
Wu Huilan, can't you take your job seriously?
Stop always looking for shortcuts.
Let me ask you something.
How exactly did I cut corners?
Oh, you didn't cut any corners?
Then what's this big bag jangling around?
It's money!
Money?
Where'd the money come from?
The kids like me.
They tossed me some coins.
No, they didn't.
You're just jealous of me.
Do you know, here in Lecang,
making 4,000 a month
with a full benefits package,
that's a rare thing.
Can't you put a little effort in?
I put plenty of effort into my work.
I work really hard too.
What are you getting at?
I get it now.
You want to go back to Shanghai.
If you want to go back, just say so.
No need to throw a fit at me here.
Yeah, yeah, I want to go back to Shanghai.
I couldn't care less about you.
I only bother because I'm too free.
I can control the wind
East Wind
Seven of Bamboo
Big win
Play it!
Today, at the West Gate Cute Pet Paradise
a people-in-bear-suits incident occurred
The heavily promoted Here Comes Baby Bear show
had its cover blown by the two performers
causing panic and chaos on the scene
The sudden exposure of the truth
made the visitors feel deceived
and highly agitated
Many parents who'd brought their kids
Mom
Sister Lan is on TV!
which threw the scene into chaos
This incident
on the visitors' experience and safety
Come quick, look!
had an extremely negative impact
It really does look like Huilan and Yiran
What's going on?
And they're even fighting!
Did they cross someone or what?
Run!
Run, run!
Hurry, run!
Here Comes Baby Bear
This project has totally taken off now.
Baixi, you're the top contributor here.
And our two stars, Bear One and Bear Two.
They're viral animal celebrities!
Seriously.
So I've decided.
Tomorrow I'm making you permanent, with a raise.
Really?
Thank you, Director Ding.
Come on, give her a hand, will you?
Keep up the good work, everyone.
Meeting's over.
Okay.
So get yourselves ready.
Director Ding.
Come on, come on, come on!
We're getting made permanent!
Tomorrow we go permanent!
You get that?
Wu Huilan, listen to me.
You behave yourself today.
Don't cause any trouble for me.
I know.
I've eaten more salt
than the roads you've walked.
I don't need you to tell me that.
Come on, let's get to work.
I'll go get you some more coins
Turning down easy money?
Wouldn't that be stupid?
Don't you go
Don't pick it up
Don't pick it up, don't, don't
Get lost!
Don't get in the way of me grabbing this cash
Not bad, right?
Sure, we'll talk when you get back.
Protecting the forest is every bear's duty!
Watch out!
Son!
Kid!
Son, are you okay? Son!
Son!
Kid, are you okay?
Wait, wait!
Don't touch my son!
You, you, you...
Let him go!
Kid!
Little one! Little one!
Help me!
Save my son!
Son!
Save him!
Little one, wake up!
Wake up!
Wu Huilan, what are you doing?
The bear is fake!
It's a person!
She's a con artist!
Con artist!
Teacher Chen!
Run! Run!
Con artist!
Don't hit her!
Don't rush forward!
Don't come forward!
Don't hit her!
Don't do anything rash!
Calm down! Calm down!
Everybody calm down!
Don't hit her!
Run! Run!
Run, run, run!
Con artist! Don't let her get away!
Go grab her!
Son, wake up! Don't scare me!
Con artist!
I'm saving people!
Get her!
I'm not a con artist!
I'm saving people!
Con artist! We'll beat you to death!
You con artist!
I'm not a con artist!
I'm saving people!
You con artist! You con artist!
I'm not!
You took my money!
I'm saving people!
You con artist!
You scared the kid half to death!
Con artist!
Run!
Run! Run!
Wait, how is it you?
Where's Wu Huilan?
You just grabbed me and ran!
I called you but you wouldn't stop!
No way, I have to go save her!
No, no, no!
We can barely save ourselves!
Let's just save ourselves!
They're over there!
Get them!
Run! Run!
You con artist!
Con artist!
We'll smash you dead!
You con artist!
You tricked us!
We'll beat you to death!
I was trying to save someone!
This... this... this...
I can't do this, I can't
I just can't do it
Li Yiran
You're really taking this easy, huh?
Still able to laugh at a time like this.
I just remembered
something Xiaofang said back in high school.
She said
life is a tragedy when seen in close-up,
but in long-shot, it's actually a comedy.
Looks like today's all tragedy to me.
Now I'm starting to get another layer of it.
Life is just a joke.
This kind of experience today,
that's what truly listening, truly seeing,
and truly feeling is.
You've said that a hundred times.
Just run, come on!
When they get here, they'll really beat us up.
See, I told you.
Today's all tragedy,
no comedy at all.
They're over there!
Run! Run!
Grab them!
After them!
Stop right there!
Stop! Stop!
Me, me!
I'm saving someone here!
I'm exhausted!
Master Chen
There's one more thing I need to ask of you
No problem at all, no problem