Is there no honorable man within our forces?
Yang Zhi, the Blue-faced Beast.
Now that is a good tale.
I must decline.
I do not wish to associate
with Liangshan Marsh any further.
Why do something so foolish?
To help you escape, An Dao Quan.
I would never lose.
I, Lin Chong the Panther Head,
will now be breaking free!
You will have Zhu Gui repay the favor
by allowing us to see Wang Lun?
I will take you to my comrades!
This invisible enemy
is aware of our presence.
Lin Chong has returned.
[Wanted: Lin Chong]
[Episode 4]
You have done well to return to us.
- Now eat your fill.
- I shall.
Posters of you cover the village boards.
I see I am now wanted across the nation.
How is Bai Sheng?
Wu Yong is looking after him.
Lin Chong, you are just as battered.
You must first worry about yourself, no?
Food has cured me of my ailments.
Is that so?
Now, how shall we acquire the fortress
within Liangshan Marsh?
My plan remains unchanged.
It is an impregnable castle.
We cannot charge in with a frontal assault.
I do not wish to lose an ally
over a reckless battle.
That is how I feel.
Sir Song Jiang, give the order,
and I shall sneak in.
Lin Chong...
Do not worry for me.
As I rest...
I am only haunted by the past.
I heard of Zhang Lan's fate.
Love does not need a reason, my dear.
Lin Chong.
Do you wish to die?
I cannot die.
You have finally returned.
I will not send you to your death again.
I shall be fine, sir.
Say, who is this?
That is Xue Yong.
[Xue Yong, Apothecary]
He concocts effective medicines.
Almost none can match his skills.
A renowned doctor and apothecary?
What a pair.
- What are you doing?
- Your treatment requires a do-over.
Even spit would prove more effective
than this "salve".
Where did you find this man?
I sent Lu Zhi Shen to him.
He carried my message across the land.
Xue Yong is the best ally I could ask for.
We will cure many illnesses together.
Lu Zhi Shen.
A man who, for one reason or another,
excels at running into capable men,
and ultimately enamors them.
You wield a good sword there.
You can tell,
without me unsheathing the sword?
Just as I can tell
a person's status from their garbs.
The might of your blade
is obvious from a glance.
The Splitting Hairs Blade.
It is an ancestral sword of mine.
Yet you stare at a noble blade
with much sadness. Why?
What is with this report?
I have merely written the truth, sir.
"Bandits"!
We did not execute "villagers" in that town.
We executed "bandits". Understand?
Write!
Write, and bring your revisions here!
Executing innocent villagers,
under the guise of killing bandits.
Gao Qiu has gone mad.
He is venting his frustrations
after failing to assassinate Lin Chong.
He has yet to be found?
Yes. We must simply continue our search.
The strongest spearman now roams free,
while we are left with a foolish general.
Nothing is more frightening
than a fool with power.
It makes their next moves unpredictable.
Agreed.
Shall we kill him?
We must not be suspected of treason.
Then what to do?
We shall simply allow him
to kick his ball as he pleases.
Why are you so stubborn?
I fight the battles I am ordered to.
That is the duty of a soldier.
I need not consider anything else.
You have the talent to command an army.
You are no ordinary foot soldier.
How can you tell? We have only just met.
I have spoken to many men in my life.
I can tell these things.
Is this not true, ancestor of Yang Ye?
Indeed. I now carry the will of my ancestors.
I report all wrongdoings
to the Imperial Guard, and...
Hah! Gao Qiu will cover up any such reports.
How do you know of the inner workings
of the Imperial Guard?
I am a wandering monk.
Rumors make their way to my ears.
I had heard of a suspicious, bald monk,
who hoped to throw our country into disarray.
Most bald folk are suspicious.
You cannot suspect us all.
Who are these "men" you have met with?
One was a man named Wang Jin.
Another, Lin Chong.
They are both criminals.
The real criminals are the Imperial Guard.
What?
Gao Qiu ordered a strike
on a tribe of bandits.
Did you hear of this?
Of course.
It was an ordinary village
that Gao Qiu had attacked.
There were no bandits in sight.
I hear they took the heads
of several hundred thieves.
No. He slaughtered innocent citizens.
Gao Qiu, failing to catch any bandits,
killed ordinary folk
to embellish his accomplishments.
That cannot be.
Would you have taken part in the slaughter?
You, a soldier who merely follows orders.
This is why our people suffer.
Our soldiers fight,
without thinking for themselves.
This country ought to...
Apologies. I got a little heated.
Here, have a drink.
I must decline.
You make this alcohol taste bitter.
There are two reasons
why alcohol would taste bitter.
One, is that your body cries for help.
The other, is that your heart cries for help.
You say this "Yang Zhi"
is more than a spoiled coward?
I believe so.
He commands ten men
like an army of a hundred,
and a hundred men like an army of ten.
If we allowed him an army of 10,000,
what would he be capable of?
That is what Lu Zhi Shen writes.
What is it, my friend?
I want this man for ourselves.
Once we have acquired our fortress,
we will need a general to command an army.
But I believe Yang Zhi will not fold easily.
Though that is another fine trait of his.
He will find his way here.
All who feel betrayed by the Imperial Guard
will eventually wash up to our shores.
We must acquire that fortress
as soon as possible.
I've got a catch!
After we acquire the fortress,
we shall gather an army.
We will have men like Yang Zhi
and Lin Chong be our generals,
and best this country, once and for all.
Sounds like a fine dream.
It is no dream. It is our end goal.
This is a big one.
Sir Song Jiang.
- Yes?
- Where are we headed?
It shall be a surprise.
Yes, sir.
Is that a delicious fish?
Depends on the cook.
Her fever persists, and she is in pain.
We cannot even converse any more.
My wife, Chen Li, will die!
Quiet.
I am listening to her breathing.
Zhu Gui.
This man is the best doctor in the country.
Let us leave the rest to him.
Yes.
You can save her, right?
Her fever will die down.
Xue Yong's medicine should take effect soon.
What?
Her fever is already less severe.
Call out to her.
Chen Li.
My wife can speak again.
Thank you for curing her.
I have not cured her.
I have only suppressed her fever and pain.
She will likely manage to sit up as well.
However, as time passes,
her fever will return.
Though it is no trouble to quell her fever,
she has a persisting sickness
in her bloodstream.
A sickness, in her blood?
There is currently no cure for such illness.
Then Chen Li...
Will my wife suffer again?
No. I can abate her pain
until her final moments.
An Dao Quan.
Can you give this couple the time they need
to converse and walk together,
to smile and dine together,
like any other husband and wife?
Yes, I can.
Zhu Gui.
How do you wish to spend your time
with your wife?
I advise you to consider this carefully.
Ma Gui and Shi Qian have sent their reports.
It seems the Imperial Guard
has layers to their command.
Intriguing. Tell me more.
The emperor lies at the head of this nation.
Yet he has no hand,
nor interest in political affairs.
The one who truly rules this country,
is the chancellor known as Cai Jing,
and the Imperial Guard,
which controls our militia.
In other words, Marshal Tong Guan.
This is all nothing new.
And yet true power lies elsewhere.
What?
To these men, their greatest obstacle
is General Gao Qiu, of the Imperial Guard.
Though he is an incompetent man,
he excels at playing ball,
and currying the Emperor's favor.
Officially,
his position is below that of Tong Guan.
Even so, he holds power,
as he is close to the Emperor.
There is always a man like Gao Qiu
behind the downfall of a country.
Most officials choose to obey Gao Qiu.
Yet Cai Jing has a group of officials
who are at his command as well.
This is the group I find to be suspicious.
I had a spy tail one of these men.
Only for this spy to commit suicide
the following day.
Of course, he had no reason to die.
So I sent another spy,
for him to ultimately meet the same fate.
The official I had them tail, was named...
Li Fu.
The man Lin Chong suspected.
Indeed.
Li Fu.
He killed two of my men,
and covered it up as a suicide.
He is no ordinary civil servant.
Then he is part of an organization.
What else do you know?
I did not have Ma Gui
investigate any further.
Song Jiang.
Ma Gui's husband died for your sake.
Do you keep her as a retainer out of pity?
I know, Chao Gai.
I will have Ma Gui retire in the coming days.
If we are against
an intelligence organization of sorts,
they will be more troublesome
than the Imperial Guard.
Do you have some plan to combat this?
We shall organize the Zhishi Squadron.
The Zhishi Squadron?
The covert squad utilized by the Wu Dynasty
of the Three Kingdoms,
to overcome all obstacles,
and sneak behind enemy camps?
Yes. They will infiltrate the enemy base,
and attack from within.
It is not an army,
reliant on the strength of one man.
But a unit, that works in harmony.
Yes, we shall revive their legend once more.
They will prove useful
in smuggling salt as well.
Song Jiang.
Do you know a man
who could lead such a covert group?
A man who is not flashy, but discreet.
Who is strong, and has fresh ideas.
A man who can operate in secrecy, perhaps?
Yes. That, exactly.
What a strange coincidence indeed.
What is this?
It is the last correspondence from Yan Xin.
I had him searching for kindred spirits,
when he found a man
by the name of "Gongsun Sheng".
He is a master of disguise,
who has honed all five of his senses.
I believe he could lead a covert unit
like the Zhishi Squadron.
However, there is just one problem.
What it is? Keep no secrets, Song Jiang.
He, too, is imprisoned.
He has been locked up for two years now.
Another jailbreak, is it?
All the capable men in this country
are either imprisoned, or killed.
I will bring to you...
this so-called master of disguise.
Yan Xin.
Even after death, you continue to aid me.
Watching them, it feels as though
they will manage to walk on forever.
Indeed, it does.
Unfortunately,
we have only given her
a higher dose of medicine today.
Chen Li insisted.
The consequence being,
she will be bedridden tomorrow.
I don't think she minds.
So long as she can have this moment.
Po Xi.
Can you assist in caring for Chen Li?
I believe she will feel relieved
having a fellow woman at her side.
I suppose she would.
Yes, I shall assist her.
The fortress at Liangshan Marsh, is it?
Song Jiang, I see you are no ordinary clerk.
You wish to use my connections
to seize that very fortress.
Zhu Gui...
There lives a monster within that fortress.
A monster, known as "authority".
No matter what noble ambitions
an individual may have,
that monster will infect you with greed.
Like it did to Wang Lun.
I will not fall trap to this monster.
Zhu Gui, I am...
It seems I cannot stop you, no?
I understand.
I will make the necessary preparations.
I was dreaming, dear.
What occurred in your dream?
Strangely enough,
I was witnessing this exact view,
where you all were at my side when I awoke.
Perhaps I am still dreaming?
No.
Chen Li, this is no dream.
I long for my family.
Your family?
I have a father, Song Ying,
and a younger brother, Song Qing.
Watching Zhu Gui and his wife today
had me ponder happiness once more.
Do you ever miss your father?
Sometimes.
I see.
Your father, Yan Xin,
was an incredibly capable man.
And now you and your mother
both work as my subordinates.
I owe quite a bit to your family.
What sort of work does my mother do for you?
Po Xi.
Leave us.
- Mother?
- Po Xi.
Yes, Mother.
Sir Song Jiang.
Why have you removed me as your spy?
Since the day my husband passed,
I have taken up his mantle as your spy.
Ma Gui.
Listen well.
These missions are to become quite perilous.
As Po Xi's mother,
I cannot endanger you any further.
I want you to find happiness,
as any ordinary woman would.
An ordinary woman?
After the death of my parents as a child,
I was raised to be a spy.
You think I can become an "ordinary" woman?
I do not know how else to live my life.
Ma Gui.
Dark in here, is it not?
You must be Gongsun Sheng.
Tell me, have you injured your eyes?
I apologize for greeting you
with my eyes shut.
They are still sensitive,
as I had been deprived of any light
for two years now.
I hope to recover my sight by moonlight.
Your long trial has now come to an end.
Chao Gai.
[Gongsun Sheng, Former Prisoner]
Why have you rescued me?
You excel in stealth, or so I hear.
As such, we hope
you will lead a particular unit for us.
What sort of unit, if I may ask?
A covert unit, the Zhishi Squadron.
Do tell me more.
Even we do not know what lies ahead.
Please, travel with utmost caution.
Yes, sir.
Wang Lun took that fortress as his home
as he, too, held grievances
towards this nation.
His goals were once the same as ours.
Yet some say he has regressed
to a common bandit.
I shall seek the truth behind his ambitions.
We will maintain communications
through Xue Yong.
Though your conversations
may be monitored within,
Xue Yong can leave the fortress
under the guise of foraging herbs.
He is a reassuring ally to have.
Song Jiang, Chao Gai.
We shall briefly part ways here.
We shall set off.
Zhu Gui.
Do you not feel an immense sorrow?
You must be referring to Chen Li's fate.
I...
No, we are happy now.
I was once determined to stay far away
from the love between a man and woman.
Even so...
When I see you and your wife,
my determination wavers.
It seems I had misunderstood you, Lin Chong.
I once assumed the Panther Head
knew only aggression in his heart.
Chao Gai.
If I one day fall to greed,
and become a mere bandit,
I ask that you strike me down.
Of course.
I ask that you do the same,
if I begin walking a similar path.
We are almost there.
Zhu Gui, thank you for your guidance.
No, I must thank you, Lin Chong.
You are the reason Chen Li smiles again.
I wish you luck.
Take care.
You worry for me?
If you do not return alive,
Song Jiang will mourn.
Come, I will escort you to our fortress.
Let us set off.
We shall take your spear.
- My spear?
- It is the law here.
Your sword as well.
Enter.
[Du Qian, Second in command]
[Song Wan, Third in command]
Lin Chong.
An Dao Quan.
Xue Yong.
I am Wang Lun.
[Wang Lun, Leader of Liangshan Marsh]
The leader of Liangshan Marsh.
Lin Chong.
There are plenty here
who boast their spearmanship.
How about a spar, as a show of greeting?
My apprentices would love to test themselves.
What do you say, Lin Chong?
Fine. Then may I have a pole?
Lin Chong.
This is not the Imperial Guard.
You shall spar with a spear.
I do not wish to kill as a greeting.
Your men must stay alive.
Are you frightened, Lin Chong?
Master Hong.
Look at how the Imperial Guard has fallen.
You are being disrespectful.
My apologies.
He had simply been stunned silent,
I felt it necessary to fill the air.
Fine.
I shall take them all at once.
An Dao Quan.
I tried to keep their bones intact.
I would like a proper clinic.
If your men are so fragile,
I will need the space to treat them.
You truly are the greatest spearman
in the nation, Lin Chong.
Lin Chong.
How goes the clinic?
An Dao Quan and Xue Yong
are steadily furnishing it.
Once we have a clinic,
we need not fear any illnesses.
Indeed.
Some illnesses cannot be cured.
What?
Zhu Gui's wife, she is...
Ah, Zhu Gui's wife.
Does he wish to join our cause?
Du Qian.
Pardon my brazenness, sir.
Lin Chong, an envoy for the Imperial Guard
will be passing this area
in three days' time.
An envoy?
They are soldiers given special orders
to search for corrupt local officials
in exchange for bribery.
This makes the role a coveted one.
However, this envoy is not unlike the others.
They say he accepts no bribes.
I see.
What's more,
it seems he is aiming for this fortress.
Then my role is simple.
I will merely do away with him.
You must not kill the envoy.
What?
That envoy is a man named Yang Zhi,
descendant of Yang Ye.
Song Jiang hopes to recruit him to our cause.
Is he capable in battle?
So I hear.
He also wields the famous
"Splitting Hairs Blade".
So I must defeat this man,
without taking his life?
You ask for the impossible.
I am certain you can figure something out.
That, I wonder.
You are in time.
A bandit?
No. I am merely a spearman,
here to test my skills.
You look to be quite skilled yourself.
I am known as Yang Zhi.
You wish to duel, knowing I am an envoy?
Yang Zhi, the Blue-faced Beast.
That is right.
Then is that the Splitting Hairs Blade?
You are aware of my blade?
Though spears are my specialty,
I do not mind dueling with a sword.
Let us each wield whatever we please.
Do not kill him, Lin Chong.
Neither man must die.
Why keep your Splitting Hairs Blade sheathed?
My Splitting Hairs Blade is a noble sword,
used to protect our nation.
I would never taint it with a bandit's blood.
Lin Chong is amazing.
Don't you agree, Du Qian?
Indeed.
I do not wish for either man to die.
They fight an honorable duel.
That is a dangerous thought to have.
The duel is over.
Lin Chong!
Why do you hesitate?
Because I do not wish to kill you.
That is what our duel has proven.
Did you have someone aiding you?
No. I simply hoped to see more of your sword.
That is all.
No, it cannot be...
Are you Lin Chong?
I wonder.
Your spearmanship speaks for itself.
Believe what you wish.
Kill me!
Do not test me, Yang Zhi!
Why use such an honorable blade
for the Imperial Guard,
and not for our people?
I am but a mere foot soldier.
If I am ordered to fight, I fight.
If I suffer defeat, then I perish.
That is all.
Does our imperial court now
warrant such fighting?
Our imperial court,
that is practically manipulated by Gao Qiu?
Defect, like I have.
Leave, and you will find your path!
Enough!
Pierce my chest with that spear of yours!
I will not wield my spear in such a manner.
Return to the Imperial Guard,
and take a good look at your masters.
If then, you still wish to die at my spear,
return here, where we stand.
He won the duel, and chased off the envoy.
Why spare him, Lin Chong?
Is he a dog of the Imperial Guard?
Splendid battling, Lin Chong.
But why did you not
deliver the finishing blow?
It would be a waste
to lose a commander of his caliber.
I see.
Tonight, we will celebrate.
Those in the Imperial Guard
acknowledged your superiority
as an ancestor of Yang Ye.
Yet you spent your time
aimlessly wandering the nation.
I surveyed our lands thoroughly, sir.
Did you enjoy your rendezvous
with those bandits?
I did no such thing!
You have proven your incompetence
despite being an envoy of my army.
We do not need men like you
in the Imperial Guard.
Prove yourself useful in the Qingzhou army.
As you wish, General.
Stand down!
I will not wield my spear in such a manner.
Return to the Imperial Guard,
and take a good look at your masters.
Men, prepare your cups!
To Lin Chong's victory. Cheers!
Cheers.
Drink up!
Bring the alcohol and food!
Tonight, we drink till dawn.
Bring the alcohol in troves!
Lin Chong!
Lin Chong! Are you alright?
Show me your tenacity.
A tiger-slaying hero
has practically fallen.
I cannot betray my country.
My ancestry prevents me from doing so.
You must know quite the tactician.
This will not end lightly for you.
Kill him.
Do you fear Wang Lun's scrutiny?
What I fear is suspecting my fellow men.
4,000 soldiers
have been deployed from Beijing.
They are after your neck, Sir Chao Gai.
You will be killed.
There is no gamble I cannot win.
Song Jiang.
Believe in me!
[Episode 4 - FIN]