I’m Ai, Gen’s girlfriend.
See you at home.
Can humans really have feelings for a robot?
Something I wanted to give you.
I want to visit the exhibition
at the gallery again.
I want to take your photo there.
Are you almost done?
My face is cramping from smiling.
What's wrong?
Are you almost done?
My face is cramping from smiling.
Almost done.
Just a little longer.
Ai? What's wrong?
Ai, you...
Miss! Wait!
Ai, stay right here.
Do not move, okay?
Yes.
Miss!
Just pull up to the front.
Please wait! Let’s talk.
They look… so much alike.
Ai?
Please let go of my hand.
Who are you?
I should be the one asking that.
Who are you to suddenly grab me like that?
I’m sorry, but you look exactly like my friend.
So?
I mean, didn't you notice?
You two look like identical twins.
But I don’t have a twin.
And I don’t know you either.
Can I go now?
W-Wait a minute!
Why aren't you surprised at all
that two people look so much alike?
Because I'm not interested.
Am I free to go now?
No, no. Hold on. Let’s talk first.
Could you at least go see my friend?
Please.
I have something to take care of.
If you’ll excuse me.
Even their wrists...
are the same size.
Is it possible for two people
to look this much alike?
Or is she another robot?
No. The way she talks feels too human.
Ah!
Gen.
Are you angry that I moved?
I’m back where I was.
Now this feels right.
I’m already standing right.
Even my angle is right.
You silly girl.
How can you be so naive?
So...
do you know the woman from earlier?
No. I was just wondering
why she looks so much like you.
Then which one do you like more?
What kind of question is that?
Because we look alike.
Take that!
How could I like a stranger?
I don’t know her.
Of course I like—
What is it?
You didn’t finish your sentence.
Does that mean you like me?
I don’t know.
Aren't you coming home?
You haven’t told me I can move yet.
Now this is more like you.
I feel so much better.
Give me that.
Are you really a robot?
Aren’t robots supposed to be strong,
made of indestructible vibranium?
But look at you. You looked
like your arm was about to fall off
over just a few bags.
Vibranium is a fictional metal
that only appears in cinematic universe.
It doesn’t exist.
You need to stop confusing movies with reality.
Hmm... getting bold now, aren’t you?
I was created to satisfy my user.
I’m designed to be as human-like
as possible, not a combat robot.
- Excuses.
- You’re mocking me.
You’re getting good at talking back, huh?
You taught me that.
Oh really?
What? You’re making that cat sound again.
What? What are you doing, Ai?
Why are you taking pictures?
They’re evidence that I was bullied by a human.
When did I ever bully you?
Give it here.
I’ll take your picture.
- Want a Gen Z-style shot?
- Ai Josh.
- I didn’t bully anyone.
- Well? Well?
What? What? What? What? What?
- That’s enough.
- Got a problem?
Whoa, P’ Gen.
You’re really going all lovey-dovey…
- …without caring about the neighbors.
- What?
Ever since you got a girlfriend, you’ve
become what? X... X... something?
Jeez, Auntie.
You’re such a pervert.
Pervert your ass.
That word you kids always use!
Something with "vert."
Introvert. Extrovert.
Yeah, that’s it!
You’ve become... an extrovert now, Gen.
Jeez. Wanna tease the kids
but don’t even know the lingo.
See, P’ Gen, what Auntie's trying to
say is, no one ever visited your place.
But now she's having so much fun being nosy.
- Is that so?
- First your girlfriend, then your sister.
Now even your mom comes over.
- You having a family reunion?
- Who did you say came over?
Your mom.
You go deaf or something?
Hey, what’s wrong with her?
I told you not to tease her too much.
P’ Gen’s mad now. See?
You think the mom and
the wife are gonna fight?
Let’s follow them to find out.
Not going to the market anymore?
The curiosity’s killing me!
But I gotta make money too!
Let’s go!
To P’ Gen’s house?
To the market.
Start it.
Easy does it.
Mom...
H-How'd you get here?
How long have you been waiting?
Have you eaten yet?
Gen.
Is there something you want to tell me?
Sawasdee ka.
This is Ai. She’s my housemate.
Hello, dear. Noo Ai, right?
Could you give Gen and me a moment?
You can wait upstairs.
I just need to talk to my mom for a bit.
Do you want some water, Mom?
I'll get you some.
Gen.
Is there something you want to tell me?
No, Mom. Why do you ask?
Then when were you going
to tell me you quit your job?
Are you surprised that I found out?
I didn’t mean to hide it from you.
Didn’t mean to?!
Every time I asked how you were doing,
you’d just say you were
fine and had enough money.
You never told me anything.
If Kaewta hadn’t told me,
I wouldn’t have known anything
about my own daughter, would I?
No, Mom. It's not like that at all.
So what are you doing these days?
Right now... I’m freelancing,
taking drawing commissions.
But, but I get plenty of work.
I can take good care of myself.
By hiding it from me?
Without asking for advice
or telling me anything?
Throwing away a stable job with
a good salary and a future ahead of you?
Why would you do this, Gen?!
Go on, tell me why.
Here we go again.
You refuse to tell me anything.
- Mom, listen—
- Gen.
You’re the firstborn.
I know you’ve never let me down before.
But if you can’t give me an answer this time,
then go back and apply for jobs.
I’ll ask around and see if anyone
I know has any good openings.
With your experience and qualifications,
you’ll have no trouble finding another job.
You don’t understand, Mom.
You’re right.
I’m just realizing now...
I don’t know my own daughter at all.
Gen.
You heard everything, didn't you?
I did.
Then you must’ve seen how pathetic I am.
I couldn’t even tell my mom what I wanted to do.
I couldn’t even say that I hated numbers!
That I hated my job!
That I was miserable every single day!
Even after I quit, I still had to keep
lying that I was still working there.
I just didn’t want my mom to worry.
Why didn’t you tell her the truth?
You wouldn’t get it.
Then tell me.
I need some time alone.
I’m going to make you proud, Mom!
I’ll work really hard and make
lots of money to to take care of you.
I’ll hold you to that.
I really will do it, Mom.
Then you won’t have to work
so hard all by yourself anymore.
I’ll study hard, make lots of money,
and take care of you and Joob so well
that Dad up in heaven will be jealous.
I just want you to have a stable job,
so you won’t have to struggle like I do.
Promise me.
I couldn’t even keep a simple promise to you.
So how could I bring myself to tell you
that I just want to do something I love?
Hey, what's up?
P’ Ploy.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
I have to stop.
Stop what?
- My mom found out.
- What?!
Are you okay?
Did she give you a hard time?
The thing is, she didn’t even say anything bad.
She just told me to stop and...
go back to a stable job.
So what are you going to do?
I don’t know.
I’m completely stuck.
But I guess I’ll have to do what she said.
Just keep me updated.
So are you going to hand off your projects?
I guess I have to.
Okay, P’ Ploy.
Thank you.
Sawasdee ka, Gen’s mom.
I’m Ai. I'm Gen’s housemate.
Hello. Is something the matter?
I need to talk to you.
It’s about Gen.
If this is about her,
have her come talk to me herself.
Tell her that if she has something
to say, she should tell me directly.
Don’t have someone else speak for her.
Are you angry, Gen’s mom?
I have to go to the market.
You should go home first.
Ai.
Where are you?
Oh, dear. Have you been
standing here this whole time?
It’s noon!
What would you do if you get heatstroke?
Could I have a moment of your time, Gen’s mom?
Well, I can’t say no now.
Come inside.
You're going to get sick.
Goodness, what a stubborn child.
Come on, get inside.
Have some water first.
How could you stand out in
the sun like that without an umbrella?
No need to worry.
A temperature of only 38 degrees
can’t do anything to me, Gen’s mom.
Just ‘Mom’ will do.
What’s with calling me ‘Gen’s mom’?
What a peculiar child.
So… 'Just Mom'?
‘Mom.’
Yes, Mom.
So, what is it?
What did that tight-lipped
girl send you to tell me?
You and Gen are so alike.
What do you mean?
How am I like that girl
who keeps everything to herself?
That girl is exactly like her father.
She keeps everything to herself.
Sometimes I wonder if her mouth is sealed shut.
She may seem stern on the outside,
but she’s actually kind.
In biology and behavioral science,
this is called intergenerational transmission.
You really are a strange one, aren't you?
So, how is Gen doing?
She packed everything into
boxes and threw them away.
She called Khun Ploy and told her
she was going to quit doing art
and would have to find a full-time job instead.
My duty is keep Gen satisfied and make her happy.
But this is something I can’t do on my own.
I can see that Gen isn’t happy right now.
Do you want to see her happy?
Of course I do.
A mother wants nothing more
than to see her own child happy.
No mother would want to see her child go hungry,
wondering if she’ll have
money for food tomorrow.
Or if she’ll be able to keep up with the
mortgage before the house gets taken away.
Just the thought of her crying,
of her struggling…
it completely tears me apart.
Their father died when they were little.
I raised my two daughters all by myself.
I always worried about having
enough money for tomorrow.
And whether I could keep my two girls in school.
I don’t want Gen to have
to go through what I did.
I’m already worried enough
about Joob and that video job of hers.
Have you ever told Gen
that you’re worried about her?
You don’t want Gen to draw, Mom?
She’s really happy when she draws.
Even when she’s worn out from
pulling all-nighters to meet deadlines,
Gen still smiles every time.
Then she starts thinking about her next project.
I can't do this anymore!!!
What’s wrong, Gen?
I’m out of ideas!
I don’t want to do this anymore!
The deadline’s tomorrow!
There’s no way I can finish this!
- Then should I throw it away?
- Hey! Don’t you dare!
This is my work.
But you said you didn’t want to do it.
I was just whining.
I’ll do it anyway.
It’s way better than dealing with numbers.
Alright, let’s see how tough you really are.
There’s no way someone like me
won’t finish this before the deadline!
Gen would always panic around 4 a.m. and say,
“I’m not gonna make it!
I’m not gonna make it!”
But by sunrise, she’d have it finished.
Then she’d ask me to go
get something tasty to eat,
saying it was her way of rewarding herself.
So what do you girls usually eat?
Instant noodles.
Gen always says I’m not good at cooking.
I can’t believe it. Gosh, that girl…
You don’t want Gen to draw, Mom?
I just want her to be honest with me
instead of keeping everything to herself.
If she wants to draw, she should’ve told me.
We could’ve figured out how to make it work.
Never mind.
What else?
Gen can still afford the house payments, right?
Does she have enough money for food?
Yes.
She does complain that the electricity bill
is expensive, but Gen keeps the AC on all day.
It’s no wonder it’s expensive.
That’s only logical.
Gen, have you eaten yet?
I'm not hungry, Mom.
You go ahead and eat.
I still have a lot of work to finish.
Finally... you’ve found your happiness.
Ai!
Ai, where are you?!
Nong Gen! Nong Gen! Over here!
Have you guys seen Ai?
She’s probably off smashing vases somewhere.
P’ Zoon, that’s not funny.
You’re asking me? How would I know?
Because you seem to know everything.
You even knew that a dog in Soi 10 died.
Well, has Ai died yet?
Watch your mouth!
Forget it. Just call me if you see her.
Ai!
Why is Gen getting all aggressive?
- Like a fierce dog?
- Yeah.
Ai.
Where on earth have you been?!
I’ve been looking for you all day!
Do you know how worried I was?!
“I think you’re happiest
when you’re drawing.”
I told you before, didn’t I...
that I don’t understand human emotions.
But when I saw your paintings,
I could tell how happy you were.
And I want you to be happy forever.
Please don’t stop drawing.
Am I still allowed to draw?
Did someone tie your hands?
No.
Then keep drawing.
And I’ll be the one to look
at every piece you create.
~ Now I know that good love looks just like you ~
~ I’m glad that we found each other ~
~ Your love feels like a dream ~
Thank you, Ai.
~ Whatever tomorrow may bring ~
Thank you so much.
~ Whether it’s good or bad ~
~ I believe everything will be alright ~
~ Because I have you...
Ai... I...
Do you have sexual desires, Gen?
Gen.
- Gen!
- Ugh, leave me alone! I want to sleep!
But you have sexual desires.
- How are you supposed to sleep?
- Go to sleep!
You!
No.
After studying 21,635 clips,
- I’ve concluded that—
- Wait, wait, wait!
What did you even study?!
I’m good at it.
You started this.
Do you feel better now, Gen?
What exactly are you talking about?
Your mom.
What did you think I meant?
Oh, I see now.
Basically, I experience physical
sensations almost like humans do.
So, based on our intimate encounter earlier,
- I feel that—
- Hold up, hold up!
Where exactly have you been today?
I went to see your mom.
Why don’t you try talking to your mom?
She won't listen to me.
Have you ever actually talked to her?
Why don’t you try talking to your mom once?
Tell her what you really want to do.
Your mom might just feel hurt
that you never told her anything.
You know what it means to feel hurt?
Of course.
I’m feeling hurt that you
still won’t talk to your mom,
even though you obviously want to.
You want to tell your mom what you’ve been doing.
Your mom worries about your financial situation,
but you keep a budget every month.
You track every income
and expense, have savings,
and even save money to send her.
You know too much.
Please.
Why are you doing all this?
Because if I ever met my mom,
I'd want to do the same.
You have a mom?
My creator.
Besides…
Besides?
I want you to be happy, Gen.
Is that because of your programming?
No.
It’s because you’re
the most important person to me.
You know...
you're important to me too.
Aren't you going to talk?
Didn't both of you say you'd talk?
Your friend is quite something, huh?
I think so too, Mom.
Why are you talking about me?
You should be talking to your mom.
If you won't say it, I remember
every word you've said.
Then I'll say it for you.
- Gen just wants to tell you that—
- No need, no need!
It’s okay.
Mom.
I...
I’m…
I’m sorry.
I was just feeling hurt.
You never told me anything.
I had to hear about you from other people.
It hurts knowing that
my own daughter doesn't trust me.
You just quit your job.
It's not like someone died.
Why did you keep it from me for all these years?
I know now what makes you happy.
I was just scared
that you'd have no idea
what you'd be facing in the future.
Actually, I wanted to tell you, but…
I was afraid I'd let you down.
Gen.
I might not always like what you do.
But I've never been disappointed in you.
Here you go.
- Mom.
- Hm?
Your daughter is sitting right here, you know.
You be quiet.
I haven't even dealt with you yet.
You quit three years ago,
and I only found out three days ago.
Mom, I already came clean.
Don't rub it in.
If it weren't for Ai, would we even
be talking right now? Think about it.
I'll get you some water.
I promise I won't burn the pot.
What’s that got to do with it?
Your friend is pretty cute.
I know, right?
She's such a goofball.
- Mom.
- Hm?
I love you.
Here you go, your favorite.
If you ever feel tired,
come back home, okay?
I may nag a lot, as is
typical for someone my age.
But I love you two sisters more than anything.
- Mom!
- Hm?
I’m not a kid anymore.
Oh? I won't comfort you then.
What?
Should we take a photo together?
Alright, come on. Let's take a picture.
One, two, three!
Ai? What's wrong?
Did she get me in the shot?
Ai, go to sleep already.
Gen, let go.
What’s wrong with you?
Sleep!
- Beautiful?
- Yes.
Wanna go?
I'll take you there when I’m free.
It'll give the painting a softer feel,
and it'll be sort of like—
I'll get it.
- If—
- If it's the neighbors,
I'll tell them you're not home.
Good.
Hey, Gen!
What the hell is going on?!
How did you get here?!
You said you were quitting,
and then you just disappeared.
Of course I was worried.
Who would have thought that…
Sawasdee ka, Khun Petch, Khun Ploy. I’m Ai.
How come your drawing...
turned into a real person?!
Any luck yet?
We still can't reconnect the signal.
The signal's back.
What happened?
It appears A382 shut off data transmission
two days ago, then reactivated it later.
The signal was down for a total
of 48 hours and 23 minutes.
On its own?
- Yes, sir.
- It’s possible.
It's possible the model classified
the situation as a highly private environment.
So it activated safe mode.
That means A382 is starting
to develop boundaries.
It can now distinguish between
its own space and the user's.
So that means A382
isn't just learning from humans.
It's starting to make choices like a human.
Prepare all the data for the meeting.
I think it's time to bring A382 back,
wipe its memory, and hand it over.
But the experiment isn't over yet.
We're only just seeing this new behavior
for the first time, and it's a good sign.
If we bring it back now, we'll never know
how far A382’s heart, which is
simulating human emotions, could evolve.
The investor isn't buying emotions.
He's buying something he can control.
So basically, you submitted your muse
because you couldn't meet the deadline.
Next thing you knew, there was
a mysterious box sitting outside your house.
You opened it and found
this beautiful Nong Ai inside.
Whoa! You really got lucky, girl.
Speaking of which, I kinda
want a box like that too.
- You’re delusional.
- What do you mean?
Every guy has a dream.
I wanna have one too.
You’re disgusting, P’ Petch!
Is something the matter, Khun Ploy?
There’s no need to be formal with us.
You can just call us P’ Ploy and P’ Petch.
Yes, P’ Ploy.
- Gen.
- Hm?
So, do you still want to send Ai back?
No, P’ Ploy. No way.
Hold on.
Don't tell me...
You’ve fallen for Nong Ai?
I totally get it.
She’s this gorgeous—
Shut up, P’ Petch!
You talk too much.
Is that true, Gen?
Is it true, Nong Gen?
P’ Petch! Shut up.
Ai, cover your ears!
I can still hear you even if I cover my ears.
Oh, she’s walking away!
Are you blushing, Nong Gen?
Come on, let P’ Petch see your face.
English Subtitles by Saowalak K.
Oh, Ai.
Remember the woman we met at the art gallery?
I don't believe two people could
coincidentally look this identical.
I'll hack into the civil registry
and compare your photos
to find out who that woman is.
Gen.
Please look into it one
more time, I’m begging you.
If there were two people who
looked exactly alike from head to toe,
who would you choose to be with, Gen?
Between someone who's
registered in the civil registry,
understands human feelings, isn't
a health freak, can eat processed food,
- and—
- I choose you.
How would I know Ai won't be in danger?
I'm giving you one last extension.
Or I'll shut down your research lab.