Sui.
Want to pick up where we left off that night?
Sorry.
You drank too much.
Rest up, okay?
Good night.
They were considering this one.
I see.
- Nothing beats a simple design.
- Hello.
- Hello there.
- Come on in.
- Don't wanna!
- Nice to meet you.
- Show them inside.
Right.
- Thanks for having us.
- Of course.
- Please, have a seat.
- Thank you.
- I wanna go home!
- Monou.
Could you grab drinks for them?
I need to take this call.
I'm on it.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you for calling.
Excuse me...
And cross. That's it.
All right.
Let me get to work.
- I'm sorry about him.
- No worries.
Shall we get started?
Surely not with him bothering you...
He's no bother at all.
First thing on the docket
would be the flooring we recommended.
Seeing as your child is still young...
All right, thank you again.
Thanks for the help.
No worries at all.
Mao's a real sucker for kids, isn't he?
I had no idea. I was so surprised.
He's not friendly,
so why do they all love him?
Kids can tell Mao's a nice guy.
I guess my kindness is too difficult
for kids to understand.
Your phone is ringing.
I'll call them back later.
It must be urgent.
I'll have to take this.
One step, two step...
- It was great talking with you.
- Likewise.
I apologize it took so long.
No, thank you for handling him.
Come on, we're leaving.
Don't wanna. I'm staying with big brother.
Thank you for your time today.
No, thank you.
You were very patient today.
Want a lollipop?
Thank you!
You like it?
- Yeah!
- I'm glad.
- But no eating it yet.
- Yeah, not with the wrapper.
What flavor is it?
- I think it's orange.
- Do you like orange?
- Yup!
- Awesome.
Want me to open that for you?
Your place lives up to all expectations, Mao.
Hey, no snooping around.
It's so stylish in here.
You're exaggerating.
I'm really not,
given the rooms of most single guys.
That's enough of that.
Here's to Monou joining our team at Idea.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Have you gotten used to the work yet?
Only thanks to you all.
You're also a quick learner, Monou.
The Hayase's already trust you
with their kitchen.
Knowing how to cater to every client's needs
has certainly been a learning experience.
A struggle our local chatterbox, Matsubara,
probably can't relate to.
Hey, it's only because I have my methods.
For example, check this out.
[Life Planning App]
A life planning app?
Doing this together
gets my clients to open up,
and acts as a great icebreaker.
You're actually giving legit advice for once.
If you doubt me, why not give it a shot?
Forcing that onto us isn't appropriate.
Aw, bummer.
I wanted to learn more about you.
I'll just direct my questions
toward Mao instead.
Mao isn't interested in your interrogation.
I don't mind.
Awesome.
Then here I go.
Question one. "Are you married?"
I know that's a "no," so onto question two.
Question two. "Do you want to get married?"
I guess.
Question three. "Do you have a partner?"
I don't.
Then that's a "no".
Question four. "Do you have anyone you like?"
I do.
What?
Those are the omelettes.
I'll grab them.
It's fine, it's your party.
I'd feel bad just sitting around.
- Then could you grab the plates?
- Sure.
It just split in half.
- Is it too hot?
- Nope.
Sorry to go without cleaning up.
Don't worry about it.
You two have last trains to catch.
We'll tidy up the rest.
Thank you.
- See you at work.
- See you.
Thanks for having us.
Sure.
Good night.
I'll get that.
Thanks.
No, thanks for helping out,
even though it was your party.
Don't worry about it.
I prefer to keep busy.
So...
Yeah?
How have things been?
Huh?
You know,
with Mr. Hirose and the presentation.
I'm editing my proposal
until I get a favorable response from him.
I see.
I figured this wouldn't be easy.
If anything, I appreciate the challenge
he's set out for me.
He was already pretty famous
by the time I was a student.
But he really is amazing, isn't he?
Yeah.
So you agree?
Huh?
No, it's just...
After speaking to someone you admire,
don't you find yourself falling for them?
Admiration and romance
are two different things.
They can sometimes overlap, right?
Maybe. Except, Mr. Hirose is married.
I know, but...
People like him have partners
who are on their equal footing.
You don't plan on dating anyone these days?
Nope.
Even if someone confessed their love to you?
Even then.
For now, I'd rather focus on
making do on my own.
That's the girl who's quitting.
Seriously? Was she fired?
Apparently.
Yikes. How'd that happen?
The person you have called
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the...
Please excuse the noise.
I'm sorry for inviting you out
when you're so busy.
Don't worry, I was getting hungry anyway.
Are you still being followed around?
Not for now.
I've also informed our boss about it.
That's great to hear.
Your lunch sets.
Thank you.
Looks delicious!
Monou.
I think you're a wonderful person.
What?
You even worry for me
and my circumstances.
But, well...
The thing is...
Yes?
What do you think of Mao?
Pardon?
Who do you think
is the person Mao loves?
I've only had eyes for Mao.
That's why, I...
I...
Mizuno.
I think you're perfect for Mao.
I plan to root for you all the way.
Thank you.
Are you looking for Imamura's past works?
Yes, but I'll find it myself.
It'll be faster if I help.
I got this covered, really.
You seem angry.
Sorry.
But I promise I'm fine.
Don't keep Mizuno waiting, okay?
She's relying on you to bring her home.
I'm worried about you too, Sui.
I appreciate the sentiment.
But that kindness of yours
can cause misunderstandings.
If someone out there has a crush on you,
they wouldn't want to see you
caring for me, either.
A stalker?
Is that girl okay?
She's already told Mr. Hoshina about it,
and Mao's walking her home, so she's safe.
Again with that bad habit of his? Jeez...
Huh?
If Mao ever sees someone in need,
his sense of justice gets the best of him.
I see.
Though, I suppose his upbringing is to blame,
so I can't admonish him too much about it.
His upbringing?
Yeah.
The reason why my family took in Mao,
was because of his father's
violent tendencies.
Auntie? Mao?
Dear, stop this.
Stop it!
Quit clinging, you nuisance!
Stop it, please!
- Damn you.
- Stop, stop...
That troublesome habit of his came to be
because he was unable to protect his mother.
As if a young child
could ever protect their parents.
You ready to go, Mizuno?
Yes. One moment.
[Blocked Caller]
- See you all tomorrow.
- See you.
See you guys.
Take care.
Mizuno?
Mao...
I...
I love you.
That was sudden.
But it's not.
I'm sure you've also noticed
my feelings for you.
I've always loved you.
Mao.
Will you protect me, as my boyfriend?
- Well...
- It's fine.
You don't need to answer me now.
Just please,
give it some proper thought.
All right, I will.
You don't need to walk me any farther.
I know you have places to be.
- But...
- See you tomorrow.
- Hey there.
- Welcome back.
Huh? You're back?
Yeah.
What about Nana?
She said she'd be fine,
so I came back to work overtime.
Wait.
You let her go home alone?
She insisted.
You didn't notice
something's been bothering her?
Damn it, I should've...
This isn't "kindness" on your part at all.
[Just Married]
Monou?
Hirose.
[Ruby on]
You...
Leave me alone!
Don't come any closer!
Please, leave me alone.
Stop!
[Uncle]
Hello?
Mao, where the hell are you right now?
I'm at the office.
Idiot, you didn't walk Mizuno home?
- Please wait right over here.
- Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yeah. It was only a slight sprain.
It looks worse than it actually is.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to get you hurt, too.
Don't apologize.
If you hadn't caught up,
it would have been worse.
Thank god you're safe.
Listen...
Nana, I really...
Mizuno.
Mao?
Mao!
I was terrified.
I was so, so scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I'm sorry I left you to fend for yourself.
Mizuno.
My answer is yes, I'll be your boyfriend.
What?
Good morning.
It was only a light sprain.
Thank goodness.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Did something happen yesterday?
Nana was almost assaulted on her way home.
What?
Mao swooped in to save her just in time.
The stalker was her ex,
who was finally arrested.
I see. That's great news.
Is it really?
Huh?
Those two are a couple now.
Want me to help later?
No, I'd like to do this on my own.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I didn't wish to eat alone tonight.
Life never quite works out
as planned, does it?
Not every family
can be blessed with children.