I came here to apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
I messed things up.
Don't be upset anymore.
I'll figure something out.
There's always a way, right?
You take care of yourselves.
I'm off.
I just got the notice.
This thing has blown up too much.
The higher-ups ordered us to close and fix things.
Now that it's come to this,
my little temple's too small
to hold big shots like you two.
Please go find better prospects, alright?
I did it today to save that little kid.
That counts as a Good Samaritan act, right?
Director, if the kid had really gotten hurt,
we'd be the ones held responsible.
I know it was a Good Samaritan act,
but right now,
she really did scare that kid into the hospital.
And the worst part is,
now everybody knows
our park's bear is just someone in a costume.
How do we deal with that?
Wasn't the costume your idea?
I told you from the start it was deceiving the guests.
Was this your call or not?
And now that it went wrong, it's all our fault?
You're just using and discarding us, you know?
You two are being way too harsh.
Is it that we're being harsh,
or that you handled this so badly?
We worked so hard, from rehearsals to performing,
for all this time.
We were going permanent tomorrow,
and today you're firing us.
What is this about?
It's all on me.
If someone takes the fall, it's me.
This isn't about who takes the fall.
The park's about to shut down,
and I'm losing my job too.
It's all your fault.
Everything was fine before you showed up.
Then you arrived, and this huge mess happened.
What? Got a problem with that?
Wu Huilian.
You're picking on honest folks, you know that?
Honest folks go to prison, do they?
Say that again.
You should be thanking me.
I gave you a way to put food on the table.
Say that again.
I said it, so what?
Auntie Lan, Auntie Lan.
Stop fighting, stop fighting.
You've gone too far.
You hit me, you hit me!
We worked so hard,
finally about to go permanent.
Okay, Auntie Lan, go home first, go home.
Just go home.
Yiran, head back first, head back.
Let's go.
Just go home, go home.
Go home, go home.
Director, calm down too.
So is there any room to smooth this over?
Let's go ask the kid's mom at the hospital first.
Come with me.
Okay.
Scrap collection!
Collecting scrap! Got any junk to sell?
Scrap collector here!
Running around all day.
That was way too much exercise.
So tired.
I'm absolutely starving.
Let's go eat, then.
I'm not eating.
I lost my job,
and you think I feel like eating?
You're the one who knows you're hungry.
An army marches on its stomach.
Skip one meal and you're famished.
Come on, come on, let's eat.
Damn it.
I'm a bear, I'm a bear.
So silly.
I'm a big old bear.
Xiao Fan, Xiao Fan.
Xiao Fan.
Director, I'm reviewing today's footage.
I was right about you.
This Returning Youth program,
the station put a big budget into it,
so you need to give it your all.
Don't worry, Director.
Oh right, there's this.
This is the new tea from this year.
Take it home for your dad to try.
And say hi to him for me.
Director, I can't accept this.
My dad would scold me.
Without Chairman Fan,
we wouldn't be where we are today.
Remember to send him my regards.
Director.
Tomorrow I'll be filming at another location.
Just handle things as you see fit.
I trust you.
Anyway, keep an eye on Chen Baixi.
And this too.
Yes.
It's Chen Baixi.
What?
Say that again.
Borrow?
Borrow 200,000?
Two hundred...
You little brat.
Have you been dating a girl behind my back?
No.
Then what's going on?
Something happened at the zoo.
So what do you have to say now?
Look at what happened to my kid!
Ma'am, I sincerely apologize to you.
I'm truly sorry.
I neglected my duty.
I really never expected this.
There's plenty you never expected.
You are fully responsible now.
Our management is very strict.
Didn't I just say?
We really never expected
that this kid
would climb up there himself.
Right?
Right.
The kid climbed up there on his own.
Check the security footage if you don't believe me.
Why should I check anything?
It's entirely your fault.
Look what happened to my kid.
It's all because of you.
He's already traumatized.
Tell me, how are you going to compensate?
Even the doctor said
your kid just has a surface scratch.
It's not serious.
Right.
The kid's nutrition costs
and his treatment costs, I'll cover it all.
I'll cover everything myself.
How about that?
I'm very busy with work.
Now I have to take time off.
Plus my lost wages,
and the kid's emotional damages.
Final price: 100,000.
100,000?
This is extortion.
You idiot.
We just don't want this blowing up,
so we want to settle privately.
And what about the other 100,000?
The zoo shut down for restructuring,
The owner fled overnight.
But the animals can't be left starving,
so I have to buy food for them.
And...
What did I tell you back then?
Don't take that lousy job.
You, you, you.
You're absolutely driving me crazy!
Fine, don't lend it to me then.
Come back.
Get over here.
I can lend you the money.
But I have one condition.
What condition?
You come back and work at the shop.
And from now on, big or small,
you do as I say.
Fine.
I'll start at Paradise Funeral Home tomorrow.
But once I pay back the 200,000,
I'm out of here.
Why you...
When your old man was twelve,
I was already traveling all over with your grandpa.
By the time I was your age,
I'd already taken over this shop.
This is the Chen family trade.
We have to secure this livelihood
to honor our ancestors.
Dad,
Paradise Funeral Home is yours.
It's not mine.
Working in the funeral business,
I get no sense of fulfillment.
And what would give you fulfillment, huh?
Acting like little animals all day does?
You ignore honest work
and do nothing but shady jobs.
What do you mean, shady jobs?
Being an actor is my dream.
Dream, my ass.
If you ask me,
you're just taking shortcuts.
Boss Chen, no job is beneath another.
So the funeral business is honest work,
but being an actor isn't?
In this world,
whether bringing a role to life or laying someone to rest,
it all takes real skill.
I sent you to college
so you'd study hard,
not so you'd learn to talk back.
I'm trying to reason with you here.
Cut the nonsense.
Tomorrow morning,
six o'clock,
be at work on time.
Leave the snacks.
As for you,
get the hell out.
I was but a wanderer of Wolong Ridge
What are you hiding in my room for?
Still haven't kicked that eavesdropping habit?
Have you?
None of your business.
Bro.
Congrats on jumping from one hellhole to another.
I know you never liked our line of work.
But Dad's getting old now.
He really needs someone to come back and help.
Well, have you ever heard the saying,
Wealth never lasts three generations?
That rule doesn't apply to our trade.
Five thousand years of Chinese civilization,
and our trade's always been a money-maker.
Then again,
you and Dad are the same kind of person.
Both pig-headed.
You both learn things the hard way.
How am I anything like him?
I'm taller than him.
And better-looking too.
Let me tell you,
back when I was in Beijing,
they all called me the Andy Lau of Lecang.
Mr. Andy Lau,
you're daydreaming before you're even asleep.
This one's not for you.
Read this one.
Good night.
I'm off to grab a snack with Pops.
Pops
I wish you were still here
It's an auspicious day
Did you all forget?
Forget it
I'll just reward myself
A little to the left
Amin, be careful
Pops, you go over there
I'll hold it
Girl, I don't need your help
Stand aside
Hey, is this for me?
I'm hungry
Amin, veggie buns
So stingy
Didn't I tell you to be here by six?
Why are you only showing up now?
I just helped an old lady cross the road
It's nine o'clock already
How on earth did you help her?
Took her the wrong way, then had to bring her back
Idiot
Wrong way, huh?
I think you took the wrong meds
I came here to apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
I messed things up.
Don't be upset.
I'll figure something out.
There's always a way, right?
I'm off.
Fan Shiqi
I'm here for Baixi
I came to discuss something with him
Not sure if you'd be interested in joining.
Sure
It's basically just continuing the shoot anyway
I think it's great
Pops
When'd my brother get so close with Fan Shiqi?
That girl sure is pretty
That little punk's got some luck after all
A fair lady
is a gentleman's desire, you know
Ran, the wise
don't fall in love
No wonder you can't find a wife
What're you staring at?
Uncle Chen
You came.
What brings you here?
Wu Huilian cost your brother his job
so she feels bad about it
She made some hotpot base and had me bring it
That's too kind of her
Tell Auntie Huilian she shouldn't have
Like she ever listens to me
Let me tell you
Anyway, my brother coming back to Paradise Funeral Home,
Pops couldn't be happier
Right, Pops?
As if
If he weren't drowning in debt,
he'd never have come back so easily
What do you mean drowning in debt?
What a splendid northern scenery
I'll come find you another day then
Sure, I'll treat you to a meal
Uncle Chen
Long time no see
I'm Fan Shiqi
Done chatting already?
Why not stay a bit longer?
I won't stay long today
I've got things to do at the station
I need to hurry back
All right, all right
Let's hang out next time then
Okay
You two are dating, huh
Dad, it's not what you think
Dad
What do you mean it's not?
You're together now.
It's only a matter of time
I'll come visit you again next time
All right, all right
Li Yiran
You're here too
Just got here
You and your mom have become Lecang celebrities lately
That kind of fame
I'd rather do without
Next chance I get, I'll come to your place
and do an exclusive interview with you
Um, Shiqi
Your car's kind of blocking the way
Maybe you could first...
See you next time then
Bye-bye
She's already calling him Dad
Honestly, are you two dating?
No way
It's nothing like that
Dad, you shouldn't have chimed in earlier
Well...
She wants me to keep filming
that feature on Returning Youth from the big city
Dad, didn't you say it yourself?
Paradise Funeral Home doesn't have much business
I figured I'd use the feature to promote us
Think of it as advertising
That's a great idea
It'll help promote Paradise Funeral Home
and you get to spend more time with her too
One single meeting
surpasses countless others in this world
Dad
There you go again
What are you even talking about?
Chen Baixi
I've got something to ask you
Sure, I've got something for you too
Hold on a sec
Yiran.
Chen Baixi.
Come clean with me.
Are you hiding something from me?
I'm not hiding anything from you.
Really?
Nope.
I just asked Director Ding.
200,000.
So you already know about this.
Take a look.
50,000. Just transferred it to you.
That's not what I meant.
I never asked you to give me money.
I don't like owing people.
Especially money.
As for the 200,000,
let's split it down the middle.
I'll pay back the other 50,000 monthly.
No, I...
You don't have to.
And this whole thing, whatever you do,
whatever you do, don't tell Wu Huilian.
I'm scared she'll cause trouble.
Also, if any money-making jobs come up,
count me in.
So you're planning to stay.
Stay, my foot.
How else do I pay off the debt?
I'm off.
Yiran.
Yiran!
When you get back, thank your mom for me.
Such great hotpot base.
Take these salt-pepper cakes back to her.
No, no, Uncle Chen.
Come on, don't be shy.
They're really tasty.
Just take them.
Go on, take them.
Thank you, Uncle Chen.
Then I'll take them.
Good, good.
Bye, Uncle Chen.
Alright, alright.
Bye-bye.
This... lipstick.
What's this supposed to mean?
The grass is always greener on the other side.
That's no good at all.
Can't have too many people calling me dad.
What are you on about?
Here, I...
Since you've decided to stay at Paradise Funeral Home,
you need to know this booklet inside out.
Read it carefully.
What's this?
It records everything
from when I first started out.
It...
Take that hotpot base back with you.
Paradise Funeral Home.
Boss Chen, someone passed at the work site.
What?
The police have already examined it.
And we've sorted out the paperwork.
The family wants you to handle the arrangements.
Thanks for your trouble, Boss Chen.
Look how badly he fell.
I heard his kid just got into college.
They even had breakfast together this morning.
One, two, three.
Who'd have thought he'd be gone just like that?
How tragic.
One, two, lift.
Come on.
Alright
Thanks for your hard work, Old Liu
No problem
Move along, move along. Disperse.
Move along, move along.
Your first job out
and you didn't puke at a body like that
Not bad
You're a natural for this line of work.
I've been around the block, you know
You think this line of work
is as easy as you imagine?
I never said it was easy
The business of the dead
still runs on the living
Showing off, saving face, you mean?
It's way harder than acting
You free? Got a job
Help sort out the belongings
My darling husband
How could you just leave me like this?
How are the two of us supposed to survive?
My darling
How can a widow and orphan survive?
What are we going to do?
Mr. Chen
There's one more thing I need to beg of you.
It's fine, it's fine.
Please get up, get up, get up.
Get up, it's fine.
It's fine.
My in-laws
rushed here overnight from back home.
The two of them are getting on in years.
So I'm begging you,
please don't let the two of them
see their son looking like this.
But... but...
Don't worry about the money.
Our bodies, to every hair and bit of skin, are given by our parents.
We'll do everything we can
to restore his body.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
No need, no need.
It's fine.
Get up, get up.
Her husband
was a construction worker.
He lost his footing on the job
and fell from over ten stories up.
The body was completely mangled.
Restoring his remains would be incredibly difficult.
Amin says
we'd use 3D printing technology
to restore his skull and body.
But this family has no money.
Who'd want to take on such a tricky job?
A job this thankless and unprofitable,
only your dad would take it on.
Amin
I'll leave this to you.
Don't worry.
What is there to say of death?
The body is entrusted to the mountains.
Come on.
You come too.
Can you handle this or not?
No problem.
Scissors.
What are you doing?
The wire.
Clamp.
Cut it for me.
Cut it off.
Here.
Yeah.
The photo.
Restoration wax.
Filler material
Here
Scissors
Grab the scissors
Help me hold it
Help me hold the neck
Come here
Press down
Harder
Hold it still, don't move
This is what your father left behind
Now I'm returning it to you
How old are you?
Eighteen.
That makes you an adult.
But even adults,
sometimes don't have to be so mature.
If you want to cry, let it out.
It's okay.
My dad...
My dad worked construction for over a decade.
Except for Spring Festival,
he never once took a day off.
He told me he worked this hard
so that I'd never have to end up like him,
working on a construction site.
I understand.
You wouldn't understand.
When I was your age,
my pops passed away too.
He passed in the summer as well,
so he was buried very quickly.
I didn't even get to see him one last time.
We'll never know
whether tomorrow or disaster comes first.
I lost my pops too.
I understand how you feel.
Yesterday...
Just yesterday I was on the phone with my dad.
I told him
I got into college.
I never expected
that today...
that today he'd be gone.
Go ahead and cry.
After today,
you'll be the pillar of the family.
In your dad's place,
you have to take good care of the family.
I'm so happy!
My kid got into college!
And also,
last night he was so incredibly happy.
He said he had no regrets.
Every sacrifice he made was worth it.
He wants you to know
that you are his pride.
Dad
I miss you
I want you to come back
Dad, Dad
Dad
Come back
I'm begging you, Dad
Dad
Who's this kid?
Chen Baixi, my high school classmate.
His dad
sent funeral home ads
all the way to our company.
From now on, you stay away from this kid.
Dad, Chen Baixi goes to college in Beijing.
He's really ambitious.
The son of someone making a living off the dead,
what future could he have?
In our Fan family,
your grandpa is a university professor.
Your mom and I are both respectable people.
If you really care about your own future,
go on a blind date with Director Wang's son tomorrow.
A blind date?
For marriage, listen to your parents.
You won't go wrong.
So just to be of equal standing,
I have to marry a man I don't even like?
Like?
Can "like" be spent like money,
or can it feed you?
If you really want to date someone,
you'd better find someone respectable.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, happy birthday
Happy birthday
So you did remember my birthday
We wanted to surprise you, of course
Someone was feeling sorry for herself this morning
This is for me?
A phone
Thank you so much
Looks like you do care about me after all
Thank you, Yiran
What did you get me?
Open it when you get home
Xiaofang
Make a wish
Yes, yes, yes
I hope everyone I love and who loves me
stays safe and sound
and becomes wealthy and prosperous.
As long as your dad won't agree
you two can forget about getting married
My sister can't stand being treated like this
Sweetie
Pops
Birthday girl
Here are your longevity noodles
Thank you, Pops
Now that we have longevity noodles
here's a red packet too
It's a big one
Thank you, Pops
I love you
Okay, okay
You're all grown up, that's still so mushy
Alright, dig in then
Pops, I haven't blown out my candles yet
Happy birthday, happy birthday
Take the seat of honor
Come on, come on
Sit
Okay
So next up, is it
the much-awaited cake-cutting?
Cut the cake, cut the cake
The first slice
has to go to my
most, most, most
beloved dad
Okay, okay, okay
The second slice goes to my
beautiful, kind best friend
Miss Li Yiran
Thank you
The third slice, here
You bought me the phone, that was too much
It's nothing
The fourth slice, Xiao Zhou
Thank you
I sent your gift by transfer, okay?
The fifth slice is for myself
Happy birthday
Who ordered the cake for me?
I did, I did
Really?
I arranged everything
Right?
Yes, you arranged it
That's very thoughtful of you.
It's delicious
Delicious
Cheer up a little
Cheer up
Exactly
The most important thing in life is to be happy
It's your birthday and you're smearing it on me?
That's right, it's your birthday
so how can we skip the cake smearing?
Happy birthday
I don't know
whether everything we're living through
is as beautiful as the wishes
we once made
But I finally understand
whether tragedy
or comedy
joys and sorrows, partings and reunions
birth, aging, sickness and death
this fleeting, dreamlike world
we must experience it all, one by one
And the only thing we can do
is in every moment of time
to hold each other close
Oh, my hardworking mother
It's a man
Oh, my hardworking husband
It's an old man
Oh, my hardworking father