Dear Wataru,
I'm sorry for writing this
letter to you out of the blue.
You must be mad at me
for transferring without saying a word.
I know I did something really stupid.
I'm truly sorry.
I wasn't planning on telling you this,
but I still want you to know.
So please let me share
a little about myself.
The first time I met you, Wataru,
was at Higashimura Park.
Huh?
When I was little,
my mom, who always wanted a daughter,
would often dress me up
in girls' clothes on weekends.
Chiharu, do you want to play too?
I'm good.
Let's go look for four-leaf clovers then.
I'm gonna catch you!
You're running too fast, big brother!
Wait for me!
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Isn't that person a little weird?
Yeah, I think so too.
They don't look like
a girl, more like a boy?
Mom.
Hmm?
I want to blow bubbles.
Sure, let's play.
Here you go.
Chiharu.
Where are you?
Ouch...
I don't want this anymore.
I want to go home.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
I'm... I'm fine.
Are you alone?
Where's your mom?
I was chasing the bubbles,
and then I lost her.
She's probably over by the plaza.
I see.
I'll take you there.
Mm...
Ah.
It got away.
Do you want to play?
No.
Hey.
Why are you wearing girls' clothes?
You can tell?
Yeah.
You're a boy, right?
Do you like wearing this?
I don't like it, but...
If you don't like it,
you can just say so.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Did I say something to upset you?
No.
It's not that.
Here, take this.
Thank you.
On the day my pent-up emotions
finally broke through,
that boy didn't say a word.
He just quietly took my hand.
Even without his cape, that boy
was still like a hero from a movie.
Thank goodness. I'm so glad.
Wataru, where did you go?
Seriously, I was so worried!
What if you got kidnapped?
I'm sorry.
Where did you get this?
I traded my cape for it.
What? Honestly.
Your sisters are still looking for you.
Alright.
Let's go.
Don't scare me like that again.
If you don't like it,
you can just say so.
Mom.
Um...
I don't like it.
Girls' clothes.
Huh...?
I've never liked them.
But you looked so happy,
so I was too scared to say anything.
I see...
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I'm not a girl.
No, no.
That's not what I meant.
I just thought you looked so cute,
and I couldn't help it...
You must have been so uncomfortable.
I won't do it again.
I'm truly sorry.
Mom
loves you just the way you are, Chiharu.
I'll always love you.
When I was too afraid to speak up,
that boy was the one who changed me.
"My Summer Of You"
(Episode 5)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Your dad said he needs
to buy a few more things.
Souvenirs?
Yeah.
I heard the people at his company there
asked him to pick some things up.
That's rough.
Are you sure about this?
Huh?
I heard from Teacher Yamada.
You asked him not to tell your
classmates that you're moving to Canada.
You didn't even tell the friend
you hung out with over summer break?
Yeah.
Why not?
Because I don't think he'd
really care even if I was gone.
You feel differently now, don't you?
I think there's still time.
It's too late.
I see.
That's a shame.
I was hoping to meet him too.
Chiharu's high school friend.
I reunited with that boy at our
high school entrance ceremony.
Ah, Wataru!
Oh, Guchi.
Wataru, where did you go?
Seriously, I was so worried!
Wataru?
Chiharu, let's go.
Okay.
At the time, I just thought he looked a
lot like that boy from my distant memories.
I've always liked you, Saeki senpai.
I'm sorry.
I already have someone I like.
Even so, just the thought
that he might be nearby
made me start using "I have someone I like"
as an excuse to turn down confessions.
- Hey, hey, sorry.
- Sorry.
Wait.
Here.
Ah, thanks.
It flew over there.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
There we go.
That was exhausting.
Ah, sorry.
I'll take you there.
Hey, Wataru! If you don't hurry,
the bread will be sold out!
Ah, my bad, my bad!
Give me a sec. Here.
I have to get some today.
It's definitely gonna sell out fast.
For real.
Finally, on that day,
I was finally certain that
the boy was you, Wataru.
From then on,
my eyes couldn't help but follow you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
So scary, so scary, so scary.
It's okay if you don't remember me.
But I still wanted to talk to you.
Alright, I might as well just buy it.
Ah, my bad.
I wasn't watching where I was going.
It's fine.
I should be the one apologizing.
Here.
Uh, we're in the same grade, right?
I think so...
I'm Saeki from Class A.
I'm Toda from Class B.
Do you like movies?
That one's great.
I love it too.
Huh?
That keychain... It's Jet from
"The Jet-Black Hawk," right?
Wait, you actually know
"The Jet-Black Hawk"?
Yeah.
If you have time,
wanna go somewhere else to chat?
Oh, right.
Let me go pay first.
Okay.
This is crazy. It's like I'm being hit on.
As we became friends
and spent time together,
every time I felt that same
straightforwardness you had back then,
you gradually became
someone special to me, Wataru.
So it wasn't a coincidence...
The reason I chose "Sea
of Light" for our pilgrimage
was because the protagonist, who learns at the end
of his journey that he is loved by his parents,
reminded me of myself back then.
What you said to me at the station
when we were hiding from the rain...
Don't worry.
If I don't like it,
I'll just say so.
And to think you actually remembered
what happened that day.
Come to think of it, I was
here too when I was little.
And I met a little girl who was crying.
Huh?
I was really so happy.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
But you still put up with me.
I'm truly happy.
To me, Wataru,
you'll always be in my summer.
Please take care of yourself.
Thank you for giving me the best memories.
Morning.
Oh, a love letter?
Hey!
(Saeki Chiharu)
Sorry.
He sent you a letter?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
- Hey.
- Wait.
Is that guy still in Japan?
Huh?
Look at the postmark.
It says September 3rd, Tamaki-cho.
Huh? You're right.
Let's go.
Kawaguchi.
Do you know where Saeki's house is?
Yeah, I know. Why?
He might still be there.
Can you give me the address?
Uh, it's near the Third Elementary School.
Is that in Tamaki-cho?
Yeah.
Sorry, Guchi.
Once you get the address,
text it to me immediately.
And tell our homeroom
teacher I'm leaving early.
- I'm off.
- Huh?
- What?
I can't believe he's leaving early
before the first period even starts.
Kawaguchi, sorry.
Can you tell me Saeki's address?
Got it.
Coming.
I'm sorry for the sudden intrusion.
I'm Toda.
Is Saeki-kun here?
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
Are you Chiharu's friend?
Yes.
Um, I heard he's going to Canada.
Ah.
He kept it a secret, didn't he?
I'm so sorry.
So, is Saeki...?
There's something I really
need to tell him in person.
He's not answering his phone.
I'm really sorry.
He's not home right now.
Huh? Did he already leave for Canada?
No.
Only my husband went to Canada first.
Because of school arrangements,
Chiharu won't fly out until tomorrow.
Then where is Saeki now?
He didn't tell me where he was going,
but he said he'd be back before dinner.
Thank you.
Huh?
Toda-kun.
Don't you have class?
I don't know where he could be,
but...
I absolutely refuse to
let summer end like this.
(Next Episode Preview)
I want to go to Moriya Beach.
I thought I had to stay far away from you.
So far that I'd never see you again.
Making decisions alone,
putting an end to things alone.
I want to hear your voice.
I want to see you.
I want to touch you.
Don't ever show your face to me again.