Monou?
Hirose.
This is...
One of my buildings.
Have you been visiting them all?
Yes.
I cannot decide what to do for our project.
So, I thought visiting your works
would give me the idea I need.
I see.
I didn't think you'd catch me in action.
How embarrassing...
Don't be embarrassed.
It shows your passion for this project.
I'm happy you wish to work with me.
I will do my best to impress.
I promise to bring
a proposal that piques your interest.
Good night.
Monou.
Yes?
Did you have any plans
for the evening?
Tonight?
Yes.
If you're free,
would you like to join me for dinner?
What?
This building feels
completely different on the inside.
I will be taking notes.
Thank you.
Cheers.
I should have asked this before,
but am I pulling you away from work?
Not at all. I appreciate any opportunity
to glean anything new from you.
Anything new, is it?
I can certainly offer you
a sorry tale, at least.
Truth be told,
I didn't wish to eat alone tonight.
You have those sorts of days as well?
Of course.
If there's something
on your mind, I'll listen.
Thank you.
My former wife has just remarried.
She will be having a child next spring.
[Just Married]
I see.
Yes.
We mutually agreed to part ways,
but when I hear of her new partner,
I can't help but feel conflicted.
See? It's a sorry tale, right?
I don't think so.
What you're feeling is entirely valid.
Thank you.
I had read previously in an interview
that you started the company with your wife?
Yes.
And I assumed we would be partners for life.
You want a child?
Why now, after all this time?
People change.
I can't make your wish come true.
Why?
Dear...
You don't think to change?
I'm sorry.
When we first met,
she wanted to prioritize her career,
and had no desire for children.
And yet...
You've never wanted a child yourself?
I am the third son of a temple.
Oh...
Surprised?
Yes, very.
That is the reaction I often receive.
Although my older brother
took up the family mantle,
he was always pressured to have an heir.
As a result,
I decided I wanted no children in my life.
I see.
Life never quite works out
as planned, does it?
It certainly doesn't.
Still, the divorce wasn't inherently
a bad experience.
It radicalized my beliefs
on what makes a home.
"What makes a home"...
After my divorce,
I wished to create homes
that were free of prejudice.
Homes, not bound by the idea
of the nuclear family.
Morning.
Your door is now locked.
Those two
are a couple now.
Am I walking too fast?
Huh?
No, not at all.
But you're dating Mizuno now.
What?
I wouldn't want to cause
any misunderstandings.
No, well...
Good morning.
Here, I bought us some tumblers.
Oh...
Thanks.
Let me treat you to breakfast.
Really? I'd love that.
Would you like to join us, Monou?
Thank you,
but I'll go on ahead to the office.
Okay, we'll see you there.
They're matching.
I see. This is my first tumbler.
It is really?
Is your proposal due next week?
Yes, next Friday.
Let me know if I can help.
Thank you.
Hirose's wife works as his secretary, right?
What an absolute power couple.
Actually, she's no longer at the company.
What?
Did they get a divorce?
Yes.
But they were perfect for each other.
Hirose said it was a good experience for him.
He didn't seem too down about it.
Did you know, Mao?
No.
Hirose works as his own secretary now.
Nana, want any coffee? I can go brew some.
No thank you. I have a cup already.
I see.
What about you, Monou?
I'll be fine as well.
Then I'll just get some for myself.
[Idea Construction Office]
Heading out?
Yeah. I have a visit with Sanou Systems.
Mao.
Promise you won't make Nana cry again.
Huh?
You know she's a fragile girl.
If you hurt her again,
- I'll...
- I promise.
I'm really sorry about the other night.
As long as you get it.
See you later.
Sui, you said you'd visit often.
Sorry, sorry.
I have an important deadline
coming up next week.
Then I won't rag on you, for now.
What's the deadline for?
We'll be inviting an architect
named Takaomi Hirose
to hold a public talk with our boss.
I'm supposed to come up
with the topics they'll discuss.
My first proposal was already shot down.
What, is this Hirose guy a stingy dude?
Not at all. In fact, the very opposite.
He's a sincere gentleman
who listens to what I have to say,
and even gives me advice.
I can tell he's passionate about his work.
Are you sure he's not just interested in you?
Huh?
Ignore me.
Glad he's such a nice guy.
I hope your next proposal goes well.
Thanks.
- Here.
- Thanks.
My famous fried chicken
is sure to keep you going.
I guarentee it.
I can't believe you're the one
cooking for us.
Your big sis is proud.
Thanks for taking care of the food back then.
Of course.
Oh, right. Take this with you, Sui.
Found it.
Here.
What's all this?
Miso from our neighbors, the Sasaki's.
I set aside a share for you.
Thanks.
Aren't the Sasaki's moving out soon?
Yeah, they'll be leaving next week.
An elderly couple bought the place.
I'm surprised they chose a family home,
for just the two of them.
Just the two of them...
It's a bit large for a retirement home,
don't you think?
It is a 4LDK.
Though supposedly
they plan to renovate the place.
But won't they find the space unmanageable?
Homes, not bound by the idea
of the nuclear family.
Rin, thanks.
I have to get home.
Huh? Sui?
Your miso! Take the miso!
What a wonderful catalogue.
This is no longer in print, isn't it?
Yeah, I bought it while on vacation.
I think you'd like this one better.
These palettes are more your style, right?
Sorry, was I wrong?
No.
I'm just so happy.
Huh?
You know what colors I like.
I was happy when you said yes to dating,
but I was worried I was forcing you, so...
What? You didn't...
No.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Mizuno.
Let me protect you. This time, I swear it.
[Good Design Cafe]
Are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Good night.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
You seem to be in a hurry.
I had a great idea
for our proposal to Hirose.
I have to jot it down before I forget.
You're losing your cool.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm really motivated right now.
Want me to help later?
No, I'd like to do this on my own.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Let's not bother her anymore.
- Right.
- See you both tomorrow.
Your door is now unlocked.
- Take care.
- Good night.
Good night.
This is the topic I'd like to propose.
"An atmosphere, to support your lifestyle".
The other day, you had mentioned to me
how you wished to create homes
that were free of prejudice.
That I did.
Mr. Hoshina also wishes to tackle
a similar philosophy.
Interesting.
Although, in Mr. Hoshina's case,
his interest is in shared homes
for those of different backgrounds.
A place where people
of all ages and genders can reside,
rather than living communities,
exclusive to seniors.
I see.
Encouraging many generations to interact
would inspire a youthful spirit
in all residents.
That sounds like a wonderful idea.
On that note.
I wanted to bring up this residence.
This is...
A home for a single lady in her forties, yes?
I'm surprised you found this one,
it's quite a ways away.
Normally, a large property like this
would be for a family,
especially one with small children.
That is true.
But she requested a home
where she could live in leisure.
That was my client's vision.
So, I ignored my preconception
of a single woman's residence,
and designed a home from the ground up.
That philosophy of yours saved me.
I saved you?
Yes.
Though this may be a bit personal,
I was recently diagnosed as infertile.
Not every family
can be blessed with children.
Yet, most model rooms
are furnished with a family in mind.
Seeing these deeply hurt me at a point.
But the homes you imagine
are free and liberating.
You aren't bound by the idea of a "family."
You treasure many different walks of life.
It has fundamentally changed how I think.
Monou.
That is the very reason I am an architect.
What?
Thank you.
I have never felt more glad
to have pursued architecture as my career.
But I am the one thanking you.
Monou.
I will gladly participate in this talk event.
Then...
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you.
May we discuss scheduling now?
Of course.
I have brought your coffees.
Thank you.
["Long time no see."]
I never imagined we'd reunite so quickly.
Listen to your heart already.
Everything all right?
I want to chip away at this alone
for a little longer.
Blame your faulty body.
Let yourself be miserable, damn it!