Hurry up
Wash your hands, dinner's ready
Smells amazing, honey
I've got two more dishes to go
Honey
Let's have a nice drink tonight
What's the occasion? Why drink?
Drink to happiness every day
and every day's a happy one
All your specialty dishes
All right then
In that case
I'll have one with you
But one glass is your limit
Obviously
Two glasses and I'd pass out
Go call Yiran for dinner
Sweetie, dinner's ready
Dad
Let me have a sip
Don't let your mom see
You can only have a tiny bit
Come on, come on
Dad's in a good mood today
Have a sip with me
Cheers
Slow down, slow down
Just a little
What are you doing?
No, I didn't tell her to drink
She wanted it herself
Lao Li
What's the matter with you?
How could you drink so much?
Look at the state you're in
Mom
I've got way too much homework
I'm drowning my sorrows
Will drinking
make your homework any less?
Well, the Poet Immortal Li Bai
only did his homework
after he'd had a drink
Exactly
Fine, fine, fine
All right, all right
You two drive me nuts
Now enjoy your mom's cooking
Here, stir-fried pork
Smells so good
My honey's cooking is the best
Free-range chicken
Your favorite
How is it?
Hot, hot, hot
Delicious, delicious
Let's have a drink first
Come on
I'll drink too
Li Yiran
You've had so much of my wine
How come you're not doing drunken boxing yet?
Means I can drink more than you
When you find a boyfriend someday
he'd better out-drink your dad first
Or I won't accept him as a son-in-law
How old is she even?
Talking about sons-in-law already?
Is there something wrong with your head?
So annoying
Then I just won't date anyone
I'll stay with you two forever
You wanna be Velcro, huh?
Stuck to us for life?
I'd love to
be Daddy's little girl forever
Cheers
Oh no!
I forgot to cook the rice today
Yay!
Mom forgot to make rice again!
Awesome!
Then we'll just enjoy the dishes
Sounds good, sounds good
Dig in, dig in!
Thank you
Thank you all
for giving my husband
such a dignified send-off
No, no, not at all
It's the least we could do
Please, try not to grieve too much
And take care of yourselves
Honey
Let's go home
Mom
Don't you worry
My tuition from now on
I'll earn it myself
Dad
Didn't the doctor tell you to quit smoking?
And here you are, smoking again
I'm confiscating this
That's right, quit already
In this line of work
if you can't keep your head straight
how are you gonna comfort anyone else?
Life is unpredictable
The world is full of surprises
Who can ever be mentally prepared for it?
Yeah
Some things...
can make you grow up overnight
We're here
Let's get out
Boss, five bowls of noodles
One without chili
What brings you here to eat?
A hot bowl of noodles after a job
It's the custom in our line of work
Have a seat
We're back again
Welcome, welcome!
Boss
Get me some pickled garlic
Sure
Here's your pickled garlic
More if you need it
Okay, okay
Thanks, boss
Before the noodles get here
I've got something to tell you
Ever since the Zhang Wei incident
business at Xiao Xi Tian
has been getting worse and worse
This line of work...
I've been at it for decades
sticking with this run-down little place
Times have changed, you know
Even good wine needs advertising
So
So you've decided
to renovate Xiao Xi Tian
right?
With comprehension skills like yours
no wonder you went to junior college
Ha
Let me tell you
loyalty is often found among the lowly
while betrayal comes from the educated
You think I can't recite poetry?
Reciting poems doesn't mean you're educated
Here we go again, here we go again
Let's get to the point
What I mean is
we can't just sit around like this
Money doesn't fall from the sky
Even a little breakfast stall like this
runs free promotions
So, starting tomorrow
all of you need to go out there
drum up some business
bring in some jobs
Got it?
How do we drum up business for the dead?
We can't exactly
go door to door knocking
asking if anyone died today
And besides
we can't very well hope for
more people to die every day
Who told you to say that?
Use your brains for once
Actually
every industry has its own traits
We can precisely target
our target group and target locations
And if that really doesn't work
why not try the most traditional method?
What method?
Excuse me, miss
Hey handsome, want to add me on WeChat?
Xiao Xi Tian, one-stop service
Check out our funeral packages
Funeral packages, my foot!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm this young and you're wishing me dead?
What's so funny?
You're crazy too
She's calling you crazy too
What are you laughing at?
Nutcase
Hi, Xiao Xi Tian, one-stop funeral service
Care to take a look?
Check out our funeral services
Screw loose in the head
Oh, Xu
You might as well die soon
Look at the state you're in
Still pining over that hussy out there
I see you pining every single day
Sorry to bother you
Our full-service package is 20% off
What, full-service?
And free 24-hour house calls too
Free house calls?
Get out of my way
Young man, is it you?
I'll teach you to pine
Pining every single day
Pining, always pining
Pining over that hussy
Stop hitting him
That young man seduced me
I'll beat you to death
Go, go, hurry up
Hurry, hurry, let's go, Yiran
I'll just beat you to death
Stop hitting me
I meant that other guy
I didn't ask for a woman
Help!
Xiao Xi Tian's buying everyone milk tea
Here, here, come on
Thanks
Here you go
Leave this whole thing to me
You're the best
How about we all take a group photo?
Sure
Just as I thought
Hard work is worthless next to talent
Seems like neither of us has much luck
Okay, everyone look at the camera
Maybe that's a good thing
Get ready
Did you forget what Uncle Chen said?
How do we pay off debt with no business?
Say cheese
Bad business means a low death rate
That's a good thing
True enough
Then here's to everyone living a long life
I'll post it in the group chat once I edit it
I'll make every one of you look gorgeous
Thanks, thanks
Hurry, hurry!
The Wang family is rushing us
Hurry up!
Come on, come on, come on!
We're running out of time!
Let's go!
Move!
Miss, the lease is up in a week
Are you still renting the place?
Yes, Auntie, I'm still renting it
What is she up to?
Miss, my phone's dead
Can I borrow your phone for a call?
It's kind of urgent
Hey, give me back my phone!
Are you out of your mind?
Stop right there!
Hey, buddy
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry
Are you okay?
Get up, let me take you to the hospital
I'm fine
It all spilled, I'm done for
Are you crazy?
Snatching phones and running that fast
What's the rush, you in a hurry to die?
Lunatic
Hey, um
I just got into a little accident
So, um
Your delivery might be a bit late
Please don't file a complaint
If you complain, these past few days of work are wasted
I'm begging you
Hey, buddy
I'm sorry
You... you...
Tell me how much you lost
Let me pay you back
Really, I...
Forget it, you didn't mean to
You...
It wasn't me
Someone snatched my phone
That guy just now grabbed it
Really, I'm not a con artist
It really got stolen
Here, buddy
Take this
Call the number on it
Find her and you'll find me
I'll definitely pay you back
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry
I'm going to report this to the police
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Our time together
was always far too short
Oh, my hardworking mother
Oh, my hardworking mama
It's a man
Oh, my hardworking husband
It's an old man
Oh, my hardworking dad
Bless your children and grandchildren
Faithful sons and grandsons
Bow
Oh, Dad
Bow again
Bow a third time
Oh, Dad
Grieving family and neighbors
The ceremony is now over
Please accept our condolences
You cried so beautifully
Here's your payment
Thank you
No need to thank us
Take a break
Money from the dead
is easy to make
Just cry a little
and that's 200 bucks
People want a big show these days
The way you cried just now
is worth 500
Worth 500!
We charged too little
How do you have so many tears?
Because I've got
a secret weapon
You even cried your lashes off
You didn't even offer me any before
I'm exhausted
Let me take this call
Hello?
Old Chen
Got a rush job tomorrow morning
Playing a mom. You in?
Just finished a crying session
I'm beat. Count me out
I'm in
I'll take any job
Just hear me out
This family's paying good money
How much?
So how much for me?
I'm in
This one only pays 200
That one's 400
Worth it. I'm in
I'm in
I'm here, I'm here
So sorry
Traffic was terrible today
Here I come, here I come
Oh no, oh no
I'm done for, I'm done for
This host family
really put on a huge show
So sorry
I'm late
We'll start right away
Oh, my son!
You've left us!
How can I go on all alone now?
You were so young!
You didn't even have kids yet!
Oh, my son!
What a cruel, cruel fate!
Aunt Lan
Oh, Little Chen!
Who are you playing today?
I'm his mother!
And who are you?
I'm the host
Oh, good heavens!
Funerals these days are so fancy!
Oh, my son!
You're such a lucky one!
Wait, wait, wait
This is a wedding!
It's a wedding!
What are you doing here?
Auntie, come here
Come with me, come with me
Where? Where to?
What's this all about?
Auntie, let's go take a look over there
The weather's nice, isn't it?
Let's go, go, go
Auntie, hurry up, would you?
What's going on here?
I'll explain in a bit
What a mess this is!
There won't be time later
I'll come down and explain
My dear lady!
Where do you think you're going?
You haven't even finished this yet!
Don't mess up the biggest day of my life!
Zhou Fang, do you get it?
Getting me this side gig,
that was a real opportunity, I know
Mr. Zhou
Why are you spoiling her?
We're the paying clients here
So what if you're the client?
You're the client, but do you know love?
Li Yiran
About me proposing to Xiaofang
you did promise me, remember?
Just relax, will you?
Even if you don't trust me
trust Xiaofang's taste in picking friends
Fine, fine, I trust you
Now I finally understand
why you and Xiaofang
are birds of a feather
thick as thieves, the two of you!
Hey, I didn't say anything!
Don't go slandering me!
Li Yiran, this groom's a real handful
If your script isn't good
you'd better watch out, or you'll owe money
Don't you worry one bit
Xu Wumei
It's Wumei
"Mei," as in plum blossom
Same thing, really
There, all done
Let me have a look
Just one quick look
Can you even read it?
I went to junior college
Of course I can read it!
Wait for me!
Coming, coming
Thank you, thank you
You're too kind, too kind
Thanks so much!
Great, great, great
This job went well
Didn't expect this much cash!
We're gonna be rich, buddy!
Mee mee mee, mah mah mah
Eight hundred soldiers dash up the north slope
The gunners run side by side to the north
Sorry, sorry
Sorry, sorry, I'm late
The host's script is here
Excuse me
Thanks
Chen Baixi
What are you doing here?
I'm here to be the host
You work in funerals
What are you doing at a wedding?
I'm desperate to pay off my debt
So of course I take any job I can get
Are you even up to this?
Whether it's a funeral or a wedding
it's all a show for the living
Life is like a play
It's all about acting
We're about to begin
Okay, okay
Dear guests
Please take your seats
The wedding is about to begin
You got this
Ladies and gentlemen
Hello, everyone
Today, we gather together
to send off this new couple
Send off?
What kind of script did Li Yiran write?
Is this some kind of mistake?
Send them off
Send them off as they finish
this long marathon of love
and step into the hall of marriage
Good
Good, good
The script
Marriage is the grave of love
Fragrant... it's a collision of souls
The auspicious moment has arrived
Let's welcome the bride and groom
Good
Everyone's acting so weird
Can't anyone give me a break?
I'm hurrying, aren't I?
I'm already running as fast as I can
Auntie Huilan
What are you doing here?
Rest in peace with a smile
What's she doing?
Oh no, this is gonna be trouble
It's fine, it's fine
Just a minor issue
Minor issue
Li Yiran
What did you write in this script?
I didn't write it
Pay up, pay up
Why is your mom here?
Where is she?
Over there
Go stop her, quick, stop her
What are you so worked up about?
All panicked like that
What's this thing?
No, no, no
These are my tools of the trade
Stuff it in there, in there
You keep it safe now
Don't you lose it
Here, you hold this too
No way
I've got valuables in there
Nobody's gonna steal it
If it's stolen, you'll pay for it
You'll pay
Pay, pay, pay
Wu Huilan
Stand still
I knew I just saw you
What are you here for this time?
No, no, listen, let me explain
Now let's welcome both sets of parents
to witness this joyous moment together
Go, go, go
I'm heading up first
I'll explain to you later
I'll tell you later
Go, go, go
Okay, okay
Aunt Lan, what's going on?
We agreed I'd come to wail at a funeral
Now it's turned into a wedding!
And you?
Funeral wailing
Didn't you check before you came?
I take the money, I do the job
Hurry up and help me out
Then let me leave
I'm just a temp too
Finish up and get out fast
Okay, okay
Today's just been a nightmare!
Shitou, Shitou!
Mom
Your son's getting married
You're so moved!
Cry, cry!
Mom, let me introduce you
This is my son
No, wait
This is your daughter-in-law
I'm so happy, I forgot!
Mom
Keep crying, keep crying!
Don't worry
We'll build a good life together
Don't you worry
What a touching moment!
Quick, snap a photo to remember!
Okay
Photo, photo!
Come on, photo time!
Come on, look at the camera!
We'll make it work, for sure
Mom, okay
Wu Huilan
Where are your tears?
Aren't you supposed to be a great crier?
Hold on, Team Leader Chen
I'm a professional funeral wailer
It's a wedding, how am I supposed to cry?
Isn't it all the same?
It's all just acting
What's the difference?
Huge difference!
That money of yours
Eight hundred!
I already sent it to that Zhang Lijuan
You gave me eight hundred?
Eight hundred
That damn Zhang Lijuan!
Wu Huilan
Give me an explanation
What's going on here?
Let me tell you
This is a bit complicated
I originally came here to wail at a funeral
What are you doing?
Auntie, why'd you show up dressed like that?
Weren't you the one who called me to wail?
"Rest in peace with a smile"
What funeral wailing?
Today's my big day
Let's not say such unlucky things
Sorry, sorry
Good luck and good fortune!
No taboos at all, no taboos!
It's fine, Auntie
Just listen to me
Hurry up and change your clothes
Your role today is to play my mom
I play your mom?
Me?
It's your wedding, why isn't your mom here herself?
My mom
What's wrong with you?
My mom's gravely ill in bed
So she can't make it here
My wife said
if there's no mom at the wedding,
she'll lose face, you know
It took me so long to get married
I'm begging you here
Come on, don't cry now
A grown man like you,
what's there to cry about?
Come on
Whatever it is, take your time and tell me
I'll pay you extra
Five hundred
Once you change clothes, come right over
That's settled then
Wait a second
Six hundred
Fine, six hundred it is
Six is a lucky number, right?
Thanks so much, Auntie
Thank you
And then?
And then you saw the rest, didn't you?
I went up and played the groom's mom
Just doing whatever they told you
Are you out of your mind?
What's that supposed to mean, Li Yiran?
I made a thousand bucks today
A thousand bucks, you get that?
Still, you can't take just any money
Take a look at that groom
One look and you know he's a con man
The groom's a con man?
Let me take a look
Come on
The moment I got there, something felt off
Someone genuinely getting married,
why hire fake parents and groomsmen to act?
Most people there looked like strangers
This whole wedding
is just a scam
Handing it out
Yeah, something's not right
Why are they handing out money?
How'd you figure it out?
How could I not figure it out?
I used my eyes, obviously
Now the bride and groom will exchange rings
Okay
That damn con man
Now, the groom may kiss the bride
May you soon have a child
Kiss her! Kiss her!
No kissing allowed!
Sis
Come here
What's this about?
No idea
Everyone, listen to me
My name is Wu Huilan
This is my ID card
I'm filing a formal complaint
This wedding today is a marriage scam
A scam!
Get down here
Should... should we keep filming?
We already took the money
Keep filming
Film it
Let me tell you all
I'm not his mother
Today I actually came here
to attend a funeral
I was supposed to come mourn today
But then this guy right here
He gave me 600 yuan
to play his mother
I'm not kidding
I may be short on cash
but I won't take money against my conscience
I already paid you
Scram
You damn con artist
He's not my son
I don't have a son
And I don't have a husband either
My husband died a long time ago
Wu Huilan!
They're all con artists
Mr. Zhou, your dad was right
Chen Xiaofang's family brings you bad luck
This is a huge job for Xidongdong
What do we do now?
Xu Wumei
Did you know all along this was a scam?
Me?
I had no idea
I'm filing a formal complaint
You dumb woman, didn't I pay you?
You came to ruin everything for me
Come at me! Come at me!
Guys, someone's making trouble
Get her!
Go on, hit me!
Stop hitting!
Stop hitting them!
Brother-in-law
Mr. Zhou
The balance hasn't been paid yet
To hell with your balance
My brother-in-law
matters most
Stop hitting!
Brother-in-law
Get back here now
What do you think you're doing?
I'll take you down with me!
Zhou Fang
I'm hurt
It hurts like hell
I need to go to the hospital
Then hurry up and go
If you don't go now
your wound will heal on its own
I'm so furious
I figured those people were unreliable
but I didn't expect them to trash the whole place
And you're still laughing
The final payment isn't even settled
That wailing mourner, Wu Huilan
and that scriptwriter, Li Yiran
It's all their fault
The final payment is no big deal
I run a wedding company
not just to make money, you know
Then how will you explain this to your dad?
That's not the point
The point is that today
I got hurt because of my brother-in-law
No way Xiaofang won't feel sorry for me
I'm going to find her right now
Did Xiaofang save your life in a past life?
You've got love on the brain
Are you crazy?
Having my brother host a wedding
What were you thinking?
Wasn't it you who said it?
Investing is about hedging
and luck is about balance
Someone in the funeral business
should do some wedding work to offset it
I got hurt today because of my brother-in-law
Look
Come here, let me see
It hurts this bad?
It hurts
A little blow and it won't hurt anymore
Let me put some medicine on it
There's more over here
Don't get all cheeky with me
It's fine, it's fine
It's okay, it's okay
Don't, don't be scared, Xiaofang
Don't be scared
Sounds like thunder outside
Thunder and rain both
Then why don't you just stay tonight?
Sure
That was worth it
What did you say?
I said, whatever you say
Okay
Then you can sleep on the couch tonight
But I'm injured
And this is how you treat me?
A favor deserves a favor
I'll get my brother to keep you company
No, no
Bro, bro
Don't wake him up
Bro
No, no
Are you asleep yet?
Fine, the couch works too
At least I'm staying at their place
Yiran
Come on, don't be mad
All right, enough
You've been sulking forever
Who was it that promised me
they wouldn't cause trouble?
Well, this
doesn't really count as trouble
Your own life is a total mess,
and you still worry about others?
Every kid is their parents' pride and joy
I couldn't just stand there and watch
that bride get taken in by a con man
I just couldn't help it
Didn't I tell you
to stop being a busybody?
To stop being a busybody!
But marriage is a huge life event
That's hardly a trivial matter
Wu Huilan,
do you know that meddling in others' fate
comes with a price?
What price is that, exactly?
Your dad and I,
if we'd overthought it back then, you wouldn't exist
A lot of things, you just can't overthink them
You get it?
And that's exactly why this family
ended up the way it is now
A ruined wedding
beats a whole lifetime that's ruined
I just wanted to save her
I don't even know what I did wrong
Let's go home
What son of a bitch did this?
Guts to do it, but no guts to own up?
I curse your entire ancestral line!
May your kids be born without assholes!
If you're this bored, go get a job
Every day just piling more work on me
Xiaofang
What are you doing here?
Perfect timing. Help me clean this up
You don't need to do this yourself
Leave it to me
Halt
Right face
Hello, boss
Hello, Mr. Zhou
Let's get to work
Xiaofang
It's okay
As long as you want it
As long as I can give it
Just sit down and relax first
Who did this?
You've got the nerve to ask?
They found out we hired funeral guys
to wreck their wedding
Said they're not done with you
So it was you two! No wonder
Boss Zhou prepared something else for you
Shut up
I didn't prepare anything
How about this
Look, this place is depressing
Let's you and me go out for a bit
Get some fresh air
Come on
We'll take my car
We're riding in this thing?
What? This isn't a real car?
Take it or leave it
I'll take it, I'll take it
Such a good deal, riding in this junker
Every one of you is weird
What are you looking at?
You're all weird too
Get to work
Something happened
According to our station's latest report
Xiao Xi Tian Funeral Home in South City
tops the city news again
This incident starts with a wedding
Sister Lan looks so pretty today
Right?
Let me tell you
I washed my hair last night
My hair's so bouncy today
Yangyang
You're getting more handsome too
Zhang Lijuan
I've noticed Yangyang is really smart
Sharp as a tack
He's got such a smooth tongue now
Of course, our Yangyang's plenty smart
So what exactly happened?
Give us the details
You want to hear it?
Your gossip streak just never dies, huh
Let me tell you all about it
When it comes to this whole thing
I've actually got Zhang Lijuan to thank
for hooking me up with this gig
If you hadn't gotten me this gig
there's no way I'd ever have
run into something this bizarre
But then again
that kickback you skimmed off me
I'll settle that score with you later
Just look at that face
Forget it
I won't get into her business
Let me just tell you what happened that day
So that morning I got up
and you told me to go take that job
I rode the bus for over an hour
and got to the place
I rushed inside in a total panic
And wow, that big estate was gorgeous
I took one look
and that damn groom's photo was black and white
How was I supposed to tell?
So bam, I dropped to my knees
and then I went
Help!
and started bawling
What's wrong, Yiran?
No, no, no
Let's talk this out nicely
Put Yaya down
Put her down
Aunt Juan
If you set Wu Huilan up
with any more of those crazy jobs
I'll snap Yaya's neck
Okay, okay, okay
I promise
Put her down, put her down
Yiran
Let's talk this out nicely
This has nothing to do with you, Uncle Daren
Wu Huilan
Remember the rules we agreed on
What are you off to do today, huh?
Handling a big life event
No way
That little brat
Now the egg's bossing around the hen
Is that a joke or what?
I mean, that kid really is
so fierce!
Good grief
You
And the rest of you
Stay out of trouble
Not my problem
Can't mess with that, no way
Really can't mess with that
Scared me half to death
Huilan
That temper of hers
is exactly like yours when you were young
Bullshit
I was pretty darn gentle, I'll have you know
Didn't you hear what she just said?
She wanted to gouge our eyeballs out
So fierce!
You're way fiercer than her
Slow down
Get ready to lift your feet, lift them
That's it
Here we go
Almost there
Three
Two
One
Li Yiran
Go do what you love
I've got your back