"Blue Lips"
(Episode 6)
Is it good?
I didn't expect
you to know how to cook.
I'm single, you know.
Just the basics.
Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
I just think
you look really especially
good without makeup.
It's not like you haven't seen it before.
I did see it last time,
but you're wearing different clothes today.
It gives off a different vibe.
You look more like a college student.
Can I ask you a question?
Besides working at Blue Moon,
do you have any other part-time jobs?
I don't mean anything by it.
I just feel like
I've seen you somewhere before.
You look really familiar.
Why
are you asking this?
Just curious.
I
also deliver packages during the day.
Why?
Nothing.
I just find it strange.
Looking at your place,
you don't seem to be doing too badly.
Why are you working day and night?
Are you that desperate for money?
Well, you smoke and play games every day.
Your fridge is always empty.
Food, daily necessities...
You don't care about any of it.
Don't you find your life boring?
Okay, okay.
Pretend I didn't ask.
You don't owe me an explanation anyway.
Eat up.
Wait.
Weren't you
going home?
You should hurry back.
The last bus
is already gone.
Besides, I was the one who
offered to treat you to a meal.
Let me clean this up.
Then,
maybe I should take a shower too.
Do you want to dry your hair?
You'll catch a cold otherwise.
Don't stop.
Why did you stop playing?
Want to request a song?
Is there a charge for requests tonight?
No extra charge.
Then I'll request.
"Dawn, Please Don't Come."
Such an old song.
Aren't you worried I might not know it?
I'm sure you do.
Dawn, I beg you,
please don't come.
Let the illusion of tonight
last forever.
You saw everything.
Why didn't you save me?
With the situation I'm in right now,
what right do I have to
drag someone else down?
Alright.
Get some rest if you're tired.
I'm going to sleep.
You're up so early.
I have to go to work.
Let me make you some breakfast.
Don't bother.
No way.
Skipping breakfast is bad for your stomach.
Listen to me.
Go
wash your face and brush your teeth.
There are new toothbrushes in the cabinet.
Grab one for yourself.
Go on.
Time to eat.
We're out of milk.
Just make do with some hot water.
Why is there only one portion?
Aren't you eating?
I'm going back to sleep after you leave.
I'm exhausted.
Did I wake you up?
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and eat.
Brother Mo!
What a coincidence running into you here.
You actually cook for yourself?
Are you seeing someone?
What are you talking about??
If I were dating, would
I still go to your bar?
You know what, you could
totally find someone at our bar.
Someone like me?
The girls at our bar
are pretty good-looking.
How am I fit to date anyone?
People from the bar...
Can you just bring someone from a bar home?
That's a harsh thing to say.
So,
are you coming tonight?
We'll see tonight.
Enjoy your shopping.
I'm off.
Take care, Brother Mo!
Bye!
Brother Heng.
No song requests today?
Hold on, let me check.
Nope.
It's a bit less fun without
Brother Mo around.
Is he not coming today?
When I saw him earlier today,
he said he had to look after his shop,
so he wouldn't make it.
But I think
it's definitely not that simple.
Why?
Why else?
A bachelor suddenly stops partying?
He must have someone
waiting for him at home.
Do you
know who it is?
No idea.
I even asked him
if he found someone at our place.
He said no matter what,
he would never bring
someone he met at a bar
back to his home.
Do you think he
looks down on us bar workers?
He's always fooling around,
it's not like he's anything special.
Running a shop like that.
A box of Vandacon.
Why don't you have an
umbrella in this heavy rain?
What's wrong with you?
What does it have to do with you?
Are you planning to go back like this?
Let me get you an umbrella.
Let go.
Look at you,
your hands are freezing.
Let go!
Listen to me.
Go upstairs and take a hot shower,
or you'll catch a cold.
Stop messing around.
I'm not going to your place.
Didn't you think I was dirty?
Aren't you afraid I'll dirty your home?
Who said you were dirty?
If anyone is dirty, it's me.
I run a sex toy shop.
Then why didn't you come today?
Should I tell the truth?
On rainy days,
my rheumatism acts up and my knees hurt.
I didn't want to go out.
Just because of that?
What else?
Why wouldn't I go?
I want to go home.
If you go back like this
and really catch a cold,
how are you going to work tomorrow?
I'd be better off dead.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Listen to me.
Don't act tough with your health.
You should drink ginger
tea when you have a cold.
I just brewed it for you.
Here.
Try it.
Let me wipe it for you.
Is it spicy?
No.
It's sweet.
I added brown sugar.
Drink it all up.
You won't catch a cold if you finish it.
Why didn't you bring your guitar today?
Because
I left it at the bar.
I didn't have an umbrella,
and I was afraid it would get wet.
You're afraid a guitar might get wet,
but aren't you more precious than a guitar?
No matter how good something is,
it still needs someone to cherish it
to show its true value.
If no one cares about it,
even a diamond
will be seen as just a rock.
Silly.
People are people.
Not diamonds,
not rocks.
Don't let whether others cherish you or not
make you think less of yourself.
Much better.
Then drink it all.
I'm going to take a shower.
Go to bed early.
What are you looking at?
The rain stopped.
I'm checking if there
are any stars in the sky.
It's cloudy.
Where would the stars come from?
Can I call you Shixian from now on?
Sure.
Shixian.
How old are you?
Twenty-one.
And you?
Thirty.
At thirty,
I've accomplished nothing.
But I think you're pretty great.
Just like what you said
when we first argued,
ending up like me
really isn't that great.
I was just...
I know.
That was...
You were just bickering with me.
I didn't take it to heart.
Shixian.
From now on,
can you stop working at Blue Moon?
Find a proper job.
When you're tired, come to my place.
Have a meal,
and get some good rest.
I'll leave a spare key for you.
I have my own difficulties.
For money?
You could say that.
Why don't you just be with me?
You want to keep me?
No, I...
That's not what I meant.
I...
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Lately,
why haven't you been coming to Blue Moon?
Didn't I promise you?
If you drank that medicine,
I wouldn't request songs that
disgust you for a few months.
Is he not coming today?
He said no matter what,
he can't bring someone he met at a bar
back to his home.
Do you think he
looks down on us bar workers?
I don't know how...
I understand.
If I don't agree,
will you just
disappear without a word again?
Pretend I didn't say anything.
It's not like we're dating.
Then get your money ready.
In your potato rice...?
It's actually just pan-fried potatoes.
You're done.
Then,
you've turned down all the clients, right?
You two.
Ah Heng.
Lately,
that new cocktail you mixed
doesn't taste very good.
I don't think so.
Anyway, it's not selling very well.
Do you know why?
You should change the salt rim
to a sugar rim.
Why?
Because you are
too salty. [pun for: you have too much free
time [to be messing around in my business.]]
I'm too salty?
You're the one who's too salty, Brother Mo.
Have a taste.
Who taught you how to cook?
Do I even need to learn?
I just watched a video and figured it out.
When I first came to Jinyang,
I wasn't used to the food,
so I learned to make some Fengzhou dishes.
Just to make do.
You're from Fengzhou?
Then why did you come to Jinyang?
That was years ago.
I forgot.
Eat.
It's delicious.
So?
Is the cat I gave you pretty?
I picked it out very carefully.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Don't you feel
they're a perfect match?
A perfect match.
It looks like you.
Then that one is you.
I think
compared to before,
you're a little different.
Yeah.
I've gotten older.
You used to
seem more like a decent guy.
Are you saying I'm not decent now?
Now,
you're like a sly old fox.
Who are you calling
an old fox? Who's a fox?
Who's an old fox?
Wait.
I have something for you.
What is it?
Close your eyes.
You're not going to hit me, are you?
Do you want it or not?
Yes, yes, yes.
Alright.
For me?
It's not some prank toy, is it?
Open it and see.
How is it?
It looks great.
It's not a holiday or anything,
why are you giving me a gift?
I saw it when I was passing by,
thought it suited you, so I bought it.
Then when you bought it,
what were you thinking?
I thought
you look better in a suit,
so I bought it for you.
You just like me in a suit?
Yeah.
Then do you like me as a person?
I give you a gift,
and you have so many questions.
I'm never giving you anything again.
You have to keep buying them.
You gave it to me,
so it's mine.
Come here.
Put it on me.
Tie it for me.
I...
I don't know how to tie it.
I'll teach you.