[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
Deep breaths.
- Was that for you or for me?
- Both.
Just relax.
It's like you've
never seen one before.
Completely normal procedure.
Well, it's just...
I've never had anything
go in there before.
And, it's just... you're a girl.
That's why Atzin's here.
We have a chaperone present
for patients
of the opposite sex.
Hi.
Don't worry,
I'm not looking at...
- You know that?
- Ah!
There's a name
for his condition.
You know, the type
who showers with shorts on?
You're totally looking at it.
The type who needs to turn off
the lights when it's sexy time?
- Oh my God, stop!
- I'm not doing anything!
Angle lower.
There's no urine.
That means you're not
in the right zip code.
And watch your sterile field.
Do you want to do this?
You're talking to who?
Is somebody else in here?
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Deep breaths.
No, no, no.
Twist it while you push it in.
Don't force it.
His sphincter will clench up
like a traffic jam.
- Got it.
- Never nude!
That's the term.
He's a never nude.
[CHUCKLING]
He's laughing at me!
- [ATZIN CHUCKLING]
- He's laughing at me!
Did he hear what I said?
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TESS] Impossible.
[NOA] Are you sure?
Since when?
How did it happen?
He's a liar. He lies.
Is there a limit?
A certain time?
So, you're telling me
he's got powers now?
[SCOFFS]
More like a curse.
Imagine Tess in your ear
all day.
[CHUCKLING]
Ouch!
Good morning, Josh.
Hello, good morning.
Thank you.
Relax, guys.
She knows everything.
Knows what?
There's nothing to know.
And who the hell is Josh?
I told you he's a liar.
Is this a thing now?
We're just, like,
talking or whatever.
Oh!
My grandma was a healer.
Because of her,
I can see ghosts.
Like you.
- Yes, Dee?
- I don't get it.
I have some crayons
in the supply room.
He'll catch up to you later.
And what the hell
is a curarachi?
A curandera.
It's like a babaylan.
- Oh.
- Duh, Ros.
It's like a white lighter.
I've been watching
reruns of Charmed.
I've always felt this ward
sits at a crossroads.
You know,
where spirits pass through.
Now that I can see them too,
I can actually help.
We can start by celebrating
Día de los Muertos.
Uh... It's not that simple.
I can handle it. It's easy.
I partied so hard in Ibiza
that I woke up
to a spiritual cleansing
from a ghost named Miguel.
He Venmo requested me afterward.
I'd rather not do a party.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
We say a person dies twice.
Once when their heart stops,
and again when no one
remembers them.
- Let's honor them.
- Tess included.
- I didn't go anywhere.
- Tess is still here.
But honoring them
might settle the energy.
Happy ghosts, calmer work,
fewer flying bedpans.
Oh, Filipinos
are so used to this.
Like candles, food, basically
a sleepover at the cemetery.
Hmm.
I'll allow it.
But you'll all need the one
with PTSD to buy in.
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Woo!
Sign me up for whatever
you've got going on, Noa.
I'll do anything you want.
Mhm! I'll bring pan de muerto.
And I'll post about it.
I have a ton of followers.
You're welcome.
So, we're doing this.
We've got a ward
full of roots,
and we're blooming
because of it.
When I see my picture
on your altar,
you'd better be ready.
[WIND HOWLING]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CHUCKLES]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
Archangel Gabriel, sir.
AOD 732198739075.
[CHUCKLES]
You've been a bad boy.
And this mortal skin.
[GROANS]
Filthy.
I've had a spotless record for
a couple of millennia now, sir.
Well, you've been called...
Upstairs.
And when they're done with you,
you will be on your knees.
I can't leave.
The veil is thin
on this holiday--
- That's why she's here.
- [FINGERS SNAP]
She will spank whatever
needs a whipping.
- [WIND HOWLING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATH QUIVERS]
You don't hear yourself talk,
do you?
Hmm?
With me! [LAUGHS WRYLY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And we are honoring the dead
for Dia de los Muertos.
Exciting!
[SQUEALS]
"Cute setup."
"My nana would cry."
"Isn't this cultural
appropriation?"
You know, don't listen
to whatever you hear.
We are not
worshipping the ghosts.
"Real Christians
don't entertain the dead."
We--
I--
[BEEPS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
And please remember to
sign Ezzekiel with two Z's.
Two Z's.
Okay, you guys.
One at a time.
Everyone will have
their turn. Okay? Relax.
Okay, but I'll go first.
I don't remember
this many ghosts.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
When the cult's adjourned,
can you go help the living
before they start haunting
my floor tiles?
This is getting intense.
They're coming
from different floors.
Okay, that's it. Boundaries.
We've got a ton of work to do.
Expired mess to dispose of.
Charts to update.
So if any of you bother me
before my shift is over,
you will not be
going on the ofrenda.
Got it?
That's my boss. You heard her.
Camille, what are you doing?
We're honoring people for
Dia de los Muertos
and All Souls Day.
Mr. Alderman told me
to take it off.
- [PAPER RIPS]
- It's ugly anyway.
[ALL GASP]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is Jane?
I don't know.
- Ah, speak of the devil.
- [CHUCKLES]
I'm not the devil, Walt.
I'm actually looking right
at him.
Oh, little tea with our coffee!
[LAUGHING]
I am well aware of the
spectacle Ward Five is staging.
Are you jealous you
weren't invited to the party?
I think it's pretty cool.
People like being seen.
What's the name of that
new nursing supervisor again?
Noa.
It's a waste of time.
And resources.
Lord, Walt.
What'd that girl ever do to you?
She's immature and all
these antics are a liability.
Boost morale
or keep raising turnover?
We're hemorrhaging nurses.
Pick your expense, Mr. Alderman.
Very well.
When we're done, Ward Five
will be off our docket.
You're going to love this, Jane.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TESS] You're late on
your charting because
you're doing this stupid party.
No offense to the dead.
[ATZIN] Look at what I found
in the break room.
It was Camille, wasn't it?
I heard she launched
an FB campaign against this.
We don't know that.
Who the heck says heathen?
[LATIN MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Good morning.
[WHIMPERING]
I'm sorry. I...
[CRYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you want to talk about it?
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I understand.
Could you just give me
a minute, please?
Sure.
Just in case you need
to speak with someone.
I'm just here.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just cancel it if it's inviting
unwanted attention.
The aunties are gossiping.
They say it's too much!
Too much?
- Oh, Noa.
- Hi.
Too much?
We literally spent
all night in cemeteries
with candles and picnic food.
And this is too much?
Don't mock the culture!
Okay then.
Do you know who's behind
the vandalism?
I'm not God. I don't have
eyes and ears everywhere.
I don't have eyes and
ears everywhere.
Tess has a point.
And honestly, I think
I'm in way over my head.
(In Spanish) Grandma!
I don't want this gift.
Take it off.
Oh, crap.
- [ATZIN] Oh.
- [GEORGE] Uh...
Hi. Sorry, I just...
[CHUCKLES WEAKLY]
No, you idiot!
I'm dating DonDon.
[GEORGE] Oh.
Oh, good.
Not that it matters,
or that I thought that either
of you two were, you know...
Yeah. Congratulations.
She's too good for you, George.
Everything okay?
Oh, right.
We have a big issue
in the break room?
Oh.
[NOA SIGHS DEEPLY] What now?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
[DOOR OPENING]
You read my test results,
didn't you?
I just came here to listen.
- [CAMILLE SIGHS DEEPLY]
- [GLOVES SQUEAKING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what?
You want to hear
something crazy?
I just realized why I love
being a nurse so much.
Yes, we study science
and the licenses.
But it's the one thing
that makes me stay.
Even when things get hard.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
When answers don't help.
When all somebody wants...
is to not be alone.
So...
I'm here to stay.
I'm here to listen.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
When my grandpa was dying...
he kept seeing ghosts.
He said it was his mom,
his sister,
and my grandma
coming to get him.
We have a term for that,
you know.
"Sundo."
It's not dying
that I'm worried about.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS]
Then...
What's breaking your heart?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm not a slut, you know.
I just trusted the wrong person.
You're not made up of
the opinions of other people.
Those who love you,
will love you no matter what.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
In essence, closing Ward Five
and making way for
private doctor's offices
will put us far in the black
for years to come.
Any questions?
That's a great presentation,
Walt.
Did you make that in Canva?
Any real questions?
I hate to say it, but if it
keeps us open a few more years,
it might be the right call.
It's not looking good, Jane.
This is still a business
at the end of the day.
Shall we put it to a vote?
Let's get this over with.
I actually have a
counter-business proposition--
Oh!
Would you like us
to call your assistant?
No, no. It's fine.
Just give me a second.
I'm sorry.
Jane, we don't have all day.
Then, tomorrow.
I would love to continue this
conversation tomorrow. Please.
I do have a patient
waiting for orders.
And I have another meeting.
Oh, why not?
A day won't kill us.
Oh.
Oh, well.
That answers our question
if we should do this or not.
This is so mean!
Maybe I should possess
that witch.
[CAMILLE GASPS]
What happened?
What do you mean what happened?
This was you.
No, I would never.
You certainly didn't
hide your displeasure.
I changed my mind. I...
I realized that God
is gracious, kind, empathetic.
What is this?
[CAMILLE] It's Hubert's
grandfather. The 505.
The Never Nude!
Thanks, Camille.
But it doesn't matter.
We're cleaning all of this up.
And I'm gonna tell everyone
it's canceled tomorrow.
Noa.
Somebody clean up this mess.
I got this, boss.
[SIGHS]
Well...
(In Spanish) Add disappointed
ghosts to my to-do list.
[GLASSES CLINKING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
[COUGHING]
Ugh.
The apple fell far from the tree
on the tequila tolerance.
This is what you and
my mom used to do?
[CHUCKLES]
Well, it was a different time.
Back in the day, medical folk
weren't afraid of bars
before you know what.
[CHUCKLES]
What are we gonna do?
We fight, kid.
[SIGHS]
What if we lose?
Then we learn to do
what everyone has to do
at some point in their life.
We learn to say goodbye.
[COUGHING]
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Ah! Ouch!
Mom, why didn't you wake me?
I just did.
You smell like you've
been working three jobs
and cheating on all of them.
Hold the door, please.
Thank you.
Oh, sorry.
Excuse me.
Where is she?
[NOA PANTING]
Hi.
[NOA] Good luck.
Now you have weapons.
Let's go.
- What's going on here?
- Oh!
Food's here.
Food already? You haven't
even brushed your teeth.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What happened to pass down?
Ward Five nursing turnover
dropped 23 percent
in the past few months,
the only unit trending downward.
Patient satisfaction scores rose
from 54 percent to 89 percent,
with highest marks in
communication and compassion.
Average length of
stay decreased by.6 days,
translating into a savings
of 312 dollars per patient.
So whatever personal BS you
have against her, Mr. Alderman,
even you can't
deny Noa's numbers.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JANE] And since we're
talking about feelings,
let me tell you the truth.
Nurses don't stay
because of dollars.
[MUSIC TURNS SOFT]
They stay because they matter.
Oh.
Good morning, boss.
Sorry we didn't respond
to your text last night.
We got your text
like super late.
I said no one needed
to bring anything.
I was gonna bring the food.
No offense,
but I wouldn't trust you
to bring the good Mexican stuff.
- True!
- [LAUGHING]
[JANE] In their ward,
they remember the nurse
who never clocked out.
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Gosh, you guys did all of this?
Hey, it was all my idea.
Say hello to my followers!
[JANE] They remember the nurse
who just wants to be liked.
The selfless ones who volunteer
for double shifts
just for the team.
I brought champorado.
Oh, is that Filipino or Mexican?
They both have it?
- Oh my god.
- [ROS FAKES SOB]
[JANE] The ones who
sacrificed and left their homes
just to care for strangers.
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [LAUGHING]
[JANE] All to look after
the patients
whose lives are about to change.
For better or for worse.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
And most importantly...
They make everyone
feel remembered.
With them, healing starts
with being seen.
Excuse me.
- [MUSIC TURNS EMOTIONAL]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[NOA SOBS SOFTLY]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JANE] They stay
because they matter.
You all told me
you would close the ward
if we didn't get metrics up,
but they are up.
And I'm gonna need you all
to keep your word.
[CLAPPING]
The numbers are fine,
but we don't even know
if they’ll pass
the next joint
commission inspection.
Sure, but that's a year away.
We can reassess then.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you sure it's a year?
Calendars speed up.
Especially when complaints
stack up.
["THE DENIAL SONG"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
["THE DENIAL SONG"
[MUSIC FADES]
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]