"Blue Lips"
(Episode 7)
Stop right there.
Sis.
Come here.
I knew you were acting
sneaky these past few days.
And sure enough, you
sneak back in the morning.
The bar has been too busy lately.
Liar.
I called your boss.
He said you left ages ago.
Who exactly did you go see?
I...
I'm really not lying, Sis.
I drank too much yesterday.
And I missed the last bus.
So I crashed at my bandmate's place.
Really.
If you don't believe me,
I'll give you his number.
You can ask him yourself.
Really?
Really.
I'll take your word for it this time.
Okay.
Sis, I'm going in then.
Stop right there.
Come back.
I have some good news.
The doctor said my
vitals are under control.
Once my condition stabilizes,
you can quit your job at Blue Moon.
And I can go back to work.
Our lives
will finally get back on track.
With you working at a place like Blue Moon,
I can never really be at ease.
It's fine. At the bar,
I know my limits.
Go on.
Stop drinking from now on.
Got it, Sis.
Looking sharp.
You even coordinated your outfit.
Is this...
Do I look bad?
You think it looks sharp too, right?
Look at Brother Mo.
Even he thinks it looks sharp.
Strutting around like a peacock.
I have to ask,
is that a compliment or an insult?
Definitely a compliment.
Ask Xiao Wu if you don't believe me.
What do you think?
Does it look bad?
You look better than a model.
Really?
Oh, right.
The money from last time,
I should have transferred it to you.
I just sent it over.
Also,
I transferred today's share as well.
Check it.
What are you doing here?
Only you intellectuals are
allowed here? We can't come?
Are you insulting me?
[Sister calling]
Looking so flashy today.
Having a second youth?
Hey, I'm working.
The stuff at home...
Let's grab a couple of drinks.
Ah Heng.
Pour us two drinks.
Brother Hao.
Let's talk outside.
Okay.
Something came up.
I'll be right back.
See you in a bit.
Hey, handsome.
Mind if I sit next to you for a while?
I do mind.
Don't be so stingy.
To be honest,
I love a gentleman.
Whenever I meet one,
I don't want to miss out.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
I don't think
that's necessary.
What's wrong?
Do you not like curly hair,
or do you just not like
me?
I...
Right.
He doesn't like you.
Brother Heng.
Something came up
today, so I won't be singing.
What's that supposed to mean?
I need a room.
Okay, please wait a moment.
All set.
What are you doing?
Interrogating me?
Cut the crap.
Tell me the truth.
What were you talking about just now?
Age, family income,
when to get married,
even picked out the kids' names.
That hurts!
Do you have any professional ethics?
When you're with me,
you're not allowed to flirt with others.
She was flirting with me!
That makes it even worse.
Teng Mo!
Teng Mo, what are you doing?
Pervert!
I'm a pervert?
You don't like it?
Stop talking.
Fine.
Let's continue then.
Teng Mo!
What did you call me?
Brother Mo.
Wrong.
Brother.
Say it again.
Brother, Brother.
Brother.
Teng Mo.
You know what, Shixian?
You look especially cute today.
You're so energetic today.
Did you take Vandacon?
I only take it when I'm
with people I don't like.
So you like me.
As if I'd like you.
There's no need to be jealous of others.
I only like you.
Shixian.
Do you have time these next few days?
Why?
The seasons are changing.
I wanted you
to come with me to buy some clothes.
Tomorrow...
I might not be free.
How about Sunday?
Sure.
We'll go whenever you're free.
Sunday it is.
Is there anything you want?
Or anything you want to gift someone?
No.
I...
I don't have anything I want to buy.
And no one to buy gifts for.
All right.
Have you been waiting long?
Why are you staring at me?
Nothing.
It just feels like the first time
I've hung out with you during the day.
It feels like a dream.
Don't exaggerate so much.
That store looks nice.
Let's go take a look.
That one?
Are you sure?
We're already here. Let's go.
It's fine, try again.
What is it?
Do you like this necklace?
No.
Just browsing.
Let's go.
Your neck is definitely missing something.
Why don't we buy it?
I'm really just browsing.
Didn't you say you wanted me to treat you?
Have you decided?
I...
Treat me to some ice cream.
Sure.
Let's go.
With all the money I
usually transfer to you,
I never see you buy any decent clothes.
You just wear the same
few outfits over and over.
Aren't you tired of them?
The audience must be tired of them too.
Didn't the boss at Blue Moon
give you a clothing allowance?
What clothing allowance?
Alright.
I'll cover your clothes from now on.
I can handle that much.
You always tell me not
to sing at Blue Moon,
but now you're spending money on me,
buying me all these clothes to support me.
Singing at Blue Moon...
That's just a hobby.
Even though I don't support it,
I'm not completely against it either.
But you're so young,
and you're drinking and doing drugs.
That's not okay.
What drinking and doing drugs?
I just go to Blue Moon to sing.
Alright, alright, just to sing.
Ultimately,
he still wants to find
a girl to marry, right?
Looks good.
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Are you sure you don't need a ride?
No need.
Alright.
Then this is it. Here.
All for me?
Of course.
With our relationship,
it's only right that I spend money on you.
A relationship...
built on money?
Got it.
Next time you perform,
remember to wear your new clothes.
I'm off.
You're back.
You bought so much stuff.
Where did you get the money?
The boss gave me a clothing allowance
to get a new look.
Are you upset?
No.
I'm just a bit tired lately.
Go get some rest.
Why hasn't today's performance started yet?
Xiao Wu got held up.
It'll start a bit late.
What happened to him?
He couldn't make it in
time from his day job.
He found a new part-time gig
as a tutor.
You didn't know?
No.
He doesn't usually
report his schedule to me.
He's still a college student?
Seeing how edgy he looks on stage...
He was the top scorer in
the college entrance exam.
That impressive?
So he goes to college in Jinyang?
He dropped out.
He's in a rush to make money.
He's that desperate for cash?
I wouldn't know about that.
You'll have to ask him yourself.
Anyway,
it's his private business.
If he doesn't want to talk about it,
it's not our place to ask.
But I think
he really is strapped for cash.
Look at all the part-time jobs he works.
The thing is, he hardly spends any money.
Well, for a guy,
needing money usually
comes down to two things.
Either he's sick,
or he's getting married.
I'm at work.
The stuff at home...
I was really just browsing.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Hurry up and get ready.
Don't be this late next time.
Got it.
Pretty handsome.
Yeah.
And still young.
At the very least, he
should have the chance
to see the woman he loves
wear a wedding dress for him.
You've got the wrong person.
I told you,
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I couldn't be mistaken.
He has the same blue lip balm as you.
Were you two together yesterday?
Did you sleep together?
Let go.
I told you,
I'm not interested in men.
Ah Heng.
Where's Wu Shixian?
He finished a while ago.
Do you want to check backstage?
Alright.
How do you explain this?
That's not even me.
Did you guys sleep together yesterday?
I already told you,
I'm not interested
in men.