[OVERDO]
[Episode 8]
Xiaolan.
I'm Susu.
I'm Susu, Xiaolan.
Susu?
It's me.
Xiaolan.
[Fang Mulan, the only daughter
of the Fang family in Nanyang]
Susu?
I know you.
No.
I don't know you.
I don't know you!
Who did this?
Was it Huo Mingxi?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'll never run away again!
I'll never run away again!
I'll take off my clothes
and sing for you, okay?
I'll sing for you.
I'm a good girl.
I'm not human!
I'm just a doll!
I'll sing for you.
Xiaolan!
I'm sorry.
I came too late.
I'll take you out of here.
Xiaolan,
I'm here.
[Huo Mingxi,
Master of the Huo Family's Branch]
Who are you?
Little girl.
You came right to my door.
You beast!
How dare you hit me!
I'll kill you!
Let's go!
They're not here!
Not here either!
Let's go!
Xiaolan.
Xiaolan?
Xiaolan!
The doctor said
she was covered in wounds,
had recently suffered a miscarriage,
and had been bleeding continuously
without receiving any medical treatment.
I don't know how she survived until now.
Think of something else.
There must be a way.
Susu.
Xiaolan.
You recognized us?
Qing, you have grown so tall.
Susu, you're so pretty.
You are both big girls now.
You only praise me for being tall,
not for being pretty.
You're playing favorites.
How did you leave the orphanage?
Did Nanny sell you?
Were you taken by the Huo family?
Don't worry.
We all escaped from the orphanage.
No one will hurt us anymore.
Good.
That's good.
It's so good...
to see you.
Yes.
We will never be apart again.
Susu.
We killed Huo Mingxi.
The Huo family
will definitely take revenge.
I'm not going to make it.
You need to leave Beicheng immediately.
We will never leave you behind.
I don't want to part with you either.
After I die,
take my ashes
back to Nanyang,
alright?
Alright.
I'll take you home.
I remember you said
Nanyang was your home.
When I was 9,
I was trafficked.
It's been 13 years.
I almost forgot my father's face.
I really...
really want to go home.
It hurts.
Sing me another song.
Okay.
Sing that one.
I will.
I'll sing it, Xiaolan.
Get some good sleep.
It won't hurt when you wake up.
♪ Spring comes and autumn goes ♪
♪ Time flows like a river ♪
♪ The wanderer grows weary
of drifting afar ♪
♪ Memories of childhood days ♪
♪ Spent playing at home ♪
♪ Feel as vivid as yesterday ♪
♪ Three thatched cottages ♪
♪ An old plum tree ♪
♪ We played hide-and-seek beneath it ♪
♪ Birds sang on the branches ♪
♪ Fish swam in the stream ♪
♪ Those were the simple joys
of carefree days ♪
♪ The happiness of childhood ♪
Dad...
Xiaolan.
-Xiaolan.
Xiaolan...
We will take you home.
[Beicheng]
Stay highly alert, everyone!
Search carefully!
Even if you have to
turn the station upside down,
you must find them!
The Huos haven't seen you before.
Take Xiaolan and go first.
What about you?
I'll lead them away.
I'll meet up with you later.
Go!
Take the gun to protect yourself.
Be careful.
Found her! Over there!
Where?
Move!
Watch out!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Don't run!
Over there!
-Hurry! Over there!
-Stop!
-Over there!
-Come here now!
-Hurry!
Stop!
[Beicheng to Feng'an]
-Stop!
Stop!
-Stop her!
-Stop!
Don't run!
She's on the train!
Hurry, get on!
[Beicheng]
Susu!
Leave here.
On the day you left,
the gentian flowers were blooming.
Didn't you say
you would show me the view?
I was planning
to sacrifice myself that day,
so my companion
could carry Xiaolan's ashes
safely back south.
But I didn't expect you
to follow me onto the train.
So I said those words to you,
trying to provoke you into leaving.
Get lost!
Don't you understand?
I approached you
only to use you.
Do you think
I really would like you?
If what you say is true...
then pull the trigger.
Susu!
What are you doing?
Just pretend that
you've never known me.
I had a death wish back then.
Letting the Huo family see you
deal with the murderer yourself
could clear you of suspicion,
which would clear the debt between us.
But I didn't expect
the Huo family to treat you like that.
So,
you only approached me from the beginning
to save someone?
On the train 3 years ago,
why didn't you explain?
Since you survived,
why didn't you come back
to find me over the past 3 years?
And since you knew
about my family situation,
why did you have to pretend
to be Fang Mulan
and marry my brother?
What exactly do you want?
You have too many questions.
That's another story,
and it comes at a different price.
Fine.
What price?
If I asked you to kill someone for me,
would you do it?
Kill who?
Master Huo.
Master Huo?
What are you doing?
Are you going to
crash straight into Master Huo
and take everyone down with him?
Isn't this exactly what you want?
What do you mean?
Someone tampered with
this plane, right?
You could fool others,
but I've known it all along.
You must have had an ulterior motive
in making
the aviation school's opening ceremony
happen.
At the banquet,
you seemed uneasy.
I also saw a foreign woman
snooping around the plane
several times.
Tell me,
what exactly did she do
to this plane?
Explosives.
Explosives?
No wonder.
You didn't want my brother
to get on the plane,
but you were willing to let me.
Didn't I try to stop you?
Ren Susu,
where are the explosives?
I don't know.
There's still time to land.
What do you mean you don't know?
What do you mean there's still time?
There's still time for you
to kill Master Huo with the explosives
in front of everyone?
Have you thought about a way out?
Are you crazy?
I told you,
what I do has nothing to do with you.
Then why are you on the same plane as me?
Do you want to die with me,
or do you just not want to waste a bomb?
Whatever you're planning,
you don't have what it takes.
Why are you being so foolish?
After landing,
listen to me.
Stop messing with the Huo family.
Stay by my side,
and I will keep you safe.
You?
You are too naive.
Me? Naive?
Fine.
What are you doing?
Rather than watching you throw your life away
because of your foolishness,
I might as well send you off myself.
That way, you won't end up
like you did 3 years ago,
failing to save others
and hurting yourself
while dragging innocent people into it.
I don't need you to send me off.
And I will never drag you into this.
There's a parachute behind me.
Put it on and get out of here!
Are you out of your mind?
Something fell off!
Principal,
something is wrong.
Do I even care about life or death?
Ren Susu.
Those who survive suffer even more!
Is that so?
Did the dead tell you that?
Let's play a game then.
There is only one parachute left now.
The winner gets to live.
The loser...
dies.
♪ How much love ♪
♪ Is enough to be wasted? ♪
Fine.
What game?
♪ I haven't forgiven you ♪
♪ So don't you forgive me ♪
Why is this plane giving off black smoke?
♪ Let the wildfire ♪
♪ Consume us and burn us to ashes ♪
Come on!
♪ Still, we choose to be moths ♪
♪ Flying into the flames ♪
Do you love me
or hate me?
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
I hate you!
I hate you so much
I want to tear you apart!
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
Correct.
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
Then let me ask you.
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
Do you love me
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
or hate me?
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
Take a guess.
♪ Forevermore ♪
You hate me.
Good.
You won.
Susu!
♪ Take away everything I have ♪
♪ Can you bear the weight of it all? ♪
It looks like someone was thrown out.
♪ I offer you my whole life ♪
Call an ambulance!
Evacuate the crowd immediately!
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
Hurry up
Bravo!
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
♪ Let the tears fall,
let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
Ren Susu.
♪ Forevermore ♪
You got guts.
See?
You can never be ruthless
at a critical moment.
So in the future,
don't pretend to be ruthless anymore.
Murong Qingyi,
we should have
said goodbye 3 years ago.
I let you down.
But now you have a new life.
Stay away from me
and live on.
Susu!
I've told you everything
you wanted to know
and everything you had doubts about.
And where I'm going,
I'll get there even if I have to crawl.
But that is not where you're going.
Also,
now that we've landed,
you should call me sister-in-law.
Ren Susu.
You are a liar.
Over here.
Qingyi!
How are you doing?
I won't die.
Cordon off the plane wreckage.
Get someone to inspect it.
If any problems are found, keep it quiet
and report to me.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me?
Everyone ran out to save you two,
and I hurt my foot
while people were pushing and shoving.
What happened?
Why did you risk your life
to follow Murong Qingyi
and jump out of the plane?
Are you really not afraid of death?
What else could I do?
I had to clean up
Tasia's mess.
It was indeed a close call this time.
But luckily, no innocent people were hurt,
and the Huo family
didn't suspect anything.
What on earth did you talk about
with Murong Qingyi?
He interrogated me,
asking where I've been
for the past 3 years,
and why I came back.
He also asked me...
Do you love me or hate me?
He asked if you had ever loved him?
How do you know?
Isn't it always the same old thing
between a man and a woman
in those stories?
What did you say?
I just said something to get out of it.
He really can't wrap his head around it.
Where else could you have been
these 3 years?
Does he really think
playing someone else is so easy?
Of course you've been training in Nanyang.
Susu,
do you have feelings for him?
I wouldn't.
[Murong Residence]
I don't want to drink it.
It's disgusting.
I had Mrs. Wang add rock sugar to it.
It's not bitter.
Have a taste.
You didn't go to Miss Fang
to show her your concern,
but instead brought soup to me?
You don't have
your sister-in-law's skills.
She used you as a shield
and only suffered minor injuries.
She is now out watching a play.
If you ask me,
Mother and I are the ones
who need to be nourished.
The opening ceremony
was ruined by him.
My Lady.
Tell me,
did you do it on purpose?
You knew today was Qingyu's big day,
and you deliberately caused trouble.
No wonder everyone says you're a jinx!
Go call all the servants in.
Yes.
Everyone, come in.
From today on,
I don't want
to hear any disrespectful terms
of address in this house again.
Some of you servants
have been working in the Murong family
for a long time,
so I overlooked your past use
of disrespectful terms
of address.
But starting today,
if I hear it one more time,
you will be expelled
from the Murong residence.
Understood?
Understood.
Get out.
Why were you so fierce?
You always
believe him and protect him.
He's my own brother.
If I don't believe him,
who should I believe?
It's still a little bitter, isn't it?
Have a candy.
Jinrui is always like that.
Don't mind her.
I don't care about her at all.
Sister-in-law fell from a plane,
yet she came out completely unharmed.
This Miss Fang,
who was pampered growing up,
is quite capable.
What are you trying to say now?
This Fang Mulan is no ordinary person.
Be careful.
You think too much.
Drink some more.
Get some rest early.
The old dog Huo must die.
You expected me to let
such a good opportunity slip away?
I couldn't do that.
If we also harm the innocent,
then what's the fundamental difference
between us and the Huo family?
If you hadn't stopped me,
the old dog Huo
would have boarded the plane
and been blown up in the air.
Then there wouldn't be so much trouble.
What about the aviation school teacher
who was flying the plane?
Should I have just let him die?
What?
Is your hatred
more important than his life?
Just because you acted on your own,
Nanny Sun has now returned
to the orphanage unharmed.
Our mission failed.
All the thrilling moments had played out,
and the plan was fully executed,
but in the end,
it all came to nothing.
It was like I was
performing a play on stage.
Whenever I see him,
every old wound on my body
festers
and oozes pus again!
I wanted to hold back my hatred,
but I couldn't!
The stench of rotting flesh fills my nose!
Only when he dies...
can I find peace.
If you had succeeded today,
such a quick death
would have been too easy
for that old dog Huo.
Rest assured.
That old dog Huo—
I will definitely make him pay
and face the consequences.
The problem now
is what we should do about Nanny Sun.
With such a huge incident
at the aviation school today,
the Huo family will definitely do
their best to protect the old dog Huo.
They will investigate
who blew up the plane,
so naturally
they won't have time to care about
Nanny Sun,
who has just returned to the orphanage.
That's right.
The orphanage will be poorly guarded.
It's the perfect opportunity
to make a move.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
I need to get some things back.
Tasia,
I understand you have a valid reason,
but if you act on your own again
without my permission,
don't blame me for showing no regard
for our sisterhood.
Understood.
[Renxin Orphanage]
Stop dawdling!
What are you looking at?
One-eye.
What are you doing here?
Get up, get up! Stand up!
I told you that
when those rich masters and madams
who can donate money are here,
you should hold this stupid doll
and cry your eyes out in front of them!
Cry hard!
Cry until they give in and donate!
Look at you guys.
♪ Fantasies reduced to ash ♪
You can't bring in donations,
♪ In a raging fire ♪
and you can't even work properly.
No one is allowed to eat tomorrow!
Come here and line up!
♪ Those caught in the wake ♪
♪ Now tell only gray lies ♪
Can't you hurry up?
You're such gluttons.
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
Let's go!
♪ Of the past ♪
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
♪ Wandering beneath a pitch-black sky ♪
♪ I smell no sorrow ♪
♪ Let the story start over ♪
♪ With a new beginning ♪