[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Miss? Which room number is...
Dessalyn Baldemor's?
On the right, Ma'am.
[MARLA] Quantum Entanglement
is a phenomenon
in quantum mechanics
where two or more particles
become linked and
share the same fate,
regardless of the distance
separating them.
If Quantum Entanglement
is accurate,
we can say that if something
happens to one particle,
the other instantly "knows"
and reacts the same way,
even if they're very far apart.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
[SOBBING]
So, if we base it on real life,
there are people we're deeply
connected to.
We immediately sense...
if something happens to them.
Daphne!
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBS] Daphne!
Daphne, why would you leave me?
Daphne, we'll reach our dreams
together, remember?
We were gonna find a new virus.
We were gonna name it after you!
Daphne, why?!
Why?!
Daphne... [SOBBING]
Daphne, we were gonna become
National Scientists together.
Daphne...
I don't care if you want
to copy how I dress,
if you want to copy how I look,
everything I say,
I don't care if you want
to copy me.
Please, come back.
Why?!
Daphne!
Don't leave me!
Daphne...
[SOBBING]
Please, you're my best friend.
Come back, please...
Daphne!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BAWLS]
Why, God, why?!
Daphne, why?
- [ERNESTO] Marla?
- [SOBBNIG]
Marla?
Daphne!
Why would you think I'm dead?
I'm still here!
Are you okay?
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Silly of you to assume
I'm dead...
Well, you look okay.
You're joking again.
- What happened?
- She was...
No! I...
I tripped...
then...
I fell, then...
I hit my head.
I'm lucky Lester was with me.
He brought me to the hospital.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Huh?
What?
Oh! [CHUCKLES]
I'm going to buy something.
I'll just buy something...
- Your favorite.
- Yes, Pa.
Thank you.
I'm going out. Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Of course.
[SIGHS]
I see...
You do look okay.
Your condition
seems stable enough...
Yes.
- You're covering up for Lester.
- Yes...
Oh, I... No!
Marla...
What happened?
You can tell me anything.
Promise,
I'll keep it a secret.
You can tell me anything.
[NYX] Daphne!
Daphne!
Who?!
Who...
who did this to you?!
Why?
Girl, you're such a kind soul.
- You don't deserve this!
- Hey, Nyx.
- The dextrose!
- What happened to you, girl?
- Nyx!
- What right did they have?
- You're too rowdy!
- They had no right to hurt you!
Why?
- You'll pull the dextrose!
- Nyx!
Hey!
What happened to you, girl?
- Her dextrose...
- I'm fine. Come on.
You're going to injure her
even more!
What are you doing here?
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's have a ceasefire.
We just wanted to see and check
on Daphne's condition.
How are you?
Contrary on the popular belief,
I'm actually not heartless.
Okay.
Well...
thanks for visiting.
Promise.
I'm really fine.
It's not like it's critical.
Besides,
I wouldn't die
even if you prayed for it.
Don't worry.
No matter how vile
or cheap a person is,
I will never pray
for someone's harm.
Shhh...
I said ceasefire!
Ceasefire!
- What is that?
- Why is there a bra?
- Why do you have a bra?
- You wanna check?
- You wore that?
- No, crazy! It's an extra.
It's so hot here
in the Philippines,
and I sweat a lot.
I always bring extra bras.
Those aren't drag marks.
They said you fell
down the stairs.
What's that on your arm?
Your elbow?
Your neck?
What's that on your neck?
What is that?
A bruise!
Admit it.
What did Lester do?
Isobel!
We need to call the police.
- Daphne...
- We have to take him
- and all of them accountable...
- Hey!
...for leaking all of our nudes.
Why are you protecting Lester?
Where the hell is Lester?
- The audacity, the nerve!
- Please stop.
- I swear, if I see him...
- Babe!
Speaking of the devil,
April, call the police.
I will detain this
freaking douche right now!
Enough.
What the hell, Isobel?
Can you, like, bring your
voodoo shit somewhere else?
Oh, and your demon elves
as well?
- Demon elves?
- Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Move!
You're just going
to stay silent?
Just like that?
You're just going to
let him do it
- over and over again?
- Isobel...
You don't know
what's gonna happen next!
You're gonna end up
like your mom,
who was black and blue!
- We need to call the cops!
- Exactly!
That's why we have
to hold him accountable
- for leaking all of our nudes!
- Can you give her a break?
- No!
- Shut up, Lester!
- Give her a break!
- You did this to her!
- Why are you protecting him?
- Please.
You don't have the right to...
- Please stop.
- You did all of this!
- She's my girlfriend.
- Enough...
- Who the hell are you?
- Stop it!
- Do you love her?
- I said enough.
Oh, God, I said enough!
Baby, are you okay?
Guys, can you just leave,
please?
Just leave!
Daphne, we can't just
leave you here with Lester.
Marla, you're not gonna
say anything?
Wait.
Hey!
[DAPHNE]
Just stop already, please!
Stop the car!
Girl, if she scans
for probabilities again,
her eyes are going to roll back.
Stop it.
See, she's getting dizzier.
poor girl.
- Go away, Lester.
- Ba... baby?
Don't even touch her.
Are you okay?
Can you move?
Guys, can you just...
give her some space!
Come on!
Babe, are you okay?
- I'm so sorry.
- I need to rest.
Please.
I want to be left alone.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- You heard her.
- You heard her too.
Leave.
- We heard her.
- Leave her alone too!
- I leave?
- Exactly.
Just me. Alone.
All alone.
Is that okay?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys, let's go.
Let's let her rest.
Shoo, shoo, shoo.
- Go.
- Go, Lester!
- Bye!
- Walk!
Babe, let me know, okay?
- Quit yapping around.
- Just go!
- Go ahead, Lester.
- Guys!
- Can you also leave as well?
- You can go ahead!
Go!
Babe, let me know, okay?
Shut up!
- I said quit yapping, loser!
- Go, Lester!
Gosh, you guys are insane.
You guys are insane!
Marla.
What?
You know Cole is no different.
Please, rethink your choices.
And you know I'm right.
Time and place, Isobel.
God.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[COLE BREATHING HEAVILY]
Rhodium...
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Lithium...
Palladium...
Hydrogen...
Helium...
Silver...
Hydrogen?
Helium...
- Lithium...
- Maybe it's time
we forget about Harvard,
and you becoming
the President of this country.
It would be too much to handle
for idiots like you!
- Sir...
--
Sir, please.
Please, Sir...
You want us to
just call Marla here
so she'd recite all that
for you?
I suppose it's only right that
you two get back together.
Because you're too stupid
to function!
Imagine, she still beat you
in the rankings
despite being involved
in a scandal.
You should be able to
put Marla in her place.
Because I only accept...
Top 1.
Yes, Sir...
Yes... yes, Sir...
You need to do something
about that girl.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
You should be able
to lead that relationship,
not the other way around.
Do you understand?
Yes... yes, Sir.
Yes...
Goddamn it!
Aside from being useless,
you're a nuisance!
You're up next.
I already expect
nothing from you,
yet you still bring me shame!
[APRIL] Uncle Jack is here
looking for you.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir!
[SOBBING]
[COLE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm the one who called Uncle.
They'll be out until
this evening
checking out some property.
Thank you, April.
Thank you.
April, wait.
April...
April, please...
Help me out here.
Please do something
about Marla.
You have to convince her
to give way to me so that...
I can be Top 1.
Please?
April, please help me.
How am I supposed
to do that, Cole...
when you ruined
their trust in me?
Just do it.
Do it.
I think you should be wary
of the other girls below you.
Me included.
We're all coming for your rank.
You're already Top 2, but...
Sir still beat you up like that.
What if you fall to Top 3?
Or...
Top 4...
5...
6...
11?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
April.
Don't get too cocky.
You're going to regret that.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BRASS KNUCKLES CLINK]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[STUDENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- [DAPHNE] I said enough!
[WARREN] Congratulations,
Miss Top 1.
It's so hot outside,
you should stay hydrated.
Thank you.
Hey, congrats to you, too.
You're great, Top 10.
I'm inspired.
Well, I was...
inspired.
Warren
I just want to say,
I'm so sorry for--
For choosing Cole?
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
I decided to give him
another chance.
And I know, my choice is...
questionable,
maybe controversial,
given everything
that's happened.
But...
he really proved to me
that he wasn't the one
who leaked my photos.
I'm sure you really thought
about that.
I just want to know, Marla,
why...
...I didn't even get
a chance from you?
Marla, I just feel that...
I also deserve to have a chance
as your friend, right?
Because if...
you gave a chance to...
someone who hurt you,
why not a friend, right?
You know, Marla,
water is boring,
but it helps quench the thirst
especially when it's hot,
Coffee may be
your favorite, but...
water is what you need
right now.
Marla...
I am a nice,
yet very boring person.
I'm not...
Not controversial.
Or anything.
Marla, you are safe with me.
I know I can't give you
the adrenaline rush of...
a rich or bad boy type of guy,
but, I can offer
something better...
it's peace and safety.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hey, come on.
- Be ready, okay?
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Cole.
Look, she's with Warren.
Marla...
I might not be the one
that you want.
I'm the one that you need.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COLE] Hey...
[COLE CHUCKLES]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
What's this?
I just wanted
to let the whole school know,
that my girlfriend is Top 1.
For you, babe.
- [STUDENTS TEASING]
- Mh-mm!
Aw!
[COLE] And, of course...
this one too.
[MARLA CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
For you.
Thank you.
- [LESTER] Woah, the move!
- [CHUCKLES]
[LESTER] Hey, hey, hey!
[COLE] Like it?
[CHUCKLES]
Aw!
I love you, babe.
You're so sweet.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Marla is hopeless after all.
Her mind functions
like a jellyfish around Cole.
So what's the game?
Hi, I'm so very sorry,
I'm fashionably late,
but you know what,
it's better late than ugly.
That's true.
Okay.
What were you up to
that you ended up late again?
No, who were you up to?
- Don't tell me it's Migo.
- Huh?!
Nyx! Just because you kissed?!
Oh, god! No! Ew! Yuck!
Never! I just styled my bangs!
This is why I was late.
My goodness!
Well, I'll believe you.
You like your men a little...
fruity.
Hey! Girl, for real?
Right here? Right now?
Are we going to be judging
each other's tastes in boys?
Keep in mind that
we became friends
because we're all stupid
when it comes to men.
So... don't mind me.
Just ignore me,
because I'm just...
cooking something.
So what's the plan, leche flan?
It's not that easy
to target Cole,
he's way too charismatic.
- He's everyone's favorite.
- [COLE CHUCKLES]
And not only that,
he's smarter than you think.
Our dad made sure
he's fit to be the next
president of this country.
That's why it'll be such
a good feeling
to see him fall
from his ivory tower.
[APRIL] We need to find a way
to bring Cole down.
Maybe it will humble him.
Because right now he thinks
he's some sort of...
immortal.
Playing us for fools.
He's treating me like a
disposable pawn in his games.
If it's so difficult
to beat Cole
we should come up
with something like...
get the sidekick first,
also known as...
Lester.
Those guys are only tough
because, of course,
their connections.
Also known as,
Principal Mckenna.
And those suck-up teachers.
Yeah, right.
- Lester.
- Hmm.
Cole needs to feel
he's the only one left.
- [NYX] Yes.
- So, if Lester falls...
I'm sure it'll cripple Cole.
Besides,
we can avenge Daphne.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS SINISTER]
I have a really good idea.
But it'll be harder
if it's just the three of us.
That is why we need
to have our reunion.
Simply put, we need a girl group
comeback right now.
So what's your plan?
Leche flan.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Class?
Reminders.
Two major activities
are about to happen
in the coming weeks.
The first one, as you know,
the annual Science Fair
is about to happen.
I have received your proposals,
but I'd like to congratulate
Ms. Briones
for receiving a grant from DOST.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
[APPLAUDING]
Mr. Javier, I saw your proposal
for the Science Fair,
but it's still rather vague.
Please see me
at my office during dismissal.
Next,
Comet...
C/2023,
also known as,
TsuchinshanATLAS
can be seen
in the Earth's atmosphere
this weekend.
For the added points,
whoever can build
the best telescope
and get a photo beautifully
will get exam exemptions.
And whoever can take
a nice photo
of International Space Station,
will also get plus points.
But we challenge everyone,
the more innovative, the better.
[MUSIC STOPS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Babe.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[COLE] Did you miss our...
Did you miss our room?
Gosh, when was
the last time you're here?
Hey.
You okay?
Come here.
It's like you're new here.
Sit down.
Don't you smell anything?
[SNIFFS]
Lavender...
Vanilla...
Citrus?
Yes.
I know you so well. [CHUCKLES]
I know those are
your favorite scents.
That's why I combined them all,
and...
I did it all at the SOSH Lab.
[MOUTH CLICKS]
Thank you, it's nice.
Uhm...
We'll just see each other
at school?
I really need to go.
I still have things
for the Science Fair.
Uh, Marla, wait.
Turns out, I've got nothing
to do today.
If you want...
I can help you out.
Just give me a copy
and I'll help.
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
Here.
Wait a minute.
- [MARLA] Oh my god.
- [COLE GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Your dad should really stop
hurting you.
Let it go, Marla.
This isn't all...
All that serious.
I'll just flex it?
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
I'm really sorry
I didn't know you were suffering
because of me.
I know he's still hurting you--
Marla.
I'm willing to endure
everything for you.
Just let it go.
What's important, Marla--
What matters now is...
we're together again.
You know, what really
worries me, Marla...
What?
You can tell me.
I'm too embarrassed to say.
It's because I feel that,
you lost your trust in me.
Marla, I don't know if...
I could still regain the
trust that was lost.
I don't know,
it bothers me, Marla.
Cole.
I trust you.
Yeah.
Maybe you believe that
you still trust me.
But you know, Marla...
I feel as if you look
at me differently now.
I've let my emotions
get the best of me.
But please, Marla,
I hope there's still a way
to show you
that I can still be trusted.
I hope you can make me feel...
You can make me feel
that I can be trusted once more.
Cole.
Believe me,
I trust you.
I believe you.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
M-Marla, sorry.
I thought I knew you.
You have to believe me.
But I still care about you,
Marla.
That won't change.
I'd take all the punishment,
if it means not
losing you again, Marla.
Maybe I can learn
to trust you again.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
No.
It's okay.
[MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA INHALES SHARPLY]
I love you, Marla.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I can't wait to go home.
What?
There you go again,
acting snobbish.
We went here to spice things up,
you better quit complaining.
It's showtime.
[PEOPLE CHUCKLING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
[MARLA] Yes, yes. Hey, hey!
- We'll get going.
- Okay, okay.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] Wow.
I got this just for you.
Star chart, diamond star...
- Oh, okay!
- you can find your star.
- Okay.
- Look through here.
Okay.
I'll get one drink.
- This one too--
- Hi, Daphne.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hi.
[APRIL] Um...
Can we please talk?
I have something to show you.
No pressure.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're pretty.
Cole? Cole!
[LESTER] Cole, my bro!
Wait up, babe. Just stay here.
[LESTER] Hurry up!
[COLE] Don't leave, okay?
[MARLA] Don't take long.
Hey.
Who's this?
Where's our guy?
Earl just left.
Dude, turn it down a bit.
Hey, guys!
[COLE] Listen.
This is tradition!
Every comet that passes
is an excuse for us to party!
May the best photo win!
- [LESTER WHOOPING]
- [COLE] Drinks are on me!
- Cheers!
[COLE] So, let's party up!
[CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nice hair, huh?
[CHUCKLES]
[MARLA] I thought
you don't like parties?
Truth is, I don't really
dig events like this.
But what can I do?
This is the...
best place to spot the comet.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's why Cole chose
to host his party here.
Give me that.
That's my shot!
Get your own drink, bro.
You saw someone
pretty enough here?
His family's really powerful,
aren't they?
He can host a party here
in a heartbeat.
[WARREN] Then look
at all these people.
Pretending to go stargazing,
yet all they really want
is to party.
- I'm getting sleepy.
- Huh?
It's giving uncle vibes.
[CHUCKLING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You okay?
I'm here.
Always here to listen.
Really?
Even...
- after what I did to you?
- [WARREN CHUCKLES]
I'm really sorry.
There are a lot
of girls here, right?
[PHONE CHIMES]
- Hey.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
[COLE] I'm still talking to you.
Who are you talking to?
Who's that?
[LESTER] Bro.
Daphne.
- There.
- Let's say...
she's feeling a little
adventurous tonight.
[CHUCKLING]
Whoo!
I thought she wasn't
talking to you?
- You fold so easily, don't you?
- [LESTER SIGHS]
Bro! You even acted
like a sad boy.
Daphne's just playing hard
to get, okay?
- She's playing hard to get.
- Hard to get?
[LESTER] Hard to get.
That's her game!
Want to bet on it?
- Okay.
- I bet you...
my allowance for one month.
- One month?
- Roughly 30...
- Thirty?
- Thirty-five...
Thirty-five?
How about 50,000?
That she misses me.
- Game?
- Fifty thousand!
- Fifty thousand?
- Still cheap.
Raise it, up, higher!
My last offer is 50,000.
Whatever, just don't drag
me down with you.
I don't know if it's appropriate
for us to be...
just friends.
Knowing that...
that...
knowing that you have...
a boyfriend.
I don't want to overstep.
Thanks.
But,
in your whole life,
didn't you ever...
go against the law, or like,
or, okay, not against the law.
No, sorry about that.
Like, have you ever
broken a rule?
Like in your life? Ever?
Uh...
You know what, bro,
I'm all in for the...
adventure!
- Don't drag me into that.
- [LESTER SCOFFS]
Do whatever you want.
Okay, fine.
Stay here, okay?
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay?
- Please, if anyone--
- Okay.
- If anyone asks...
- I said okay.
If anyone asks,
I'm at home, okay?
Okay, whatever.
[CHUCKLING]
[LESTER] I'm so excited, bro!
I jaywalked before.
[WARREN] But I only
did that once.
Just once.
[CHUCKLES]
- That's it?
- Mm-hmm!
- Are you sure?
- And...
right now?
The way I'm still
talking to you.
I think...
that's basically breaking
the rules already.
[LESTER CHUCKLES] Whoa.
Daphne, you naughty girl.
What the hell is this?
What?
[CHUCKLES]
No way, no way!
Huh? Okay.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Okay.
"Take off your clothes."
Okay, okay, okay.
"Then...
Cuff yourself and
put on the blindfold.
I want you helpless."
Okay! [CHUCKLES]
Whoo!
Wait! Whoa!
Whoa! Hold up!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Babe, is that you?
Wait up, babe, I haven't...
Wait, wait, wait. Okay.
Relax, relax.
Let me just...
[LESTER] Take the lead, babe.
[LESTER GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES] Whoa!
Whoa!
Whoa! Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right.
- [METAL CLANKING]
- [LESTER] Whoo!
Okay, all right, cuff, yes.
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
- [WARREN CHUCKLES]
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I wanted to ask you, like,
have you ever done--
[COLE EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [COLE] Hi, babe.
- [MARLA] Cole?
I miss you.
- Why'd you suddenly leave?
- Hey, hey, hey.
I was looking all over for you.
Who's this with you?
Why...
[COLE] Why are you
with this creep, babe?
[MARLA] Shh! Stop.
We're just talking.
Didn't I tell you to never talk
to my girlfriend again?
Marla, I think, there's...
a better spot there
for the comet.
I'll just go there.
Good decision.
Enough, hey.
I don't ever want
to see you here.
You're drunk. You're drunk.
Look at you.
Look at you, you're so drunk!
Babe...
[COLE] We were just talking
about the comet.
- The comet?
- Yes.
That's why we're here.
- But I'm here, right?
- Stargazing.
You know what?
[MARLA] What?
I think there's something
between you two.
[COLE] Babe, I'm jealous,
like legit.
[MARLA] Cole, my God,
can you stop drinking?
[COLE] No, babe, please?
Please don't go near him again.
- Pretty please.
- Stop drinking.
[MARLA] But stop drinking first.
Just one more.
- How annoying. How pushy.
- Please?
Come on. One last more.
- Last.
- Yay!
[CHUCKLES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Bye-bye!
At least you're here,
right by my side.
Oh, my God, stop it.
- Last one.
[COLE] Hey.
Can I have, please?
Thank you.
- Hey.
- [COLE GRUNTS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] Last one, okay?
Of course.
- [CUFFS, STRAPS CLINKING]
- [LESTER] Ooh.
Whoo!
Baby, the choker's
a little bit too tight.
I can't...
My neck...
[LESTER] Daph,
you're not playing around.
You're not playing around.
[GROANS]
Daph, wait. [CHUCKLES]
[PULLEY TIGHTENING]
Hey, what...
What is this?
Okay, all right, uh...
[CHUCKLES FAINTLY]
Okay, Daph, can you...
Can you, like, go easy on me?
Like, don't go too hard on me?
[LESTER CHUCKLES]
This is my first time.
This is...
Um, you know what?
Screw it. Fuck it!
Go hard on me. Come on!
Come on, baby!
Let's go!
Good boy.
[MAN] Are you ready, Lester?
Huh?
Daph... babe?
You sound like a man.
Uh...
You okay, babe?
Do you have a sore throat?
I mean,
I've got lozenges in my bag.
I mean, if you want to,
you know, eat one up.
[MAN] Ready?
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
[LESTER] Babe? Wait!
Daph! Wait, wait, wait!
Daphne! Daph! [LAUGHS]
Daph, it hurts!
Wait, what is this?
- Daph, what is this?
- Relax, Lester.
- The fuck? What the fuck?
- Relax.
What the fuck is this shit?
[MAN] Just think of it as
a little science project, okay?
So, this apparatus is
a lie detector machine.
But...
- with a twist.
- With a twist?
[MAN] If it senses that
you're lying about
everything that
I'm going to ask you,
it'll work on its own.
Intense tickling, Lester.
Until you turn so pale
or you tell me the truth!
The truth?
- What the fuck?
- The truth.
Bastard, you're not Daphne!
- Wait, what the fuck?
- Ready?
- One more?
- No!
- One more time?
- No, what the!
Who the fuck are you?
- [MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LESTER LAUGHING, SHOUTING]
Lord, Lord, Lord! Please!
Fuck, fuck!
Wait, wait!
[LAUGHING, SHOUTING]
[LESTER] Please, please,
please, please...
Gosh, babe, I got so drunk.
I told you so.
- Babe, did you enjoy?
- You drank so much!
- I liked that drink so much.
Are you dizzy?
- Yes.
- Good grief.
- Let's eat out.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
Wait, wait.
[PHONES CHIMING]
[COLE] What's that?
[MAN] Did you and Cole leak
the nudes to the campus?
Yes or no?
[LESTER] Nudes? No.
No! No!
It wasn't us, no!
No! It wasn't us! No.
[LESTER LAUGHING]
It's live.
It's happening right now.
[LESTER GROANING]
[MAN] Wrong answer.
What answer?
[MAN] But...
did you have a group chat
where you send nude photos
of female SOSH students?
Yes or no?
[LESTER] No!
No, no, no, no!
We don't have a group chat!
- No!
- No? No?
[LESTER] Please let me go--
- [MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
- [LESTER LAUGHING]
Yes! Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
[LESTER] Yes, yes, yes.
- [MAN] Yes?
- [LESTER] Yes.
[LESTER] I need...
I need to pee.
- [MAN] Answer this first.
- [LESTER GROANS]
[LESTER] I need to pee.
Please stop.
- [LESTER WHIMPERING]
- [MAN] But...
Cole is the mastermind, yes?
No!
What mastermind?
Cole? No!
No!
[LESTER] What the fuck!
The fuck, let me go.
Just let me go! Just...
- No!
- [BEEPS]
[GRUNTING, LAUGHING]
[WHIMPERING]
No! I'm peeing!
I'm peeing.
I'm peeing, no!
Please, stop, stop...
No...
One last question.
Please stop. Enough.
Did you hurt your girlfriend?
- Daphne?
- Yes, Daphne.
No!
I love Daphne!
I love Daphne, you bitch!
Hey! [LAUGHING]
[MAN] Is it true, Cole?
Did you leak the nudes
of Marla and the others?
Are you all gullible?
What?
You believe some guy in a mask?
Huh?
I couldn't do that to Marla,
Right, babe?
We even got back together, see?
We're already holding hands,
can't you see?
Babe,
please tell them that I wouldn't
do that to you, babe.
Right?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LESTER LAUGHING, SCREAMING]
I wanna pee!
Please...
Babe, I know where this is.
I'll go with you.
[DOOR OPENS]
[COLE] Marla, here.
Lester!
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
Who did this to you?
Shit.
[METAL RATTLES]
[PHONE RINGS]
Marla, I'll be right back.
Marla, wait.
- Try to help him.
- Okay, okay.
Hello, Sir?
[ADOLF]
Are you out of your mind?
Sir...
What is this trouble
you've gotten into?
[ADOLF] You can't even handle
a simple prank?
Sir, sorry, sir...
[ADOLF] If this leak
affects our family's reputation,
you are not going to Harvard.
Sir, sorry, please, it's...
[ADOLF] Fix this now!
Yes.
[ADOLF] Or I will send you
straight to military academy!
Or don't come home!
Okay, Sir.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wow, great.
You unlocked it?
So, is this you, Marla?
Is this part of your grand
plan to destroy me?
Cole?
What are you talking about?
I've always been good
at solving puzzles, like...
like... these!
So, of course,
I've unlocked it.
Marla,
you can't play me anymore.
What?
We both know that only Nyx
can make a machine like that.
And this is probably
Isobel's scheme.
Are you working together?
You're all ganging up
on me, Marla?
Cole, enough.
You're scaring me.
You may have the
photographic memory, Marla,
but you can't outsmart me.
You can't fool me.
Marla,
because everything I did...
I did it because I love you!
That's enough.
You're just drunk, okay?
I'm not drunk, Marla!
Good for you
that I still accepted you.
Huh?
Despite the entire school
knowing everything about you,
they've seen all of you, Marla.
- Cole...
- Okay.
Let's just go home, please?
Let's just go.
Enough.
You wanna know if I was the
one who ordered April
to leak your nude photos?
Do you really wanna know, Marla?
What are you saying?
Yes.
I coerced April to do it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?
I asked April
so it won't be
traced back to me.
You wanna know why I did that?
I did it because you were
in over your head!
You think you're better
than everyone else, Marla.
But I know your weakness.
Like every other girl
Love.
Just like your friends.
And like your mom.
Love, Marla.
Love, right?
[CHUCKLES]
You may be smart, but you're
stupid when it comes to love.
[CHUCKLES]
[SMACKS] Fuck you.
Fuck you!
You stupid fuck!
Marla, stop.
You used me.
You manipulated me.
You sick bastard.
Marla, stop.
- Stupid.
- No.
Stupid,
stupid boy.
Stop.
Marla, stop.
Always keep this in mind...
No, no, stop!
[COLE WHIMPERS]
...whatever you do...
Stop, Marla, no, stop!
- Stop! Stop, Marla, stop!
- You'll never beat me!
- Just stop!
- You don't stand a chance!
- Make it stop!
- You're just a stupid coward.
- Stop, Marla. Marla, stop!
- Hiding behind
your father's name?
- Stop!
- No, no, no, fuck you!
- Top 5 are idiots!
- You stupid,
stupid boy!
[CRYING, PANICKED BREATHING]
Marla, stop!
Why? Why?!
Why would I stop?
- Why would I stop?!
- What'd you say?
You better get used
to being second place
because that's all you are.
- Marla, stop!
- Second place!
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS] Ah!
[PANTING]
[MARLA EXHALES SHARPLY]
Cole, stop!
- [GRUNTS]
- [MARLA SCREAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]