[OVERDO]
[Episode 9]
Come.
Good boy.
Sit. Come.
Sit on my lap.
Good boy.
Help me
complete a small task
before you go to sleep, okay?
Come.
All the children in the orphanage
will come to this room
and eat a piece of candy like this.
Because
this is your only way
to never
go hungry.
Come.
Pick a color.
You like the pink one?
These different-colored candies
represent different parts of your body.
The pink one
means you volunteer to give up a leg.
Now, I
will let you experience
how a broken leg can keep your belly full.
Who is it?
Dazhuang?
Always pranking.
Who are you?
Are you human or a ghost?
It's so late.
Why aren't you resting?
Y-Y-You...
Y-You are...
You are so forgetful, Nanny.
We just met earlier today.
Don't you remember?
I remember!
You are Miss Fang.
How could I not remember?
I...
Come.
Come, quickly.
You little brat.
It really hasn't changed at all—
not a single bit.
Quick.
She is an honored guest.
An honored guest.
He's too dirty.
There is a dog hole over there.
I crawled through it back then.
But...
you won't need it anymore.
Go back quickly.
Y-Y-You are...
You are...
Su...
Susu?
Impossible.
Susu is already dead.
How could a dead person
a-a-appear here?
Seeking revenge?
An evil spirit is seeking revenge?
Nanny.
My body's warm.
I'm not some evil spirit.
It's...
It's warm...
Warm...
You're still alive!
Thank goodness!
You've become a noble lady!
I am alive,
but do you remember Xiaolan?
L...
Xiaolan...
Xiaolan?
You have killed too many people—
I'm afraid you can't remember.
I...
I can't remember.
An evil spirit is seeking revenge.
I'm not an evil spirit.
But I can still seek revenge.
Help.
Somebody help!
Help!
Somebody!
This orphanage is always so cold.
Don't those lingering wails
haunt you every night?
Those you've murdered—
I'll avenge them personally.
This is your honor.
The orphans' files over the years
should be here.
Found it.
Why are you here?
She's not dead yet,
don't you know?
Don't worry,
I'm not here to pester you.
It's simply because
you are Qingyu's fiancée.
The things you do are sloppy
and full of flaws.
I don't care,
but Qingyu's reputation
must never be tainted by murder.
The Huo family arranges for police
to patrol here every night.
They could appear at any time.
Did you plan what to do?
Do you think I'd be unprepared?
[Renxin Orphanage]
Deal with this quickly.
Oh my goodness!
Where are the adults in charge?
They went to the new building.
The new orphanage is under renovation.
They are all there.
It's raining so hard.
What are you doing here
instead of sleeping upstairs?
Practicing singing.
Nanny Sun said
we didn't sing well enough during the day,
and the nobles didn't like it,
so she told us to practice more.
Mister,
could you have a listen?
No, no.
I'm just patrolling around.
I'm leaving now.
Mister,
do you also think we don't sing well,
and are unlikable?
That's not it.
Then let us sing for you, Uncle.
We learned Polish especially for this.
Nanny Sun said
the nobles would surely like it.
Start.
I didn't expect these children
to be so clever.
They just come from a sad background,
but they are smart.
Well sung!
We need to speed up.
All right.
That's it for today's singing.
Everyone go upstairs to sleep.
Hurry up.
Go to sleep.
Singing out here so late.
You all live on the second floor?
Go to sleep quickly.
Who is it?
Who's there?
Who?
I-Is...
Is anyone there?
Anyone here?
The matter is settled.
I have no intention to celebrate
this murder with you.
You don't need to follow me anymore.
Ren Susu.
What else do you want to do
with the name of my brother's fiancée?
Both our hands
are tainted from what happened tonight.
I suppose there is no need
for either of us
to leak this,
bringing trouble upon ourselves
and destroy each other again,
right?
Ren Susu,
what right do you have to lecture me?
Just now at the orphanage,
if that nanny crawled out
to call for help,
what would you do
if you were trapped there?
The corridor outside the room
is 36 meters long.
At the stairwell,
there is an iron threshold
25 centimeters high.
In her state
of hypothermia and blood loss,
Nanny Sun couldn't possibly crawl out.
I left her with one breath
to let her experience fear.
Yet you gave her a quick death.
Taking a step back,
I'm your brother's fiancée.
No matter what I do,
only your brother
has the right to question it.
You don't have the right.
Whether I have the right or not
is not for you to decide.
Xiaolan,
♪ Fantasies reduced to ash ♪
I finally did it.
♪ In a raging fire ♪
This is just the beginning.
Rest assured,
together with the wronged souls
of the dead children,
♪ Those caught in the wake ♪
♪ Now tell only gray lies ♪
I will take revenge
on those who did evil back then.
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
♪ Of the past ♪
Those animals
-chose us like goods.
-Come here. Hurry.
-If it weren't for you...
-Go!
Protecting me and Xiaoqing all along,
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
we might have died a long time ago.
Go! Go!
Hurry up!
♪ Wandering beneath a pitch-black sky ♪
Go!
♪ I smell no sorrow ♪
Xiaolan!
Stop!
[13 years ago, Nancheng]
♪ Let the story start over ♪
Susu, push this aside!
♪ With a new beginning ♪
Susu!
♪ When our paths cross again ♪
♪ I shift my gaze away ♪
Susu.
Xiaolan.
♪ Only then can I ♪
Drink some water.
♪ Rid all hope ♪
Drink slowly. Don't choke.
Susu, eat some of this.
I'll figure something out.
♪ No longer able to break free ♪
Don't eat it all at once.
♪ From the shackles of destiny ♪
Just like this,
♪ No more questioning ♪
we grew up in that hell,
♪ The cruel jests of fate ♪
until the Huo family found us.
♪ Now I know to appreciate ♪
♪ The calm as it shatters ♪
-Nanny Sun.
♪ No longer craving ♪
♪ Absolution from the heavens ♪
Baby,
♪ I've walked alone ♪
so you're lying here.
♪ Into the deserted wilderness ♪
-Playing dead, huh?
-Nanny.
♪ Hunting slowly ♪
She's sick.
I'm telling you,
♪ Waiting for someone
to sink deep into it ♪
as long as she's not dead,
she has to come with me!
Get up!
She's sick.
♪ In the chaotic rainy night ♪
Nanny, she's really sick.
-The Huo family taking a liking to you...
-She's really sick.
♪ If we brush past each other again ♪
-Is your blessing.
-Nanny, she's sick.
Get up right now!
She's really sick!
♪ And have only hatred ♪
-Nanny!
♪ There's no difference ♪
She's really sick.
She's really sick, Nanny.
If she's sick...
♪ No innocent yesterdays ♪
who'll go make the money then?
I'll go, Nanny.
I know how to dance.
♪ All trapped in the mud ♪
I can dance.
I'll go.
-Let me go dance.
-You go.
I'll go.
♪ There's no room to retreat ♪
What kind of pipe dream are you having?
♪ It's more dangerous to leave ♪
I can... I can go.
I can go too.
Xiaolan.
♪ Without an end in sight ♪
I can go.
Xiaolan.
-Xiaolan.
♪ My intuition is my only faith ♪
Nanny.
-Nanny.
-Nanny,
When I woke up,
♪ Pull out all the stops to deliver ♪
Xiaoqing told me
♪ A show-stopper ♪
that you went to the Huo family for me.
Xiaolan!
-You never came back.
-Xiaolan!
♪ Wandering beneath a pitch-black sky ♪
♪ I smell no sorrow ♪
♪ Let the story start over ♪
♪ With a new beginning ♪
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
This lass is interesting.
♪ Of the past ♪
Send her to my place later.
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
[Serial Number: Number 37, Category Bing]
[Code Name: Xiaolan]
Susu.
Xiaolan.
Do you think we will ever
be like those girls outside—
living a normal life
and going to school?
Why not?
A lifetime is long.
One day,
we can be like them,
studying in a classroom
and walking on the streets.
We can also go watch the sunrise
and the sea
together.
Xiaolan.
The sun has risen again.
Nanny Sun is dead.
Rest assured,
all evildoers
[Zhang Xiaohe] [Zhang Xiaocui]
[Lin Xiaoshuang] [Yang Xueqin]
will be punished.
[Axiang] [Lianmei]
[Wang Abao] [Tang Lengxiang]
What I'm worried about is,
if the Huo family gets anxious,
what will happen
to the kids at the orphanage?
The police and the press are keeping
a close eye on Nanny Sun's disappearance.
The Huo family doesn't dare
to do anything right now.
Not only that,
they will treat the kids even better.
You've thought it through.
The Huo family
should be making a move now.
That's right.
Next,
it's time to send the Huo family
on their way.
But where would the Huo family
conduct
their dirty business?
Where do we even start?
The Huo family's business
is only ever open to
the rich and powerful.
We can't go wrong
starting with those people.
Nanny Sun is missing.
What about the ledger?
The ledger has gone missing too.
Sir.
Could Nanny Sun have been bribed?
Then, will the orphanage
be exposed?
Previously,
you were supposed to take the plane
at the school's opening ceremony.
But the aviation school said
there was a plane malfunction.
I think someone tampered with it.
Now Nanny Sun has gone missing.
Connecting these two incidents,
I'm afraid someone
is targeting the Huo family.
Send someone to the orphanage
to investigate
who went there last night.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Don't just ask the adults.
Sometimes,
kids know more.
Understood.
If you're free,
come to the theater
and watch a show with me.
I'm going back.
I have to try on wedding outfits
with Qingyu.
Qingyu?
What about Murong Qingyi?
Are you really so set on revenge
that you won't waver at all?
There's no need
to drag him into my business.
Keeping his mouth shut
is the best thing he can do.
You know this—
I only settle old scores,
but I never dwell on the past.
[Fresh Series]
Miss Fang,
the wedding dresses you ordered
are all here.
When will Principal Murong arrive?
There are some measurements
that need to be adjusted.
Soon.
[Current Affairs Daily]
[A grand opening of the aviation school]
All the newspapers in Nancheng
gave us front-page headlines
for our school's opening ceremony.
Even out-of-town newspapers
sent telegrams
saying they want to interview you.
[Current Affairs Daily]
You are wise, Principal.
What's with the flattery?
I got the planes
and I was the one who flew them.
What's so wise about him?
Of...
Of course,
Young Master Qingyi is also
smart and brave.
Then tell me,
should the Cheng Army
be inherited by me?
Well...
Go do your work.
You've been angry all day.
What do you want to say?
Speak.
Aren't you going to try on
wedding outfits with Fang Mulan?
Why aren't you leaving yet?
You were calling her Sister-in-law
a couple of days ago.
Yet these few days,
you're calling her by her full name.
I'm not worried about Mulan.
But you—
joke around,
but know your limits.
What did I do?
Scolding me right to my face.
Is she really a good person?
She is your sister-in-law.
Principal!
Principal,
something happened.
Ms. Ye...
Ms. Ye took the children
from the assisted elementary school
to a volunteer teaching class.
They were surrounded by tabloid reporters
asking about the opening ceremony.
They are now fighting.
Fang Mulan is waiting for you
to try on wedding outfits.
Tell your sister-in-law for me
that I have an emergency today.
I will go with her another day.
Ms. Ye...
Shoo!
What are you doing?
Just you wait.
How dare you yell at me?
I am a reporter.
-I have the right to report the truth about the aviation school!
-Are you okay?
You can interview me,
but I have to take the children
to class now.
Can you let them have their class first?
News is time-sensitive.
That's right! You must tell us today.
Is there some shady business going on?
-Quick. Tell us.
-Tell us. Tell us.
-Don't leave.
Don't leave!
Move!
Don't be afraid. It's okay.
The children are terrified.
I'll take you back to school first.
Okay.
It's all right.
I'm here.
Come.
Line up.
Let's go.
The film.
This is the first and last time.
It won't happen again.
Qingyu must have been held up.
Please wait a bit longer, sir.
It's all right.
Miss Fang, don't worry about it.
No need to wait anymore.
My brother is tied up
with important matters today.
As for the wedding dress,
I guess you can't try it on today.
Miss Fang.
There are several fabrics
for this wedding dress.
They are all imported from France.
If we don't finalize it today,
I'm afraid
we won't have enough time.
Seeing that Second Young Master's figure
is almost identical to the principal's,
could we
trouble you to try it on for him?
What do you think, Sister-in-law?
Then I'll have to trouble you,
Second Young Master.
But I'm not the groom.
I don't want to try it on.
The wedding is approaching.
Even if you don't want to do it for me,
this suit is for your brother, after all.
I'm sure
you don't want our wedding
to be delayed by such a small matter.
You always ignore me.
Now that you need my help,
how can you still act so high and mighty?
Then please, Second Young Master,
could you try on the wedding suit for us?
Your expenses at Xanadu for this month,
I will reimburse them.
Miss Fang is so generous.
Since you need my help,
I'll definitely
try this suit on properly today.
This is the set
the principal personally chose.
Miss Fang is the daughter
of the Boat King of Nanyang.
This outfit
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
is too conservative.
It doesn't look good.
♪ The more icy ♪
♪ Our present clash ♪
Try that instead.
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪