( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Happy Birthday to you
Make a wish
Thanks, thanks, thank you
Hope our ACE keeps being prosperity
Let's get rich together
May everyone of us
hits over a million in sales next month
What's wrong
Uncle Ma
I'm Sorry
Sorry
What happened
What's up
What the hell happened
In fact, we were planning
to quit last month
But then we thought, Uncle Ma, your birthday's coming up
so we stayed to celebrate with you
before leaving
Think you've grown some wings
Barely learned to walk, now you wanna fly
Did you forget
what you're like when you first came in?
Who was it that raised you up and made you shine?
Sorry
"sorry" and that's it?
You guys really got some consciences, huh
If "apology" fixed everything
what do we need cops in the world for?
Never mind
People aim higher
It's only human nature
It's all good
Thanks for staying to celebrate my birthday
Hope things go better and better with you after the leave
Alright?
Lily
Yes sir
Keep an eye on them
Make sure anything belongs here
they don't get to take a damn thing with them
Copied
What are you still standing here for?
Waiting for me to give you bonuses?
Get the hell out
Move
I bet
They're jumping ship to
the new club that just opened
Ungrateful bastards
The top five have all jumped ship
Who the hell's gonna carry the numbers this month?
Wy is she here?
Who tipped her off?
Nothing on this block stays quiet
Qin-jie
You think you can keep something this big from me
No way, we wouldn't dare
That's right, Qin-jie
In fact, we've already made arrangements
The new hire's starting in a couple days
Is that so
I'd really like to see how you turn things around
All the hot shots are gone
It's my face on the line, the major investor
You guys might not care about but I sure do
If the numbers dip again this month
I'll take the club back and run it myself
By the way, Ma
Happy birthday
Thank you
Take care
Where can we find so many newbies
in such short period of time
It's super tiny
The air of freedom
What is this place anyway
ACE
What about B and D
A-B-C-D-E, this isn't a cram school
What are we doing here for
Yeah, feel like we're about to get sold off
Let me make it clear, even though I am good at fucking
but this part of me ain't for sale
Stop guessing
My uncle owns the shop
Might be a good place to lay low
You should have said so if it's family, let's go
Just pray we don't run into anyone we know
Food is served
Let me take these
wow, so tasty
Yu Chuan, bro.
I don't think your uncle should've run a bar.
Why?
These guys, should do
With such good cooking skills, he should open a restaurant
Just them
Are you sure it's gonna work?
Definitely
I think they’ve got more potential than Leo’s group.
They may just become a hit overnight
They came here to lay low
Would they want to stay and work?
No worries, let me find out
Tony
The favor you mentioned —what exactly is it?
Yu Chuan
As you know we’re in the service industry
the favor I need from you guys is to
"serve" our customers properly
Got it, got it
Bringing food and drinks to the table
easy-peasy
Is that it?
Of course not,
You'll also need to mingle with customers, drink with them
Get the vibe going, you know
Occasionally, mix up some special drinks for them
like a bartender?
Something like that
Isn't that a gigolo?
Gigolo?!
They're called male companions
Wait...
Does that mean there are lots of female customers who will
come up to me automatically?
Chang YiHao, this job suits you perfectly
You can make good use of
your "high efficiency" skills
Tony,whatever you want me to do
I'll do it
Male companion
First time I’ve seen someone so eager to be a gigolo
and so exciting about it
I told you, it's called male companion
How many times do I have to say?
A host is a host
Boss Biao
Li Xun got away
What do you mean
Looks like Li Xun
had already noticed
Our guys reported back
When they went in
the room was completely empty
They only saw pillows disguised as someone lying in bed
Seems like he was prepared
You think I'm easy to fool, huh?
Can't even handle such an easy job
Go find out
where Li Xun is hiding, now
If you let him escape again this time
If I'd known earlier
there's such a job as a male companion
What would I have wasted time to get certified as fitness trainer for?
If this was five years ago
I'd be the pretty boy king of the male PR world
Cha Eun-woo
More like a porn actor!
Cha Eun-woo, my ass. Don't talk nonsense.
Well?
Did you notice there are only two beds?
Rock-paper-scissors
Loser sleeps on the floor
One round only
No cheating
Let's go
Scissors, rock—
hold on
Don't those two have to play?
Never mind
Rock, paper, scissors.
Sleep on the floor
Hsu Chenghan, sleep on the floor
I'm going to poop and take a shower
You guys, get moving
Behave yourselves
I can do this myself
Better let me do it
Dad
Mom
I'm sorry
I was unfilial
I failed to protect you
But please rest assured
The ones who harmed you
I'll make them pay
Uncle Li
Auntie Li
Don't you worry
I'll protect Li Xun
from being hurt
Take the med
Rest early tonight
Thank you
Do we need to say anything between us?
Don't worry
We’ll have a chance to bring Chiang down
What's with that face?
Don't overthink it for now
Looks like we have a lot ahead of us
I've prepared some clean clothes for everyone
Anything else you need
feel free to tell me anytime
So comfy, so nice
All clean
Indeed, one with lots of potential
Uncle Ma, right?
Uncle Ma, I'm telling you
You really bet on the right horse this time
I'm known for being the best in the fucking dept.
Can you stop?
Sorry, man
Even though everyone
has no choice but to be
trapped here temporarily to help
business is business, friends are friends
There are some rules in this workplace
I still need to make clear to you
This is your employment agreement
As long as you're here
you must follow these rules
Work for accommodation
Fair enough, right?
Check this out
$2000 per hour
It really pays high, man!
that's right
And that doesn't even cover special circumstances
What do you mean by
special circumstances?
You'll find out when it happens
OK with me
$2000 per hour
Are you kidding me?
You're asking a billionaire to work as a male companion
You two, to the right
You two, to the left
Where on earth did he run off to?
Okay
We'll go this way
I've already checked that spot earlier
Check on the right side
I'd better stay in the ACE for now
lay low until things cool down
Hey, let me tell you something
Hotpot isn't hotpot without fish balls
You know why
'Cause things can go smooth, all wrapped up
Got it?
Rolling with Boss Bo is the best
Got meat to eat and soup to drink
beats the hell out of fighting and killing on the streets
You ass kisser
Only when you're full to get energy to work
C'mon, toast to the boss
Come
To Boss
Just joined less than a week, I already get to have a gun?
Tonight is a real deal
Yo, be careful
Stay sharp, man
I'm telling you, Boss Chiang don't tolerate screw-ups
Looks like F.T. Crew know how to enjoy themselves!
At this hour
still sitting there and having hotpot
Boss Qi, should be "yuan-yang" hotpot
I smell spicy dock blood and pickled cabbage broth
With a nose like that
You should be a dog
Brother Zheng
Bo-zai, you sure know how to enjoy yourself
You ain't even got the money yet
and already diving into the hotpot
Brother Zheng, Chill out
Only when you're full to get energy to work, right?
Same old rules
Goods for goods
We're on the same side!
You idiot
I freaked out, man
Where's your gun?
My gun's empty, I...
You low-life idiot
Boss Qi
Didn't I tell you not to go
Boss
Lord Guan bless me
My Jesus help me
If I make it out alive this time
I'll pay my vows at Xingtian Temple
I'll do charity
I won't steal donation money anymore
I'll light candles and pray
Amitabha
Amen
Look, it's so pretty
Rest in peace
Amitabha.
I'm sorry
So, this is what diamonds look like
Relax
Take it easy
You won't be able to take these with you
ain't taking them with you
Good
Show for tomorrow night go smoothly
Boss Chiang
The deal went south
Everyone's dead
Both the dope and the diamonds are gone
Boss Chiang, call for you
Hello
Chiang, that guy of yours, Pan Hao…
Hasn't he learned the rules?
When the deal blew up
He stole my diamonds and took off
Are you sure it's Pan Hao who took the diamonds?
The factory's surveillance caught it clearly
So tell me - does Pan Hao look down on Fe-Hu-Tang
Or he just doesn't take you seriously?
Pan Hao has disgraced Azure Dragon Syndicate
It's my fault for not keeping my man in line
I'll handle this myself
A-Qiang
You know me, I'm not the patient type
Don't keep me waiting for too long
Otherwise,
even I can't promise
what kind of ugly shit I might do
Are you threatening me?
How the hell do you train your boys
Get Pan Hao back. Now
Yes,boss
Everyone, get up!
We've got a major situation
What's going on?
Qin-jie
You are here so early today
Are the newcomers here yet?
Yes, they're all here
Watch out
I specifically take my girlfriends to check out these rookies
You won't disappoint us, will you?
Guarantee the ladies will like them.  You'll all be satisfied
This way, please
I look really handsome from this angle
and this look is impeccable
chop chop
Today is a matter of life and death of the ACE
Move it up!
Remember
Service comes first
Customers above all
that's right
Just do your work as long as you're here
since you've already signed the temporary contracts
Then you must work hard and do well
okay?
Today we have to satisfy our VIPs
Alright?
Roger that
Yeah, got it, got it
Okay, I hear you
Don't worry, have faith in yourself
It's gonna work based on what they've got
Alright, a quick recap
Do not ask what does the customer do for living
Cheers — clink glasses
Hand over a tissue, brush their fingertips
Whisper secrets by their ear
While you're being as seductive as possible
You must also make your customers feel honored
What's the key?
You gotta be playful
Where are they?
They'll be out here in a minute
Ma
We've worked together for so many years
You should know me well enough
The competition in this industry is so fierce
Leo and his team got poached
If these rookies can't hold up
Tell me
What should I do
Don't worry, Qin-jie
Tony and I will manage to boost the sales for sure
Let's wait and see
Our honored guests
Welcome to ACE
Now
Allow me to grandly introduce our
Brand-new team
Ladies and gentlemen
The muscle hunk — Hunter
With diamond-level figure
and overflowing virility of hormone
Every inch of his muscle would capture your eyes
The intellectual caring guy — Daniel
Tender and dependable
Whether it's heart-to-heart chat or relieving your sorrow
He can always brighten your mood instantly
The versatile boy — Asa
who knows everything in all aspects
Being with him
We guarantee your time at the men's club will be marvelous
Can I get an ACE
ACE
Now, the bad-boy hottie —  Jay
Handsome with the naughty charm
His burning eyes
will absolutely light up your adventurous desires
Next, the sunshine boy
JUSTIN
passion romance
Definitely the best boyfriend pick for the night
Come
Greet
Hello, beauties
Zhou Qin, these rookies are really good
When have you ever said no to
This one is really tall and handsome
I'm telling you, those shoulders are broad
Right... I like that tall one the most
That fair-skinned one
Don't you fight me for him
This one
He just winked at me
Please, stay calm today
Stop scaring them away
Shape up
Take good care of my besties
Do your best
to take good care of us
I like this one, I'll take him
Don't you fight with me
You're way too quick!
Fine, he's all yours
Miss Lin, you have great taste
Justin won't let you down
Come, drink with sister
Come, come, come
Come
Sis, please have a drink
You, drink three glasses first
I...
Sorry, can I drink water instead?
Water instead of liquor?
Excuse me
I come here to drink and have fun
You don't drink
If you don't drink, what fun do I have?
Because I
Sis, Daniel has a stomach ulcer these past few days
How about I drink for him
just to cool you down
Well⋯ it depends
Okay
Not too shabby
I will drink with you, then
Hurry up, what's dragging you?
How come your arms are so hard?
Sis, I've got something even harder
You're so nasty, such a devil, I'm not playing anymore
Come
It's really so hard
Hurry up and serve
Pretty good
Why don't you stick by me today
and serve me properly
Sis, do you play finger-guessing game?
Of course
How about number-guessing?
Okay
Then you go first
Sure
Five
Ten
Fifteen
Oh no, you're all wet
Let me help to wipe it clean
Sorry, I'll go change
No
How could you run off to change and leave your guest waiting?
That's rude
Sorry, sis.
I am not being professional
My apologies
Let me wipe it for you
Those muscles
they can be built easily
is that true?
I can show you how
I don't believe it
I want you to train me in person to get this body in shape
Sure
Training my ass! You crazy bitch
You're hopeless
Are you aware of your age
Girl, you're old enough to know better
Your metabolism is so slow now
Come on, save that for me, will ya?
What’s all this fuss?
I know my body is amazing
But I still think my butt could be perkier
Such sagging butt and you want him to touch?  Forget it
Come, let's go have a word, now
Move! Get lost!
Where are you going?
Get back here!
Really piss me off!
Sis, you drag me in here in such a hurry
Do you have something to tell me?
Don't talk
Do something to make me happy
How could I not fulfill such a simple request?
Let's see how you perform, then
Don't worry
I'll ensure your satisfaction
Would you like to dance?
Then⋯  teach me how
This feeling
Isn't it just right?
I'm furious!
That bitch Song always likes to play tricks
I'll never hang out with her again
Sister Chang, don't be mad
Let's have a drink to chill
Sis, how about
letting him hang out with you in the VIP room too?
there could be unexpected surprise for you
Nah, not my vibe at all
I'm into guys like Hunter⋯ you know, all muscles
Sis, are you mad?
Yes, I am
How can someone look so pretty even when they're mad
you'd be even prettier if you smiled
You really are the sweetest
Qin-jie
The new team is so popular
You shouldn't worry about the numbers for next month, right?
What's the rush?
The show just started
Tofu, anyone?
Me! Me! Me!
Thank you
Anyone else?
I'll get some sauce
Dow you want sesame sauce
Try some
Thanks, Uncle Ma
Smells so tasty
Everyone
I really want to thank all of you today
for helping our club to get through the toughest time
Thank you
Thanks, everyone
This club
is run by me, Uncle Ma, and Zhou Qin
Zhou Qin is also the owner of this building
and the biggest shareholder
She's very pleased with how you all did today
However
if possible
I'd like to ask you to help out for couple more days
We'll find new staff as soon as possible
It's our duty, we'll go all out
As long as it takes
Why are you guys acting like this
Free food, free lodging and we even get paid
Where can you get such a good job?
You're the only one who thinks this way
Well, tell me
Where can we go now
The customers here are too upbeat
I can't handle it
How about this
if you run into any difficult customers in the future
Don't worry, leave them to me
I'll take care of it
You'd be more than happy if everything was handed to you
Each to their own needs,“each rider to their own mount"
Each rider, huh?
I promise, one month top
I'll get the whole crew together
Yu chuan, what do you say?
I
It's alright
If it's really inconvenient for everyone
You don't have to
No pressure
We'll figure something out
They say raising kids won't provide for your old age
But we poured our sweat and tears into
raising the kid from nothing
Since he's not willing to lift a finger for us
what else can I do?
Fine, fine, fine!
I agree
Are we good now?
I knew it, my Yuchuan is the sweetest, most thoughtful person
Alright, if there are no further questions
That settles it
Okay, we're all in agreement
I believe Pan Hao won’t refuse
Deal
Let's stay for a full month
Great, the deal is sealed, then
Pretty sure everyone is very tired today
I'll get off your back now
If there are any questions
let me know
If not, I’ll head out first
Have some more
Thanks, Tony
boys, take your time
I'll have Lily to get you more food
Take your time
Thanks, Uncle Ma
Come on
Don't be shy, make yourself at home
Eat
Cheer up, bro. right?
Have you seen this guy?
Any news about this guy, notify me right away!
A big bounty on him
Don't run
Stop running
Stop
Bunch of idiots