( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
NO
You don't even make sense to the logic of the universe
Bite bite bite
All day, man
Pan Hao
Pan Hao, is that you?
Pan Hao Pan Hao
Hsu ChengHan
It's really you
This is crazy
Still the same lame-ass look
Why are you an attendant staff here?
Wasn't it said you went abroad
after graduating from junior high
Attendant
Don't run
Not safe here, let's talk somewhere else
Even the dogs won't stay here
Why are you here?
Ain't it 'cause I stole my boss's diamonds
Why did I say it out loud?
What do you mean
Why do you have that ID badge
Do you know this guy?
Looks familiar
Pan Hao
Wasn't me
Get him
Over there
Stop running
Don't run
Stop
Bunch of idiots
Sir, are you alright?
Do you know how to drive
Are you okay?  Sorry
Are you hurt
What the hell? Road hazard rookies
sorry sir, sorry, my bad
You're not hurt, are you?
Be careful next time
You hear me?
I'm really sorry
Why the hell you two dressed like a couple?
Bullshit, that's too much
Are you serious?
You're pretty sick, bro
Didn't think your imagination to be greater than mine
You have a very serious
cognitive frequency dislocation
You should be wearing my patient gown instead
No man, you..
why do you dress like this
Why am I here
I was in an underground fight match
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
And then
Then, I went to the hospital for a check-up
The doctor said
I have Triggered Cerebral Split Syndrome
Triggered Brain Damage with Samrtmouth Syndrome?
Are you even listening to me?
Yeah I was
Long story short
Whenever he sees blood,
Another personality pops out
turning him into a relentless killing machine
You can see him?
He's my roommate
His name is Chang YiHao
wait, I mean what's wrong with him?
Why does he keep smiling at me like that?
Nothing's wrong with me
The quack is the one with problems
He said I got behavioral hyperactivity disorder
specially in the fucking department
That matter
In short, he's too good at fucking business
His brain doesn't stop
Neither does his body
Day or night
He's always on overdrive
Here I come
One more time
Again?
Let's do it again,
Let's change the spot
Are you done?
Almost there
That's enough
Stop
Damn bro, you really can fuck, huh
I admire your talent
Don't you think it's weird
Everyone likes people who's good at fucking business
Am I wrong to be too good at it? Am I?
For real?
Hand it over
What do you guys want
Grab him
He's the mole here to jack our brain juice energy
He's with them
Get him
Let go off me
Run
Let him go
So many people
Sticking your neck out will bring heat
That's Brain-Rage Syndrome
Must be new comers
So agitated
Fresh meat
New comers new comers
Did they hurt you?
new...
Yo, are you cleaning the floor or actually fighting
Swing harder, man
So hard!
There's even harder part
stop it
I’m not playing anymore, you devil
Come
so nasty
Sis, please have a drink
You, drink three glasses first
Sorry, can I drink water instead?
water instead of liquor?
Excuse me
I come here to drink and have fun
If you don't drink, what fun do I have?
Li Xun and Pan Hao are at the ACE?
Just found that out when I took the girls there
to check out the new crew
Figure I'd ask you to come over for discussion
I was thinking
What if we just took Pan Hao
made him handing over the diamonds,
and used Li Xun to take down Chiang
Wouldn’t that be
killing two birds with one stone
But if Pan Hao refuses to hand over the diamonds
we would be stuck
We need a solid plan to get those diamonds
What about Li Xun?
I have ways to make him come out on his own
Then I’d like to see
what clever trick my smart man comes up with
Weird
Why does Zhou Qin look so familiar
Where have I seen her before
Working out this late
So hardcore
Let me tell you something
Skip leg day in your 30s
and your "engine" will stop working sooner or later
Seriously
It's not weakness that ruins young men
but forgetting to eat your greens
That's the real truth
Come on, come on
I'm good, I'm good
Not weak
I'm telling you
Did you see how those girls
went crazy over our muscles
We gotta train harder
Can't let the customers down
Can some of us get some sleep?
Dude, why did you throw that at me
Wasn’t me
Keep it down
I told you, you slurp too loud
You’re too noisy
Shower's mine—I gotta poop
I called it first!
My poop's about to come out
Wait up, I'm coming
Hey
please wrap this up for me
Pan Hao
Rou Rou
Rou Rou, this is
I'm your senior schoolmate, Zhou Limin
Make yourself comfortable, it's on me
Thanks, senior
Pan Hao, have a seat
What do you like to eat?
Take whatever you want, don't be shy
I'm going to the restroom
Be right back
I’ll go with you
Nah, I’m good
You guys chat
I'll be back soon
alright, be careful
I think anyone
can see the gap between us
I'll cut to the chase
If you truly care about Rou Rou
you should've known better what to do
Who can provide her happiness
I don't need to spell it out, do I?
This is the birthday gift I prepare for her
Look at these diamond earrings
Don’t they suit her perfectly?
I asked my dad to get them
from England just for her
You won't find these anywhere in the market
I remember Rou Rou said she wanted to try horseback riding
I'm taking her to Tamsui tomorrow
for horseback riding
then to Bali for the sunset
Why are you telling me this?
Just to remind you
Not anyone
gets to like her
Now, tell me
am I qualified?
Joe
Boss Tony
Wipe that tables clean
the customers see everything
Wipe it clean
Yes, Boss Tony
Andy
Yes
Don't miss the spots behind the booths
Yes, sir
Lily Lily
Boss Tony
where are my
where are my handsome
glorious babies
Coming right up
You'll be satisfied
My five new darlings
Tonight's your debut
Don't let me down
I can't wait to show off
Stop the shaking, will you?
You'll scare the customers off
What do you know
this is my hormone charm
Of course we don't
After all, we're not like you
shaking the pecs all day long
Sounds like jealousy to me
Cause you've got no muscles to jiggle
no pride to wiggle
Everyone
How are we doing?
Tonight is your debut
bring your A-game
No problem
leave it to me, Chang YiHao
I'll make every guest who come
fall in love with ACE
Where’s Pan Hao? Haven’t seen him
Probably hiding somewhere practicing
Or still napping
Don’t tell me he bailed
What's the matter?
We're about to start in minutes
go find him
I'll go
Listen up
Tonight's my big night
nobody screws this up
Pan Hao
Should be safe if I stash it here
No one will find out for now
Tony said to get ready
Why are you slacking
I was just tidying up
What are you hiding
stashing something like a thief
Are they the diamonds
you stole from your boss
How did you know
Who told you
So this is what a diamond looks like
Tell me
Chenghan once said
you got some kind of Cognitive Frequency Disorder
I didn't believe it
Now, it might be true
Makes sense—if you really had so many diamonds
why hole up in this shabby place with us
You'd be wining and dining in style out there, right?
Bro, take my advice
cash in your pocket is what matters
Now hurry and get ready, okay
Later—move it!
What's wrong?
You seem down
This job is absolutely brutal
I have to write proposals
Do company's accounts
and review contracts
Meanwhile, I'm slammed during the day
still have to entertain clients with my boss at night
It's killing me
That really sounds tough
How about this
I'm good with computers
I could hack into your company’s system
and shut it down for a whole week
So you can get a break
How can you be so sweet
Come here
and drink with me
Come
Wait a second
what you need right now isn't the drinks
Here
This relaxation tea I made is only for you
to release the stress
Try it
No one wanna have tea here
I'm here to drink and relax
Come
Here
Drink up
No, I can't...
That's right
Beautiful
This one is specially made for you
“Full Moon Temptation”
Take just one sip
You'll feel
its magic instantly
What the hack is this?
It's Jay's exclusive creation
Not everyone gets used it on the first sip
How about this
Let's go to a private room
I'll get you a classic Martini
and arrange something special
Now, that sounds about right
This way, Gorgeous
What the hell...
Seriously?
Hello... Wake up
No kidding?  You pass out after just one drink?
Tony, what's the matter with him?
I'm truly sorry
What's wrong with him
He's not in a good shape today
How about
I get someone else who's
handsome, fun and can really drink
Does it sound good?
And then?
Did that cop really see a ghost?
They found out the taxi driver
was dead 3 years ago
That's it?
What a crappy story
Asa, other than story telling
what else can you do?
well
Ladies
Not feeling it yet?
Come
Get them a round of shots on me
Asa...
He just loves telling stories
He's a big fan of ghost stories
How about this
I have those two dancers on the stage
to come and keep you company
Switch things up a bit
Sure
Jacky Jerry Coming
Hello, beauties
Miss Lin
This opening dance is specially prepared for you
Hope you like it
You look even better today
Sit
Thank you
Come here
All these drinks tonight
are my appreciation
for your dance
You're so kind
That means a lot
I promise you won't regret tonight
Incredible
You got me
In that case
What comes next
I don't need to spell it out, right?
How about
I change the position
Let's play another round
A different position
will bring you a completely different experience
I get the feeling
you're aiming for
something else
You've been busy all morning
Probably haven't eaten yet, right?
I went out of my way to get dim sum from your favorite place
Have some while it's still hot
Leave it. I don't have an appetite
That won't do
You'll ruin your health if you keep skipping meals
Fine
I'll have some
Boss Chiang
You wanted to see me?
You can't even handle Li Xun
How many damn court summonses do I have to deal with?
I,
The CEO of Azure Dragon Syndicate
running in and out of court all day long, tell me—
does that make any sense?
I'll take care of it this time, I promise
Again with "I'll take care of it"
Always the same line
What about the diamonds?
Did you find them?
I've narrowed it down to a few spots
We'll have updates soon
Ah Biao
This time
if you screw up again
get ready
to join Brother Zheng
and keep him company
Don't ever let me see this stuff again
Get out
Yes, sir
How long has Ah Biao been working for me
and he still can't handle such a simple job
Don't be mad
You still have me, don't you?
No...
I can't drink anymore
Beautiful
You really are my soulmate
What a major murder scene
Such a lightweight
Here you go
Can't even cover yourself properly
Geeze
Pan Hao, do you want...
we'll continue after you wake up
It's gonna be plenty
Let's drink
Looks like they need some serious training
Fine, let you guys get some sleep first
Beautiful, get beneath
It's me
Get ready to take actions
Location
Westside factory
I'm going out to get some stuff
then straight to the dressing room
None of my business
Don't oversleep
or Tony will get mad
I already set the alarm
You'd better..
Hi Tony
Idiot
You're the idiot
Ugh, what kind of day is this?
Is this finals of the screwing-around competition or what?
Go hand out flyers
Why me?
Or else?
Hurry up
Get up and face the reality
Such shitty performance
How come I'm not standing in the middle
This flyer is not qualified
You've got a man worth hundreds of millions to be a male model
You two, to the right
You two, to the left
Where did he run off to anyway
Okay
We'll take this way
Sun Rou Rou
Let go off the girl
I'll give you guys a break this time
Who do you think you are
What are you doing?
Don't push it
You think you're tough
Get lost, you all
Psycho
Wait and see
Don't run if you've got nuts
I scare myself when I go crazy
You're bleeding
Let me take you to see a doctor
No worries
This is nothing
How about you
were you scared?
ouch, it hurts
So you say
Let me take care of your wound first
Let's go
Watch out
Okay
Hey
since you're the hero today
I'll buy you a drink after class tomorrow
as a token of appreciation
Really?
I'll order the most expensive one, then
Deal
Not exactly a cool hero
At least I scored
Isn't this my reward
Are you still playing?
Pan Hao, hurry
hitting on girls, huh?
Coming, just a second
bringing the girl to the course
Coming
Hold this for me
Showing off
I don't need to try
Stay here
Shoot
Defense - do you even know how?