( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
It reminded me of what you told me before,
that you had a bad feeling
when Mikoy met the Valtrovi family.
What does she want?
She never refused my invitation.
Tell me why?
And be honest, or I'll kill you.
But you know what she's capable of.
This idiot still thinks he can fool us.
- What's going on here?
- Dad?
I'm sorry, I just got startled.
Startled?
That's how you react?
- I thought someone broke in to rob us.
- You almost hit me.
Well, why were you walking in the dark?
You should've turned on the lights!
I just wanted to get some water.
I didn't want to wake anyone.
Dear… No one can break in here to steal.
I've got it covered.
I'm really sorry again.
Okay. Take a rest now, Chiara.
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
Do you want some tea?
Are you even able to sleep?
I can't sleep because
you keep moving around.
I'm sorry, love.
I think I'm just feeling uneasy.
Why is that?
It's about Chiara.
What's wrong with Chiara?
Well, I don't know, love!
- But…
- But what?
I talked to her earlier.
And then, the things
she was saying felt off.
She even said
they've made a lot of enemies
because they're rich.
Just because they're rich?
She said they've stepped on
a lot of people!
So what's the problem?
Of course, I'm worried about Mikoy.
He's gotten himself into a dangerous life!
Tess.
There's nothing we can do.
This is Mikoy's life now.
I just wish we had
better protection for our family.
If we knew the truth.
So keep getting close to Chiara.
we can finally know the truth.
La Fornarina.
One of the famous paintings by Raphael.
But you know,
Raphael isn't just a Ninja Turtle.
He's also considered
one of the great artists
of the Italian Renaissance
alongside his fellow painters,
Michelangelo, Donatello,
and Leonardo da Vinci.
I know a bit of gossip.
That the woman in La Fornarina
is actually his lover.
Margherita Luti.
You're probably wondering how I know
all of that information.
But it's not enough
for us to identify who we're up against.
Since it came from Viktor's man.
But it begs the big question,
why is he telling us all this?
Is he saying this
to see if we'll take the bait?
Or is he saying this
because he's really turning
his back on the Moravianos?
Speak.
I don't want to be a Moraviano!
Mikoy?
La Morte Bianca wants him dead
because we believe that
he is actually the true head
of our enemy, the Sinigang Cartel.
Yes, I really heard that
from the enemy when I was kidnapped.
You are a fool if you believe
you can bring down
the Moraviano with your pathetic
Government Agency!
Because the government
is the real syndicate!
For me, he's just an ordinary bureaucrat.
He sent an agent to investigate us.
Oh my!
I thought that was the end for me.
The end of what?
Bad weeds take a long time to die.
That's why as long as you live, do good.
So I can atone for my sins in life.
Oh, by the way,
how is my grandchild? Sofie.
Oh my! She's growing up to be a weirdo.
Well, you know, her mother
passed away early,
so I was the only parent she grew up with.
She turned out just like me.
Lacking that mother's touch.
So what if she grew up just like you?
You're a good man
and a decent public servant.
Oh my! Thank you, Senator.
By the way, what brings you here?
I just arrived in the country.
that can help with your problem
with the Moravianos.
Dear, once you kill him,
oh my,
you can be free.
Sorry, I got a bit emotional there
for a moment
because these are tears of joy.
Because at least, child,
you'll finally be free
from this chaotic life,
this chaotic world.
You can finally live a normal life
and love for real.
The hardest part for me
is leaving all of you behind
in this world.
Dear.
You have already done enough
for our family.
That's right, dear.
You've sacrificed so much.
For all of us.
So…
maybe it's time to put yourself first
and pursue your happiness.
Give your heart the chance
to truly love,
and I'm so happy for you.
This is necessary.
You can't just lie in bed all day.
- True!
- This is important.
- Yes.
- At least get some…
- Let the blood flow.
- Blood flow. Let the blood flow.
- Yes, flow.
- Flow, so you'll recover.
- So you'll recover. Ready?
- Okay, let's do this, child.
- Ready. Ready. Here we go.
- We can do this. Come on!
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Is this cha-cha?
- four, five!
Like this.
There! There! There! Got it?
- Can you do it? Can you?
- I've got this, Dad!
- There!
- Slowly.
Two, three!
- Angelito!
- Hey!
- Dad!
- My child!
- Brother, how are you?
- I'm good!
The most blessed among the Pinagpala!
Come on. Come on. Follow me.
- Let's exercise. This is easy.
- Put your bag there, hurry!
- Come join us.
- Raise it a bit.
- Lift it a bit, Mikoy.
- Come on.
Hey, wait a second.
- Here, come on. Game.
- I'll get some water first.
- Okay.
- So it's better.
- How do you do this, Mom?
- What are we going to do next?
This Angelito here.
- What, how?
- What are we going to do?
Game, what?!
Move your hand slowly!
What? Is there a problem?
Dad, I think
there's something you need to know
about Chiara's family.
What? What do I need to know
about Chiara's family?
Chiara!
- Angelito!
- Chiara!
Good thing you dropped by! How's school?
I'm doing okay, Chiara.
School's going well.
Well, good thing you're here
because I went shopping for all of you.
This one's for you, Angelito. Here!
- Dad, this one's for you.
- What's this?
Mom, this one's for you.
- I'll just put it here.
- Thank you!
- Wow! That's so sweet!
- Wow!
- It's like you're
healing very well!
Yes, of course!
- Ouch!
- There!
- That's what I'm talking about!
- Oh no!
You're showing off again, kid!
Just because your love is here! Show-off!
- That's what I'm telling you.
- That's what I'm saying.
You see, that's ridiculous.
I'll tell you all.
I have very sensitive information.
This is my heart.
Take care of it. It's very sensitive.
But I'm…
You're so funny, buddy! Are you Google?
Why? Because there are
a lot of jokes on Google?
Well, because Google has a lot of answers.
just like you, you have many answers…
in my heart!
So, why are we here right now?
on unified policing,
intelligence exchange,
counter-terrorism,
organized crime suppression,
and administrative synergy,
I was able to talk to representatives
from the Czech Republic!
So are you saying
that because of this forum,
we can coordinate our investigations
with Moraviano through Czech authorities?
And…
- You're so good, Bok.
- And because of my efforts
at the European Forum
on unified policing,
intelligence exchange,
counter-terrorism,
organized crime suppression,
and administrative synergy,
And because of that,
it will be easier to build
our case against the Valtrovis
and their Moraviano syndicate.
When will this intelligence sharing…
start?
Wait, the European Forum
will be sending
an intelligence coordinator.
And look, he's already here!
What happened to you?
Oh, Chiara. How are your parents?
- Has your mother returned?
- Yes.
And we just had a good breakfast earlier.
How's your mom? How is she?
She's doing okay.
Still full of punchlines.
She even told me she's the undisputed
beauty queen of Mabalacat.
But when I met her, she seemed more like
an over-the-top Kapampangan jokester.
- Like that!
- You're right!
Actually, we were talking
about you earlier, Mikoy.
Dad suggested that once you've recovered,
you don't need to go back
to the office yet.
He'll handle Vertex Global for now.
What? No need! I can handle it.
And I was hoping
maybe we could go back
to your parents' place.
- Maybe we can help out with the eatery.
- Nice!
Oh, of course!
You're always welcome in our home.
If you want, you can even
stay there forever.
I'll do it.
It's your turn to eat.
- Later.
- No, no.
- Here, have some chayote.
- There's plenty.
- I got it, I got it.
- Here you go.
- Here.
- Okay.
Good?
Bistek has spent a long time
in Viktor's household.
And not only that,
they have deep knowledge of the Moraviano.
From missions
to their operational profile
in Central Europe.
And more than that,
they've spent almost a decade
conducting counter-operations
against this group.
So they started moving their operations
to Asia because they were feeling
growth on opportunities,
like weaker police and the legal system.
Because if we can't do it,
the national government
will dissolve this agency.
Oh, here.
Your mom said to bring this to your dorm.
Put it in the fridge.
When you get hungry,
that's when you heat it up.
Okay, here.
I added some extra.
What were you about to tell me earlier?
Dad, I didn't want to say anything bad
about Chiara's family.
They've only been good to Mikoy, right?
It's up to you, son.
Sometimes there are things
that are not good to say
but need to be said.
Because it's the truth.
Do you remember what I told you before,
that rumor about the Valtrovi?
The one spreading online?
I have a friend, Dad.
She said the rumor is actually true.
That the Valtrovi are part of a syndicate.
That's what her father said.
Who's her father?
Not the president,
but a very reliable source.
Her father is the director
of a major police agency,
the Government Agency
for Global Operations.
Her father is the director there.
General Norberto Ruiz.
Is it true?
That the government is going
to dissolve the agency?
The Valtrovis are part of a syndicate.
Her father said that.
He's General Norberto Ruiz.
Yes, this is Mikoy!
You won't say, "How are you?"
I know that you miss me so much.
What if Mikoy has a flaw?
What if he's a womanizer?
But I'm trying to tell you that
Mr. Pinagpala is currently
on an indefinite leave.