( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
He or she made sure
no trace was left behind.
But haven't the police said anything?
Don't they have any initial findings?
Like who's behind the group that caused
trouble at your event?
Well…
They just needed money.
Just money?
No one will pay
for what they did to Mikoy?
Compadre…
I'm sorry. I hope you don't mind,
but I can't forget
the trauma Chiara went through
and both our families.
But for now,
we want to move on from all of this.
You know I can't agree, compadre.
- I feel like, there--
- Mario.
Oh, right, Viktor.
Where's Donabel? How is she?
And you, didn't you get shot?
Good thing you can move now.
It wasn't life-threatening.
Donabel, she's okay.
Mom will be okay.
And I'm sure she'll come back
much better and happier
after everything that happened to her.
Oh my, dear.
Let me talk to my in-law.
I know, all she needs
is someone to chat with.
Of course, to ease her trauma.
Right?
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
Agent Sianong and I strongly believe
that this is a Moraviano operative.
And we have very strong reasons to believe
that this person killed Attorney Redi
and carried out the Sinigang massacre.
We are dealing here
with a world-class assassin.
Based on our initial information,
there is an emerging modus operandi.
I have a strong belief
that if we gave them a samurai sword,
they might even be better
than Kenshin Himura.
Like, Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Exactly. That's why she is very dangerous.
But it's very important
that we identify her.
Because he or she knows
a lot of secrets
about the Moraviano group.
- Maybe it's Viktor Valtrovi himself.
- No, no, no.
Based on our information,
Viktor was in the hospital
during the Sinigang massacre.
And Donabel wouldn't talk either.
As a matter of fact,
Donabel is in Prague right now to lay low.
If he or she is as skilled
as a ninja or a samurai,
he or she must be Japanese?
What do you mean by interesting?
When we started investigating,
I reached out to my contact
in immigration.
I asked if they could alert us
of any Central Europeans
with a strong military background.
If I'm not mistaken,
he is the head of Viktor's security.
What's his background?
He became well-known
when he was deployed to Afghanistan,
where he extracted a high-value asset
right in the middle of Taliban territory.
The operation resulted
in the deaths of dozens of civilians.
He was dishonorably discharged
and was dubbed
Noční Řezník.
Or "The Butcher of the Night".
Where did he go?
Love.
Why do you have
so many questions for Viktor?
Remember, they're victims, too.
Think about it.
Donabel was kidnapped.
Chiara is probably still traumatized.
I'm just frustrated, Tess.
It feels like there are
so many unanswered questions.
There are so many things
that just… just don't make sense.
For example, out of all people,
why do they get targeted by the gangs?
Our child was shot.
And then, it's like…
like nothing happened.
No investigation.
We didn't even find out
who the suspect was
or who was behind all of this.
It reminded me of what you told me before,
that you had a bad feeling
when Mikoy met the Valtrovi family.
I was really worried that something
might happen to our child
if he accepted that job.
Maybe there's something…
There's something to what you felt.
If you ask me,
there's still so much we don't know.
I think Viktor has a serious enemy.
Just the truth.
So I can reassure myself
that Mikoy's life is safe now.
And that his life won't be at risk again.
Just remember, dear.
What we need to keep in mind,
whether it's dangerous or not,
is this is the life Mikoy chose.
This is what his heart chose.
I think he's just a father
who's concerned about
his child's well-being.
Of course, after what happened,
he'd want to know if Mikoy is really safe.
What does she want?
MAREK VONDRAK
ATTORNEY GENERAL OF CZECH REPUBLIC
Marek Vondrak?
- Chiara, my dear.
- Yes, Mom?
I'm going shopping now.
Do you want me
to buy anything else for Mikoy?
Good thing I already made a list.
- We need to buy healthy food for Mikoy.
- Wait!
- To aid his healing and recovery.
- Wait.
- Okay, game.
- All right.
There's just a few things I need, Mom.
To aid his body's ability
to repair tissue.
That's why we need protein.
- Okay, protein.
- We need
chicken, eggs, fish,
- tofu, lentils, beans.
- Fish.
We also need to boost his vitamin C.
To boost collagen,
so his wounds can heal faster.
- We also need to boost his zinc and iron.
- Broccoli.
So we need to prepare meals
with spinach,
green leafy vegetables, nuts,
- and seeds.
- Nuts.
To help reduce inflammation,
we need healthy fats from avocado,
olive oil, or fatty fish, like salmon…
Wait, my dear.
- You already listed everything, right?
- Yes.
- Maybe just text it to me.
- Okay.
Or DM me.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Mom, just use the driver too.
- Okay, yes.
- Thank you very much!
- Bye!
My sweetheart is really something.
I should be a good boy.
Or I might get hit.
Sweetheart! What are you doing here?
I'm taking a bath.
Well, of course,
I'll help you take a bath.
No need. I can manage, love.
Sweetheart, you can barely move.
Are you sure?
Why? Don't you want me to?
Okay.
I'll do it.
- Ouch! Sweetheart, don't do that.
- What?
I'm ticklish there.
So you're ticklish.
You know what?
They say if a person is ticklish,
it means they lack something.
Lack of what?
Lack of…
Of what?
You know!
Come on.
That thing.
Chiara, my dear.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for loving Mikoy.
I really feel it these past few days.
Just how you…
pour out so much love for my son.
Mom, I should be the one thanking you.
Because I got to meet Mikoy.
I'm the truly blessed one
because I became part of your lives.
You're both blessed.
Because you're both good people.
I hope you're right, Mom.
Why do you say that?
I know.
And I can feel your doubts.
Especially Daddy Mario.
It shows on him.
I know you're wondering
whether this relationship
is right for Mikoy.
- Chiara.
- Mom, it's okay.
It's understandable
that you feel scared for Mikoy.
For your son.
Our worlds are very different.
it also comes with a lot of challenges.
Sometimes those challenges
come from enemies,
opponents, and rivals.
Because of my Dad's high status in life.
But I promise you, Mom.
No one will hurt Mikoy anymore.
I won't allow it.
I won't let anyone hurt the person I love.
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
I understand. I will fix this.
I'll take care of it.
Sir?
I just got a three-way call
from the Secretary of Justice
and a certain Attorney General
from the Czech Republic.
And I was reassuring them
that I didn't have any agent stupid enough
to kidnap a Czech citizen!
Technically, not kidnapping, sir.
Sir, we were trying
to bring him to the office,
but he resisted,
so, we kind of kidnapped him.
Kind of? Kind of kidnapped?
Are you kidding me?
We were just defending ourselves, sir.
Still, you have no right to hold him.
Sir, are you sure
we're going to release him?
But I saw him working for Viktor.
He is a Moraviano.
If we release him,
he'll just go back to Viktor,
and we'll be in deeper trouble.
You need to release him,
or we'll lose everything.
Is Mikoy okay now, Dad?
Don't worry.
Your mom and Chiara
are taking good care of him.
I have a break tomorrow. I'll go there.
Okay. I'll let your mom know.
How are you?
I'm okay, Dad.
But can I ask something?
Do you have any news about
who caused the trouble
at brother Mikoy's event?
What did Mister Viktor say?
He said he already fixed everything.
But is Mikoy still safe?
Why do you ask that?
I've been hearing things here, Dad.
You heard something? About what?
About Chiara's family.
That they're connected to syndicates.
Syndicates of what?
Nothing, Dad.
Let's just ignore it.
It's probably just online gossip.
That's trending nowadays.
Engagement farming, clout chasers.
There are a lot of those now.
It doesn't seem true.
It's probably just nonsense.
Angelito, don't listen
to those rumors, okay?
We'll take care of your brother.
Okay?
Me personally.
Okay, Dad. Love you, Dad.
Send my love to Mom and Mikoy too.
I love you too, my son.
Okay, bye-bye.
What are you doing there?
Have you been there long?
Sorry, Angelito.
I couldn't help but hear
your conversation with your father
about the syndicates.
But what if it's actually true
and not just gossip?
I have a reliable source who says that
the Valtrovi are really connected
to syndicates.
Don't joke like that. That's not funny.
Angelito, I'm not joking.
You've gotten close to me,
and I feel like you deserve
this information.
Information? That you just read
from internet forums!
Remember that police officer
I told you about
who I get information from,
my reliable source?
How can you be sure
that police officer is reliable?
Because he's my father.
The Sinigang Syndicate
attacked the Valtrovis?
Why would they do that?
They're not thinking!
The Moravianos
will definitely strike back!
The Valtrovis won't allow themselves
to be disrespected like that!
Huh?
Your dad is the reliable source
you're talking about?
Yes! And not just any police officer.
He's the director of the best
law enforcement agency in the country.
The agency that investigates crimes
against Filipinos beyond borders!
Who else is more reliable than my father,
who is the police agency director?
Right? No one.
But listen,
I'm telling you this in confidence.
Don't ever spread it.
I just wanted to warn you
because we're friends!
Warn me about what?
Of course, so you can tell
your brother to be careful.
Whether he likes it or not,
because of his girlfriend,
he's already entered
the dangerous world of syndicates.
And that won't be the last time
his life gets threatened.
She never refused my invitation.
Tell me why?
And be honest, or I'll kill you.
Oh my goodness! Oh my God!
PAPA
She thinks Mikoy is distracting you!
It's because of Chiara.
What's the problem with Chiara?
I talked to her a while ago,
and she's saying different things.
She said that they have a lot of enemies
because they're rich.
I'm afraid for Mikoy.
He got into a dangerous life.
Dad, I think you should know
something about Chiara's family.