MkvDrama.net
"Man-ila" zoo!
I was with him the whole day,
and he has a whole bunch
of corny pickup lines.
Because "wa-lion".
I didn't expect that I can appreciate
that kind of humor.
Do you know what it's called?
Love.
What matters is you're happy
when you are with him.
If Mikoy really loves you,
he'll accept you for who you are.
Whoever you may be.
What if the person betrays you?
Would he still be called a snake?
Why are you telling me this?
You're betraying me, aren't you?
I strongly believe that Chiara
has something to do with the Moraviano.
Do we really need to involve his daughter?
If we kill his daughter,
it will send a clear
and unmistakable message!
A Filipino can deceive a fellow Filipino.
It's time that the whole Philippines
get to know the Valtrovi family.
How are you?
Hey.
Let us see the mark of your survival.
I think I had my guardian angel
with me that night.
Right?
Don't! It hurts!
Your return came
at the perfect time, Agent Kian.
We need an additional hand
for an upcoming mission.
I just don't get why they
would risk being exposed,
especially since they have
so many illegal activities.
Isn't that counterproductive?
So if they can throw a party
this big and this extravagant,
it creates the impression
that they are completely legit.
So this Vertex event is telling the public
that the Moraviano
is ready to do business.
Exactly!
That's why this is the perfect opportunity
to have eyes and ears on the ground.
Oh!
Sorry, I'm late.
Snacks.
Hello, Mom?
Why does your voice sound like that?
Are you sick?
I'm okay.
Why… Why did you call?
Didn't your brother tell you?
Chiara and her family
are having a party later.
It's a formal event.
So, I already brought the outfit
you wore to your prom.
Son, why don't you bring your date?
So, you'll look even more handsome.
A date?
-Who would I even bring?
-Oh, come on!
Stop pretending.
Sophie!
The one who often sleeps in your room.
Oh, my child. Angelito.
I'm just reminding you.
You should focus on your studies, okay?
But all right.
Bring your date.
So your brother can meet her.
Mom, Dad.
I can't bring her.
Hello?
Mom, Dad! Sure.
And I'm also excited to meet his brother.
All right, dear.
There we go!
Give us a sample speech.
That's the thing. I don't have any.
There's just so much work at Vertex.
And also here, there's a lot of…
What?
There are a lot of people
who can help write my speech.
You know, I'll lend you my book.
The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People.
So your speech will be,
you know, inspiring.
And then, I'll refer you to my barber.
Don't worry about me.
And that speech, I can handle that easily.
I'll just take a shot
before going on stage.
That should do it, right?
Just go straight in.
-That's the spirit, Mikoy!
-No need to be nervous.
Looks like you're getting the hang
of being an undercover agent.
Thank you, sir!
But team,
we will be there as undercover agents.
Our goal is to gather
as much intelligence as we can.
With so many elite guests invited there,
we'll surely get new information.
And judging by the guest list,
it looks like we have
a lot of persons of interest.
And this is also a big opportunity
for our case.
And as agents of this agency,
our goal is not to attract attention.
Oh, right.
Here's the invitation.
So who exactly is Viktor Valtrovi?
He is an ultra-rich Czech citizen
who's been the talk of elite circles.
They say he plans to invest
and transfer all his wealth
here to the Philippines.
But why the Philippines?
Viktor fell in love
and married a true-blue Filipina.
Notorious as someone
with expert-level beauty.
Hailing from Mabalacat, Pampanga,
Mrs. Valtrovi a.k.a. Donabel.
We have another fellow Filipino
who made it in life.
This is really who everyone
has been waiting for.
Their only daughter.
The biggest secret of the Czech Republic
is about to be revealed!
Chiara Valtrovi!
I can see everything clearly.
SEARCHI
Well, from what it looks like,
it seems Viktor is about
to introduce himself
to the world of Manila's wealthy
and influential people.
Not just a strong statement.
We need to smoke them out.
So we can eliminate those pests.
Uh…
Good evening to all of you.
I am Michael "Mikoy" D. Pinagpala.
Did you know that when I was a child,
I was always teased--
Why did they schedule
this party at rush hour?
And then there's Sofie.
She's so eager to come along.
She's even later than me.
All right! Stop staring at me.
I know you think I look good.
Hop on.
The party's waiting for us.
So, let's go!
Join me for a dance there, okay?
Hop on.
Of course.
I'll dance with you later.
Hold on to me. There.
Thank you!
Oh, hello there!
-How are you?
-Good.
What about you?
I'm good.
-Thank you very much.
-Yes.
I'm inside now.
I've got my zone covered, too.
Wait!
What is that?
This is what I'm seeing.
Do you see it, too?
Nice!
This isn't just an ordinary
rich people party.
Better than the United Nations.
There's diversity.
There's even inclusivity.
The man who caught the attention
of millions of Filipinos
who are chain smokers!
Because he owns thousands
of vape shops in the Philippines.
They own "Sana All Glow".
A skincare brand loved by Gen Zs.
Lebron James!
Former MVP on the court.
Now an all-around producer
of pageants, of movies, and concerts.
Where's that cake already?
Where is it?
Serve the food already!
We can't refill anything there anymore.
Why is it only coming out now?
-Sorry, Chef.
-Go ahead. Bring it out.
Hello, Engineer. Ready for fumigation.
the new global Czech charmer stud.
Sir Viktor Valtrovi!
our very own Filipina beauty represents,
the incredible Donabel!
Nothing so far, Mother Eagle.
But if Viktor and Donabel
have a production number,
then surely, there's also
a production number
for Mikoy and Chiara.
And that's what I'm looking for.
Maybe it's nothing.
Just someone who fell asleep
and ended up lying there.
How about this? I'll go down.
Eagle 3, we need to stick
to our game plan, okay?
But our game plan is to stay alert
for whatever might happen.
That's why you have to stick
and stay alert at your post.
What the--
Code 10-7? Why, who died?
The security guards.
Looks like they were the first casualties.
So if someone got past
the Moraviano security…
That means the enemy is inside.
We can handle this.
We are already in the middle of a mission.
It's natural that all factors
are working against us.
Mother Eagle, we're unprepared, okay?
I don't want to risk all your lives. Okay?
-That's part of our job.
-Exactly.
Looks like I still have eight lives left.
-I'll make the most of it.
-Eagle 3!
What about Mikoy?
And the Pinagpalas?
We can't just back out.
If the enemies got past
the Moraviano security,
that means they're here at the party,
dressed up and clapping.
But just like us,
they're pretending and waiting.
Mr. Michael "Mikoy" Pinagpala!
Michael "Mikoy" D. Pinagpala.
Uh…
Good evening to all of you.
My name is Michael "Mikoy" D. Pinagpala.
You know, when I was a kid,
I was often teased about whether
we were really "blessed".
Because honestly, with all
the hardships our family went through,
you can't really blame them.
Even I started to wonder.
It made me think,
are we really blessed?
But you know,
no matter where life takes me,
no matter where I end up,
whether in Quiapo, Boljoon, or Prague,
in the end,
I still made it to this very stage,
standing before all of you
as the new COO of Vertex Global.
And I'm ready. I'm fully prepared.
Of course, there's a bit of nervousness.
But what I feel more strongly is,
that yes,
I truly am blessed.
I am blessed with the love and guidance.
Mom… Dad…
Thank you so much.
For all the sacrifices you made for me.
I love you.
And not just that.
I am also blessed with the trust
and support you've given me.
Papa Viktor, Mama Donabel,
thank you so much.
I will try my best as much as I can.
I won't let you down.
You know, I've never won the lottery.
But maybe this is what it feels like
to hit the jackpot.
Chiara. You are the greatest blessing
that has come into my life.
I just want you to know
that I will do everything for you.
Whatever needs to be done.
Whatever is right.
For everyone.
Chiara, just don't ever forget
that I love you so, so much.
That's all. Thank you very, very much.
Mikoy!
Wait.
Three o'clock!
It's over for you.
Honey, I really need to pee.
-I can't hold it anymore.
-Come with me.
-Right now?
-Yes.
-Come with me.
-Sure, sure.
We'll be back.
-All the sacrifices you made.
-We'll come back.
All the times you held back.
From doing things for yourself
because you always put others first.
All of that is what brought you here.
You'd better just cooperate with us.
And don't add
to your failed murder attempt.
Because you have a big, big heart.
You can't stop me.
Mr. Michael "Mikoy" Pinagpala.
Mother Eagle. Mother Eagle,
there are many of them!
Chiara!
-You go ahead first!
-Chiara!
-Mikoy, you'll survive, son!
-You can do it, Mikoy.
-Let's wait here.
-My son!
Brace yourself.
Your brother Mikoy is in the hospital.
He got shot.
How's Mikoy? Where is he?
I heard from the ER
there's a gunshot victim.
They took your mother.
Viktor!
Do you think what your husband
did to us is funny?
like a conquering hero.
He built the Moraviano
without advice or permission.
Your husband ruined everything.
Not only properties, but many families!
For what? To be a tyrant?
You're just a criminal.
You got outsmarted by a criminal
who's better than you.
He's my husband.
And I will make whoever
did this to Mikoy pay.
MkvDrama.net