( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
My husband is just one call away!
What do you want?
He can pay you, you, and you. Yes!
We're going to make you pay
for all the hardships your husband caused!
But they hit our asset instead.
He's not the one you should be afraid of.
But he threw himself
in front of me to save me.
And I'll make whoever did this
to Mikoy pay.
Is it my fault there
was an emergency at work?
Do you think it was part of my plan
for some rich person to get kidnapped
that I now have to investigate?
How many times have I told you
to always choose the flexi option
when booking a flight?
So it's cheaper in case
you need to rebook a flight.
You really have some nerve, don't you?
You just disappeared into thin air.
And you brought a guy?
For what?
To insult me even more?
To rub it in my face
that you can just twist the knife
in my heart?
Hey! Alexandria Cortez!
I've moved on.
Ben, can you just listen first?
And it comforts me
that this guy right here
is the one you replaced me with.
I'm clearly more handsome
and have way more sex appeal
than this idiot.
And compared to us,
I'm am more qualified
to be the MMFF Best Actor!
Can you just…
Can you just listen to Alex first?
Huh?
You talk too much!
Clearly, we're here because you need us.
Help? I don't need your help.
I can rebook my own flights!
Actually, I just called customer service,
and they said I can already manage
my booking through their app!
Ben, we're not here
because of your rebooking issues.
We're here because we have information
about the Valtrovis.
What are you talking about?
Why are you interfering
with my investigation?
Because we know
who kidnapped Donabel Valtrovi.
If you don't stop that,
and you're busy
rebooking your flights and hotel,
you are clearly left behind, brother.
Whether you like it or not,
you need our help.
I don't need your help.
I already have a suspect.
I'm just waiting for the doctor's
clearance to interrogate him.
At the end of the day,
in law enforcement,
we're still the best at this.
What is that? Hello?
Huh?
- What's happening?
- There's a fire.
- Fire? Where?
- In the security room.
But it's under control now.
Good thing our staff saw it.
The computers short-circuited. Excuse me.
A fire in the security room?
The CCTV controls
are in the security room.
Is someone sabotaging
the security cameras?
Where's your suspect?
Hello? It's me.
But someone wants to talk to you.
Your wife has memorized
your cellphone number.
Because of what you did,
you will lose everything.
All that will be left of you
is peace of mind.
Because you will be resting in peace soon.
You were the first
to make a move against us!
We were minding our own business
in our country.
You came here and caused trouble.
Do you still want to see her alive again?
Fine.
I can replace a wife
anytime, anywhere, any nationality.
Hey, you two! Help them!
- No one gets in! Move!
- Yes, boss!
Hello? I need your help.
The Moravianos are attacking me!
Send your men right now.
Now-- Hello?
Your husband is such a bastard!
He'd just let you die?
I told you,
you're no match for the Valtrovis.
You took long enough!
We arrived too late at their hideout.
Mrs. Donabel Valtrovi was already rescued.
Believed to be the head
of the Sinigang Cartel.
At our HQ,
this is considered as case closed.
And word is,
the Valtrovis' private contractors
handled the job.
But I have a strong feeling
this isn't just a simple case.
There's a deeper and more complex story
behind all of this.
Where are we?
Last time, you underestimated
your enemies.
Are you sure you've
finished them off this time?
What do you mean?
You are a fool if you think
your lousy government agency
can take down the Moravianos!
The government is the real syndicate!
Who?
G.A.G.O.
The Valtrovis refuse to talk.
There's clearly a media blackout.
Even social media posts
are being cleaned up and deleted.
And even I,
I'm being ordered by my superiors
to look deeper into this case.
Can you just tell me
what's really going on with this case?
Do you really have nothing to say?
Like what we had meant nothing?
Nothing.
But I can help you
rebook your flights and hotel.
Don't change the subject!
You know, that's what you're good at!
That's why we never worked out!
You never fought for us!
Oh?
Right? You have nothing to say?
I did everything to make us work.
But I'm starting to believe
you just used me.
Ben, let's not relitigate our past.
This isn't the right time
or place to talk about that.
If not now, when?
If not here, then where?
Huh?
Mikoy?
Mikoy!
Why are you crying?
Who hurt you?
He's awake!
Bro!
Mom! Dad! Bro is awake!
Son! Son!
- My son!
- Son!
- Tess! Tess!
Tess! Tess! Tess!
- Oops, sorry.
- My son!
Mikoy survived the bullet wound.
He'll die because you're heavy.
Are you saying I'm heavy?
Love, you really are heavy.
In love.
There it is.
- So silly.
- Of course, in love.
Son.
Don't ever do that again, okay?
Because I might die
from worrying about you. Huh?
Mom, don't worry.
It will never happen again.
Really?
I promise.
I will never let anyone hurt you again.
Whoever tries, I'll chop them into pieces!
Wow!
Chiara is scary!
Our suspect was able to enter the hospital
and get into Attorney Salazar's room.
I'm assuming
he or she is pretending
to be a hospital staff
to move that easily.
And he or she is not only physically good.
He or she is also very, very smart, too.
He or she made sure
no trace was left behind.
Because he or she
physically destroyed the drives.
With whatever kind of trickery,
he or she was able to extract
information from Attorney Salazar.
That's probably how she found
the Sinigang Cartel hideout.
And there is a very real possibility
that she was also the one
who hit the hideout
and virtually took down the entire
Sinigang Cartel leadership.
I strongly suspect she knows a lot
of secrets about the Moraviano.
But, Bok.
We know how dangerous this operator is.
So, we all need to be careful, Bok.
All of us.
Because if we're not careful,
maybe later, you, me,
Dara, or anyone in our agency
will be the next in a body bag.
And once we find out who this is,
then we have a new target.
Someone we can extract information from.
Wait, I'm getting ticklish!
- Why?
- Sweetheart, come on.
So you're ticklish.
Yes!
But you know…
If you're the one tickling me,
I'd get shot every day.
Do you know how close
my heart was to exploding
while you were in the operating room?
You shouldn't have stopped the kidnapper.
Why?
Was that really a kidnapper?
If you hadn't played the hero,
then I would've just been kidnapped.
Do you think
I would let you get kidnapped?
No one is taking you from me.
I already love you.
You don't need to act cute anymore.
Are you sure?
Of course, I love you so much.
Come here.
I know, but I really don't remember much
about that event.
The last thing I remember
is heading to the venue.
That's normal for gunshot victims.
Usually hazy or foggy memories
because of trauma.
But it's okay. It will come back.
You know, I can only imagine
your mother's trauma.
How is she?
She's okay.
She was released by the kidnappers.
Dad paid the ransom immediately.
Chiara, were they really just kidnappers?
Does your dad have no enemies?
I don't know.
So, even you
are under tight watch in this building.
And you, you need to be careful, too.
Because if something happens to you,
I honestly don't know what I'd do.
Nothing will happen to me.
Not while you're here.
Right?
CHICKEN BALL
HOTDOG
How's your brother?
He's okay now.
He's already out of the hospital.
And he's recovering now
with our mom and dad.
Hey! So you're a big deal, huh?
Your family is connected to the Valtrovis!
I heard those people are extremely rich.
That's kinda "sus".
Could it be the Valtrovis
are connected to a syndicate?
Where did you get that information?
Nowhere! I just read it on Reddit.
Reddit. Reddit.
Don't just believe everything you see.
There's a lot of fake news these days.
Why are you so defensive?
You know that it's serious
and traumatic for my family.
My brother almost died.
That's traumatic for Chiara's family, too.
We don't deserve
to be the subject of online conspiracies.
We are real people affected by that chaos!
Sorry. You're right.
I'm so insensitive.
I didn't realize.
Sorry.
This is good!
But
how did you know that something bad
happened to my brother?
Also,
who was that you called?
From a police officer.
You know someone in the police?
Come here. Chiara, have you eaten?
- Here, eat my porridge first.
- Thank you.
- That's good.
- Okay, dear, this is for you.
Oh, I'm good.
How is Mikoy?
Oh, he's resting. He's okay, Mom.
Okay.
Well, good thing
he has no internal injuries.
But he still needs to move around.
So his bones won't get stiff.
We also decided Mario and I
will stay here for a few days
to help you take care of Mikoy.
Honestly,
I feel a bit guilty.
If it weren't for me,
none of this would have happened.
It should've been me, not Mikoy.
Come here.
You know, child.
Don't blame yourself anymore.
You're not the one who shot Mikoy.
And you're not the villain in this story.
Correct.
Out of all people,
why were they targeted by the gang?
It reminded me of what you told me before,
that you had a bad feeling
when Mikoy met the Valtrovi family.
I'm sorry, Angelito,
I couldn't stop myself from overhearing
your conversation
with your Dad about syndicates.
What if it's true
and it's not just a gossip?
I also have a reliable source
that the Valtrovis are connected
to a syndicate.
When we started investigating,
I asked if they could alert us
of any Central Europeans
with a strong military background.
He became well-known
when he was deployed to Afghanistan.
With so called Noční Řezník,
or "The Butcher of the Night".
No one will hurt Mikoy.
I will not let anyone hurt my loved ones.
What does she want?