( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Viktor Valtrovi and family.
This is really who everyone
has been waiting for.
Their only daughter.
The biggest secret of the Czech Republic
is about to be revealed!
Chiara Valtrovi!
Chiara!
Mikoy!
Bring them there!
What happened?
Something exploded loudly!
There are people with guns.
- How many are there?
- A lot!
Wait. Hide! Hide!
What exploded?
Let’s go back inside.
- Why?
- Go inside.
No! Viktor!
Viktor!
- Who are all of you?
- Gotcha!
Viktor!
We have been here for a while.
Maybe we can go out now.
- Tess, please keep quiet.
- Maybe it’s okay now.
Wait, it’s not safe outside yet.
Mario, our kids… What about Mikoy?
- Yes, wait… I’m thinking.
- Your son is alone there.
- Viktor!
- All good.
Let me go!
Viktor!
Hey! Let go!
- That’s enough!
- Come on!
I don’t want to!
Viktor!
- Get inside!
- Fine!
- Are you leaving me here?
- Tess, just a moment.
- Ma’am, sir, please go inside!
- I'll go with you.
Don’t go outside! It’s too dangerous.
- Our children are out there.
- All right…
- They’re out there!
- We’ll handle it.
- All right.
- Please go inside, sir.
Come on!
Is this the right place we came to?
Is this really the party venue?
But this doesn’t look like a party.
Looks like a disaster.
- It's coming!
- Hurry!
What about Mom and Dad? And my brother?
Oh my God, they’re inside!
- Come on. Let’s help them!
- Angelito.
Listen carefully.
I understand that you’re worried.
But right now,
the best way to help your family
is for us to find a safe place.
If there really is a bomb,
it’s just a delay tactic
to cause panic among everyone.
You mean,
those explosions were just the intro?
The chaos isn’t over yet?
We’re not sure.
Not until the mission is accomplished.
Mission? What mission?
Whether the target
is meant to be dead or alive.
They kidnapped Donabel,
but I put a tracker on her.
Okay, go after them.
- Okay.
- Go, go, go.
My son! Take care of him… Mikoy!
- Mikoy!
- What happened?
Mikoy!
Mikoy! You'll get through it!
My child!
He will make it. He will make it.
Mikoy, wait-- Doc!
Doc, please help my son.
Yes, just wait. We understand.
Yes. We will do our best.
We’ll keep you updated, but we’re sorry,
you can’t stay here.
Tess.
Whatever happens to Mikoy,
he can handle it.
He’ll get through this.
My child.
‪I can't take this…
- Take him inside.
- Doc.
I need any information
that we can gather from our lawyer.
Anything. I need to gather them.
So… Okay, please.
- Yes. Please wait for the nurse.
- Chiara?
Help us pray, my child.
Let’s pray for Mikoy, my child.
…to get information about everything…
Do you think I care who you are?
Please treat Mr. Valtrovi. He’s injured.
Who are you?
Who are you? What do you want from me?
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you want?
Money? You want money?
Just one call to my husband… Come on.
He's easy to talk to, you know.
You know the saying,
"You reap what you sow."
And now we’re here to make you pay
for all the suffering your husband caused.
Once there’s an update,
inform me right away.
What did they say?
Angelito.
Listen to me carefully.
Prepare yourself. Okay?
Your brother Mikoy is at the hospital.
He was shot.
Where’s my brother Mikoy?
He’s in the operating room.
We’re still waiting for an update.
Mom, Dad.
What happened?
What matters is we’re all here for Mikoy.
That's what matters.
My child.
Let’s offer more prayers for your brother.
Yes.
Dad!
I’m okay, child. I’m okay.
Where is he?
I was praying so hard it wasn’t one of us.
Mikoy is still in the OR.
They took your mother.
Just one call to my husband…
I’ll call him.
he’ll find a way
to handle whatever this is.
Do you even know us, Donabel?
Do you know what we need?
Whatever it is that you need,
I’m easy to deal with.
that what we need
is to see your husband dead?
I’m so sorry.
You got dragged into this mess.
We’re the same.
We’re all victims here.
The truth is,
I’m just as confused as you are.
They took your mom,
and the police aren’t doing anything.
You know, Viktor,
if you haven’t received
any ransom note or ransom demand,
chances are Donabel is still alive.
Your mother
means everything to me.
I don’t know…
I don’t know what I’ll do…
without her.
Let’s talk this out calmly.
So everyone can be happy!
It must be your sense of humor
that attracted someone like Viktor to you.
Do you think it’s funny
what your husband did to us?
He built the Moraviano
without notice or permission.
You are no longer allowed
to pass through this route!
No notice at all,
and no regard or respect.
Kneel!
Kneel, I said!
You and your husband destroyed everything.
Not just property, but countless families.
For what?
To act like kings.
To control every territory.
And worst of all, a Filipino like you,
his accomplice, crushing our dignity,
stealing everything we worked for.
Why are you smiling?
Do you think this is funny,
what your husband did?
No.
It's just weird.
You act all righteous,
but you’re just a criminal.
You got outplayed
by a better criminal than you.
My husband.
How is my child, Doc?
He sustained a gunshot wound.
We operated immediately
to remove the bullet
and repair the damage.
Good thing, no vital organs were hit.
Let’s pray there are no complications.
Can we see him?
He’ll be transferred to the ICU shortly.
So you may not be able to talk to him yet.
- Okay.
- Thank you very much.
What if I blow your head off?
Do it!
I’m your last chance to survive this.
Because if anything bad happens to me,
good luck.
To your friends,
your bar,
and your entire family.
You think I’m afraid of Viktor?
He’s not who you should fear.
What happened at the event?
They took Donabel Valtrovi.
Rody Salazar.
What did he do?
He tried to assassinate Chiara,
but he hit our asset.
Fortunately, sir, no.
Why would Attorney
attempt an assassination?
Maybe force them to negotiate with them
to divide territories
or forge a truce between
the local syndicate
and the new foreign syndicate.
Why did you operate out in the open?
What got into your heads
to publicly challenge the Moravianos?
It's better that the Moravianos
are openly challenged,
so the public learns about them.
So whatever they're hiding comes out.
After the events tonight,
they won't be able
to hide anything anymore.
The public will smell their stench.
Do you think they won’t smell
our group as well?
So we don’t get implicated.
I have already manipulated
the entire agency to bring them down.
But you ruined all of that!
You are a fool if you believe
that the Moravianos can be taken down
by your lousy government agency!
If the government
were the answer to the problem,
then the Philippines
would be developed by now!
Because the government
is the real syndicate!
What was meant to happen
has already happened.
And I will find Viktor,
wherever his hideout is!
I will expose whatever dirt
they’re hiding.
Even if it means gunfire at Luneta.
I will challenge him!
Just to bring their dirt out!
The most complicated part here,
is this guy went rogue already.
So I think
this was not really planned
by the Sinigang cartel
to assassinate Chiara.
It’s probably just
Attorney’s personal vendetta,
and they just want revenge on Viktor.
Seems like you don’t have
approval from your bosses.
That’s not good.
Of course,
if your bosses don’t like you,
your performance review goes down.
And if your performance review is low,
you won’t get a bonus. What a waste.
I’m sure
your conversations are always fun.
Of course!
Where you can be killed
by your enemies anytime.
You’ll realize you should
just enjoy the moment, every day.
I guess that’s our coping mechanism.
Right?
In another life,
perhaps we would get along.
When we dug up Attorney’s body,
it turns out he was the brother
of Congressman Celestino Salazar.
And it looks like he wants Viktor
to feel the same pain he went through.
Where is Attorney now?
He is now in police custody,
but he had to be taken to the hospital
because he sustained minor injuries.
What do the police know now?
I don’t know anything!
If only I could,
I would tell those criminals
to not commit crimes
while I’m on vacation leave.
That’s not allowed!
I’ll just call you again, buddy.
Can I ask a question, friend?
Are you looking for a restroom?
There might be one at the end.
No, I peed already.
I’m Mario Pinagpala.
What is your relation
to the gunshot victim?
I’m his father.
Sir, I know you just need information,
but to be honest,
it’s still under investigation.
I understand that.
I just want to know if you have…
a theory.
Who would dare do something like this?
If you think about it, it’s very brazen.
The attack.
I mean, if it’s kidnapping
what they wanted to happen,
who would have the courage to kidnap
someone from a very prominent family
in a very public place?
Sir, do you have a background
in criminal investigation?
None.
Just curious.
Because no matter how you look at it,
from any angle,
this is not normal.
But you’re right.
Even us,
we are surprised
by how brazen this operation is.
Something like this
can only be done
by a very desperate group.
Why aren’t we doing anything?
We already know the cartel’s location.
Hey… Kian.
- I know.
- And now you still want to save them.
- Who's also a Valtrovi.
- I know.
But a crime still took place.
What are we going to do
with this information?
Just sit on it?
And there’s nothing we can do.
And we cannot interfere.
Hey!
In case you’ve forgotten.
But our agency doesn’t need
this kind of exposure.
And by launching a rescue operation
for Mrs. Valtrovi,
it will just make it look like
we’re siding with a syndicate.
Plus, if we rescue Donabel,
they’ll find out we’ve been
monitoring the Moravianos.
Wow.
Maybe there’s still something we can do.
What do you mean?
If we can’t act on this information,
maybe we can pass it on to someone
who can actually use it.
I have activated everyone
to find your mother.
Even if his punchlines are super corny.
But he threw himself
in front of me to save me.
Child,
I don’t think this is stupid.
And I will make whoever
did this to Mikoy pay.
- What’s happening?
- There’s a fire.
- Where?
- In the security room.
Fire in the security room?
All CCTV controls are inside
the security room.
Security cameras are being sabotaged.
There’s someone who wants to talk to you.
What will be left of you
is just peace of mind.