( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 34]
If it weren't for you,
we would have been together long ago!
Chen Xuanqing, you're insane!
Yes, I am insane!
The moment I found out
you were going to marry him,
I went insane!
Chen Yanyun,
you sit up high
with absolute power.
But you're just a hypocrite.
You said you took pity on me
and brought me to the Chen family,
but you only thought I had a bright future
and could be of use to your Chen family!
Yet you couldn't bear to see me soar,
so you manipulate and control me
at every turn!
You knew full well that Jinzhao and I
were in love,
yet you deliberately arranged a marriage
for me with the Yu family.
You claimed to worry about my background
and my future.
You did all this
just to steal Jinzhao away!
Nonsense.
This is all your imagination.
Is it?
Is it my imagination,
or are you under his spell?
Dare you deny
that you used to like me?
You went to
great lengths
to get close to me at the Academy.
Even when you were beaten by Ye Xian,
you endured it.
I've read all the letters
you wrote to me.
I wrote,
"As a wanderer, my heart is full of
a hundred woes.
I've roamed a thousand miles away
all alone."
You said you also had
this feeling of being a stranger at home,
and told me not to be too depressed.
You understand me so well.
Dare you say you don't like me?
That day on the bridge,
I went,
and I also saw the kite
you flew for me.
Did you know?
You're too naive,
that's why you were deceived by him.
He has always played political games,
and is best at manipulating people.
What you see
is only what he wants you to see!
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
-Third Master!
-Let go of me!
Third Master!
Throw him out!
Yes!
I did nothing wrong.
Get up.
You can't be mad at me because of
what happened
in the past.
I want to be calm and rational too，
but I...
I can't do it right now.
Leave me alone.
Chen Jiuheng!
If you leave,
you're not allowed to come back!
Is what you said true?
How would I know if it's true or not?
I heard it from my fourth son.
He said his wife
became a completely different person
after coming back from the Chen family.
She kept saying
that Third Mr. Chen
wants to avenge her father.
But where would Third Mr. Chen
get the evidence?
When I executed Yanhong,
I couldn't have been more careful.
Regardless,
Yuanweng, you should make plans early.
This matter is no small thing.
If it gets exposed,
all of your ambitions
will go down the drain.
What are you talking about?
If our Master's plans are ruined,
do you think you'd gain any advantage?
Why are you stopping me?
Third Mr. Chen knows about Yanhong.
What?
Who?
The woman that
Prince Chengqing gave to me back then.
Wasn't she thrown into the Tongfu River?
It's been so many years.
How did they know?
How should I know?
This is too scary.
This...
Master, what should we do?
Calm down.
I wasn't the only one
who colluded with Prince Chengqing.
Even if they find out something,
the Senior Grand Secretary knows me.
If it really comes to that,
I, Wang Xuanfan,
am not afraid to burn everything down.
Someone!
Master.
Send some men to keep a close watch
on Third Mr. Chen.
If there's any sign of trouble,
report back immediately.
Yes.
Also...
We previously suspected Third Mr. Chen
of colluding with the river bandits
back then.
Investigate this matter
thoroughly again.
And that Chen Xuanqing.
I remember
he was adopted
from Xuzhou Prefecture.
He might very well be connected
to the river bandits.
Investigate it carefully.
Investigate it ruthlessly.
We must find solid evidence.
Yes.
♪ Once I wrote of spring and fall ♪
♪ Yet fell through time's abyss ♪
♪ Every shade turned bitter ♪
♪ Every longing became sorrow ♪
♪ I've seen through right and wrong ♪
♪ Old vows washed away like ash ♪
♪ True devotion is knowing
the freedom within your heart♪
♪ Word by word, hand in hand ♪
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
Hurry, Mr. Jiang!
Hurry!
What exactly happened to Third Master?
You didn't see the state he was in.
Something is really wrong!
What kind of state?
I can't describe it!
Just... come see for yourself!
Let's go.
Hurry up!
Slow down!
Third Master, Mr. Jiang is here!
Third Master, you...
Third Master.
Wang Xuanfan
has made a move as expected.
Not only did he send several people
to follow you,
but he also made contact with the bandits
in Zhending Prefecture.
Go on.
Normally,
our plan
can proceed as usual.
But if
you want to postpone it...
No need to postpone.
Just proceed as planned.
Okay.
Um, Third Master,
Qingpu
came to see me.
What did she want to see you about?
Qingpu said
she wants you to return home
and see Madam.
She said
Madam has been waiting for you all day,
not eating, not drinking,
and not sleeping.
She wouldn't stop eating and drinking
for me.
You haven't gone back to check.
How...
How would you know?
I know
I shouldn't speak out of turn.
But this matter
really isn't Madam's fault.
Madam has been
hiding from Young Master Xuanqing
these days,
staying out of his way whenever possible.
It's Chen Xuanqing who insists...
Insists on forcing her,
right?
Yes.
Young Master.
Please..
Please say something!
Let me...
Let me pour you some water.
I have already written to the Yu family.
Your engagement to Wanxue
is hereby annulled.
You will be sent out of the capital.
You can't.
You can't do this.
I got Third Place in the Imperial Exam.
You can't send me away.
If I hadn't intervened today,
given your impulsive and extreme nature
and your character,
Jinzhao
would likely have been ruined.
The Chen family would have been disgraced
as well.
I won't let you
stay in the capital anymore.
Go to the provinces.
If you can
serve as an official steadfastly there,
perhaps I might still think
somewhat highly of you.
Third Uncle!
I was wrong!
I was truly wrong, Third Uncle!
Third Uncle!
I have studied for so many years.
I am a palace graduate,
a compiler at the Hanlin Academy.
His Majesty also appreciates me.
Third Uncle!
You can't send me away.
Wang Xuanfan
is already investigating
your biological father.
Making you leave the capital
is also for your own good.
Take care of yourself.
Young Master!
Why do you think Third Master
is doing this?
He clearly cares deeply about Madam,
yet he is still being so stubborn.
Besides,
this matter really
isn't Madam's fault.
It's all Chen Xuanqing's fault.
The matter is over,
yet he insists on digging it up
and asking for trouble.
Do you think Third Master
doesn't know that Madam is innocent?
He just can't
get over it himself.
[Everything is properly prepared.
We can proceed once we leave the capital
the day after tomorrow]
What... What does that mean?
Think about it.
In Third Master's life,
whether facing treacherous
and unpredictable Court
or the harsh realities
of the martial world,
he has experienced countless hardships.
However, romantic love
is completely new to him.
And romantic love
is the most inexplicable
and complicated thing.
Yet our Third Master
has extremely high standards
and is reserved when facing problems.
So with all this back and forth,
he becomes conflicted.
I don't get it.
Just remember,
Third Master not returning home right now
is also to spare Madam from worrying.
After all,
this plan of ours
was kept a secret from Madam as well.
[Linxia Restaurant]
It's been a few days.
Why hasn't brother-in-law returned yet?
Can we not talk about this nonsense?
I heard you caught a chill a few days ago.
Your complexion still doesn't look good.
You should rest well at home.
Why did you have to come?
Some matters
should be settled
sooner rather than later.
It's better
to do it here than at home.
Sister Jinzhao.
What exactly happened?
Why suddenly break off the engagement?
Sit down.
What did
your father tell you?
Father only said there would be
no marriage.
He didn't say
a single word about anything else.
I went to see Xuanqing once,
but he refused to see me.
Father found out later
and scolded me.
He forbade me from seeing Xuanqing again.
If you hadn't sent someone
to pick me up today,
Father wouldn't have allowed me out.
I asked you here today
because I wanted
to explain this matter to you
face to face.
You heard
what Xuanqing said that day
at Lan's residence.
After weighing the pros and cons,
Third Master,
your father, and I
feel that you and Xuanqing
are not a good match.
It's you!
The person in Xuanqing's heart...
It's you, isn't it?
I actually guessed it a long time ago.
That day, Xuanqing
seemed to be talking to me.
But he was clearly looking at you
the whole time.
I knew then
he wasn't being honest with me.
He was using me
to express his feelings to you.
That's why the engagement was broken off.
Wanxue,
you should find someone
who knows you, understands you,
-and truly loves you.
-What's the use of saying
these things now?
I clearly told you
that I've had feelings for Xuanqing
since we were little.
I even said
that no matter what,
I'd be willing to marry him.
And you have already
married Third Uncle.
Why did you have to
expose all of this?
Couldn't we just live our own lives?
Wouldn't that be better?
You can't
knowingly
jump into a fire pit.
Do you still have feelings for Xuanqing?
Of course not.
Then could you
talk to Uncle Chen
and ask him not to
call off the engagement?
No.
Xuanqing will soon
be transferred away,
and won't return to the capital.
Just forget him.
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
Are you willing
to be with me?
When we encounter a problem,
don't be in a hurry to back down.
Let's see if we can
come up with a better way
to solve it.
You once said
we'd face things
and solve them together.
And now?
I want to be calm and rational too,
but I...
Since you are hiding
and avoiding me like this,
I'll have to be ruthless
and force your hand.
Let's see if you really intend
never to look back.
[Chen Yanyun] [Gu Jinzhao]
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
Take this
to Chen Yi
and have him give it to Third Master.
[To Third Master]
My Lady,
is this really necessary?
Maybe we should wait a little longer.
I have already
waited for many days.
I don't want to wait anymore.
Since he clearly knows
I'm not at fault,
yet still makes things difficult for me,
I naturally won't indulge him either.
Yes.
Third Master.
Everything is ready?
Yes, it's ready.
Let's go.
Oh right, Third Master.
Qingpu brought this,
a letter for you from Madam.
Madam?
Yes.
[To Third Master]
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
♪ Once I wrote of spring and fall ♪
♪ Yet fell through time's abyss ♪
♪ Every shade turned bitter ♪
♪ Every longing became sorrow ♪
♪ I've seen through right and wrong ♪
♪ Old vows washed away like ash ♪
♪ True devotion is knowing
the freedom within your heart♪
♪ Word by word, hand in hand ♪
♪ My heart grows cold like rust ♪
♪ The stars send you far away ♪
♪ Yet one thought still remains ♪
♪ You share bright days with another ♪
♪ I walk with my lonely shadow ♪
♪ Filling every broken fold
with memories of us ♪
[Linxia Restaurant]
Miss Zhao really knows
how to get things done.
She even managed to invite all the wives
of the Grand Secretaries.
We won't have to worry about our business
from now on.
I'm not worried about the business.
I'm worried about my eldest sister.
This tea smells so good.
This is this year's
first flush of Songluo.
It was brewed with mountain spring water.
This pattern leaves some margin.
Madam, you can cut along
the outer edge of the pattern
along with the fabric.
As if I didn't know
I need to cut it with the pattern!
Exactly.
It's just a piece of fabric.
If it's ruined, it's ruined.
What do you mean "if it's ruined,
it's ruined"?
Are you saying
I ruined it on purpose?
I...
We are cutting fabrics today
to imitate the Empress Dowager
and encourage the people
to plant mulberry trees.
But if we ruin too many fabrics,
it rather defeats the original purpose.
I actually have an idea.
The ruined fabric
doesn't have to be thrown away.
Have someone sew the pieces together
to make patched blessing clothes
and donate them to the children
at the Hall of Benevolence.
That's a good idea.
Madam Chen is truly clever.
Now that you say it,
we don't feel burdened anymore.
In my opinion,
Madam Chen's cleverness is only secondary.
What matters most is her composure.
If it were anyone else,
with their Second Uncle
dismissed from office
and their ancestral home
losing half its assets,
they would have cried themselves to death.
But Madam Chen
remains calm and collected,
even enjoying tea here.
My Second Uncle broke the law.
He deserved to be punished.
What is there for me to cry about?
Well said.
Madam Chen really
has seen her share of storms.
I heard
when Madam Chen was little,
she was sent to her
maternal grandparents' house
because
her fate
was supposedly hindering
her father's official career.
I originally didn't believe in
these things.
But thinking about it now,
it's true.
Your father
was indeed demoted
and sent out to Pingyang.
This time, your Second Uncle
was also dismissed.
Could it be that
this fortune-telling stuff
actually makes sense?
Madam Chen,
you must be careful.
It's one thing if it's your father
and uncle,
but what if it affects Jiuheng?
Why are you saying all this?
I'm just joking.
Mrs. Wang
is deliberately causing trouble today,
isn't she?
She is just angry.
The investigation into the Gu Deyuan case
has reached this point.
Over thirty court officials
have been implicated
and thrown into prison.
However,
it hasn't involved Jiuheng
in the slightest.
But the matter of Wang Xuanfan
colluding with the late Prince Chengqing
is becoming more and more evident.
I heard
they have already found the family
of the concubine who died suddenly.
My Lady!
What's wrong?
Today, Third Master
went to Mount Yu to inspect Dingling tomb
and was ambushed.
My Lady!
I was right, wasn't I?
What are you doing?
You...
If our Master
has any mishap today,
I will hold you
entirely responsible!
You will answer for him with your life!
Madam.
I am incompetent.
I failed to protect Third Master.
Please punish me, Madam!
My Lady!
Mother,
let's go back first.
Let my sister-in-law stay with Yanyun.
Why are your hands so cold?
Third Master.
Because we left in a hurry,
Third Master only took me with him.
Shortly after leaving the capital,
we unexpectedly met assassins.
They outnumbered us,
and had archers ambushed in the woods.
Do you suspect anyone?
Yes.
The whole Court is talking about it.
They all say Wang Xuanfan
was caught with evidence by Third Master
and he hired assassins
to kill him in desperation.
[Wang Mansion]
I did not assassinate Third Mr. Chen!
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
Master,
Lord Wang Shenzhi, Chief Justice
of the Imperial Court of Judicial Review,
is here.
He said he wanted to ask
about the assassination of
Lord Chen Yanyun.
Go tell him
that I don't know who
assassinated Chen Jiuheng.
But it definitely wasn't me.
Exactly!
Does he have evidence?
How dare he come asking?
From what he said,
it seems he might have evidence.
I...
I just received the news
that one of the men
we sent to spy on Chen Yanyun
is missing.
You may leave now.
Yes.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Tell me the truth.
Did you do it?
It really wasn't me!
It's true
that I would love to kill Third Mr. Chen,
but that breaks the rules.
A Grand Secretary assassinating another
is unprecedented.
But everyone out there is saying
you were afraid Third Mr. Chen
would produce
evidence of your collusion
with Prince Chengqing,
so you were backed into a corner
like a dog
and hired an assassin.
Who are you calling a dog?
I...
Everyone out?
No, no.
Someone is trying to frame me.
Yes, yes, yes.
This...
This must be someone framing me!
Who would dare to frame you?
Third Mr. Chen?
I've asked around.
He really got shot by an arrow.
The injury is serious.
Could it be...
Could it be
the Senior Grand Secretary?
Impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
The Senior Grand Secretary still needs me.
He will definitely protect me.
Third Mr. Chen's tricks
are useless.
Definitely useless.
Why are you crying like this?
Don't worry.
I won't die.
How can I not worry?
You bled so much,
and were unconscious for so long.
It's my first time seeing you like this.
Don't ever
scare me like this again!
How do you feel now?
Just so-so.
Then rest yourself.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Come back!
Sit.
I won't sit!
Just say what you want to say.
Why are you so stubborn?
Because you make me angry.
You were the one who wanted a divorce.
Why are you angry?
Why am I angry?
Chen Yanyun!
You have some nerve saying that!
Why did I want a divorce?
It was all because you ignored me.
You treated me coldly,
staying in the Hall of Literary Profundity
all day
and never coming home!
It was you
who didn't want to be with me anymore,
yet you put the blame on me.
Are all you Grand Secretaries like this?
No wonder the people of Great Yan
are in dire suffering.
I didn't stay away from home
on purpose.
I was angry that you knew clearly
about Chen Xuanqing's treason,
yet...
yet you didn't tell me.
Tell you?
You tell me.
If you were in my shoes,
what would you say?
Just speak openly.
Say that you and Chen Xuanqing
had a past.
No, it's a relationship.
Just say that you and Chen Xuanqing
had a relationship.
It started from the coming-of-age
ceremony,
and stopped abruptly
before the metropolitan examination.
That is a matter of the past.
But Chen Xuanqing
keeps pestering you
time and again.
You can't do this.
You are being unreasonable.
Has being reasonable ever worked?
Since you have investigated
the ins and outs of this matter
so clearly,
do I still need to be reasonable?
Would you even listen?
I know I shouldn't blame you.
I am just angry
that you actually
pursued another man.
And that man wasn't me.
I'm angry at myself too,
for not realizing earlier
my feelings for you.
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
Where did you learn all this?
Directly from you, the Grand Secretary.
What's wrong? Does it hurt again?
I'll go get the physician.
Don't move.
Let me hold you a little longer.
Third Master!
What is it?
The Court of Judicial Review,
based on the clues we left,
has already found the men
Wang Xuanfan sent to spy on us.
Then have the men
keeping an eye on Wang Xuanfan's residence
withdraw.
We don't want them getting discovered
and ruining our plan.
As for the rest,
we'll wait and see.
Yes.
So,
was this assassination really
the doing of Wang Xuanfan?
Truth and falsehood mix,
making it impossible to tell
what is real and what is fake.
You're being mysterious.
[A Heart of Purity and Loftiness]
If you have anything to ask,
just ask.
About this assassination,
what exactly happened?
I really can't hide anything from you.
So, it was actually faked?
Does it hurt again?
Oh, my dear.
The assassination was fake,
but the wound is real.
You did this
just to bring down Wang Xuanfan?
Wang Xuanfan and I
are completely at odds.
He had people tail me,
which was already breaking the rules.
So I just played along
and put on a full show.
Since
this assassination was fake,
why did you get hurt so badly?
It was all because you sent me
the Letter of Amicable Separation
this morning.
You saw the Letter of Amicable Separation
and didn't even dodge the arrow?
I didn't want to live anymore.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I wanted a divorce,
not to become a widow!
It hurts.
Does it hurt again?
Do you still want to divorce me?
No, I don't.
Third Master.
The Senior Grand Secretary
has arrived at the gate.
The Senior Grand Secretary...
He probably didn't come
to see about your injury, did he?
Definitely not.
He is most likely here
to plead for Wang Xuanfan.
Another half inch,
and it would have hit the heart.
Lord Chen, you are indeed fortunate.
Glad you are fine.
I'll go write the prescription then.
Come with me.
I'm fine.
Please have a seat, Mentor.
Imperial Physician Zhou,
in terms of treating external injuries,
is unparalleled
in
the Imperial Medical Academy.
I have worried you, Mentor.
Seeing you so seriously injured,
I'll get straight to the point
with my questions.
Was it truly Wang Xuanfan
who sent the assassins after you?
I heard that
all the men
Wang Xuanfan sent to watch me
have been captured
and
they have all confessed.
How much do you actually know
about Wang Xuanfan's collusion
with the late Prince Chengqing?
Actually,
I wouldn't dare hide it from you, Mentor.
I truly don't know much either.
What I said
in Court back then
was just a bluff to rattle Yuanweng.
I thought that
if provoked,
he would definitely give himself away.
Sure enough,
he actually sent assassins
to kill me.
A Grand Secretary assassinating
another Grand Secretary...
Truly appalling.
I couldn't believe it before either,
but to bring down Fan Chuan, Yuanweng
replaced the grain with bran,
disregarding
the lives of hundreds of thousands of
famine victims
in Pingyang.
Since then,
I feel like
anything he does
wouldn't surprise me anymore.
So about this matter,
you still
hold a grudge.
But there was a reason.
Doing this
makes you seem rather petty, doesn't it?
Mentor, this summer is a bit long,
and the summer flood is very severe.
Officials from the River Conservancy Office
reported
that in the lower reaches
of the Huaihe River,
there are a full twenty-three
riverbank breaches.
Yes.
It's hard.
Fifteen breaches
were not caused by fierce floods
or the river changing its course,
but because of
cutting corners
in river construction.
The wood used for flood control
was all rotten.
Among them,
the chief administrators in six places
are Wang Xuanfan's students.
Wang Xuanfan has gone
too far!
The other nine
are all under you, my mentor's name.
[A Splendid Match]