( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 24]
[Chen Mansion]
[Ancestral Virtues, Our Guiding Light]
Keep this wine warmed in hot water.
The weather is getting colder now.
We can't drink cold wine anymore.
And take those flowers away.
They are out of season.
Hupo.
Have someone
to pick some osmanthus branches
and put them in a vase.
They'll look lovely
and smell wonderful.
Scatter a few petals
in the washbasin as well.
It'll give off a natural fragrance.
You just got back and you're
already busying yourself.
Why not get some rest?
Mother.
Sister.
[Qin Xianlan —
Second Madam of the Chen Family]
I heard
Yanyun is coming back.
Seeing the servants
doing a poor job of tidying up,
I couldn't help stepping in.
You've got a real talent
for arranging things.
The balance of ornament
and empty space is just right.
It's truly fresh and elegant.
Thank you for the compliment.
When I was
at the Shaanxi yamen,
no matter how many different ways
I decorated it,
people there
would only say:
beautiful.
You cheeky monkey.
The house gets lively
once you're back.
Mother.
Yanwen.
Xianlan.
Sister.
Is Lady Wang still sick?
Yes.
She's still got a bit of a cough,
so I didn't ask her to come,
so she wouldn't
pass the illness on to you.
Why didn't Yanzhang come this time?
You know him.
He's always so devoted.
I told him
it's been two years
since we all left home.
If he wants to serve the country,
fine, let him stay.
As for me, I don't care.
I'm going back to the capital
to take care of Mother
and fulfill my filial duty.
Why isn't Yanyun here yet?
Didn't they just say he was on his way?
Where is your Master?
Old Madam,
Third Master has gone to Baoxiang Temple.
He asked the Old Madam, Second Madam,
and Sixth Miss to eat first.
There is no need to wait for him.
Why did he suddenly go to Baoxiang Temple?
He didn't even send someone back
to tell us in advance.
The whole family has been waiting for him.
Yanyun has been
the Grand Secretary for so long.
He's used to having people wait on him.
But it's not right
to keep Xianlan waiting.
It's not about right or wrong.
We are family.
Besides,
he just came out of that place.
It makes sense for him
to go to Baoxiang Temple
to offer incense and
pray to the Bodhisattva,
to get rid of the bad luck.
You're right.
That was the prison of the Penal Court.
Mother,
why don't you and sister go ahead
and take your seats for the meal.
I'll change my clothes and be right over.
Alright.
To bring down Fan Chuan,
he actually went so far
as to replace 12,000 tons
of disaster relief grain
with bran.
Fan Chuan has indeed fallen.
But
what did the refugees do wrong?
It only shows that
when someone as capable as mentor
becomes absorbed in power,
the harm they can cause is a hundred
or even a thousand times greater than that
of those without talent.
I came to understand it
while I was in prison.
Neither Fan Chuan, Wang Xuanfan,
or my mentor,
are my kind of people.
But
you are a student
of the Senior Grand Secretary.
If you part ways with him,
I'm afraid
you'll face a lot of criticism.
Yes.
The path ahead of me
will certainly be difficult.
What do you mean?
Are you trying to persuade me
to stay away from you?
What are you panicking for?
I'm not clinging to you.
I actually want you to cling to me.
But
I also have to
consider the risks for you.
So what exactly have you decided?
Come with me.
What is this?
I already have plenty of jewelry.
Open it.
Letter of amicable separation?
Who is this for?
It's for you.
Unfold it and take a look.
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
[Original Nature]
The marital bond
is deep and profound.
Since when are we husband and wife?
I'm not reading this.
Come on, read a bit more.
I drafted it four times
while I was in the Penal Court prison.
All land, property,
clothing, and provisions
shall be fully used to make restitution.
A list is attached hereafter.
All my words and deeds,
whether right or wrong,
shall have no connection with my wife.
Let this document serve as proof.
I have stamped it,
but I haven't filled in the date.
You can fill it in whenever you want.
[Chen Yanyun]
In that case,
if I ever run into danger
at court in the future,
you can
take this,
fill in the date,
and leave without
having to consult anyone.
Or,
if you grow tired of me,
you can use it too.
You just came up with this
while you were
in the Penal Court prison?
What do you think?
You seek neither
wealth nor fame.
What you fear is losing your freedom.
I am also afraid
that a slight misstep in the future
might implicate you.
After much thought,
this is the only solution.
Your three-year mourning period is over.
I wrote two copies.
I plan to
take one to Old Madam Ji
in Tongzhou.
That way,
it will be easier for me
to formally propose to you.
[Enlightenment]
Okay.
That would be good.
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
[Original Nature]
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
Qingpu.
What do you suppose
he was thinking
when he wrote this?
I don't know.
Grand Secretary is really something.
He's different from
ordinary people like us.
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
You don't seek
wealth or fame.
What you fear is losing your freedom.
I am also afraid
that a slight misstep in the future
might implicate you.
[Letter of Amicable Separation]
If I ever run into danger
at court in the future,
you can
take this,
fill in the date,
and leave without
having to consult anyone.
Or
if you grow tired of me,
you can use it too.
May you, after this parting,
have a bright future,
radiant as the morning sun,
with all things going your way
and a life of ease and joy.
What?
You want me to pay?
Our Gu family has suffered
a great disaster this time.
All the men in the family
were thrown into prison.
This whole disaster
was brought about by
your dereliction of duty.
It's only right that your branch
bears the compensation.
What do you mean I caused it?
I was framed
by Sun Shitao.
I'm wronged too.
You're wronged?
You are the Director of the Treasury.
12,000 tons of grain from
the Daxin granary were switched out.
They used your seal,
and you didn't even know!
You still claim you're wronged?
Who do you think
is more wronged—you or me?
I have worked hard
in the Censorate for so many years,
finally getting a chance to rise.
If it weren't for you,
I'd already have been promoted.
And now
who knows how long
I'll have to wait again.
Exactly.
He was thrown into prison for nothing.
That's hardly a good reputation to have.
He may never
get another chance because of this.
Will you stop
jinxing it?
Dezhao.
Deyuan suffered this time
purely because of you.
He was just collateral damage.
If you know what's proper,
you should bring out some silver
to compensate the second branch,
and let this matter
end here.
I can't.
I've already been
exiled to some godforsaken place
as a petty seventh-grade official.
And you still want me
to give money to them?
You might as well ask me to die.
My Lady.
My Lady,
you're finally back.
My Lady.
Your branch
has made our whole family suffer so much.
I just took a few of your things,
and you're stopping me?
And you dare to scold me?
Someone!
Take everything
from those shelves!
Yes, My Lady.
Get up.
You, go over there.
No.
No!
Don't touch it!
Don't!
-You can't take this!
-My Lady.
You can't take this!
My mother gave this to me!
Give it
back to me!
I'll beat you to death!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am crazy.
What are you doing?
Mother!
My Lady.
You wretch!
Mother, she scratched my face
and tried to strangle me!
You little wrech!
Being raised by a concubine
has made you utterly vicious.
You're truly malicious.
Someone!
Seize her!
Yes.
Mother.
She was trying to kill me!
My Lady.
Let go of my lady!
-Don't hit her.
-I'll teach you!
Don't you dare hit her!
-Stop!
-You wrech!
You think you're tough, huh?
Stop!
Let her go!
Don't let her go.
She hit Lian.
She can't go.
Qingpu!
Yes!
Zhao.
Lian wanted to take my things.
I refused,
so she snatched them.
What do you mean "snatched"?
You're the ones
who owe us.
Owe you?
Second Aunt,
what does that mean?
This disaster in the household
was all caused by you.
Our second and fifth branches
were just collateral damage.
You should compensate us.
Compensate?
Old Madam has already agreed to it.
In that case,
we might as well talk it out
in front of Grandmother.
Does it hurt?
Can you still go?
I can.
I will go with you.
They've gone too far.
Let's go.
What are you looking at?
Since Zhao wants
to lay everything out at once,
then let's do it.
Dexiu is on duty.
Rong and Xian
are at the academy.
There's no need for them to come back.
Even though the Gu family
has been struck by this unjust disaster,
it ultimately comes down to
Dezhao's dereliction
of duty.
You can't say that.
Dezhao.
Let Mother finish speaking first.
We've already reached an agreement.
This time, the fourth branch
must compensate 100,000 taels of silver.
Zhao.
Although you are a junior,
everyone knows you in charge
of the fourth branch.
What's your view on this?
100,000 taels of silver?
Our entire household's annual income
is just over 20,000 taels.
And you're asking
for 100,000 just like that?
Do you really think I have mountains
of gold and silver?
You can't say that.
We suffered a huge loss this time.
Your Second Uncle
was originally about to
become Vice Minister of Personnel.
Second Uncle won't be able to
Why?
Because Lord Yao Ping
also wants the post.
He has followed
the Senior Grand Secretary for many years
and ranks ahead of you.
What...
what do you know
about court politics?
I at least
had a chance.
But because of the trouble Dezhao caused,
it's all gone now.
What...
what do you mean I caused the trouble?
I'm also the victim
of that unwarranted disaster.
Do you all think
this case of relief grain
being replaced with bran was caused
by our master?
If so,
then our Gu family
will be in for another disaster.
What do you mean?
True.
Master is guilty of dereliction of duty.
But he has already
been convicted by the court
and demoted to
a seventh-grade county magistrate.
The case has been concluded,
and the court has already dropped it.
Now that he's home,
why hold him accountable again?
Are you suggesting that
His Majesty and the court were unjust,
and that you wish to set up your own court
and retry the case?
You... you're just
being unreasonable.
If you insist on taking this money,
then I'll go straight
to the Shuntian Prefecture
and have the magistrate pass judgment.
I've been there twice anyway.
I'm not afraid
to go there once more.
Right.
Gu Jinzhao.
Don't be unreasonable.
The court
has treated this as a state matter.
But here and now,
it is a family matter.
Since it's a family matter,
it should be be settled by family rules.
Don't bring up criminal charges here.
So
you mean
you won't pay a single penny?
Not exactly.
Our master is not entirely
without fault in this matter.
I will have someone check
the losses of each branch
in their shops and estates,
calculate a reasonable amount
and provide compensation accordingly.
I will hand it all over to you
for distribution.
Do any of you
have any objections?
Zhao's proposal is reasonable.
Our branch has no objections.
Hui should be awake by now.
Mother.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
You should all go now.
I should get some rest as well.
Wait.
Lian tried to take Lan's belongings
and even smashed her
jade-and-gold necklace.
Shouldn't Lian compensate for that too?
There was such a thing?
H... how much do you want?
That necklace
was recorded in the register.
It is worth 500 taels of silver.
500 taels?
I'm not paying that!
If you don't want to pay, that's fine.
Later,
We can simply
deduct it from the silver
allocated to your branch.
You...
Zhao.
Then can I...
Thank you, Zhao,
for upholding justice for me.
I was just about to say something to you.
While I've been away,
I heard you spent money
to make sure
Rong was looked after in prison.
I'm now planning
to renovate Linxia Restaurant
and reopen it
as a new shop.
I want to expand the shares.
If you are willing,
you can take a stake as well.
But
you have to think it through.
Business always
comes with both profit and loss.
I'm willing.
Thank you, Zhao.
Mother.
This...
Zhao.
Do you still have any shares
left in your Linxia Restaurant?
Right.
We are all family.
If there's profit to be made,
we should share it together.
Share the profits together?
You really have the nerve to say that.
Lan, let's go.
I'm exhausted.
Saying all these things
gave me a headache.
My Lady, you are too kind.
You even gave them
the properties as compensation.
Honestly,
even if you didn't pay a single penny,
what could they do?
They couldn't do anything to me,
but they could annoy me to death.
Besides,
our branch
is not entirely
without fault in this matter.
Let's just pay them.
Moreover, whether they can even keep
this small amount of silver
is still another question.
Why?
Think about it.
If I marry Third Master,
would they dare
reduce my dowry?
They wouldn't dare!
Exactly.
This Zhao
is really unreasonable.
Lan is just a concubine-born sister.
Why did Zhao give her shares?
She should give them to me.
I am her legitimate cousin.
Besides,
I am going to marry into the Yao family.
Pleasing me
is much more useful than pleasing Gu Lan.
I'm talking to you.
Don't you think so?
Yes, My Lady.
You are not clever at all.
-Why are you so stupid?
-My Lady.
You're not even close to Tang.
My Lady.
It hurts.
Isn't this Ziling?
Come here.
Well,
do you understand?
My Lady,
that won't do.
Why not?
If you don't do that,
I'll have you sold off
first thing tomorrow morning.
Believe it or not.
It hurts.
Ziling.
C... come here.
Xiuju?
What are you doing here?
I sprained my ankle.
Can you help me up?
Let me see.
It hurts.
Is it here?
Over here.
Here.
It hurts so much.
Let's go.
Luckily they dug out
the pond mud a few days ago,
so the water wasn't deep.
This Gu Lian
is truly going too far.
Oh, right.
Good thing it didn't get soaked.
I went to three silversmith shops
before finally finding one
that could repair that necklace.
This is the deposit receipt.
I'll keep it safe for you, My Lady.
You're still worrying about
the deposit when you're like this?
All I can think about
is how to get revenge on her.
Yao Wenxiu
has sent another letter, hasn't he?
Yes.
Bring it to me.
He actually wants me to go admire flowers?
He really has no shame.
Bring me
my writing materials later.
My Lady, are you going
to meet Young Master Yao?
Yes.
But
Young Master Yao
is Miss Lian's future husband.
That's exactly why I'm going.
Well...
I'll go get them then.
[Baiwei Restaurant]
What's the rush?
Have a drink with me?
Wine?
I prepared it specially for you.
I heard you like Zhaoyebai.
Alright.
You prepared it for me,
yet you started drinking first.
Come on.
Not bad.
You've been to the file storeroom?
It was quite an eye-opener.
Did you read the ones
bearing my name?
Yes.
The file storeroom
contains 167 iron chests
of surveillance records.
Among all the court's
senior officials,
some have one or two chests,
some have more than a dozen.
But there is one person
who has none at all.
Fu Hailian.
If I'm not mistaken,
after His Majesty ascended the throne,
he ordered Zhang Ling
to secretly destroy them.
Have you interrogated Zhang Ling?
Every form of torture was used,
but he refused to confess
even a single word.
I want the leverage
you hold over Fu Hailian.
Since you have information about
Zhao Jichang
bribing court officials
from more than ten years ago,
you must also have something on him.
I don't have any.
You're lying.
I really don't have it.
Even if I did,
it wouldn't prove anything.
Think about it.
If I had known
about his crimes,
why would I have
followed him until today?
So you regret it now?
Not exactly.
Anyone in his position
may not necessarily
have done better.
I know you hate him
for framing the Marquis
and the Marquisate,
so you want to find leverage
to bring him down.
But now is not the time.
Fan Chuan is dead.
Mentor holds immense power.
From the Emperor down to the ministers,
no one dares
speak against him.
If you go against him now,
you stand no chance.
You are afraid of him?
I am.
So,
I advise you
not to act rashly.
[Generations of Excellence]
Give this contract
and the account book
to Grandmother.
The distribution of silver for the second
and fifth branches
has all been recorded there.
Yes.
Honestly,
you are the most wronged in all this.
It was clearly Master's fault,
but you have to bear it all.
Then what else could I do?
With such a huge incident,
if I didn't take responsibility for it,
the entire family,
including myself,
would be in trouble.
Although this incident
is ultimately the Imperial Court's fault,
if our Master
had not been so negligent in his duties,
others would not have targeted him,
and things
might not have come to this.
[Land Survey Register]
Zhao is quite impressive.
She's more reasonable than her father.
Exactly.
If she'd kept being unreasonable,
we couldn't have forced
the money out of her.
Mother.
One of these shops
is in Dazhanmao Alley, and the other
is near Xiaodongmen.
How about our branch
takeing the one in Xiaodongmen?
I happen to have a dowry property
there,
so it will be more convenient to manage.
I was just about to say that.
The property in Xiaodongmen
is more valuable than
the one in Dazhanmao Alley.
If I give it to your branch,
the fifth branch definitely won't agree.
If it were the other way around,
would you agree?
I've thought it through.
Let's keep it in the common fund for now,
and when there's a surplus
at the end of the year,
we'll divide it equally.
Alright, put it away.
Yes, Mother.
This is
stinginess
taken to the extreme.
This was clearly compensation
from Zhao to our branch.
On what grounds is she keeping it?
She talks nicely about letting me
manage the household,
but she won't let go of any control.
And your father
always does whatever she says.
It's driving me crazy.
Mother.
Right now,
all I hope for is that
you'll marry into the Yao family soon
and become the daughter-in-law
of a third-rank official.
Then I can finally
enjoy some prestige
and hold my head high.
Don't worry, Mother.
After I get married,
I'll come see you often
and back you up.
In your dreams.
What family lets a new bride
go back to her mother's home
every other day?
Wenxiu dotes on me so much.
He even said
he'll do
whatever I say from now on.
Silly girl.
Let's go.
My Lady,
how about we...
Don't try to stop me anymore.
Lian has gone too far.
If I don't teach her a lesson,
she'll drive me crazy.
My Lady.
Lan.
I had planned to come early
and wait for you,
but I didn't expect
to still be late.
Young Master Yao.
I told you.
Don't call me that.
Wenxiu.
Your dress today
is so beautiful.
I didn't expect you to reply so quickly.
I thought it would be like before—
no reply at all.
Actually,
I hadn't intended to come today.
Why?
Why play dumb
when you know exactly what I mean?
You are Lian's future husband,
yet you keep writing to me
and inviting me to admire flowers.
But you still came, didn't you?
Don't worry,
I don't like Lian.
Don't talk nonsense.
I mean it.
So what?
You still have to marry her.
Are you jealous?
You smell so lovely—
far sweeter than these flowers.
You... don't be like this.
Alright.
I won't tease you anymore.
Dear Lan.
Since you are here,
it means you still have me in your heart.
I'll tell you the truth.
I plan to end my engagement
with Lian.
What?
You are going to break off the engagement?
In a couple of days,
my mother will go to your family
to discuss it with your grandmother.
Why?
I never wanted to
marry her in the first place.
She always throws tantrums.
I really can't be bothered.
I've brought it up
at home several times already.
My parents couldn't persuade me,
so they finally agreed.
That way,
we can...
I still have a zither
to pick up at Siming Hall.
I need to go get it now.
Please excuse me.
Ziling, let's go.
Lan!
My Lady, why are you leaving so suddenly?
The Yao family
is going to break off
the engagement with Lian.
What's the point of me staying?
Yao Wenxiu that lying bastard
is full of nonsense.
He said he disliked Lian,
so the Yao family agreed
to call off the engagement.
But the real reason is that
my Second Uncle
was imprisoned once
and his career is ruined now.
Second Uncle is still
a fourth-grade official at least,
and they already look down on him.
Now that my father has even lost his post,
do they still think they'd accept me?
And yet he still had the nerve
to flirt with me.
You really see through it all.
Should we tell Miss Lian
about the Yao family
calling off the engagement?
Of course not.
Don't tell anyone about it.
Just wait and watch the show.
[Chen Mansion]
What did you say?
You want to marry Zhao?
Yes.
W... why have you
suddenly decided to marry her?
Does the Gu family know?
What about the Ji family?
I have already informed Old Madam Ji,
and she has agreed.
Wait.
You went to Tongzhou yesterday
just for this?
What about Zhao?
Does she know?
Yes.
And she has also agreed.
Right now,
I just need your approval, Mother,
and I can go and propose.
So,
I'm the only one you kept in the dark?
I didn't mean to keep it from you, Mother.
Of course you didn't!
You just didn't want
me to know too much.
You've been like this
since you were little.
People outside
only think it's glorious that
I gave birth to a son
who became a Grand Secretary.
But in fact,
you're not close
to me at all.
Mother,
just listen to me first.
You listen to me first!
I really don't understand.
Why do you want to marry Zhao?
Zhao... she...
We all know exactly
what the Gu family is like.
Zhao's reputation
isn't good either.
She's too headstrong.
Anyone can tell
that she is not someone
who will take care of the family properly.
She would
bring no benefit
to you or the Chen family.
What I like about her
is that she brings me no benefit.
What do you mean?
You all think
I am the Senior Grand Secretary's
favorite student,
thriving in the court
and at the height of power.
But have you ever considered—
what if one day
my mentor falls from power?
How could that be?
Of course it could.
No flower blooms forever.
Mentor is now immensely powerful,
with not a single voice
of opposition in court.
But precisely because of that,
he is in greater danger.
Leaving everything else aside,
His Majesty,
is growing older.
Sooner or later,
he will take full control of governance.
When His Majesty's authority
is fully consolidated,
think carefully—
who will he deal with first?
If that day really comes—
when the tree falls
and the monkeys scatter—
what will happen
to all his followers
and even his family?
To call it utter ruin
would be an understatement.
So
you refused to marry Xue Qinglan
because of this?
Yes.
Of course, I don't like Miss Xue either.
Mentor wants me to take a side,
but I don't want to,
and I can't.
But you are still
the Senior Grand Secretary's student.
Everyone says
you belong to
the Fu faction.
That's only for now.
Do you...
In any case,
I cannot marry
the woman Mentor wants me to marry.
But if I marry
someone else,
Mentor would definitely be displeased.
But Zhao is different.
First,
Mentor already knows
the Ji family works for me,
and Zhao and I
have feelings for each other,
so he would have no grounds to object.
Second,
the Chen and Ji families
are already tied by interests,
so Zhao would not betray me.
If I marry Zhao,
she represents
no factional power in court,
so no one
would feel threatened.
Third,
I like her.
Then naturally I must marry her.
After all this talk,
you are going to marry her anyway.
Mother.
Jiuheng is right.
This isn't just
about his career.
It also affects our whole family.
Wait.
When did you start to fancy her?
You two haven't had much...
Could it be that you fell for her
at her coming-of-age ceremony?
No, not that soon.
Alright, alright.
I don't want to ask anymore.
Do whatever you want.
Thank you, Mother.
Then I
will have someone propose right away.
[The Penal Court]
[The Cold Iron Judge]
How bold of you
to trespass into the Penal Court.
Your men may be fierce,
but I just said one thing...
and guess what?
They didn't dare stop me anymore.
What did you say?
I'm considering
whether to be the Commander's wife.
[The Cold Iron Judge]
The walls in your office
are too thin.
I can hear
everything clearly.
Normally, you couldn't.
I had an interrogation room
moved up here.
Good idea.
You really are different.
Is there something wrong with you?
I fancy you.
What is wrong
with saying it openly?
Why must I hide it?
What is this?
This is medicine for my heart condition.
You have a heart condition?
Since childhood.
Since the age of six,
I was given all kinds of poison
under the guise of treatment.
No physician has ever
been able to cure me.
My days
are numbered.
I heard
you were widowed once before.
If you've grown fond of being a widow,
then just keep clinging to me.
You asked about me?
You're interested in me too,
aren't you?
Get out.
Ye Xian.
Do you like Gu Jinzhao?
I had someone look into it.
You've had a cold temperament
since childhood
and never liked getting close to others.
Yet you alone kept
in contact with Gu Jinzhao.
You even helped her raise
a cat.
Get lost.
[The Cold Iron Judge]
Get lost!
[A Splendid Match]