( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 30]
We succeeded?
Fourth Master,
we did succeed.
Great!
Do you know what this is called?
It's called karma.
My good third brother...
He was cruel enough to ruin
his own brother's future,
so don't blame me
for making him taste the agony
of losing his true love.
But Fourth Master,
that Xie said
they couldn't get out of the city.
With no other choice,
they can only hide in the capital for now.
What?
This...
Wh-What else did he say?
He just said...
"Making him taste the agony
of losing his true love"?
Third Uncle's true love?
Everyone who is supposed
to be in the mansion is still here.
Could it be Gu Jinzhao?
For the next two days,
put everything else aside
and keep a close eye on Fourth Uncle.
No.
He won't show up himself.
Just keep an eye on Chen Zhong
and see what his next move is.
Hya!
Mr. Jiang has sent a message.
We've found traces of the criminals.
It seems they headed toward the capital.
You just
locked her inside like this?
With people coming and going,
what if someone finds out?
You don't understand.
It's darkest under the lamp.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow morning,
a human trafficker is coming to see her.
Once she's in their hands,
they have plenty of ways
to erase her traces.
Chen Yi!
Take my calling card
to the Five Wards Military Command
and tell them I will arrive shortly.
Also,
return to the mansion to fetch my seal.
Hurry!
Yes!
Third Master,
are you going to...
Lock down the city!
Since they are in the city,
lock down the capital completely!
Close the gates and search!
I'll take both.
Forty taels of silver.
Not a single coin more.
Follow them.
What are you doing?
Let us go!
Sir,
give me some water.
You talk too much.
Don't eat it then.
Sir, sir!
This is really terrible.
I can't eat it.
How about this?
Take this thing
on my wrist.
If you take this to a pawnshop,
it's worth at least 100 taels of silver.
Look. What's this?
You're really impressive now!
Of course I am.
[Ji's Pawnshop]
Hold on.
Seize
this woman!
You...
What are you doing?
This pink pearl
is from the West Sea.
It's the only one in the entire capital.
It's a dowry gift
from our Old Madam
to our Eldest Miss.
Tell me!
Why is it in your hands?
I...
I don't know!
Madam,
this is the Young Master.
You may leave.
I heard you want someone
with good looks,
who is literate,
and comes from a good family.
This kind of girl,
I do have one.
However,
she's not cheap.
Name your price.
Two hundred taels it is.
[50 taels]
[Great Yan Bank
General Circulation Banknotes]
Why is this only 150 taels?
This jade pendant of mine
is worth at least 50 taels.
However...
you have to let me see her first
before I give it to you.
You want to inspect the goods, huh?
Alright.
Then come with me.
She is right inside.
Let's go.
Right now...
they've already been drugged.
It'll be easier for you
to take them away later.
The drug won't hurt.
Move!
Third Uncle's voice?
Don't run!
Don't move!
It's alright now.
-Third Master...
-It's alright.
I was so scared!
It's alright now.
It's alright. It's alright.
How do you feel?
Third Master...
Jinzhao? Jinzhao!
Stop!
Don't pull me!
Get away!
Go to hell!
Young Master...
She saw our faces.
I know.
Young Master,
don't be afraid.
I killed her.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid, Young Master.
Gu Jinzhao was taken away?
Yes.
In a moment of desperation, Lord Chen
contacted the Five Wards Military Command
and locked all the city gates.
They claimed to be catching bandits
and searched from house to house.
In the end, they found them in a courtyard
in the southern part of the city.
Gu Jinzhao, is this the man you chose?
You,
take a few men
and my warrant
to the Five Wards Military Command
and bring the villains
who kidnapped Gu Jinzhao
to me.
Tell them this case
will be tried by Xuanfeng Guard.
Yes.
Bring out the prisoners
caught yesterday.
Yes.
My Lord.
No need to follow me.
[Ancestral Virtues, Our Guiding Light]
Why aren't they back yet?
Hupo.
Go and check the door.
Yes.
Mother,
why don't we go back
inside and sit down to wait?
Seriously,
Yanyun's wife is too headstrong.
When a newly married woman
visits her natal family, she usually goes
to her father's side—
yet she
went to her mother's family instead.
See?
Now something has happened.
Mother, please calm down.
Yanyun's wife
is indeed a bit willful.
But
she couldn't have known
she would be kidnapped.
Fortunately, she was rescued,
right?
It's just that...
she was missing for a whole day and night.
Who knows what happened?
She is the wife
of a Grand Secretary, after all.
In the future,
there will definitely be plenty of gossip.
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
If people gossip about her,
it will also drag our Yanyun down.
Seriously!
Master.
How was it?
They were all caught.
I took a shortcut
to come back and bring you the news.
Master,
before Third Master traces it back to us,
let's run.
If we don't run now,
it'll be too late.
It's over.
We are totally doomed.
They're here!
Master.
Jinzhao is back.
Let's go there too.
You go.
I...
I need to go out.
Go out? To where?
Chen Zhong just sent word
that the
Southern Metropolitan Administration
will issue 2 million
extra salt certificates next month.
I must go there immediately.
Chen Zhong, get the carriage ready.
Yes, Fourth Master.
Wait.
Is it that urgent?
Can't you leave tomorrow morning?
What do you know?
Mother...
Well...
It's...
You'd better put me down.
I'll walk by myself.
Mother,
Jinzhao just got a fright
and sprained her ankle.
I'll take her back to her room first.
Go back to her room.
Yunting.
Young Master,
don't you think
I look like a joke?
How could there be such a thing?
Shameless.
Mother,
Yanyun
is obviously doing this on purpose.
On purpose?
This is our home.
Is there a need to play so many tricks?
Seriously.
A good man has been led astray.
As for what happened today,
no one is allowed to mention it
in the future.
Yes.
If anyone
dares to gossip
and I hear about it,
there will be no trial—
they will be beaten to death on the spot.
-Yes.
It's getting late.
Everyone, dismiss.
Just sit, alright?
Let me help you take off your shoes.
How do you feel?
You suffered a lot.
You were abducted this time,
so it's inevitable
that people will gossip.
By carrying you in like this,
if there are still any blind fools,
then don't blame me
for not warning them.
Third Master.
I'll be right back.
My Lady,
let me serve you your bath.
Ms. Zhao can do it.
You should go back and rest now.
If you feel unwell anywhere,
just tell me.
It's alright.
I'm fine.
Just listen to Her Ladyship.
Go back and rest.
I'm here.
It's fine, Ms. Zhao.
Let's do it together.
I have some urgent matters to handle.
Let them serve you your bath.
Get a good sleep.
Don't wait up for me.
I'll be right back, okay?
I'll be right back.
Take good care of Madam.
Yes.
I clearly warned you,
but you did it time and time again.
And this time,
you even dared
to target your sister-in-law.
Because I held a grudge!
Why?
Just because I killed Fifth Brother?
But I didn't know anything back then!
I knew nothing!
You are my brother.
You could have taught me!
Why did you ruin my future?
I also studied hard for 10 years.
But now I can only handle trivial matters!
Do you know how much
I've held this grudge?
So you know that
you killed Fifth Brother?
You deserve it!
I deserve it.
I deserve it!
Chen Yanyun, I deserve it!
No!
It's because you are jealous of me.
You are jealous
that Mother only liked me since childhood.
So you ruined my whole life!
I won't let you off easy too!
I want you to taste my pain!
A pain worse than death!
I know.
By the way you looked at that woman,
I knew
she was your weak spot!
I wanted something to happen to her.
I wanted to kidnap her,
sell her to a brothel,
and let the world trample her!
Given your numerous crimes,
exiling you 3,000 miles away
is not excessive.
Go to Shaanxi and find Second Brother.
I've written him a letter
about everything you've done.
He will deal with you.
Your son and wife are innocent.
The family will take care of them.
Chen Yanyun!
Go sleep in the study.
Are you mad at me?
I am.
Leave right now.
I don't want to see you.
Don't talk to me.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm not leaving.
If I leave,
I'm afraid you won't let me come back.
You are a Grand Secretary.
Are you really afraid of that?
Yes.
This Grand Secretary is afraid of nothing,
except for this.
Where did you learn to talk like this?
The Hall of Literary Profundity?
I learned quite a lot.
Alright, alright.
I was wrong, okay?
Just now,
I sent Fourth Brother to Shaanxi.
He probably won't be coming back.
Why?
The kidnappers who abducted you
were bribed by him.
To get revenge on me,
he went to great lengths.
Why did he do that?
It's a long story.
Do you remember
that I have a
fifth brother who passed away?
He accidentally fell into the water
at the age of 6.
But it was only years later
that I found out
he didn't fall accidentally.
He was pushed by our fourth brother.
Therefore,
I ruined his imperial exam prospects
and forbade him from taking it again.
But at that time,
he had already passed the provincial exam,
so he hates me to the bone.
If
I had known he would
take his revenge out on you,
I would have...
What would you have done?
I would have done
something even more extreme.
But he just disappeared all of a sudden.
If Mother finds out,
won't it be hard to explain?
To the family, I'll just say...
that Fourth Brother just went
to Shaanxi for business.
For the next few days,
get some good rest.
No need to pay respects to Mother.
I'll just tell her
that you're not feeling well.
You're taking matters
into your own hands again.
Linxia Restaurant will open soon.
I was thinking
of going over to take a look tomorrow.
I know
you're worried
that Mother and Sister-in-laws
will ask me too many questions.
But I have nothing to hide.
Instead of hiding from certain things,
it's better to
face them openly.
Okay.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll go with you
to pay respects to Mother.
I'll let her know in advance.
Otherwise,
she won't let you go out again.
You absolutely must not go.
It would seem like
I'm using your authority
to force her to agree.
By then,
even if she agrees on the surface,
she will still blame me in her heart.
I have my own ways.
Alright, alright.
Whatever my wife says.
It's getting late.
So now...
let's go to sleep, okay?
Come.
This Yanwen.
[Virtue Through the Ages]
He just left without a word.
What kind of business is it?
It's so far away,
and he didn't even take anyone with him.
I offered to go with him
to take care of him.
But he refused,
saying that this time
he had to go to Yulin Pass,
which would be too exhausting.
Yanwen
must have learned from Yanyun
to dote on his wife.
Yanyun
dotes on his wife a bit too much.
Third Madam is here.
Greetings, Mother.
Take a seat.
Have you recovered?
Thank you for your concern, Mother.
I am fine now.
Where is Yanyun?
Early this morning,
he went to
the Hall of Literary Profundity.
So he went back
to the Hall of Literary Profundity
to handle affairs?
Yes.
Well...
this is great news.
Since Yanyun
has regained his position
as a Grand Secretary,
as the wife of a Grand Secretary,
inside and out,
you must act with proper decorum.
Yes.
By the way, Mother.
Linxia Restaurant under my name
is preparing to reopen.
So I had the chefs
make some
pastries in new styles.
This morning,
I ordered them to make and send them here.
I hope you
and Xianlan
can let everyone try them.
Jinzhao, you are so thoughtful.
The pastries from Linxia Restaurant
are naturally good.
However,
you can just give them to us.
Mother
never eats sweets.
Xianlan, you're right.
My grandmother
has already reminded me
that Mother has diabetes
and shouldn't eat sweets.
So these pastries
were made separately.
I had a separate portion made for Mother.
And there's no sugar in it.
Only licorice and dates
were used for flavor.
I also asked
your regular physician
to check them.
He said you can eat them.
That's why I brought them here.
It's nice of your grandmother
to care about me.
Since it was so carefully prepared,
I must taste it.
Not bad.
I'm glad you like it.
I have a presumptuous request.
My Linxia Restaurant
is still short of hands.
I heard your maiden family
is a large clan.
If you could recommend a few people to me,
it would be a great help.
I see.
Mother, rest assured.
Since they are recommended by you,
I will make sure
they are well compensated.
Alright.
I'll write to my maternal family tomorrow
-This Third Sister-in-law
-to ask
-is quite something.
-if anyone
-She knows that Mother has always
-can come
-cared about her maternal family.
-to help you.
She actually used this method
to please Mother.
Jinzhao...
She was kidnapped
when visiting her maternal family.
-It's such a big deal.
-Since
-you're busy with your business,
-And she just let it go?
you are excused from
your daily morning and evening greetings.
Yes.
Since Jinzhao's Linxia Restaurant
will only serve female guests from now on,
I suppose
the wives of the Grand Secretaries
will be regular customers there.
The madams
of the Hall of Literary Profundity
hold a tea party
on the 7th of every month.
Now, Jinzhao,
you're one of them,
and the day after tomorrow is the 7th.
Have you
already received an invitation?
I have never heard of this tea party.
It's normal that you didn't receive one.
After all, you are still young.
Those madams are older than you
and come from noble families.
Naturally, they have nothing in common
to talk about with you.
Right.
Old Madam,
Third Madam.
Prime Minister Wang's residence
just sent an invitation,
inviting Third Madam
to their residence for tea
the day after tomorrow.
Got it.
[Ancestral Virtues, Our Guiding Light]
How is your injury?
I'm fine now.
Have they caught the mastermind
who kidnapped you?
Third Master is still investigating.
I didn't ask much about it.
It was really a stroke of luck this time.
If Third Uncle had been any later,
you might have
been killed.
I really didn't expect
that you would choose
to marry him in the end.
Is it because of
his high position and power?
But in my heart,
you shouldn't be that kind of person.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I have something to do,
so I'll leave first.
Are you so unwilling
to talk to me?
What are you talking about?
I'm just in a hurry to go out.
By the way,
since I'm married to Third Master,
you should call me Third Aunt.
You...
Sorry.
I accidentally stepped on it.
Forget it.
I don't want it anymore.
[Ancestral Virtues, Our Guiding Light]
Young Master,
let's go back.
Tomorrow,
take this earring
to a jewelry shop
and ask them to make an identical pair
to give to Gu Jinzhao.
Young Master,
we can't do this.
We can't...
make any more mistakes.
Just go.
For her,
I have already...
Why does she still
act like nothing happened?
So there is such a tea party.
What?
You want to go?
You don't want me to go?
Of course I do.
I'm afraid the Wang family
might play tricks on you.
Does it have to do with the scholars
blocking the road last time?
Yes.
What is wrong
with Wang Xuanfan?
During the relief grain case last time,
he deliberately
framed you
and got you imprisoned.
Why is he doing this again?
After that incident,
I told my mentor
that if we want land reform
across the country,
we must start with ourselves.
Grand Secretaries
must take the initiative
to audit their own families
and clear their own taxes,
so they have the justification
to audit lower-ranking officials.
And lower-ranking officials
must clear their own taxes
before they can audit
the gentry and the rich.
So my mentor ordered
officials of the third-rank and above
to self-inspect
and proactively return ill-gotten gains.
Wang Xuanfan is a famous landlord
in Daming Prefecture.
He had to cough up
tens of thousands of taels of silver
at once.
No wonder.
Cutting off someone's wealth
is like killing their parents.
No wonder he hates you.
So
he came up with an idea
to incite the scholars
to make trouble for me.
Regardless of the outcome,
he wanted to pin the blame
of unfair land reform
on me.
A blemish
is what a Grand Secretary fears most.
With a blemish like this,
if someone holds on to it,
it's very likely
I'll be discharged in disgrace.
I see.
The invitation
has been sent to the Chen Mansion.
Madam Chen said
she will definitely come.
Which Chen Mansion?
Third Mr. Chen's?
The day after tomorrow is the tea party.
I invited Gu Jinzhao.
Why did you invite her?
Do you have nothing better to do?
She is also the wife of a Grand Secretary.
Isn't it right
to invite her to the tea party?
Did something
upset you,
and you came here to take it out on me?
What else could upset me?
Isn't this all because of
your terrible idea?
Alright. All...
All of you, leave.
You told me to incite those scholars
to stop Third Mr. Chen's carriage
and protest the unfair land reform.
And what happened?
Now I've gotten myself
caught up in it.
Third Mr. Chen knows about it?
There's nothing to fear even if he does.
Those scholars
were right in the first place.
The land reform is indeed unfair.
You know nothing!
Do you know what those scholars
are shouting as slogans now?
"Clear the imperial estates
and inventory
His Majesty's private properties."
I told them
to protest against the unfair land reform.
I didn't tell them
to clear His Majesty's land.
So you got scolded by Fu Hailian.
What else could it be?
In front of Third Mr. Chen,
he scolded me harshly.
And look at you.
You even invited Gu Jinzhao.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why should I be embarrassed?
You are the embarrassed one, okay?
Since this time
you suffered a loss to Third Mr. Chen,
I have even more reason
to invite Gu Jinzhao.
What?
[Where Spring Caresses Jade]
Do you really want to go that badly?
You noticed it?
I'm afraid they'll play tricks on you.
I'm not easy to bully.
True.
I'm more afraid
that you'll clash with them.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid you can't protect me?
Trying to provoke me?
As a dignified Grand Secretary,
although I lack seniority,
I am more than capable of protecting you.
That's fine then.
I want to attend the tea party
not for my own amusement.
It's because
it's the Grand Secretaries' wives'
tea party.
If I don't go,
wouldn't I be
isolating myself from this circle?
That would also bring shame to you.
I know.
These Grand Secretaries' wives
are all more senior than me.
Even Madam Shen
comes from a prestigious family
with a profound family background.
Don't worry.
I won't offend them.
Alright.
Then I'll ask around for you
about these Grand Secretaries' wives'
personalities
and preferences.
Where are you going to ask?
They are all noble ladies in the capital.
If people find out,
they'll laugh at you behind your back.
I have my own ways.
Madam Chen, this way please.
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
Madam Fu.
Madam Wang.
Madam Yao.
Madam He.
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
Greetings, Madams.
Greetings, Madam Chen.
Please take a seat.
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
Miss Qingpu,
please follow me to rest over here.
Look at the new bride.
She's so plain,
yet very beautiful.
Her skin is so dewy.
It is so good to be young.
You flatter me, Madam He.
I don't deserve it.
In terms of looks,
all of you ladies
are much more magnificent.
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
I was just
born a little later.
By the way.
Today
is my first time at this tea party.
I prepared gifts
for all the ladies.
Please, no gifts.
This is a tea party,
not a place outside
to curry favor or do business.
The husbands of those of us sitting here
are either Grand Secretaries
or high officials of the Imperial Court.
We ourselves
also hold imperial titles.
If we give each other gifts
and word gets out,
at best we'll be a laughingstock,
and at worst,
we'll give people an excuse to gossip.
When Madam Fu first set this rule,
I thought she was overthinking it.
I didn't expect
someone to actually bring gifts.
It was presumptuous of me.
This is my first time
attending this tea party.
I thought one couldn't go wrong
with being too polite.
I didn't know the tea party
had such rules.
I'm to blame too.
I started preparing gifts
right after receiving
Madam Wang's invitation.
I should
have consulted Madam Wang first.
Since you sent her the invitation,
you should have given her some pointers.
Yes.
I overlooked it.
Is everyone here?
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
Yes.
The garden is ready.
Let's all go together.
It doesn't matter.
Don't worry.
[Integrity, Prudence, Diligence, Harmony]
I heard
the Left Vice Minister
of Rites position is vacant.
There have been 2 rounds of recommendation
in the court,
but no one was selected.
If you ask me,
Lord Zeng Ruoyu
is prudent.
He is also a famous scholar,
perfect for this position.
Madam Yao,
what do you think?
My husband
has praised Lord Zeng several times.
For this recommendation,
he will probably recommend Lord Zeng.
That's good.
My husband said
the Hall of Literary Profundity
is short of several drafters.
I remember you have a nephew who became
a palace graduate
in the 35th year of Jingning.
Why not let him give it a try?
Then on behalf of my nephew,
I thank you.
Madam Shen?
You seem a bit
absent-minded today.
Madam.
You know
my husband's temper.
It comes and goes quickly.
Go back and tell Keqian
not to worry too much.
He only gets angry like this
at people he trusts.
I see.
Thank you, Madam.
-Let go of me!
-I'm an Imperial Court official!
-Do you have any respect for the law?
-Let go of me!
Let me go!
Commander,
at the inn in the west of the city,
I captured An Deyu and his wife
and found a seal.
Please take a look.
An arrest warrant?
The Three Judiciary Offices
are still investigating.
How could His Majesty issue an edict?
Ye Xian!
Investigating Censor of the Censorate,
An Deyu,
sold government posts, neglected
his duties, and corrupted the law.
By imperial decree,
take him to the imperial prison.
Nonsense!
You are framing me!
Master!
[A Splendid Match]