( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[A Splendid Match]
[Episode 32]
Lord Chen, you're here.
Miss Zhao is in the main hall.
I'll take you in.
Okay.
[Blessings Passed Down for Generations]
Miss Zhao.
Miss Zhao?
Lord Chen.
Maybe the ladies
went back to their own courtyards.
Please have a seat, Lord Chen.
I'll go find them.
Okay.
Wanxue.
Actually,
there's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
Go ahead.
Third Aunt.
Third Master.
Isn't that the Madam?
You're our elder.
There are a few things
I'd like to say to Wanxue.
I hope you'll bear witness.
Actually,
I've always had
someone else in my heart.
Don't talk nonsense.
You and Wanxue
are engaged.
Who?
Who is she?
Chen Xuanqing.
You are no longer a child.
You should know what to say
and what not to say.
[Hall of Virtue and Splendor]
Tell me.
I can't tell you.
I just want you to know
that there is such a thing
and such a person.
If you don't want to marry me,
we can call off
the engagement.
Enough!
Do you even realize
what you're saying?
What do you mean, if she doesn't want to,
the marriage can be called off?
If you have someone else in your heart,
why make things difficult for her?
This is outrageous!
Wanxue.
Don't worry.
The Chen family
will give you an explanation
regarding this matter.
Let's go.
Wait.
Since you have
another woman in your heart,
why did you propose to me?
Did you fall for her
-after the proposal?
-I liked her
before I came to propose.
Then why?
Because we can't be together.
In this life,
I'm afraid I won't be able
to be with her.
Are you crazy?
If that's the case,
I won't call off the engagement.
I can accept that
you have someone else in your heart.
I still want to marry you.
Why are you doing this?
Because
I've liked you since I was little.
Ever since my father told me
that he would arrange our marriage,
I've been looking forward to that day.
Whenever my stepmother mistreated me,
I would tell myself,
Wanxue,
just bear it a little longer.
You'll be marrying
Xuanqing soon.
Your hard times will be over.
I don't want to call off the engagement.
I don't want to.
Wanxue.
You...
Okay.
Since you are willing,
then we will
proceed as planned.
Third Aunt.
I hope
you won't tell anyone
about what happened today.
Less trouble is better than more,
right?
Since Wanxue
has made her decision,
I naturally won't get involved.
But I also hope you can
be wholehearted toward Wanxue.
Third Master.
This...
Do not mention
what you saw today to anyone.
Yes.
Third Master,
Should I send someone
to
investigate what happened?
No need.
I don't need those methods
when it comes to Jinzhao and me.
She will tell me herself.
Yes.
Okay, pass down the order.
Madam.
Why are you here?
I went to the Ministry of Revenue
and came by
on my way to take a look.
I also stopped in
to offer my congratulations
to Third Miss on her new residence.
Good timing.
I want to go back too.
Okay.
Let's go home.
I still need to go to
the Hall of Literary Profundity.
You go back and rest first.
Okay.
I always thought of him as a gentleman,
yet I never expected him
to say something like this.
My Lady,
do you think we should
tell Third Master about this?
I should tell him.
But if it is made clear,
given Yanyun's temper,
the marriage between
Chen Xuanqing and Wanxue
might be called off.
Yet Wanxue
is determined
to marry Chen Xuanqing.
Well,
pass on my words—
without my permission,
even if I am not present,
Chen Xuanqing is not to be allowed
into our courtyard.
You also need to pay more attention
and keep a close watch.
Whether it is
paying respects or having meals,
as long as Chen Xuanqing is there,
I won't go over.
I'll try my best to avoid him.
Yes.
Put the stir-fried bamboo shoots here.
Old Madam likes this.
Hurry up.
-Yes.
Check the kitchen
for any hot dishes
and bring them all out.
Yes.
Be quick.
Arrange them properly.
Xuanqing.
Have you been busy with your duties
at the office lately?
Grandmother.
These days,
the Hanlin Academy
has been compiling
the Great Yan Code of Statutes,
so it's a bit busier than before.
But it's fine.
I can handle it.
Good.
The other day, Madam Yu
came by and mentioned
the marriage between you and Wanxue.
Old Madam.
Our Madam
may be a little tired from the day.
She's feeling a bit unwell right now,
so she won't be coming to dinner tonight.
Since she's unwell,
let her rest properly.
She doesn't need to come
pay her respects tomorrow either.
Yes.
Let's eat then.
What time is it?
Is it time to go to court?
There's still some time.
You've been so busy lately.
Yes.
The summer floods are approaching,
and riverworks must be prepared.
Officials from all regions
have come to the capital for funding.
If that's the case,
you won't be getting much sleep each day.
In that case,
you might as well stay overnight
at the Hall of Literary Profundity
and save yourself the time
of going back and forth.
What's wrong?
You were fine just now.
Why the long face?
You want me to stay
at the Hall of Literary Profundity?
Of course I don't.
I wish you
could be at home every day.
Since we got married,
except for visiting my parents,
we haven't had the chance
to go out for a proper walk.
I was just worried you might be tired.
Then let's take a walk now.
What is the punishment for roaming
in the streets during curfew hours?
I have a special edict from His Majesty.
Our Third Master
really carries a lot of weight.
You're acting indignant?
More than that.
I want to impeach you.
For what?
For waking me up early in the morning,
and giving me attitude.
Still holding a grudge?
Of course.
♪ A good moment is strewn with starlight ♪
For a long time.
Then keep holding it.
♪ Flames burn away
the frost of bygone days ♪
Don't forget.
♪ Reflections tremble,
hearts beat in unison ♪
♪ Candlelight weaves the web of fate ♪
♪ Petal shadows
trace the lines of your face ♪
♪ Fleeting light
sketches the shape of fate ♪
♪ Footsteps fall lightly,
yet feelings can't be concealed ♪
♪ In a backward glance,
a few hidden feelings slip through ♪
♪ Ask the passing time
whether it has forgotten ♪
♪ The moonlight of our first encounter ♪
♪ Year after year,
it etches your likeness ♪
Fine.
Seeing no sadness on her face
♪ Count the faint shimmer
of the starry river ♪
and how happy she is,
if there are things
she doesn't want to say,
♪ Yet none compares
to the gentle light in your eyes ♪
then let it be.
♪ At last, I see the galaxy
shimmering and swaying ♪
♪ Reflected in our eyes ♪
♪ I'll be with you forever ♪
♪ And enjoy
the beautiful scenery with you ♪
♪ For all the days of our lives,
our love will endure ♪
[A Heart of Purity and Loftiness]
My Lady.
Where did you go
early this morning?
I knocked on the door for a long time
and no one answered.
I opened the door
and found that there was no one inside.
You scared me to death.
In the morning, Third Master and I...
How could Third Master
do something so outrageous?
Come on.
Has he ever done anything
that wasn't outrageous?
My Lady.
That person
already left this morning.
Let's go.
Let's pay respects to the Old Madam.
Do you mean that the moment I left,
Gu Jinzhao went to
pay respects to Grandmother?
Yes.
Young Master.
Also,
the Old Madam has entrusted Third Madam
with handling
your engagement to Miss Yu.
What?
Isn't this matter
always managed by Second Aunt?
How did it become her responsibility?
I don't know either.
I heard that
Third Madam volunteered for it.
She did it on purpose.
I think so too.
Young Master.
Third Madam has made it clear
she wants to keep her distance from you.
You should also
keep your distance from now on.
Don't let any ridicule arise
once Miss Yu marries into the household.
Gu Jinzhao.
Young Master.
Where are you going?
Young Master, please stop.
If you are looking for Third Master,
just go to the front courtyard study.
This is the inner courtyard—
please
mind propriety.
I am looking for Third Aunt.
I need to consult her on something.
You are a dignified Hanlin scholar.
What could you possibly
need to consult Madam about?
Madam has been busy
with your marriage these past few days.
She is occupied with many matters
and has ordered that no one be seen.
Please go back.
Fine.
♪ Who, deep beneath the water ♪
♪ Once shared the warmth of a palm ♪
♪ Setting the gears of fate ♪
♪ In motion ♪
♪ One curtain divides two worlds ♪
♪ Winter and spring
entrust their unspoken feelings ♪
♪ Sparks dance in the air,
lighting up the night ♪
♪ Alone, drunk in a fleeting dream ♪
♪ In dreams, I miss you, beyond words ♪
♪ My hand gently brushes past,
and dust settles on the scroll ♪
♪ Amid endless twists and turns ♪
♪ Love quietly sinks into silence ♪
♪ Time can never be looked back upon ♪
♪ I only regret missing
even a moment of togetherness ♪
♪ If longing bears no fruit ♪
♪ I'd rather we both sink away ♪
[Ancestral Virtues, Our Guiding Light]
Two thousand.
Five hundred.
Why hasn't the account from
the Prince Ning'an's residence
been recovered yet?
I've urged them several times.
But they are indeed poor.
Over a bit of property,
concubines and illegitimate children
are ready to fight to the death.
As for the Prince himself,
he only indulges in pleasure
and spends lavishly without restraint.
I don't think
they'll be able to
repay the silver anytime soon.
But
it's the Prince's household after all.
Maybe
they're still somewhat useful.
What use could they have?
At your last tea gathering,
Lord Chen's wife behaved disgracefully
and left you feeling upset.
I couldn't stand it either,
so I wanted to get back at her for you
and help you get even.
How do you plan to get even for me?
Master is back.
What are you whispering about?
So sneaky.
Prime Minister.
We were just discussing
how to give Chen Yanyun some trouble.
That's good.
Good idea.
Then think it through properly.
Go on.
Today is the opening of Linxia Restaurant.
Why didn't you wait for me there,
but came all the way here to pick me up?
By the way,
on the 8th,
Lian and Yao Wenxiu are getting married.
Do you plan to go
in the morning of that day,
or stay at Daxin the night before?
I'll just go on that day.
Anyway, they won't
be too pleased even if I show up.
Zhao.
I have a presumptuous request.
Go ahead.
It's the Mu family.
They want to propose marriage.
What?
Speak louder.
The Mu family wants to propose marriage.
I don't want them to go to Daxin.
Can they go to the Chen residence
to discuss it with you, Zhao?
Sure.
What?
You don't think
Young Master Mu is dull anymore?
Maybe after spending more time with him,
I feel
he's actually quite nice.
So that's why you came here.
Is Wanxue
also getting married soon?
Yes.
In a few days,
we should go to the Yu family
to set the date.
It will probably
happen this year.
[Western Regions Tribute Hide]
[Linxia Restaurant]
My Lady. Madam Chen.
The administrator
of the Prince Ning'an's residence
has brought men
and surrounded our courtyard.
Mr. Luo is stopping them outside.
Prince Ning'an's residence?
We've never interacted with them.
Well,
go with Uncle Ping
and see what's going on.
I will stay nearby
and check the situation.
Okay.
[Linxia Restaurant]
Our shop has always been law-abiding
[Opening]
and paid taxes on time.
We only do legitimate business.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Third Miss.
Uncle Ping.
This is
the administrator
of the Prince Ning'an's residence,
Lord Lai.
This is
the owner of our shop,
Miss Gu Lan.
Greetings, Lord Lai.
Miss Gu Lan?
But I heard that
the owner of Linxia Restaurant
is the wife of the Grand Secretary
Chen Yanyun.
So you are...
Madam Chen is my eldest sister.
If you have anything to say,
you can
speak to me as well.
I see.
Here's the situation.
[Linxia Restaurant]
In our residence,
there is an opera performer
who plays female roles,
named Xia Xiaohan.
He sings very well
and is
quite clever,
so he is much favored by our Prince.
But a while ago,
he suddenly disappeared
for no clear reason.
I sent people to search for him
and eventually found his whereabouts.
He is currently here
in Linxia Restaurant.
So please,
hand him over.
So I can go back and report.
Isn't Xia Xiaohan a man?
Did they really hide a man?
What is going on here?
My Lord,
our shop only receives women.
All servants, maids,
and kitchen staff
are women.
The Xia Xiaohan you mentioned
couldn't possibly be hiding here.
You must be mistaken.
What?
Miss Gu,
are you deliberately hiding him?
I wouldn't dare.
It's just that
our shop is opening today,
and you've brought people here
demanding someone.
Isn't it too much of a coincidence?
How would I know
it's your opening day?
I am also acting on orders.
If you still refuse to hand him over,
don't blame me
for what comes next.
[Linxia Restaurant]
Guards.
Search!
Wait.
Lord Lai.
Not to mention that my sister is
Grand Secretary Chen Yanyun's wife.
Since our shop opens today,
if you search it like this,
my business
will definitely be ruined.
If you do find him,
then I will go with you
to your residence and accept punishment.
But if you don't find him,
then the Prince Ning'an's residence
must give us
an explanation.
All the expenses prepared
for today's opening will have to
be borne by your residence.
Everyone here can serve as witness.
May I ask, Lord Lai,
can you agree to this?
They don't dare.
But I do!
Move aside.
Shuntian Prefecture on official business!
All idle persons, stand clear!
[Linxia Restaurant]
Shuntian Prefecture
is searching for a fugitive.
All idle persons, stand clear!
Go.
[Linxia Restaurant]
[Seal by Shuntian Prefecture
in the capital]
Zhao.
The Shuntian Prefecture officers
are here now.
Should we inform Chen Yanyun?
[Linxia Restaurant]
Third Miss.
Uncle Ping.
No matter how much silver it costs,
get their lead officer
into the private room opposite.
I have something to ask him.
Yes.
[Opening]
Thank you.
Please.
You guys go out first.
Yes.
You're showing me such respect—
if I still dodge you,
I wouldn't be a man.
Honestly, I'm not
that sure either.
Miss Gu.
Why don't you think carefully.
Has your backer
offended anyone
recently?
With someone of her status,
there can't be many who would dare
to cross her, right?
Uncle Ping.
I am busy with official duties,
so I won't disturb you further.
Farewell.
I've seen this kind of thing so much,
so it's really nothing
to make a fuss about.
Jinzhao.
Why are you here?
How could I not come?
Chen Yi has already
told me everything.
I'll go with you
to the Shuntian Prefecture.
No need.
I already have some leads on this matter.
Moreover,
the root cause is not
the Shuntian Prefecture.
You should go back
to the Hall of Literary Profundity.
Don't worry about me.
What are you talking about?
How could I not worry?
I know
you're used to the schemes
of the business world.
But since this
has involved
the Prince Ning'an's residence
and Shuntian Prefecture,
I naturally have to step in.
It's really not necessary.
I've always
dealt with
the authorities myself.
You have to trust me.
Besides,
if I rely on you whenever
I encounter a problem,
wouldn't that be
using your name
to do business outside?
If the imperial censor finds out,
it won't be good for you.
Actually,
you don't need to think that much.
I got it.
Alright.
Let's do it your way.
I'm leaving now.
Third Master.
The Shuntian Prefecture must have
some serious nerve to openly
trouble Madam like this.
Zheng Xiaoyou is the Governor
of Shuntian Prefecture,
a third-grade official of the court.
Since he is so willing
to be Wang Xuanfan's dog,
very well.
Let's deal
with him first.
[Hall of Literary Profundity]
[Perfect Harmony]
Mentor,
I must take my leave.
My wife's shop opened today,
but she was framed
and the Shuntian Prefecture
ended up sealing it.
Which scoundrel did this?
Has the Shuntian Prefecture
no sense of shame left?
Right.
I was also wondering
how the Shuntian Prefecture
could be so arrogant.
They must have
someone backing them.
Fortunately,
the truth will come out.
As for the person behind this...
Why are you looking at me?
What do you think, Prime Minister Wang?
[Perfect Harmony]
He is really interesting.
What
does it have to do with me
if his wife suffered a loss outside?
[House of Virtue and Brilliance]
Yanyun is a Grand Secretary,
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
and you are his wife.
It's not worth
letting the whole capital see a joke
over such petty gains.
Listen to me.
For Yanyun's reputation,
whether it's Linxia Restaurant
or any other business,
no matter how profitable,
stop running them all.
You are right, Mother.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
It's wrong to think like that.
[Orchid Chamber Fragrance]
Mother.
You came back early today.
I heard
something happened at Linxia Restaurant,
so I hurried back.
The business of Linxia Restaurant
should not only continue—
it must be done well.
Third Master.
It's already turned
into such a scene today.
Aren't you afraid
it will damage your reputation?
Mother.
What truly damages my reputation
is not Linxia Restaurant,
but those who try
every possible means
to bully my wife.
If Jinzhao
were to stop
all her businesses because of this,
wouldn't that make it seem like
I truly fear them?
That would be the real loss of face.
That's true.
[Immersed in the Classics and History]
You're already married to me,
and you still like sneaking looks at me?
You really know how to play the good cop.
No wonder you like playing Guan Yu.
Of course.
I'm used to playing the good cop.
Chen Yi.
[Immersed in the Classics and History]
Tell her
what you found out.
Yes.
Madam.
Prince Ning'an's residence
did lose an opera performer.
-But that was years...
-My Lady.
Third Master.
[Immersed in the Classics and History]
I've found it out.
How is it?
Just as you expected,
the person behind this
is Wang Xuanfan's wife.
I followed Lord Lai
back to the Prince Ning'an's residence.
Not long after,
Mrs. Wang's servant
also entered the residence.
Lord Lai then hurried out again,
and I followed him.
He turned out
to be going to a pawnshop
to redeem something.
I spent some silver to investigate.
Unexpectedly,
what he redeemed
was the Imperial Pardon Certificate.
The Imperial Pardon Certificate?
That is an item
bestowed by the late Emperor.
Prince Ning'an
must be tired of living.
-Actually, I found out that...
-In that case,
it makes sense.
For a dignified prince,
even if he owed some silver,
he would not willingly
become someone else's tool.
I never expected him
to pawn the Imperial Pardon Certificate.
If Mrs. Wang
is willing to forgive
part of the debts
and lend him another sum
for its redemption,
then the Prince's residence
would naturally follow her orders
and be at her disposal.
So
the Prince's residence has also borrowed
Mrs. Wang's usurious loans.
You knew Mrs. Wang
was lending money
at exorbitant interest outside?
How did you know?
At the tea party,
she made things so difficult for me,
so I naturally had someone
look into her background.
And once
I looked into it,
I found
she was lending money outside at interest—
and at usurious rates.
I found out...
The Prince of Ning'an's residence
owes Mrs. Wang a full 20,000 taels.
That's the result of compound interest.
Unable to repay,
and with Mrs. Wang knowing
they have pawned
the Imperial Pardon Certificate,
they are forced to submit to her control.
Coincidentally,
she also bears a grudge against me
for exposing her involvement
in imperial tribute goods,
so she had the Prince frame
and retaliate against me.
You are right, Madam.
This is exactly
what I found.
As a court ennobled lady,
Mrs. Wang is already
violating the law
by lending money outside.
To use usurious interest
to threaten military nobility
is truly audacious.
I can have someone
impeach Wang Xuanfan.
How far can you go with it?
How far
do you want me to go?
If we can't
bring down Wang Xuanfan in one move,
then there's no need to rush.
We can try my method
first.
What method?
A woman's method.
You're quite strong-willed.
I've always been strong-willed.
Qingpu.
Third Master.
I didn't expect
Madam to get information
this fast—
and so thoroughly.
It seems
the people you placed in the capital
are a waste of money.
Third Master.
About the 100,000 winter clothes
in the Ministry of War,
we have a lead.
The Armory Bureau did a spot check
and found that half
of the 100,000 garments
destined for the Nine Border Garrisons
were filled with
moldy, black cotton.
But the contractor
is the Dai family,
the maternal relatives of
Mr. Fu's wife.
So the Armory Bureau
neither dares to report the matter
upward
nor dares to actually
dispatch the garments
to Nine Border Garrisons.
They are in a dilemma.
Chen Yi.
Pass this information
to Qingpu.
But
do not say it came from me.
Yes.
Mr. Jiang.
What does the matter
of the winter garments
have to do with Madam?
It has nothing to do with her.
But if Madam
can solve this,
it would be
a favor to
the Senior Grand Secretary's wife.
It's benefits would be endless.
Think about it.
The key is
not to let Madam realize that
Third Master instructed you
to pass this on.
But, but...
why is that?
You wouldn't understand
even if I explained it.
Just do as you're told.
Ever since that incident,
people have been talking
about Linxia Restaurant—
saying it only caters to women,
and who knows
what kind of filthy place it really is.
That's why I said your idea was brilliant.
This batch of plain silk is quite fine.
It's yours.
Thank you, Madam.
This was an open scheme from the start.
I never expected Gu Jinzhao
not to find out I was the one behind it.
But even if she does, so what?
Can she scold me,
hit me,
or bite me?
With Chen Yanyun's influence,
Linxia Restaurant
will eventually be unsealed.
But simply lifting the seal is useless.
Its reputation is already ruined.
In the future, if she keeps claiming
to serve only women,
who would dare to go?
Which husband
wouldn't fear that an actor
or a man is hiding there?
That is what it means
to have grievances with nowhere to air
and suffering with nowhere to speak.
No one is wiser than you, Madam.
Recently,
we lent out another twelve thousand taels.
Our capital is getting a bit tight.
should we
add more funds?
We lent out that much again?
Since last month,
we've added a dozen more accounts.
It's all
one telling another,
and they just keep coming
one after another.
Although the court has managed
to recover quite a bit of tax silver,
those destined to be poor
are still poor.
Then I'll give you
another five thousand taels.
Madam.
An invitation from the Chen family.
She's actually coming to us?
[To Mrs. Wang.
From Gu Jinzhao of the Chen household]
[Meet at Baiwei Restaurant
at 8 a.m. tomorrow.]
Why arrange to meet outside?
This Gu Jinzhao
really has a lot of tricks.
[Baiwei Restaurant]
Why have you secretly arranged
to meet me here?
I came to return your silver.
What?
What silver?
It's a few servants from my shop.
Well,
Linxia Restaurant was sealed,
so I couldn't pay their wages.
Their families
also had some troubles.
Out of desperation,
they had to borrow usurious loans.
Who would have thought
they ended up borrowing from you.
I only just found out.
I said
such loans should not
be taken lightly.
It should be repaid immediately.
The total loan
[IOU]
is 13,000 taels.
The actual amount received
is 11,700 taels.
The daily interest is three li.
It was borrowed for seven days,
but we'll calculate it as ten.
So the interest alone
comes to 390 taels.
This is really a loan-shark debt.
If they can't repay,
they might even lose their lives.
It's best to return it to you at once.
[IOU]
What loans?
What does it have to do with me?
Is that so?
But I heard
it was your personal maid
who's been lending money.
Weren't you
acting on Mrs. Wang's orders?
Of course not.
You are so young.
How can you slander me like this?
How could I
possibly do something like moneylending?
I knew it.
Given your status,
how could you dare
lend usurious money outside?
That's a grave taboo.
So this really isn't your money?
Absolutely not.
In that case,
I won't be repaying it.
Qingpu.
Pass down my words.
If anyone comes to collect the debt,
send them to me.
I will just
take them to Shuntian Prefecture.
What does the Great Yan Law
say about this?
Those who privately
lend at usurious interest
shall receive 300 strokes.
Mrs. Wang,
we will take our leave then.
Madam,
I never expected that
the newly added accounts
were deliberately arranged
by Madam Chen.
I deserve to die. I deserve to die.
[Baiwei Restaurant]
My Lady,
Mrs. Wang really refused to admit it.
I never expected her to.
I just wanted to
give her a warning—
to let her know
I'm not so easy to bully.
To bring down Mrs. Wang
and revive Linxia Restaurant,
I need another person
to help me.
Miss Qingpu.
Why are you practicing your sword today?
I practice every day.
It is summer now,
yet it's quite cool.
Don't you feel
that these past few years
have been getting colder year by year?
If it's this cold
in the capital,
it must
be even worse
at Nine Border Garrisons.
The winter clothes for the soldiers
must not be delayed.
Master Yao.
My Lady, Yao is here!
Qingpu!
My Lady.
Zhao.
Yao.
Why did you come
to see me so late?
As soon as I arrived in the capital,
I came straight to your residence.
Does he treat you well?
That's good.
Have a seat.
You mean out of 100,000 winter garments,
half
were made with moldy cotton?
Yes.
No way.
Back then, the Dai family
relied on Madam Fu's influence
to forcibly win this bid.
Yet
they made such a huge mistake.
I suppose these days,
Madam Fu
must have been deeply troubled.
That is why
I have come to see you.
[A Splendid Match]