With immense strength
guarding the immortal gate
Even if all heaven's soldiers fall
I'd still dare alone
to fight the Great Sage
Mighty Spirit Power!
The Mighty Spirit dares fight the Great Sage!
What do I, Zhao Qiansun, have to fear from you?
Is my aura
really that strong?
But I haven't even gone all out yet!
I've failed Tianhuo City.
I've lost.
You really are strong.
No, don't be discouraged.
Actually, you're...
you're actually pretty strong too.
Kid, how did you even win?
Impressive!
Su Yang.
Do you have some dirt
on these Black Street guys?
They're trying way too hard.
Su Yang.
I'm talking to you.
Again.
Next up.
Truly a contestant from Shanhai City.
Such a calm demeanor
is simply admirable.
We're done for.
This kid's putting on an act.
He'll blow his cover sooner or later.
Call him back.
I see.
In a bit,
I'll send you out.
Don't disappoint me.
Why?
I could wipe out their whole team.
I believe
you have the power to sweep the field.
But shouldn't you give the others
a chance in the arena too?
Fair enough.
Go on. Go get some experience.
Go.
Next up for Tianhuo City is Wang Qiang.
Shanhai City's next contestant
is an adorable girl.
That's right.
Her name is Zhong Jun.
Congrats to Zhong Jun on her total victory!
Indeed. Meanwhile,
Tianhuo City has sent out
their third contestant.
As we can see,
on Shanhai City's side,
Zhong Jun is still taking the challenge.
Beautiful!
Zhong Jun has defeated her opponent again.
Let's congratulate Zhong Jun on two wins in a row!
Oh my goodness!
Defeated three in a row!
Looks like we can bring out
Tianhuo City's fifth member.
I forfeit.
What?
Tianhuo City's fifth member
has actually chosen to forfeit!
He didn't even dare to step on stage!
Truly one of the eight main cities, Shanhai City!
Their strength is indeed formidable!
So let's congratulate Shanhai City!
Next, please enjoy a cheerleading performance.
After the performance,
we will bring you
Xingguang City versus Shushan City.
It's over.
Zhong Jun has successfully proven
that Shanhai City
isn't entirely full of losers.
Then I'm heading back to sleep.
Been playing too much mahjong lately.
Staying up late, haven't slept well.
You're not gonna scout the opponents anymore?
Old man An and that fool,
what's there to watch?
Then wait for me.
Hold this.
I'm leaving too.
As everyone knows,
Shushan City has always been a cultural hub.
Of the ten top schools,
six of them are in Shushan City.
That's right.
Shu Qi has been famous in Shushan City for years.
Serving as captain and starter this time,
he's sure to bring us something special.
Indeed.
Xingguang City is also a dark horse.
Their captain, An Budong,
is also starting in this match.
Who will win this match?
Let's wait and see.
Please.
Fire.
Li.
Zhen,
becomes thunder.
Fire borrows the wind's force,
spreading a thousand miles.
Wild winds sweep across,
flames raging on.
Meeting water,
they're extinguished.
Thunder and fire collide!
What a dazzling fight!
That's right.
It's just spectacular!
Perhaps this old man
will win unfairly today.
What a pity
the world will lose a kindred spirit.
Jiang Ziya.
Thunder technique.
Fuxi.
Your Bagua
is truly profound.
Balancing offense and defense,
advancing and retreating with measure.
But both of us
have exhausted our immortal energy.
How about
we call it a draw?
A draw?
Why a draw?
I don't think we're kindred spirits.
While you were reading countless books,
I was fighting.
While you cultivated your temperament,
While you were taking a beating...
Your cane is made of iron!
Stop!
I lost.
I concede.
I know.
Your tailbone must really hurt right now, huh?
Come on, come on.
Let me help you up.
Come on.
He actually escorted his opponent off stage himself.
What a touching moment this is.
Indeed.
I believe if not for the competition,
they could've become great friends.
Let's watch together
An Budong's next performance.
Next.
I'm from Shushan City,
Bai.
Looks like after the last match,
An Budong has lost patience for slow fights.
Yes.
Now he's going for speed.
Are the people of Shushan City
all bookworms?
My body's a bit weak.
I can't fight those young guys anymore.
I leave it to you.
Got it.
What?
Xingguang City is substituting!
At the height of An Budong's fierce battle,
Xingguang City actually chose to substitute.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Xingguang City!
Xingguang City actually defeated
Shushan, one of the eight main cities!
But Shushan City has always been a cultural sanctuary,
so it's understandable they're not great at fighting.
Exactly.
Up next we bring you
Tianshui City versus
Yunhua City, one of the eight main cities.
Tianshui City's Wu Qianqiu
landed an elegant one-hit strike.
Awesome!
Yes.
Wu Qianqiu, even in Tianshui City,
is one of the standout fighters.
Tianshui City's Wu Qianqiu
actually, single-handedly,
tore through four Yunhua City players,
even including their captain.
Yunhua City is one of the eight main cities,
with heritage far surpassing Tianshui City.
To put it bluntly,
Tianshui City is smaller
than even a district of Yunhua City.
This is incredible!
But Wu Qianqiu is also seriously injured.
She'll probably step down, right?
No.
She chose to keep fighting.
She could have stepped down with honor,
yet...
I'm about to cry.
Just forfeit. Yeah.
Stepping down now isn't shameful.
She still has four teammates.
What on earth is she holding on for?
Alright!
Tianshui City's Wu Qianqiu
is defeated!
Coming up next
is Tianshui City's second contestant.
I forfeit.
What?
He... he actually chose to forfeit!
Your captain risked her life to wound him,
yet he doesn't even have the guts to fight.
Let's welcome Tianshui City's
third contestant to the stage.
I forfeit.
Let's welcome Tianshui City's fourth member.
I forfeit too.
After Captain Wu Qianqiu,
three teammates in a row
couldn't even beat one heavily wounded man.
How pathetic.
Let's welcome Tianshui City's
fifth contestant to the stage.
I forfeit. Can't beat him.
What do you mean "can't beat him"?
You don't even have the guts to try!
Oh, Tianshui City...
Congratulations to Yunhua City for advancing to the top four!
But from this day on,
I will always remember the name Wu Qianqiu.
She's my idol for life.
Indeed.
Coming up next is Fengxue City...
Xingguang City.
Keep an eye on them.
Forget it.
Not important.
No matter who wins in the end,
they'll be crushed by Haotian.
The Imperial Capital
will surely take first place.
You may go.
San Gou,
you've been visiting my brother
quite often lately.
He tried to win me over before,
asking me to spy on you,
but I refused.
Ever since then,
he keeps summoning me over,
trying to make you misunderstand me
and drive a wedge between us.
Don't worry.
I'm not stupid.
Go contact Wang Qiusheng.
Some things
need to begin now.
I have a feeling
he's hiding something from us,
but I can't read him.
Whatever.
In this world,
everyone has their own secrets.
What we need to do
isn't to dig up his secrets,
but to let him
take his secrets
to the grave.