( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
and she dropped us into the pits of misery.
How is Sayaka feeling?
She's recovering.
I see.
I'm sorry my girl keeps causing you trouble.
No worries.
Only one suspect remains.
Kaori Wakamatsu - Sayaka's mother.
This is delicious!
I'm glad to hear it.
Thank you again, Kazuomi.
Holding another ceremony
is nothing short of a dream.
I knew you were a reliable man.
I just want our wedding
to be a happy memory for Sayaka.
Is that so?
I was so frustrated the ceremony ended
the way it did.
A wedding is once in a lifetime.
I wouldn't want to have regrets.
She's been spearheading this ceremony
as if it were her very own.
She chose the venue, Sayaka's dress, and...
I would like my daughter to play the violin
after her vows.
What?
Performing in a pristine dress...
Doesn't that sound lovely?
Yes.
I'm sure the crowd would love that.
She pushed Sayaka to perform,
and even chose the piece.
She was likely aware
of our catering menu as well.
Which would mean she knew
of the blue champagne.
Kazuomi, would you be a dear
and hand this to Sayaka for me?
[J.S. Bach]
And this is?
A score, of course.
It's for the upcoming ceremony.
We can't have her perform the same piece.
This is a concerto for two, composed by Bach.
You're having her perform, again?
Yes! Sayaka and I will duet this time.
But...
Tell her to practice hard, alright?
- Mother, I don't think -
- My, would you look at the time?
I must be heading to the clinic.
Clinic?
Yes. I have to pick up
my prescribed medication.
Medication?
There is a medicine
that turns water blue when dissolved.
It's a type of sleeping pill.
What sort of medication, if I may ask?
Oh, it's just my usual prescription.
I'll be headed this way.
Take care.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the
🤫 Secrets in Champagne 🥂 Team @ viki.com
The "usual prescription", is it?
Yeah. She didn't specify what it was for.
Suspicious, right?
Either way, I'll continue tailing her.
Careful not to get caught.
Yeah, yeah.
Close call.
Honestly, I've had my suspicions about her.
Given how Sayaka's mother is,
it stemmed from issues at home.
You know how her mother is, right?
Sayaka was always overly conscious
of her mother.
It's like she was her mother's puppet.
To force an activity onto her child,
and exhibit controlling tendencies...
She's the very definition of a toxic parent.
That doesn't mean she had no love for Sayaka.
We'll never know
unless we press her about it ourselves.
[Ikebashi Mental Health Clinic]
"Mental Health Clinic".
It seems she's seeing a psychiatrist.
A psychiatrist?
I'll head in, and continue observing her.
I'll call back with any reports.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry I couldn't join you two today.
No need to apologize.
You should still be resting anyway.
What did my mother say?
She was worried about you.
I see.
What's that?
This? It's nothing.
Your mother sounded excited
for the second ceremony.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thank you, Kazu.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
Mrs. Wakamatsu. Mrs. Kaori Wakamatsu.
Here.
Please state your full name.
Kaori Wakamatsu.
And your primary psychiatrist
is Dr. Sato, correct?
- Yes.
- Dr. Sato has prescribed you two medications.
She was given a medication to take
after meals, and before bed.
Before bed.
Does this mean...
Yes. She was likely given sleeping pills.
That's it.
Shall we confirm the facts ourselves?
We're finally going head-to-head
with the culprit.
We can't afford to make mistakes here.
[Wakamatsu]
Let's not get hasty, alright?
Yes?
This is Hayashida.
Welcome! I'll open the gates for you.
You're quite early.
We apologize for visiting
on such short notice.
He'll be creating the slideshow
for our ceremony.
I see. Well, I have plenty of photos to share.
I hope you find whatever you need.
Thank you.
If I knew, I would have given you
the pictures over lunch, Kazuomi.
In any case, come on in.
Sorry for the mess.
Thank you for having us.
Thank you.
That's her bag.
I'll go grab it now.
No, she's headed our way!
It's fine, I've got this.
Everything alright?
Yes, fine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
We lost our chance.
Let's plan to get her to open up
through conversation.
If only I could directly ask
if those were sleeping pills.
Don't get pushy. She'll start to suspect us.
Here are the albums.
Thank you.
She's adorable.
Should I add this one?
Yeah. It captures Sayaka's charm.
Oh, do the photos stop here?
No, the rest are in the next album.
[Sayaka Wakamatsu]
This uniform...
[Unhappiest wishes to you, Red Riding Hood]
So that was her middle school uniform.
Does this mean Sayaka's mother
sent the threat?
Oh, Sayaka. What to do with a girl like her?
She practically attracts trouble.
Trouble?
Not serious trouble, of course.
She simply has a real habit
of bothering others.
As her mother, I'm ashamed of her.
How could she grow to be such a weak girl?
What an absolute pity.
She only continued to act depressed
in high school.
Chie and Airi were her only saving graces.
Really, she was lucky
to have friends like them.
Now these two girls
are splendid individuals.
Sayaka is no different, Mother.
Every day, I feel blessed to have met her.
She's a sweet, modest girl.
A real rarity nowadays.
And her cooking is especially delicious.
No, no. Her cooking is nothing special.
Sure, she may have attended
a culinary school.
But she only learned to make meager desserts.
I had my expectations
for her career as a pâtissier,
but she ultimately worked
a cash register, no?
Even then, she quit due to a bit of trouble.
That girl has no resolve, I tell you.
She can't keep at anything for long.
- Mother, please -
- My, I almost forgot!
The neighbors gave me some pastries.
Let me grab some to accompany our tea.
How could she say that
about her own daughter?
All she's done is humiliate Sayaka.
It's a bit much,
even under the pretext of "acting humble".
Yeah.
That toxic mother doesn't love Sayaka.
Now I'm sure of it.
She's the one who hurt Sayaka.
What are you doing?
My, what happened?
I'm sorry, I spilled a bit of my tea.
You should wash that right away.
I suppose so.
I'll head to the restroom.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
These are wonderful albums.
- Really?
- Yes.
I can see your love for your daughter
reflected in them.
Hayashida is a wonderful match for her.
He cares greatly for Sayaka.
Yes. He graduated from an excellent school,
and has a promising career.
I'm truly glad my daughter -
Kazuomi?
Are these from Sayaka's recitals?
Yes, they are.
She won her first when she was seven.
I see. That's amazing.
I've always loved the violin,
ever since I was a young girl.
Like mother, like daughter, no?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the
🤫 Secrets in Champagne 🥂 Team @ viki.com
What are you doing?
Kazuomi, tell me what's going on.
Well...
I thought you two were acting strange.
He didn't need to join us here, did he?
Mother, I...
Why have you really come today?
Mother. What sort of medication is that?
Your psychiatrist prescribed them,
did they not?
Yes. The whole affair at the wedding
affected me significantly.
Then are those sleeping pills?
Why do you want to know?
The reason Sayaka collapsed...
wasn't solely because of an ulcer.
What?
Someone drugged her.
Drugged her?
Sayaka!
Kazuomi...
Are you suspecting I did such a thing?
We simply want to confirm -
I would never.
This is a psychotropic medication.
Then please, show us the contents.
Enough!
You think I hurt Sayaka?
The absolute disrespect.
Do not even jest.
You two could never understand how I felt
raising my child.
I have lived my very life for Sayaka's sake.
I have sacrificed everything
for her happiness.
I'd be there for her. I'd worry for her.
I gave up many things for her.
And yet that child has betrayed
my every expectation.
Even so, I love my daughter
from the bottom of my heart.
I would never harm my own child.
Mother...
Just, wow.
Excuse me?
"Wow"?
"Wow", you say?
I-It was a slip of the tongue.
I'm terribly sorry.
You come to my home,
and meddle in my family's business?
Who taught you manners?
Did you even attend school?
Answer me.
Are you a mere high school graduate?
You must have attended a no-name school.
I suppose that's no surprise,
given you're only a photographer.
And now you've come here,
judging me for my own choices?
Oh how I'd love to see your parents.
They must not be very cultured themselves.
Mother. Sakuraba is a skilled photographer.
His work impressed you too, did they not?
Forgive me for speaking out of turn,
but you cannot judge a person
based on their education or career.
Sakuraba's photos are first class.
I will not allow you
to speak down on his work.
His education doesn't matter.
I trust him.
I'm the one who asked for his help.
He feels responsible, as another party
who was at the scene of the incident.
And please, do not berate Sayaka as well.
What?
Mother, you held ill will towards Sayaka
for betraying your expectations.
You couldn't stand to see her get married,
and escape from your clutches.
Ill will? Ridiculous.
Is that not the reason why
you ruined our wedding?
I only...
You cannot say you've done this
for your daughter.
If you truly cared for Sayaka,
you wouldn't belittle her.
So you think I'm the one behind it all?
You also told me not to report this incident.
Fine. I've heard enough.
This is all too much.
I feel dizzy.
Leave.
- Mother -
- I am not the culprit.
You may be my daughter's husband,
but you have gone too far.
Now leave.
♫ ♫
- The culprit is...
- Yeah.
[Triazele]
[Sleep aid pills]