( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I can't stand working
for Choi Ki-young anymore.
That has nothing to do with us!
Go to another company...
Let's hear the details.
As I promised Mr. Choi,
TORINNER achieved first place
in the debut song ranking.
But he said their sales amount
doesn't justify the expenses
and that's akin to a betrayal.
No way...
So you got fired for overspending.
Just shut up and listen.
I understand
he's stressed out as the CEO
but he calls me incapable
and useless every day.
That's so mean!
Like I said,
it's none of our agency's business.
And like I said,
just shut up and listen.
I've devoted my entire life
to producing artists.
This job is the only thing I have.
But Choi Ki-young has influence
all over this industry
so I can only come here
to escape from him.
True, he does hate our guts.
Clever thinking!
How is that clever thinking, Minase?
Have you forgotten all the trouble
this woman has given us?
That's true!
Besides, this woman stole
the TORINNER members from us
and presented them to Choi Ki-young.
Now that NAZE's career is
starting to take off smoothly
this traitor wants to come back here?
No way!
That makes sense.
I am very sorry.
What?
Please let me work with you again.
Wait...
But, we already have Mr. Azuma
as our producer--
Okay. Let's do it together.
She's the best person
we could ever hope for
if we want to help
those bumbling fools get better.
Wait! Do you have no dignity?
Training NAZE properly is my dignity.
NAZE's current goal is to win
the Best New Artist Award at MAMA
the music festival that is
garnering worldwide attention.
So, the next song we release must
beat TORINNER and get first place.
Ms. Park was the one
who trained TORINNER
so her social network and strategy
will be useful, don't you agree?
You're right. This is
a dream collaboration.
Hey, Nam. Tell me how you feel.
I'm pissed off.
Okay, it's decided.
Are you okay with this, Ms. Nam?
I'm not okay!
But I have no other choice.
Feel free to give us any suggestions.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working
with you, Mr. Azuma.
Good.
Ms. Park Ji-soo will join
our team starting today.
A round of applause.
What? She's joining us?
Mr. Azuma and I will turn you
into top stars together.
I look forward to working with you.
"Together"?
How about that? This is the birth
of the strongest duo!
Today, we're holding
a welcome party for Ms. Park.
- Yay!
What's this?
Yaminabe, the only dish
Mr. Azuma is good at making.
You're supposed to eat it
in a dark room, though.
Japanese people sure are weird.
Most Japanese people don't even
know about something this obscure.
Hey, that's rude to your producer.
Today's hot pot tastes good, too.
Okay, let's eat.
You know, you don't have
to force yourselfto eat.
Shut up.
Wait a minute. It's delicious.
Right?
Okay. Dig in, everyone!
- Yes. Let's eat!
It looks delicious!
He never served me food before.
Mr. Azuma,
do you cook for them yourself?
Occasionally. It tastes different
every time, though.
Do-hyeok, eat your veggies!
No, I'm good.
- Eat it!
- Eat it! It's good for your health.
You lied to me.
Incompetent people deserve to die.
You're worse than leftovers.
I'm not complimenting you.
Get out!
- Eat!
- Eat more!
- Hurry up!
Wow!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It's warm.
Sure is. It's hot pot, after all.
Right.
What? Do you guys sleep here?
Yes, it's the only room.
We sleep next to each other
like fish in the market.
You can leave
if you don't like it, jerk!
- Nice catch!
- Mr. Azuma, do you sleep here too?
These aliens have disrupted
the peaceful life of an innocent man.
You feel lonely living alone.
I don't feel lonely.
Hey, stop playing!
Go and take a bath now.
- Yes!
I told you to use the rag
when you wipe!
It's okay. I can use this.
Mr. Azuma is a strange person.
Look who's talking.
I agree, he's quite unusual.
I'm very interested now.
What? Is that...
What kind of interest
are you talking about?
My interest in him
as an individual, of course.
I'm leaving first.
We have an early day tomorrow.
What's with her all of a sudden?
Or rather, I should say he's
an interesting person to study.
Is Ms. Park serious
about coming back to us?
Of course she's not.
She must be plotting something.
What's wrong, Yuya?
It's nothing.
Just that I haven't been able
to get a hold of Ryo for days.
What? Ryo isn't calling back?
That's weird.
TORINNER must be so busy
since they're superstars.
Yeon-woo, are you okay?
Who said you could help him?
Is that your limit already?
That guy who just fell...
I don't know his name
but he's a member of TORINNER, right?
Are you okay?
Mr. Choi.
As you instructed
we've been having lessons
since this morning without a break.
Could you please let us
have a short break?
I haven't taken a break either.
Now that Ms. Park is gone,
I'm responsible for you guys.
If you feel that as strongly as I do,
you wouldn't have fallen.
Continue.
- Hey, let's do it.
- Yes.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four...
Do-hyeok!
You got it wrong again!
- What?
- Why?
Get your act together!
Once more!
This is it.
What?
They're close, cute, and innocent.
Oh, that?
That is the team's strength...
as well as their obstacle.
Obstacle?
Let's have a meeting.
NAZE's strength is that
they support each other as friends
and they're earnest.
They exude boyish innocence...
They're honest and very good boys.
But they'll never beat TORINNER
if that's all they have.
What? What did you say?
- Ms. Park is right.
- What?
It's nice to show respect
out of friendship
but fans will find it
too predictable.
She has a point.
It's good enough to select songs
matching the group's concept
before they find their own identity.
But if we want to reach out
to a wider audience
it would make sense to expand their
repertoire in a different direction.
Did I get that right?
But our members are fixed.
This isn't easy to achieve.
They're losers if they can't do it.
Watch what you're saying!
If they don't change
or challenge themselves
and stay in their comfort zone
people will grow tired of them soon.
I'm impressed, Ms. Park.
Thank you.
What do you think
about specific ideas like these?
You work fast.
I summarized the concepts
and visual images of new songs
by their patterns.
Overall, I think the ideas
you gave were great, Ms. Park.
I can't come up with ideas anyway.
That reminds me.
What's the matter, Mr. Azuma?
Ms. Park says maybe we can try
adding Korean zucchini to Yaminabe.
Go do some grocery shopping.
So, the costumes...
Darn you!
Why do I have
to buy groceries and cook?
I'm not your domestic helper.
Minase, are you angry?
You're emanating
a very negative aura.
Sorry. I couldn't help
saying my thoughts out loud.
We'll help you cook.
Thank you.
But Minase, you're so nice.
You'll make a good wife.
Hey, I agree!
What? Why are you saying that
out of the blue?
Your only flaw is that
you can't cook.
Shut up.
Minase, do you have a boyfriend?
No, no, I don't.
But...
There is... someone I like.
- What?
What is he like?
Well, he's usually brusque
but he's actually
a romantic at heart.
He's working hard
towards pursuing his dream.
- Wow!
- Wow! Isn't that nice?
- Are you going to ask him out?
- No. Somehow...
I don't think he's interested in me
and I think he's in love
with someone else.
It's over if you give up!
We'll root for you!
Where would be a good place
for a date?
A romantic place would be nice.
Yeah, I agree.
- The Sapporo Snow Festival!
- Too soon for a night together.
- How about a flower field?
- It's winter right now.
Wait, how about the aquarium?
Hey, good idea!
What do you think, Minase?
That sounds nice!
- Yay!
Nice idea!
An aquarium?
In the dark corridor
of the aquarium...
Your hands might overlap
one another...
So you bring a handkerchief
to keep your palms dry.
While the fish are dancing
in the tanks...
You're mesmerized by them
and nearly trip.
Then, he catches you in his arms.
The two of you look
into each other's eyes...
And after that...
Hey, watch the stove.
It's boiling over.
What are you guys doing?
What have you been doing?
Look at your dancing, singing,
and facial expressions.
Everything is the same.
There's no change.
You think you can beat TORINNER
like this?Are you kidding me?
You think this is enough
to entertain the fans?
You make no effort to improve.
Can you call
yourselves professionals?
You haven't improved at all
since I first trained you.
You're satisfied with your debut,
and then you disappear.
It's the typical end of
a hopeless group.
Does she have to be so harsh?
For example, Turn.
Your dancing skills
are the best in the team.
Thank you.
But as the main dancer
who is supposed to lead the team
you've failed.
Hey!
You lack charm as a dancer.
That's why the dance doesn't have
a proper flow.
I'm sorry.
Next, Do-hyeok.
Your looks are the team's strength.
Thank you.
But good looks are all you have.
Your facial expressions
and dance movements are stiff.
As a performer who should
enthrall the audience
you've failed.
I'm sorry.
One week.
One week later, we'll hold
a second auditionfor NAZE.
I'll assess whether you are essential
this team or not.
So, if you conclude
that we aren't essential...
You'll have to leave NAZE, of course.
Seven members are too many
to show off your individuality.
Let's see...
Five should be just right.
Hey, Mr. Azuma...
Well, we're in trouble.
Idiot! Why are you so nonchalant?
Look, NAZE's selling point
is their friendship and teamwork.
Why are you trying
to cause a rift between them?
Exactly.
There's no way
we'll remove any member.
Mr. Azuma said he wanted
to turn NAZE into top artists.
I'm just providing
the necessary support.
Azuma didn't say he'd fire them!
Ms. Nam.
Will they be able to beat TORINNER
as they are now?
Did you mistake the K-pop industry
for an aquarium
full of beautiful fish?
We're in a school of hungry sharks.
They need to evolve continuously,
or they'll be devoured in no time.
A second audition sounds interesting.
I look forward to seeing
another side of them.
You agree with every single thing
Ms. Park says.
Will they really get rid of
two of us?
Ms. Park said that,
so I think they'll do it.
How can they do this?
She said my looks are
my only strength.
That's not true.
Don't take it to heart, Do-hyeok.
But at this rate...
I think Ms. Park is right.
We can't survive if we keep
repeating the same routine.
I should've realized
something so important.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Ato, it's not your fault.
This concerns everyone.
But I also agree that
we can't continue like this.
What? So you agree
to her layoff plan?
Then we can't stay as seven.
- But...
- In order to survive...
I'll fight, even against our members.
I see you're still working hard.
How about having
some Japanese oden together?
It's perfect for a cold day.
Thank you.
Are Ms. Nam and Minase okay?
They'll be okay.
It might have been
too harsh for them, though.
This is my flaw.
Same here.
Still, there are times
when I have to treat them coldly.
But I tend to hesitate if I'm alone
so I appreciate your surprise attack.
Why will you hesitate?
In the past
I had pushed
some talented young men too hard.
SS.
That's SEVEN SEAS, the group
you produced in the past, right?
They had an audience
of 200,000 in Japan.
Their Asia tour was successful.
So I assumed
everything went smoothly.
Then, I pushed them too hard.
I kept telling them to work harder.
I unilaterally imposed
my dream on them
and made them suffer.
And in the end, I abandoned SS.
I gave up on everything halfway.
Are you okay with ruining our lives?
I had read in a gossip magazine
that you abused your power.
That's right. Then, I was
blacklisted by the industry.
I was told not to get involved
with them again, and I agreed.
Because I thought it was
the best I could do to protect them.
But SEVEN SEAS retired
right after that.
I have no idea where they are
and what they're doing now.
I acted all cool
and talked about my dream.
I let them choose a life that was
all about singing and dancing.
Yet, I couldn't take responsibility
until the end.
I was the one who ruined their lives.
Guess I went on too long
about all that boring stuff.
Anyway, enough about my story.
I know you're playing the bad guy
to help NAZE grow.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Okay, it's time
for a special training session!
Screw that second audition!
I swear I'll make you all win
and stay here!
What?
The song I just played will be
your next assigned song.
Use this song to show us
a completely new side of NAZE.
This is the evaluation criterion
for the second audition.
A completely new side of NAZE?
What does that mean?
You want to survive
in the K-pop world, right?
Then think about what you need
to improve yourself.
Line distribution, choreography,
and facial expressions.
Think about this song from every
angle until your brain is fried.
Where's your answer?
- I understand.
We'll have a midterm assessment
in two days.
I expect everyone
to do their very best.
The song Park Ji-soo brought
has a totally different style
from their debut song.
- Are you sure about this?
- The song is good, right?
It's perfect for their image
as their second single.
When things go according
to her plan, I just feel like...
Enough of that.
Did Choi Ki-young call to protest
and tell us to give Park back?
Not a single call.
She did say that he was angry that
she overspent on promoting the group.
Choi fired her. Besides,
her personality is horrible.
How about doing this here?
Five, six, seven, eight.
It's the same as usual.
Make it flashier.
We can add some steps, for example...
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Movements like these
are too difficult.
It's pointless
if we don't try something new.
I'm telling you to face reality.
- Hey...
- Wait...
You two! Fighting isn't productive.
Did you see such a lovely girl?
Did you see such...
Hey, stop! Stop!
Your face is totally blank.
- You must remember to smile!
- I'm sorry.
He won't get it
unless you give him precise advice.
- Make Do-hyeok understand.
- But I've explained so many times!
But he doesn't get it.
- Calm down.
- How can I not be annoyed?
I could be fired
if I don't practice too!
I am sorry, Younki.
It hurts! Don't bump into me!
What? It's your fault
for being there.
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey, keep it down!
You'll get injured!
Watch out!
Fight outside if you want to fight!
Now, let's begin
the midterm evaluation.
- Yes, ma'am.
Play the song.
Is this a joke?
You're only trying your best
to dance and sing.
You don't understand what is
necessary to perform this song.
I can't believe you think you can
perform like this in front of people.
In the end
losers can never change.
This is only the midterm evaluation.
Let's do our best
during the real thing.
Mr. Azuma.
What will happen
if we fail next time?
Is it really over for us,
just as Ms. Park said?
Yeah.
If you can't discover
your new potential
you're better off
considering a different career.
I feel the same.
It's natural to feel bewildered
when someone tells you
they'll remove members from the team.
You couldn't focus on practicing.
It can't be helped.
That's exactly why we failed.
What?
Times like these
are when we need
to practice as hard as we can.
But we aren't united.
There's no way
we can perform well like this!
- You're one to talk!
- Stop it.
Seriously. It'll be over for us
if this continues.
But it's not like
we've been slacking off.
We've been working pretty hard.
I'm quitting.
What are you saying, Do-hyeok?
Neither my dancing nor my singing
skills are useful to the team.
It'll be better for NAZE if I leave.
Don't think like that--
I'm sick of us fighting!
We've been doing this together
and I wanted you guys
to always get along.
But I couldn't do anything.
So I'm going to quit!
That's the only thing I can do
to make myself useful to everyone.
I love NAZE.
I love you guys too.
That's why
I want the seven of us
to become top artists together.
I want us to beat TORINNER
and become number one.
What about you guys?
I feel the same, but...
Me too.
But they'll eliminate two of us.
Yeah.
But first of all
what should we do
the best version of NAZE?
Why don't we
think through it once more?
I'm sure
it's something
that only we can come up with.
Because all seven of us
made NAZE.
You're way too passionate, as always.
We don't need to change everything.
We have tons of strengths, too.
That's right.
Ato's singing.
Yuya's breakdance.
Kun's rap.
And Do-hyeok's amazing visuals.
But she said
my good looks were all I had.
That's not true!
Our youngest member's charm
is our team's strength!
Wait, what about me?
There's nothing about me?
Well...
Seriously? Nothing?
We're kidding!
Kaisei, you're the best
at being calm and mature!
That just means I'm old!
Join us, Minase.
Really?
Got it.
Then...
Let's do our best.
One, two...
- NAZE!
- Let's do our best!
- Let's go!
Yay!
It's from Ryo!
Sorry, we've been having lessons
from morning to night every day
without any break.
It's killing me.
Did something happen, Yuya?
Actually,
we're having a tough time too.
I looked up on social media,
and I found two of our strengths.
Two?
People say we look close
and seem like naive, innocent boys.
So we can either double down
on that impression
or go in a different direction.
A different direction?
It's difficult.
Guys, I just talked to my Ryo.
Really? What did Ryo say?
He said we could try something
a bit more mature.
- Mature?
- Us?
Yes. So far, our songs
and choreography
have been very energetic.
But this new song
sounds a bit more mature.
- I see.
- Right...
Is this finally my time to shine?
Well, it's a medium tempo song
so a mature concept
could be a perfect fit.
I see.
Showing off mature charm?
I'm the only one who can do that.
Wait. Do-hyeok, stand up.
What is it?
Raise your chin slightly.
Pose your arms like this.
Keep that pose
and look at the center of the pot.
What do you think?
It looks delicious.
That's not what I meant!
Guys, what do you think?
Doesn't he look sexy?
He's the youngest, though!
- I see it!
- Right, I agree!
- He looks kind of sexy.
- The hot guy is now even hotter.
We might be able to pull this off.
A grown-up NAZE!
Wow. I'm impressed, Yuya!
It's all thanks to Ryo.
Hang on! Why are you guys
ignoring me?
Let's do this. A new NAZE!
- Yeah!
Come on, sit down.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
five, six, seven, eight...
It's the same as Younki's.
Okay.
Okay, once more.
- You can do it, guys.
- Yes!
- NAZE!
- Do our best!
Looking good, guys.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
five, six, seven...
What's the matter? Why are you here?
Now, let us commence
with the second audition.
- Yes, ma'am!
Play the song.
You did it.
You showed us your new charm.
A new NAZE.
You did very well. Good job.
- Thank you.
But...
You said you would be
eliminating members.
Yesterday, one of your members
came to talk to me.
He said NAZE had fallen apart once
but now, you're able
to unite as one again.
He asked me to eliminate only him
if I had to.
I couldn't just let you bawl
and cause a commotion there...
Please just eliminate me!
Ato.
What? Ato?
I'm sorry.
Hey! What's going on, Ato?
You guys worked very hard
and are shining so brilliantly.
I thought we couldn't afford
to lose any of the members.
So if anyone had to leave
I thought that I should be
the only one.
So you had made up your mind
back then?
No, you can't!
Ms. Park, please don't eliminate Ato.
We were only able to do our best
because he's here!
NAZE will fall apart again
without Ato.
If you need to get rid of someone,
just eliminate me!
Not you too!
NAZE is the seven of us together.
Okay, okay! You're all so annoying.
Ms. Park is well aware.
She knows your true abilities
and what you lack.
Just a few days after joining
she compiled your data
and explained the situation to me.
Then, she decided that the next song
should have a more mature concept.
She believed that would allow us
to capitalize on NAZE's skills
and draw out
the group's brand-new charm.
So she prepared this song for you.
Let's see. If we want
to make them go all out
why don't we threaten
to eliminate some members?
Will they believe a lie like that?
Don't worry, the boys are very naive.
What?
Azuma, you were the one
who came up with that mean idea?
Yes. Don't be surprised,
but I'm the true mastermind!
Darn it! I won't forgive you.
- Ms. Nam.
- What?
- Stupid Azuma!
- Ouch... Sorry.
So, then...
Does that mean I don't have to quit?
NAZE won't be the same without you.
Right?
- Yay!
Lift him up!
One, two!
Hooray!
One, two! Hooray!
You aren't allowed
to contact anyone outside
let alone the NAZE members.
They're your rivals.
But Yuya is my brother!
And what about that?
You're here to become stars.
You're different
from lowlifes like them.
I don't need anyone
who isn't able to stand on top.
Don't forget that.
Geez, we've been at it
from morning to night.
This schedule is insane!
Still, he let Ms. Park go?
Mr. Choi is nothing special.
(Korean)
SEVEN SEAS'S ABUSIVE PRODUCER
AND HIS REIGN OF TERROR
This will make us even stronger.
Don't worry.
Mom, we'll get first place
for you this time.
Okay, talk to you later.
Kun.
I have something good for you.
I won't be able to come home
for a while, but I'm doing well.
Just get in touch with me
if you're worried about anything.
Turn.
Do you have a minute?
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Why did he call us here so urgently?
Geez, we've been at it
from morning to night.
This schedule is insane!
Still, he let Ms. Park go?
Mr. Choi is nothing special.
Right.
I received a report
from my secretary.
I poured everything I had into you
but it looks like
some of you betrayed me.
Traitors will not be forgiven.
Driving them into a corner is
my style.
I'm very sorry!
We didn't mean it!
We were just whining
because we were exhausted!
I'm sorry!
You two betrayed me.
I hope you're prepared for it.
Mr. Choi!
- I'm sorry!
Please forgive us!
I'm sorry!
Feel free to give us any suggestions.
Seven members are too many
to show off your individuality.
Let's see...
Five should be just right.
Don't worry, the boys are very naive.
It's warm.
Sure is. It's hot pot, after all.
I thought we couldn't afford
to lose any of the members.
Training NAZE properly is my dignity.
You know, it's not too late yet.
What are you talking about?
You're the real deal.
As a producer and a person.
You're the most reliable colleague
one could ever ask for.
That's what I believe.
Thank you. I look forward
to continuing to work with you.
Haven't you done enough?
You don't have to go back to him.
You came here because Choi Ki-young
told you to trip us up, right?
We used to work together
as producers.
Back then,
he was by no means cheerful
but he was an honest person
who pursued music diligently.
But it appears that he has changed.
I asked Nam
to look into things for me.
It seems like he's
keeping TORINNER occupied
with tons of practice.
What are you trying
to accomplish with this?
It's important to work hard
but this is insane!
I'm sure he must be putting
a lot of pressureon you every day.
When I look at you
I can tell that
you really love your job.
You must be someone
who wants to exchange ideas
with your colleagues
as you perfect your craft.
Do you really need to lie to yourself
and force yourself to do this?
I don't...
believe in myself enough
to live in my comfort zone.
I need to be on top.
I need to be number one.
Otherwise, I can't feel my own worth!
I understand your point,
but humans are fragile.
Don't think you're capable of
doing everything.
I'm free to live my life
the way I want!
Sorry.
I'll think about what you told me.
Why is she so awkward?
Good luck.
You have the talent
to make people in the world happy.
The two of you and your families
need to be happy too.
Don't you agree?
- Yes, ma'am.
In that case, why don't you
join TORINNER?
We'll welcome you
as official members.
Let's aim for the top together.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL
It's over for Azuma.
You'll regret it
if you continue to trust Mr. Azuma.
That jerk killed him!
Have you made up your mind
to join TORINNER?
You won't be able
to see the boys again!
I'll be in NAZE's way if I stay.
So I'm going to disappear.