Here's the list of the top sixteen.
Please take a look.
Among them,
on Starlight City's team,
there's an old man and a young one.
Their strength is impressive.
The old man's Divine Blessing is from Fuxi.
His skill is the Bagua Diagram.
The young one seems a bit simple-minded,
but he has brute strength.
His Divine Blessing info hasn't been revealed.
And the leader of Tianshui City's team,
is skilled in ancient martial arts.
She's a woman.
Her Divine Blessing
is from Holy Lord Erlang.
My brother's side,
any recent moves?
Lately he's been in close contact
with managers of some small cities.
They often gather privately for drinks.
But strangely,
all the cities he's in contact with
were eliminated in the knockout rounds.
Even their contestants
barely put up a fight.
They just surrendered.
Very good.
You've done well.
Once the tournament ends,
that Immortal Artifact
will definitely be yours.
By then, you'll become one of the blessed,
still able to look down upon this world.
Your subordinate vows,
I would give my life for you.
Zhou Sangou
turns out to be a useful pawn.
In the finals,
the Imperial Capital will take the crown.
But Shanhai City's people
stole the finals prize
and were killed on the spot.
We can then confront Shanhai City,
demand the Immortal Artifact in 3 days,
or we go to war.
At this juncture,
fifteen small cities joined forces
to attack Imperial Capital's Young Lord Gu.
So the Imperial Capital has grounds
to declare war on multiple parties at once.
I can already smell it,
the scent of gunpowder in the air.
Some things
really don't need to be said out loud.
I'd hope your Sky City
could show some sincerity too.
The sincerity we've brought,
isn't it enough?
Without the testing devices we made,
how could the Imperial Capital obtain
data on all Divine Blessing holders?
With stats of all Divine Blessing holders,
if anything still goes wrong,
that's no longer our problem.
Even without that data,
we, the Imperial Capital,
could still wipe them out all the same.
Whether your Imperial Capital wants
to contend for supremacy,
or ignite the flames of war,
it won't drag Sky City into it.
I only want that Immortal Artifact.
It's the instrument of my Divine Blessing.
With it,
my power will skyrocket.
But of course.
Come,
here's to a pleasant partnership.
I hope you
won't go back on your word.
Sky City is one of the Eight Major Cities.
Once the dust settles,
I'll deliver the Immortal Artifact
into your hands.
A hundred cities,
that's far too many.
This world only needs
one Imperial Capital, and that's enough.
I'm really looking forward to that day.
Gu Changkong and Gu Changye scheme deeply.
Neither will yield the Immortal Artifact.
From here on,
I'll likely be their primary target.
To be safe,
I'm leaving the group chat first.
Sangou.
Outside Black Street,
people call me Boss Dog.
Sangou has left the chat.
Does he actually think
that's super cool and stylish?
Cutting off mid-sentence.
So,
are we still entering the tournament?
No matter what,
take first place.
Demand the Immortal Artifact.
If they refuse,
we'll tear the Imperial Capital apart.
Welcome, everyone,
to the Hundred Cities Tournament arena.
I'm sure all of you
have been looking forward to this match.
That's right.
We can see on the stage,
Wu Kai from Jing City
and Wu Qianqiu from Tianshui City
are already in position.
Their builds differ drastically,
but as for the outcome,
let's wait and see.
Wu Kai of Jing City, here to face you.
Tianshui's
Wu Qianqiu.
No need to doubt it.
In the face of absolute power,
external factors don't matter.
Tianshui City advances to the top eight!
Congratulations to Heavenly Fire City,
successfully advancing to the top eight!
Everyone,
the Hundred Cities Tournament has ended.
I'm sure you've all seen
the results on the big screen.
Yes.
The small cities advancing to the top eight
are as follows:
Heavenly Fire City,
Tianshui City,
Starlight City,
Jingtian City,
Huicao City,
Yunlan City,
Yangui City,
Shuangyue City.
Let's congratulate these eight cities
for standing out among the hundred,
qualifying to challenge the major cities.
Everyone,
tomorrow, the quarterfinals
will officially begin.
Good luck!
The quarterfinal draws are out.
The next city challenging us
is Heavenly Fire City.
I watched their matches in advance.
Their strength is average,
far weaker than Starlight and Tianshui.
Against us,
their odds of winning
are zero.
Alright.
Honestly, I still can't figure out
what the quarterfinal format designer
was actually thinking.
No individual matches,
no team matches,
just five people taking turns to fight.
The winner
stays on the stage.
The loser
gets swapped out for the next.
It ignores overall team strength.
As long as one person is strong enough,
he can wipe out the whole opposing team.
But thankfully,
this time on our team
we have Su Yang.
So,
I'm actually very satisfied
with the Imperial Capital's format.
How about it, Su Yang?
Got the confidence to take on five?
Does it really have anything
to do with my confidence?
Pointless.
It's pointless to even talk to you.
Wasting your precious time.
I had expert analysts run the numbers.
Given Heavenly Fire City's strength,
we don't need to send Su Yang in.
So that means
we can give you a chance to shine,
I mean,
a chance
to bring glory to Shanhai City.
So tomorrow,
Yu Shuai goes first.
Your Divine Blessing is pretty flashy,
so it'll grab the audience's attention.
Zhong Yun,
you're second.
If
the first opponent
gets badly wounded by Yu Shuai,
then you just go up and throw a couple punches,
and walk off in style.
If they aren't badly wounded,
just surrender right away.
Xu Siguo goes third.
Liu Xiaorou fourth.
Su Yang as the closer, any objections?
Name of Heavenly Fire City's captain?
He's called
Fatty Zhao with a cleaver.
So,
you laid out all these messy tactics,
what does any of it have to do with this?
Are you just trying to prove your worth
as the Young Lord?
No, no.
I know Fatty Zhao is a Black Street guy,
but some things,
you just can't say out loud.
Right?
Alright.
So tomorrow,
we'll officially make Shanhai City's name
echo throughout the Hundred Cities.
Are we confident?
Yes! Yes!
Meeting adjourned.
I'm really glad
I pulled you on board for this tournament.
Black Street folks are way more reliable.
Look at the Eight Major Cities' leaders,
every one of them elusive as a dragon,
acting all high and mighty.
But look at you,
like a sidekick,
showing up everywhere.
Come on, listen to yourself.
I'm broke, aren't I?
If I had money,
I wouldn't be out here hustling either.
Get in.
Why are you riding in my carriage?
Because
we only rented our bus for one day.
Get in.
Hyah!
Shanhai City, Yu Shuai, No. 3
Sakura City, Su Qing, No. 6
Yunhua City, Xiao Zeyi, No. 5
Heavenly Fire City, Zhao Qiansun, No. 3
Based on the draw results,
today's first round match
is Shanhai City versus Heavenly Fire City.
That's right.
Will Heavenly Fire City manage to defeat
Shanhai City, one of Eight Major Cities,
and pull off an upset?
Who will come out on top?
Let's wait and see.
First match:
Shanhai City's Yu Shuai vs. Heavenly Fire City's Zhao Qiansun.
A true Eight Major Cities contender.
Such incredible composure!
I have to say,
when I called the Hundred Cities knockouts,
some folks stepping into the arena
were already shaking like leaves.
Now let's take a look at
Heavenly Fire City's contestant,
Zhao Qiansun.
What a memorable name!
He constantly carried his four teammates,
a truly god-like presence.
Are we talking a bit too much?
Then enough chatter,
the match officially begins!
This kid is way too cowardly.
He's about to wet himself.
Looking this lame against other teams,
how's Shanhai City gonna take first place?
These two contestants
are truly...
unshakeably calm.
Yeah, totally calm.
Su Yang,
do you think
Yu Shuai can win?
I don't know.
I think he's about done for.
Then let me help build your confidence.
Come on!
Make your move!
I'm looking forward to
an honorable showdown between masters.
Green lantern...
Green lantern by my side...
Mighty axe...
Green lantern ever by my side,
mighty axe cleaving mountains.
The immortal path is vast and distant,
descending into the mortal world.
Chenxiang Splits the Mountain!
Now that's more like it.
What a powerful aura!
Truly a master of Shanhai City.
He...
He said my aura's strong.
He's...
He's wary of me.
If I don't strike now,
I'm afraid I'll lose the nerve to.
Take my vertical slash!
Your strength
is truly terrifying.
But even so,
I'll use my very life
to defend Heavenly Fire City's honor.
A hundred thousand celestial soldiers
shall lead the charge.
With colossal strength,
I guard the immortal gate.
Even if all celestial soldiers fall,
I'd still dare alone
to fight the Great Sage.
Colossal Spirit Power!