What do you think you're doing?
(Tarot Reading See your destiny)
You think this is my first time
dealing with people like you?
People like me?
What did I even do?
Just because you're a star,
you think you can do whatever you want?
Isn't it you, though...
The one sending those disgusting
letters to my house.
Following me like a shadow
and selling photos like a creep.
I said it wasn't me!
Okay, okay, everyone calm down.
I need to get home for my cat's livestream.
Are you mocking me right now?
At least you're decent looking.
"Handsome", my ass...
You look like a cat's nut sack.
Hey! That's verbal abuse!
That's an insult!
I'm suing him!
Geonwoo!!!
Are... are you okay?
Wh-wh-what happened?!
Call my lawyer.
Uh... I was going to...
You think I don't have a lawyer?
What do you need a lawyer for?
This is exactly when you need one.
I have one too, just you wait.
(That law school kid! Finally useful.
(I'm being framed. Give me your number.)
Pick three cards.
What?
But where are you...
Focus on your question first.
Then pick three from the table.
Oh...
Will Jaeyeon like me?
Pick one more.
Hmm... you'll get one chance.
What?
If you miss that moment,
you'll be friends forever...
(That law school kid! Finally useful.
(I'm being framed. Give me your number.)
(Calling Jaeyeon)
It was 20,000 won, though.
(T/N: He only gave 10,000 won.)
Lawyer! Over here!
Hey, what's going on?
Taewoo, he keeps calling me a creep...
A stalker...!
Jaeyeon?
What's going on here?
You brought him here?
Jaeyeon?
You.
What did you do to my brother?
Bullshit...
What's really going on?
Yeah, what the hell...?
What happened?
I got the CCTV footage.
Should we take a look?
Fine, play it.
This guy...
I don't think he's a stalker...
Really?
"Really"?!
Here's your chance.
What...?
An interview.
Forget the apology,
get an interview instead.
I know my brother.
Don't expect a sincere apology from him.
I can apologize for Geonwoo...
No, it's fine.
How about some compensation then?
Is a million won enough?
Better than an apology, right?
Forget it...!
Just do one thing for me.
Do it with me!
Do what...?
Wh-wh-what exactly?
An interview... an interview!
He stutters when he's nervous...
Thirty minutes is all I need!
Just a thirty-minute interview.
Tomorrow at 4 PM, at my place.
Send him the address.
About what happened earlier.
I wanted to apologize for him...
You didn't do anything wrong.
He's just like that sometimes.
But he has his reasons.
He's lucky.
Huh?
He always has someone on his side.
Hey!
I'm on your side!
I'll always be on your side!
You'd better stay on my side then.
Here's my number.
Text me, and I'll send the address.
Okay, okay.
So...
Taewoo!
Yeah?
He wasn't always like that.
What?
Your brother...
Never mind... see you later.
Are you an angel?
Yeah, pretty much.
Then can I have the other popsicle too?
Don't be greedy.
And here I thought you were an angel.
You're the type who'd
steal an angel's underwear.
That text scared the life out of me.
When they said they'd call a lawyer,
I got nervous too.
Is that why you said I was a lawyer?
Yeah.
That's fraud, you know.
Whatever.
It worked out in the end, anyway.
So why is it so awkward
between you and your brother?
Didn't you just see why?
Yeah, I guess...
You know my parents are divorced, right?
Yeah, I know.
Did you know my dad went to prison?
I didn't... wait, what?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Did I act too surprised?
A little bit, yeah.
But why?
My brother's the one who reported him.
What?
After the divorce,
my brother blew up as a child star.
My mom was always busy with him.
My dad still came to see me sometimes...
At least I had him.
I didn't feel as lonely...
But maybe he missed my brother too.
He'd just take him away without a word.
Hey... is it okay for me to hear all this?
If it's not you , then who else is going to listen?
My mom and brother reported him.
He ended up in prison.
Truthfully, that's just what my grandma told me.
So I don't know the whole story...
Did it become... better for you?
No.
My mom got even more protective of him.
I just got pushed aside even more.
Honestly, my brother
didn't do anything wrong.
But I feel like he stole
my parents from me.
So I just grew to resent him.
Am I being childish?
No!
Not at all!
You grew up well.
And honestly, you're way
more handsome than your brother.
You're smart, too.
True.
I'm the best, aren't I?
Wait, what?!
Fine, fine.
"Fan Service"
(Episode 2)
Um... hey!
Could I... get an autograph?
My name is Noh Jaeil.
Thank you!
(William)
That prick...
Want to know what his cards meant?
The first card means no romantic feelings.
It's more like friendship or family.
The second is platonic love.
Deeper than friends, but not lovers.
The last one says they'll be like family,
but never a couple.
(What about that extra card?)
That's the one chance I gave him.
Whether he takes it... I don't know.
(But why are you talking informally more and more...?)
30,000 won.
(You said 20,000 earlier...)
30,000 won...