So Geonwoo, what does success mean to you?
When I was a kid, it was being on TV.
It felt like the whole world was inside.
Then it was doing commercials,
and as I got older, starring in a drama,
winning awards, and so on.
The bar just kept getting higher.
Yeah.
But lately, I'm not so sure.
When my insomnia is really bad,
just getting a good night's
sleep feels like success.
When I'm on a strict diet,
being able to eat whatever
I want feels like a win.
My definition of success
is always changing.
So, what's the hardest part
about being in this industry?
Always having to smile in front of people.
Even when I'm falling apart inside,
no one can really tell.
That's the hard part.
Can you check if I look okay?
Uh... do I look alright?
Is that really so important?
I've always wondered something.
Huh?
When did you and Taewoo get so close?
We first met at a local gym.
Taewoo was pretty shy back then,
so I looked out for him.
You might already know this,
but when I was a kid,
back when I was a child actor,
there was a scene
where I had to get in a car.
I was actually kidnapped that time.
Kidnapped?
Yeah.
People said I was unusually calm.
When I got out of the car,
I didn't even cry.
I seemed totally fine.
That's because
the person who took me
was my father.
We started filming and got in the car.
My dad was in the driver's seat.
I was so excited, asking
where we were going.
But my dad...
just kept crying and saying he was sorry.
He took me to a toy store,
bought me a robot,
and then he just left.
It never made the news.
Only my mom, my manager,
and I knew about it.
I really didn't want the world to know.
But...
is it okay that
you're telling me this?
Yeah.
I just needed someone to talk to.
For some reason, I
felt like I could trust you.
Hyung, what are you talking about?
So you don't trust me?
You knew I hated you, yet
you still kept this from me?
Taewoo, it's not like that...
Not like that?
You know
I've always been the odd one out.
To everyone else, I'm just
Geonwoo's little brother.
Even the stuff about
Dad only belongs to you.
I knew you felt left out.
That's why I couldn't tell you.
If you had known about Dad too,
it would've hurt you even more.
Stop making excuses!
That's my business too.
You just made me look like a fool.
That's enough.
Let's calm down before we talk.
Jaeyeon...
You said you'd always be on my side.
Taewoo.
I'm not taking sides here.
Taewoo, don't be like this.
This isn't Jaeyeon's fault.
Enough.
I get it now.
In the end, I'm always second best.
Taewoo!
Let go of my hand.
I'll be right back.
I'll go talk to Taewoo and come back.
Please wait for me here.
Taewoo!
Hey, where are you going?
What am I supposed to do?
What am I supposed to do staying here?
Don't run.
I'm right here.
Let's go together, okay?
Come on.
Taewoo...
Stop drinking so much.
Huh?
About your brother...
Jaeyeon...
I know.
I know he's hurting too.
He's been on set since he was a kid.
He barely even went to school.
He doesn't really have any friends.
I know.
I know I've just been blaming him.
I know...
Taewoo...
You were just a kid back then, too.
We're still young.
We're only in our twenties.
Let's just consider this part
of the healing process, okay?
I feel so bad for my brother.
I had no idea back then.
I just really missed my dad.
I hate that I'm like this.
Looking back...
I'm really glad I have you.
Jaeyeon...
If I didn't have you,
I don't think I would've made it this far.
Man... you're so heavy.
Finally...
Don't go.
This isn't right...
Goodbye...
"Fan Service"
(Episode 4)