Geonwoo, are you awake...?
What's the deal with you two?
Don't tell me... are you
guys actually dating?
Should we be?
From this moment on.
Let's start.
Come on.
Dad...
Taewoo...
Geonwoo.
Back then... I think I was out of my mind.
After the divorce,
I just started hating the whole world.
Taewoo, I really let you down.
Geonwoo...
I have no excuse for what I did.
So...
I just ran away.
But seeing you both doing so well...
I'm just so grateful.
I was afraid my guilt would
only weigh you down again,
so I couldn't find the
courage to reach out.
But you're still our dad. Let's
stay in touch from now on.
Yeah, let's keep in contact, Dad.
Jaeyeon... thank you.
This is all thanks to you.
I didn't do anything.
Taewoo's right.
I wouldn't have had
the courage without you.
So you two are a thing now, right?
Yeah.
I guess that's how it turned out.
You guys actually look
pretty good together.
Well, obviously.
You're still a total jerk, though.
You want to die?
I need to take this call.
I'm sorry about what happened that day.
Huh?
For kissing you without asking.
Oh... uh... hey...
I don't even remember that.
Why are you still dwelling on it?
I like you.
I've liked you since we were kids,
even before you can remember.
But I'm not going to anymore.
Taewoo...
We're friends.
The best of friends.
Closer than family.
Yeah.
That'll never change.
Give me a hug.
Hey!
What do you think you're
doing with my boyfriend?
You really want to die, don't you?
You're so possessive,
Jaeyeon's gonna run away.
Really?
No, what are you even worried about?
Fine, I hope you two
live happily ever after.
I'll just take my cue and leave.
Aren't you staying for dinner?
Nah, I'm busy.
Get home safe.
Yeah, see ya.
Why...?
You let Taewoo hug you.
That's different. You're an actor...
If you're so worried about getting caught,
do you want to go to my place?
Hi, Geonwoo.
I heard you went to Cannes this time.
I have to ask how it went.
Before we get into that,
why don't we take a look at the trailer?
That summer...
(That Summer)
we were young and foolish.
But that's why we were fearless.
Even if we could go back to that day,
knowing everything we know now,
would we still run to each other?
(A time-loop queer romance)
"That Summer"
(Directed by Ryu Jeong-hyeok | Starring
Kim Geonwoo, Lee Jaeyeon)
So, I heard this movie is a gay love story.
How did that feel for you?
Yes.
It's a film by a director I deeply respect.
And for this project,
I treated it as a tribute
to my own personal muse.
Maybe that's why the
response has been so great.
That muse must be very happy.
You guys should just go public already.
Feeling lonely?
Taewoo, don't be like that...
It's just nice to see them so happy.
Maybe we should try it sometime.
In the movie,
their love doesn't work out in the end.
My character gives in to family pressure,
gets married, and has kids.
It's not until he's much older
that he meets his true love again.
Really?
That's so sad.
Well, that's not going to be us.
We're staying together until we die.
Should we go ahead and
order matching coffins?
Okay, okay, I get it, Mr. Possessive.
So,
what are you doing tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah.
I'll have to check with my manager.
I think I have a shoot in Apgujeong.
Apgujeong?
I thought that drama was already finished.
Not yet, there's a little bit left.
I think they're doing some reshoots.
Still, I'm glad I got to see you today.
Why? What are you doing tomorrow?
Me?
I'm just a college student.
I don't have class tomorrow,
and I've already finished all my work.
Really?
Then I'll be waiting for
my possessive boyfriend.
Let's have dinner the
day after tomorrow, then.
Sounds good.
Hey.
Are you gonna buy me something good?
You're paying!
"Fan Service"
(Episode 6)