( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[both continue laughing]
-Ouch! That hurt!
-[laughing]
We'll go on summer break soon.
I've never been this excited
about summer break.
What do you want to see next?
Let's do something that will make
everyone in town wake up to a shock...
There's no need to rush.
We've got plenty of time to think.
Okay.
Kasuga,
how do you feel right now?
Happy, right?
Thanks to me.
You'd better appreciate it.
[Takao] I'm going to do it.
This time,
I'm going to become the person
Nakamura wants me to be.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[student] What is that?
[teacher] Go to your classrooms!
Stop looking!
There's nothing to see here!
[Yamada] Is it that pervert again?
Give it a rest already.
Amirite, Kasuga?
I know, right? They're totally crazy.
Yeah.
-[Yamada] This guy's crazy.
-[Kojima] Yeah.
Why would anyone do something like this?
Why were my underpants the only ones
that he didn't take?
[voice shaking]
Is he in love with Nakamura?
[breath trembling]
I can't go on like this,
without any answers...
It's just unbearable.
[♪ opening theme music playing]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 6
[Takao] Summer break is upon us.
I'm gonna find it...
our "other side."
We'll make everyone in town see.
We need something just right...
7 DAYS UNTIL THE YAGIBUSHI FESTIVAL
STYLE
::cue()
I'm going to do it.
I'm gonna do it for Nakamura.
STINKY! TASTY!
GARLIC-FLAVORED CHIPS
What are you doing with that junk?
I'm hot.
Hurry up and fan me, you piece of trash.
Yes, ma'am.
I was thinking...
The summer festival's coming up.
Maybe we can do something there?
It's the one time in the year
that we have huge crowds of people
in this otherwise dead town.
We'll unleash it all there.
We'll show them our "other side"!
What do you mean?
For example...
we could draw on this board,
and glue underpants onto it,
then string them together, and then...
[Sawa] I see...
Not bad.
[chuckles] Thanks.
I guess I'll give you a treat, then.
Show me your face.
[exhales]
[grunts, sniffs, gags]
It reeks of garlic, doesn't it?
[stutters] Uh... No, not at all.
But your eyebrows are twitching.
You're trying to bear the stench.
You perverted piece of shit.
I'll draw that face for you.
Kasuga, the scum!
Please don't. How embarrassing.
Shut it! Now show me a better look.
[exhales]
[grunts] Stop it already!
[Sawa laughing]
I knew it stank!
You eat it, too, garbage rat!
[straining]
[Sawa cackles]
-You look like a koi fish!
-[Takao laughs]
[laughing]
You want another one, don't you?
Come get it!
[Takao] I wonder what awaits us?
[Sawa laughing]
[Takao] Collapse?
Destruction?
No.
I...
I'm going to become a true idiot.
[Takao grunting]
-[exclaims]
-[Sawa laughs]
[Takao] Ah!
[laughing] See, you can't move now!
What'd you do that for?
Let's keep you like that
and plan for the festival.
What?
So, what shall we do?
Oh, this looks like fun.
Yeah, I think so, too.
Remember your place, you scum.
[Takao grunts]
[both laughing]
[Takao] I'll just go.
I'll go with Nakamura.
[Sawa] Idiot, idiot, idiot!
[Takao] No matter how far...
How far we go!
YAGIBUSHI FESTIVAL
DIE, SHIT BUG
STYLE
::cue()
Well, see you again tomorrow.
[Ai exclaiming] It stinks in here!
Garlic-flavored chips?
MASTER PLAN
PLAN FOR THE DAY OF THE FESTIVAL
[Nanako] What is this?
[♪ somber music playing]
6 DAYS UNTIL THE SUMMER FESTIVAL
THE OTHER SIDE
IDIOT KASUGA
TO THE OTHER SIDE!
[voice cracking] Everyday,
just the two of them,
in here...
It's still warm...
I can't stand it.
[breath trembling]
[scratching]
[Ai gagging]
[Ai retches, coughs]
[sobbing] I can't take it anymore...
Isn't this enough?
Let's go to the police and--
I'm sorry I got you involved.
Why?
Why are you so obsessed over Kasuga?
What do you see in that guy?
He's not worthy of you at all, Nanako!
When I went...
on my first date
with Kasuga...
he told me about the books he reads.
I didn't understand
what he was talking about,
but he had this twinkle in his eye.
It's like he was telling me...
It's okay to like something
even if other people don't get it.
[breath trembling]
I'd never,
not even once,
thought about things that way.
My whole life, I've liked things
that my dad and mom wanted me to like.
Only the things
that grown-ups expected me to like.
But,
the truth is...
Kasuga was the only person
who saw the real me!
Do you really think Kasuga sees you?
Or are you fooling yourself
because he confessed his love to you?
You just like the idea of being in love!
You're not in love with him.
You're just resentful 'cause
Nakamura took him from you!
STYLE
::cue()
That's not true!
Ai,
what makes you think you know?
Nanako!
[panting]
[phone ringing]
Takao, could you get that?
Hello.
[Nanako] Kasuga...
Saeki?
I found the thing
you'd least want to see destroyed
down at the riverbank.
What?
Saeki...
How did you find this?
Kasuga,
did you and Nakamura...
have sex?
What?
You see,
I give up.
I'll give it all up.
[gasps]
[voice shaking]
Saeki... What are you giving up?
[♪ tense music playing]
Tell me, Kasuga...
Where do you think you're heading?
It's just a dead-end ahead.
"The other side"?
No such thing exists.
But you know that, don't you?
Kasuga...
Do it with me.
Please put your clothes back on.
Why would you...
If you run...
you won't be able
to live in this town anymore.
I'll forgive you for all of it.
I'll give you all of me.
Okay?
[grunts]
No.
Please don't.
This isn't you, Saeki.
Kasuga...
Remember what you said that day?
That you didn't want to face
the real me?
[bra snaps open]
[gasps]
But, the thing is...
I'm a human being. [sniffles]
Look at me.
Touch me. Do me. Please, Kasuga.
STYLE
::cue()
We have to do it.
Everyone does it. It's a part of life!
Here,
in this town!
There's no way in hell!
I...
I'm going to create "the other side"
inside this town.
For Nakamura.
[laughing]
What?
"The other side"?
Stealing people's underpants
and making this shit is "the other side"?
[laughs]
You're addicted to her.
You can't live without Nakamura, can you?
You really are empty.
How sad.
[chuckles dryly]
But...
It'll all be okay now.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Takao straining]
[Takao grunting]
Stop it!
Kasuga...
[both breathing heavily]
[Takao grunts]
[both panting]
[Takao straining] Stop... Please, no...
-[zipper rips]
-[groans]
[Takao staining]
[Nanako grunting]
Don't resist!
[panting]
[Takao groans]
[exclaiming]
[groans]
[Nanako grunting]
[Takao screams]
[both grunting]
[Nanako panting]
Let's be together forever...
Kasuga!
[breath trembling, sobbing]
[screams] Get off of me!
[♪ music ends]
I...
I'm in love with Nakamura.
Wait, please...
[♪ intense music plays]
STYLE
::cue()
[panting]
[crackling]
Oh...
-[woman exclaims]
-[indistinct chatter]
Kasuga...
What is this?
Good evening, Nakamura.
Hey, wanna know something?
Kasuga and I...
did it.
[chuckles]
[♪ tense music playing]
"Did it"? Did what?
I mean, we became one.
Kasuga and I.
So what?
Do what you want.
I don't care.
You see,
Kasuga was only using you
as an escape, Nakamura.
He was taking the easy way out.
But I've accepted him for who he is,
and together, we're taking steps forward.
So, he no longer needs you, Nakamura.
Tell me, how do you feel right now?
Kasuga's been taken from you,
and everything's up in flames.
How do you feel right now?
So dumb.
It's really so dumb.
Ain't nothin' dumb about it!
You've always made fun of me,
looking down on me this whole time!
[♪ music fades]
-[siren baring]
-What the hell?
Let go of me!
[sobbing] Say you're mad at me!
You're resentful
that I stole Kasuga from you, aren't you?
You're frustrated! Admit it!
[sobs] Damn it.
[♪ somber music playing]
Damn it!
Why... [sniffles]
Why can't I be you, Nakamura?
STYLE
::cue()
There, you finally spat it out.
Still...
You're more rotten inside than a fly.
You will never understand me,
and I'd rather die
than let you think you could.
[siren wailing]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
[Takao] Let's start over again.
We still have two days until the festival.
[Sawa] Kasuga,
where does this road lead to?
At the end of this road, everything's...
dead.
I...
don't want to die.
Then...
what can I do?
Where should we go?
I'll think of something.
I promise I'll find it!
So...
So, please...
[♪ somber music playing]
[Nanako] Excuse me.
Yes? How may I help you?
That fire on the riverbank last night...
MASTER PLAN
I'm the one that set it.
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing theme music playing]
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
[narrator] Saeki strips Kasuga
and Nakamura of any safe space they had.
Where will the two head to together?
Next, on episode seven,
Nakamura takes Kasuga
and sets out to reach "the other side".
Translated by Yuka Kristi