( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 31=
(Real-Time Viewer Count)
Let's give Lin Zhanqiao a day.
Let her enjoy the moment.
I don't want to see
this Prefrontal Cortex
above me for even a day.
(Exclusive Licensing Contract: Gu Yan)
Give them some hope.
The higher the hopes,
the harder the fall.
(Top Sales Ranking: "Drunk Old Friend",
"Order of the Mountain Ghost")
We're number two! Number two!
Keep it up! Let's go!
Congratulations!
Get the new updates ready.
Get them ready.
- Publish it during prime time tonight.
- Congratulations!
Let's push harder on the promos
to secure our spot on the ranking.
- Keep it up!
- Let's go!
Ms. Lin.
The comment volume
for the first ten chapters
is soaring right now.
Our traffic push worked.
Also,
the comments
on today's update keep growing.
The comment section is super active.
I hope we can hold onto second place.
(Zhou Zheng)
Dad?
Where are you?
(Dingqi Reading Platform, Colorful
Culture Media,  Star Writer Gu Yan)
Hello, Ms. Zhao.
Ms. Zhao.
Ms. Zhao,
the backdrop is all set up.
Here's the schedule
for tomorrow's signing.
Take a look.
Tomorrow morning, we'll pick up
Gu Yan two hours early.
You must
arrive 40 minutes early.
Also, the hotel
will set up a dedicated livestream area.
After your livestream,
there might be a live interview.
Let me
walk you through
tomorrow's interview process.
Between 2:00 PM and 3:00 PM, we'll...
Okay, I got it.
Ms. Zhao.
After the ovulation injections,
your estrogen levels will rise.
You might experience
bloating, backaches,
and other discomfort.
Your mood will also be affected.
After the shots,
you'll have mood swings.
You may feel vulnerable or irritable,
cry suddenly,
or feel anxious.
(October 21st, Good Morning)
What happened?
Where's your suit?
At the dry cleaners. I can't pay for it.
You paid the rent.
If you're breaking up,
she should be the one leaving.
To be fair,
I haven't given her money in a while.
When business was good,
she lived comfortably off you.
At my age,
if I have someone around
to eat and drink with,
maybe I'll live a bit longer.
Then, you should find a partner
who's less demanding.
She stuck with me
for seven or eight years.
That was when you had money.
She wouldn't
last a week if you were broke.
Now,
the problem isn't her, it's me.
If I have no money
and can't give a woman a good life,
who would want to stay with me?
I have no money.
If you need a place, stay here for now.
Does your mom know I'm staying here?
She doesn't.
What if she comes?
Deal with her yourself.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Stay and chat.
I'm afraid you'll slap me
if we disagree.
Mei...
Just...
So resentful.
Just like your mother.
As I get older,
I just hope we can
chat more often.
You should have thought
about getting old sooner.
I used to think
I would never get old.
Or at least,
not this fast.
I'm still young.
I have to go to work.
Ms. Lin.
Thanks.
Mr. He Han.
Zhangzhu.
It's almost 9 PM. Peak reading time.
How's the ranking?
Just focus on writing.
Don't worry about it.
What? Did I edit too much?
Desperate times call for heavy fire.
His original pacing was too slow.
We need emotion to drive it up now.
No sugarcoating. Just drop the bombs.
No, I just think you edit fast.
How's the ranking?
Still second.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
What happened?
I checked online.
It might be the hormones.
Ovulation injections...
You're taking these?
Since when?
Shortly after the surgery.
The doctor said
my follicles aren't mature enough.
If we want a baby soon,
I need these injections.
It's one shot a day right now.
It might become two shots a day later.
Because I'm hoping, if possible,
to have twins.
Does Ling Yikai know?
No.
Taking these shots
is really bad for your body.
But having a child is always hard.
This little bit of suffering is nothing.
But if you keep crying like this,
when will it stop?
If I cry after getting pregnant,
I can just blame it
on pregnancy hormones.
I don't think
I've ever seen you cry.
I have
shed as many tears
as I have these past few days.
It seems...
I haven't really cried
since I was five or six.
And I don't think
I'll cry much in the future either.
So I feel like
I'm crying all the tears
for the rest of my life.
Why are you crying?
Maybe...
hormones are contagious.
I can't wait until tomorrow.
As long as
Prefrontal Cortex is above me,
I can't sleep at all.
Before I go to bed,
knock him down to at least third place.
Just posted.
Gu Yan is signing
with Zhao Lanxin tomorrow.
Sansan is Gu Yan's
other pen name.
It's generating buzz.
Once everyone finds out
that Sansan is Gu Yan,
out of curiosity,
they'll read
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui".
(Drunk Old Friend, Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui, Order of the Mountain Ghost)
We lost second place.
Tell Prefrontal Cortex
to keep updating tomorrow.
(Dingqi Reading Platform, Colorful
Culture Media, New Rising Author Gu Yan)
(Joint Celebration Party)
Let's look forward to it.
- Great.
- To our...
bright future.
Come on.
- Cheers!
Mr. Fan,
the livestream is ready.
We can start.
Okay.
Welcome
to Dingqi's livestream.
I'm Fan from Dingqi.
Today is a day of double blessings.
Now, the first blessing.
Dingqi Reading Platform
has finally,
after much effort,
formed a wonderful partnership
with Colorful Culture Media.
(Dingqi Chinese)
(A perfect match.)
(The second blessing...)
(Colorful Culture Media...)
Let me sleep a little longer.
I've barely slept two or three hours.
Wake up and look!
(The top online author)
(Gu Yan.)
Not interested.
Know your enemy.
I know this "enemy" all too well.
I've been watching Gu Yan's expression.
I've noticed
he doesn't look guilty at all.
He must feel a little guilty.
As long as he knows
this is a livestream
and it's in He Han's old apartment,
and that his old colleagues
and I are watching,
anyone with a conscience
would feel uncomfortable.
(Get a close-up of the cake.)
(A powerful union.)
(Gu Yan.)
(All together.)
(Mr. Fan, join us!)
(Here we go.)
Well, I don't see it.
(Great!)
(Not bad!)
(Awesome!)
(Gu Yan is amazing!)
(Next,)
(we have an even bigger surprise.)
(An Easter egg.)
Don't you feel like
you raised a backstabber?
He probably thinks
I'm just a hypocritical slavedriver.
People always try to find
ways to justify their actions.
Besides, he's so young.
Mr. Fan and Zhao Lanxin
offered him such a sweet deal.
Anyone else would probably
have a hard time refusing.
Are you making excuses for him
or trying to convince yourself?
I'm just saying,
given his track record,
dumping Zhao Lanxin
is only a matter of time.
I'll be the one
to reveal the Easter egg.
Sansan, who continued Phantom Knight's
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui",
has always kept a low profile.
(Looking forward to it.)
(So who is he?)
(Here it comes!)
(I'm sure you all want to know, right?)
(Yes.)
(Allow me to reveal the answer.)
(What's going on?)
(The person writing as Sansan)
(is none other than Gu Yan!)
(Is he writing two novels at once?)
(Gu Yan is awesome!)
(Gu Yan is the best!)
(That means the number one)
(and number two books on the ranking)
(Really?)
(are both written by Gu Yan.)
(Send to Douyin Promo Group)
(He updates two series at once)
(Xiaohongshu Promo Group)
(while keeping their styles)
(completely distinct.)
(You can imagine how hard that is.)
("Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
Author Sansan Revealed)
(Gu Yan is Sansan)
(Top: "Drunk Old Friend",
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui",)
("Order of the Mountain Ghost")
("Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
Author Sansan Revealed)
(Author of "Drunk Old Friend": Gu Yan)
Zhangzhu left early.
I didn't see her when I got up.
I'm going to the office.
Didn't you just come back at dawn?
Why are you going again?
It's going to be a tough day.
(Everyone's reason
for entering this industry)
(is different.)
(So there isn't much common ground.)
(And the process is different too.)
(Some people
have it easy from the start.)
(Some people...)
Your course sales
are way below expectations.
To sell courses,
you have to hype them up.
You refuse
to do promotional livestreams.
How will people know
if your course is good?
Let me tell you.
If you were willing to livestream,
my hundreds of thousands of fans
would help promote it in the fan groups.
The conversion rate would be amazing.
So,
if I agree to livestream,
can we do it today?
Today?
What's your plan?
Bringing an author on the stream.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Didn't you say you're good at promoting?
I'd like to see
just how good you really are.
Challenging me, huh?
Depends on how you cooperate.
Make your demands, and I'm game.
Scandals.
Attention-grabbing, over-the-top stuff.
Okay?
Sure.
Like what?
Like exposing the love triangle
between you, me,
and Lin Zhanqiao.
Hello, who are you looking for?
Mantou.
Okay, sign here.
Hello, Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin.
Please sign here.
After the news
about Sansan being Gu Yan broke,
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
took first place.
And our series?
Not great.
What about more updates?
We already added two rounds.
Where is Prefrontal Cortex?
Sleeping inside.
He was exhausted. I didn't wake him.
Good morning.
Hey, where are you?
I'm at a livestream with Mr. He Han.
And Mimi,
a big influencer.
What livestream? Where?
Okay, got it.
If everything looks good,
please sign here.
Okay.
In a bit,
(Top Web Novelist He Han Recommends)
I'll start by talking
about my past with He Han.
Then you act like you're...
really curious.
Just show
that you're eager for the gossip.
Gossip.
Right.
Don't panic.
Let me explain.
So, Mimi and Prefrontal Cortex
are already live in there.
What are they talking about?
What's the topic?
You know how Mimi got famous.
So you can probably guess
the topic and direction.
I know you don't like this approach,
but isn't the goal
to drive traffic to Prefrontal Cortex?
Blame me if you want.
But let's talk after the stream.
Okay?
I'm going in to see.
Don't go.
You won't like what you hear.
Just go back
and see if our traffic push worked.
See if the read count
went up.
Mr. He Han.
Mimi is cueing you.
My turn.
Wait for the results.
As long as we succeed,
the process
doesn't matter.
Right?
I hope you'll all show your support
and like the stream.
Thank you!
After all that buildup,
we finally have Mr. He Han!
Welcome! A warm welcome to our idol!
- Hello!
- Mr. He Han.
(Hello, everyone, I'm He Han.)
(I'm so happy)
(to meet you all on this livestream.)
(I also want to recommend an author)
(you just met,)
(one I greatly admire, Prefrontal Cortex.)
(His novel, "Order of the Mountain Ghost,")
(Mimi is so pretty!)
(is quite unique. It's definitely worth a read.)
(It's unlike anything you've seen.)
(Just joined.)
(I highly recommend it.)
(He Han is amazing!)
(We have a lot of giveaways, right?)
(So handsome!)
(VIP memberships and stuff.)
(What's going on?)
(I hope you all support him.)
(Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui, Drunk
Old Friend, Order of the Mountain Ghost)
First off,
a question from everyone.
At your peak as a web novelist,
how much did you make a year?
That would be quite a sum of money.
So where did all that money go?
Food, clothes, housing, and travel.
And of course,
making girls happy.
That's right, guys.
I can vouch for that.
When He Han and I were dating,
anything I liked,
he would buy for me.
Of course.
And on all kinds of holidays,
he'd give me little surprises.
He was very thoughtful.
Yeah, the sense of ceremony matters.
Right?
Romantic.
Right? Jewelry,
handbags, and whatever.
(I want to join, too.)
They are nice gifts, right?
Romantic.
Let's move on to the next question.
Is Prefrontal Cortex
Lin Zhanqiao's new boyfriend?
I don't think so.
Never heard anything about that.
So for this question,
let's have Lin Zhanqiao herself
answer it for us.
Please welcome her!
Are you sure?
For real?
Let's have Lin Zhanqiao
say hi to everyone.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Lin Zhanqiao.
Actually,
Prefrontal Cortex and I
met on a dating app.
A dating app!
So you were looking for love!
(How are you so sure)
(Prefrontal Cortex
wasn't after your money?)
(When I saw his profile...)
Come here, look!
Come look.
(What's going on?)
Ms. Lin and Mr. He Han are live,
promoting our novel.
(Don't cry, Lin)
(I figured,)
(What's for sale today?)
(for work and dating,)
(why not interview for both at once?)
I really underestimated Ms. Lin.
She went on Mimi's livestream.
She's giving it her all for the novel.
I think it's quite inspiring.
She doesn't seem
like the Ms. Lin I know.
It's a bit heartbreaking to watch.
This must be Mr. He Han's idea.
I can't imagine it.
He Han and Lin Zhanqiao,
together on Mimi's livestream.
It's just unbelievable.
Friends, as the editor
of "Order of the Mountain Ghost",
I have to say,
every single timeline in our story
is deeply rooted
in mythology.
If you're interested,
please hit follow.
Once you read it, you'll see
the sheer scale of our imagination
and the depth of its quality.
If you love it, darlings,
give us lots of likes and follows!
We are giving away
100 reading cards
for "Order of the Mountain Ghost".
If you want one,
type "Want" in the chat.
Our system will draw winners randomly.
If you're new to it,
click in and read a sample.
The first 50 chapters
- are completely free.
- Mr. Lin.
Yes, exactly.
Today, the full-book reading cards
are 50% off.
And limited-edition merch!
Now, let's invite Prefrontal Cortex
to tell us about
the origins of his story.
Certainly.
Your dad.
Prefrontal Cortex, please.
I'm back.
Dad?
How's Mom?
(Oncology Department)
First, calm down.
First,
your mom is not
in life-threatening danger.
That's the good news.
The bad news is,
she's in the ICU right now,
in a coma.
They just did an MRI.
The doctor said
it might be
the tumor spreading to her brain.
Third,
if you're in a meeting right now,
don't rush over here.
There's nothing you can do here anyway.
And you can't see her.
The doctors are trying to wake her up
as soon as possible.
So...
Did the doctor say
when exactly she'll wake up?
No idea.
They're still figuring it out.
I'll ask them
and let you know.
Hurry to the hospital.
I'll handle things here.
My dad just said
even if I go now,
there's nothing I can do to help.
You still have to go!
Don't worry.
Spouting nonsense is my specialty.
Me streaming here with you
is better than you doing it alone.
I have Prefrontal Cortex.
I'm sending him back to write in a bit.
Let's go.
Consider it a test.
Let's welcome He Han and Lin Zhanqiao
back to the livestream!
Hello! Hi, everyone!
Hi, everyone, we're back.
Thanks for your patience.
I didn't expect that taking a quick call
would bring so many new friends
into our livestream.
- Awesome!
- Exactly!
These are all your fans.
I want to emphasize this again today.
This livestream to recommend
"Order of the Mountain Ghost"
isn't to make money or anything.
It's purely out of our love for it.
And it won't happen again.
This is the only time
we recommend a novel
on a livestream.
Because it's worth it.
Right?
So I want to ask He Han,
do you think Prefrontal Cortex
will be your successor?
My successor?
That's impossible.
He will surpass me.
The new generation
always surpasses the old.
See that?
Mr. He Han is going all out.
Isn't he just lying through his teeth?
Prefrontal Cortex is
nowhere near his level.
Not even as good as Gu Yan.
He's going to lose fans over this.
But isn't he doing it for us?
Can ruining his own reputation
really help us?
It's pretty limited, isn't it?
Worse if he didn't help.
("Order of the Mountain Ghost")
(Looking forward to it.)
(is a bona fide romantic myth.)
(So handsome!)
(Well said.)
I can't say
Prefrontal Cortex surpasses He Han,
but I absolutely trust my eye
for picking authors as a senior editor!
Definitely.
And he will definitely surpass me.
I'm putting it out there today.
To back that up,
I'm personally giving away
another 100 full-book reading cards
for "Order of the Mountain Ghost"!
Let's draw!
Mr. He Han is going all out today!
(Livestream Concurrent Trend)
Generous, right?
A bit desperate, right?
Seriously desperate.
Is he crazy?
He's yelling in the livestream.
After driving a taxi,
he just...
Is this even He Han anymore?
He's just doing it for Lin Zhanqiao.
If she asked you
to hype up another author,
would you do it?
Of course not.
I'm not him.
He's a has-been anyway.
(For those who haven't read it,)
(go read it now!)
(I'm serious.)
(Seeing is believing.)
(The first 50 chapters are free.)
(A full-book subscription
costs less than a few cups of milk tea.)
Between milk tea and novels,
novels are definitely healthier.
Exactly.
"Order of the Mountain Ghost"
breaks the mold.
The female lead
is a master of deception.
She's not your typical righteous hero.
So,
it's extremely
entertaining and satisfying.
But its core is still true,
good, and beautiful.
Right.
If you're interested, dive right in!
Go for it! Check it out!
(I was reading it last night!)
(I'm at the latest chapter!)
Mantou, how are the numbers?
Well, the traffic push
definitely had some effect.
But Gu Yan's numbers are growing faster.
It's not looking good.
You should prepare for the worst.
What's the problem
with web novels today?
Old wine in new bottles.
That's boring. "Order of
the Mountain Ghost" is different.
It's new wine in old bottles.
Familiar themes with a fresh twist.
Very rare.
It gives your brain
an unprecedented shock!
Exactly.
Yes! I can't wait to read it!
I hope you all go support it!
(Dad: The doctor says
your mom might not wake up.)
If you love it, darlings,
be sure to give us
lots of likes and follows!
The link is right below.
With so many perks today,
you have to grab them quickly!
Come on!
Here are the big ones.
Guys,
how about I read
a page for you live right now?
You two go rest! Go on!
Leave it to me!
If you still won't read it after this,
I'll read the next page!
Give me the tablet.
I'll do it.
I don't need a tablet.
Using her own life force as fuel,
Chu Yao faced the Shanhai Beast alone
to protect everyone.
Ji Dan couldn't bring herself
to ask her to surrender.
Because she had no right
to stop a warrior
from fighting
with dignity to the bitter end.
"Chu Yao,
we will see each other again."
Ji Dan's voice was barely a whisper.
Yet, Chu Yao's silhouette,
gripping her long blade,
seemed to hear it.
She turned slightly
and waved,
just like she always did.
Don't say goodbye in hopes of a reunion.
Say it for tomorrow.
The bell tolled.
It echoed in everyone's ears.
Ji Dan struggled to her feet.
She watched the setting sun
slowly sink beneath the horizon.
With every friend she lost,
a piece of her died, too.
But the wounds would quickly heal over.
This loss
swept over her like a hurricane.
But she had to stay standing
to face the cruel tomorrow alone.
Hard to say.
We'll just have to wait and see.
(Don't cry, Lin.)
(Thank you, for the emotional reading.)
(So awesome!)
(You can tell)
(the emotion she poured
into "Order of the Mountain Ghost")
(is no less than the author's.)
("Order of the Mountain Ghost"...)
Zhanqiao is amazing.
I think she could just
go play the female lead.
These tears
just come on cue.
I don't think
she's crying over the novel.
It's because
no matter how hard she tries,
the company still can't survive.
There's no point in watching this.
She's protecting Prefrontal Cortex.
Are you jealous?
She wouldn't fall for Prefrontal Cortex.
I think
he's jealous
of how Zhanqiao and He Han
look out for each other.
(For those who posted)
(long reviews
of "Order of the Mountain Ghost"...)
If there's nothing else, just leave.
I have to work.
Living in a big suite has changed
even your attitude.
You're bossing people around.
No, of course not.
He knows he owes it all to you, Mr. Fan.
Right, Gu Yan?
The numbers are up.
You're right.
Looks like the livestream worked.
This newcomer is good. Look,
it just keeps climbing.
(Drunk Old Friend, Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui, Order of the Mountain Ghost)
You did your best.
If it's not enough, we'll stream again.
In the short term,
it definitely boosted the numbers.
But we both know
it's just a drop in the bucket.
Now I just need to decide...
whether to take a gamble
and throw
the company's last cent into it
before admitting defeat.
Or perhaps I can pull the plug now.
Maybe we should
take that gamble.
Gu Yan must be under a lot of pressure.
Without your help,
he has to write two novels on his own
while maintaining his standard.
He might be in first
and second place now,
but he's bound to slip soon.
I've done everything I can.
And you've helped
in every way
you could have.
I want you to succeed.
I know.
That's why...
I was praying for a miracle just now.
I hoped the novel would go viral
and blow up the charts.
So Chenxing would be saved.
And that my dad would text me...
saying my mom woke up.
♪I keep asking myself♪
You did what you had to do.
Let's go to the hospital.
♪To follow what my heart truly wants♪
♪Like a drifting dandelion♪
♪Turning where it drifts♪
♪Into soil where it can grow♪
♪When the rain comes, I hide♪
♪In a flower shop at the corner♪
♪Even spring borrows its fragrance♪
♪Moonlight keeps me company
on lonely roads♪
♪Across fields of blooms,
a boat awaits me♪
♪Swaying in the shape of the wind♪
♪Not waiting for calm to come♪
(There was no miracle.)
(Being strong)
(is sometimes)
(endurance race with no reward.)
(He Han couldn't save me.)
(Just like when He Wei passed away,)
(I couldn't save him either.)
(But at least,)
(through this unspeakable
fear and loss,)
(we know the other person)
(feels the exact same way.)
Sorry, I couldn't come
until this afternoon.
It's fine.
I understand.
Given the situation,
you have a lot to handle.
Chenxing is shutting down.
But "Order of the Mountain Ghost"
still needs to be finished.
I want to make sure
you're taken care of.
I'll transfer you
to a company
and editor you'll be happy with.
Actually, the novel
isn't as good as they say.
Right?
Who said that?
It's top three on the ranking!
That's because of you.
You put in a lot of effort
to push me up there.
Of course,
there's He Han.
Who else is lucky enough
to have He Han edit their novel?
I'll at least have
a great story to tell in this industry.
You'll do even better.
No.
This is as good as it gets for me.
Really.
I'm more than satisfied.
I'll keep writing.
Even if my future work
isn't as good as this,
I'll keep at it.
Because I love it.
I'm sending you a WeChat contact.
Zhao Lanxin
from Colorful Culture Media.
Her company
will take over your novel.
Zhao Lanxin?
Isn't she your rival?
Will she help you?
She really likes your work.
So she came to me first.
Like you said, she's my rival.
So, she's not trying to help me
by taking over.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪