( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 28=
Dad.
She fell asleep.
I went to fetch some hot water.
(Oncology Department)
You stayed with Mom for so long.
What did you talk about?
Just old memories.
A few old friends
got back in touch with me recently.
Why is it only
after she got seriously sick,
that you're willing to stay by her side?
Even though
we weren't living together before,
and lived a bit far apart,
your mom knew
I was still there for her.
She knew where to find me.
And she knew if anything happened,
she could call me anytime for help.
Your mom and I
have different ways of living.
I like being alone.
But I was always there.
And she knew that, too.
Now that she has fallen sick,
she can't come looking for me.
This morning, when I heard her talking,
she sounded so weak.
So...
I need to stay closer to her now.
If...
the one who got sick had been me,
I would've moved back, too.
So you
have actually always cared about her,
right?
But I could never care for her
in the way she wanted.
Before this, I honestly thought
you didn't like her.
Once I married your mom,
I never thought about anyone else
for the rest of my life.
Ladies, you're not coming home
for dinner?
Why are you here?
Just you alone?
I sent them a message just now.
None of them is coming back for dinner.
Can I come in?
Just milk?
Come, eat something.
Why did you suddenly come by?
Something happened
at Chenxing, right?
You work in renovations.
How would you know that?
You work at that company.
Of course I pay attention.
And Lin Zhanqiao
is someone I should care about, too.
Still haven't found yourself
a new girlfriend?
Haven't met the right one.
I'm getting older now.
Got to be more picky,
right?
What have you heard
about Chenxing?
When a small company runs into trouble,
it's always about money.
So this time,
I came to tell Lin Zhanqiao
that if there's anything I can do,
I'd like to help.
Of course, I can't do anything huge.
I can invest some money.
I don't think she would accept it.
She helps you.
I help you.
Nothing wrong with that.
Life is just people
helping each other out.
Look at me. My business got this big,
and I'm always willing
to help others.
And I'm not afraid to ask others
for help either.
Ms. Lin isn't like you.
Ask her when she gets back then.
No need to ask her.
She won't accept it.
Whether she accepts it or not
is up to her.
But shouldn't we
at least show our sincerity?
Even if she refuses,
she should still know
there are people willing to help her
and support her.
Wouldn't that make her feel
a little better?
That's true.
Madam,
please have some time.
Just wait a moment.
He'll be here soon.
Alright, thank you.
Hello, madam.
I'm Zhou Mei's coworker.
Tim had to leave early.
Here's your thing.
Okay.
Please check if anything's missing.
This is all I need.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll walk you out.
No, thanks.
It's fine. I happen
to be heading out, too.
We're on the way. Let's go.
Alright.
Please.
Madam,
is Mei finally getting
some good news soon?
What good news?
Her good news with Lawyer Bei.
She finally got her happy ending
after waiting for so long.
What...
What are you talking about?
Is she going to
marry Lawyer Bei?
Yeah.
Are you worried people will talk
because Lawyer Bei just got divorced
and is going to remarry?
Honestly, younger generations
don't care about that anymore.
We all know
Zhou Mei waited for him for so long.
It really wasn't easy for her.
You go ahead first.
I need to use the restroom.
Okay.
Hello, Mom?
Did Tim give you the document?
A female coworker?
Is Lawyer Bei the man
who came to our house with you
last time?
What is your relationship with him?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Where are you right now?
Are you with a client?
Well, come home tonight.
I'll wait for you at your place.
Send it to this address.
Alright.
Here's your receipt.
The total is 2,888 yuan.
Put it inside.
Okay.
Thank you.
How long have you known him?
A few years.
When you met him,
did you know he was married
and had a wife?
Yes.
And you still got involved with him?
I wanted him to divorce his wife
and marry me.
Do you realize
what you just said
is the most shameless thing
in the world?
Have you forgotten
what kind of person
caused all the misery in our family?
Of course I remember.
Nothing left a deeper impression on me
than that.
When you went to confront my dad
and that mistress,
you took me with you.
Why did you take me there?
Could I help you fight her?
Or could I help you win Dad back?
If not,
then why did you take me?
I wanted you to see
what the ugliest thing in this world
looks like!
What the most shameless kind of person
I wanted you to see it as a warning!
So you would never choose
a man like that,
and never become a woman like that!
You were just trying
to cover up your own cowardice.
You should've fought for
your own husband yourself.
You didn't dare beat that woman.
Instead, you forced me to stand there
and watch them together.
What did I even understand back then?
Dad was yelling at you
to take me away.
Even that woman
was telling you to leave.
But did you ever care about how I felt?
I was a victim, too.
I had nobody else around me
but you.
And for all these years,
you kept dumping your anger and fear
onto me.
Did you think that meant you won?
Did you think that meant
you beat those women?
Listen. You didn't.
I bought these clothes
to deal with you.
I would never wear clothes
this old-fashioned.
Do you know why I stayed
at Lin Zhanqiao's place?
You think it's closer to work?
It's because everything I use and wear
is over there!
I only keep this house to deal with you!
Don't you think this place feels cheap
and hasn't changed at all?
You've lost your mind, Zhou Mei.
You're not my daughter.
You made me become this way.
Why are you doing this?
Do you mean to torture me?
Doesn't this
hurt you?
No.
What hurts is dressing
like this every day,
pretending to be the obedient,
sensible daughter you wanted.
Deep down,
you must despise yourself!
I don't!
I'm the winner!
I won against your control.
And I won against
that woman, too.
You lost, didn't you?
I don't have a daughter like you.
Then you have nothing left at all.
♪First time in love♪
♪It tears my heart apart♪
♪Keep chasing all♪
(Deep love)
(often comes with harsh expectations.)
(Beneath Zhou Mei's breakdown)
(is anger at herself)
(for being unable to mend
the relationship with her mother)
(and also a desperate cry)
(to free both herself and her mother
from resentment.)
(For some reason,)
(we always hurt
the people closest to us the most)
(with cruel words without thinking,)
(and then spend the rest of the time)
(regretting them.)
♪I see you at the end♪
♪Now I cross the line♪
You're here.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Too bad I didn't keep liquor at home.
But today,
we have to drink.
Guess we'll drink this instead.
Ten-year aged
scallion-ginger cooking liquor.
Sure.
Never tried it before.
Give it a taste.
Here.
How is it?
Nice.
As expected of ten-year aged brew.
The aroma is intense.
You and Lawyer Bei
were never talking about marriage.
He didn't divorce his wife
because you forced him to.
Why did you have to act like
you had done every terrible thing
in front of your mom?
To get back at her.
Actually, I was on edge
before I talked to her.
But when I faced her head-on
and saw how upset she was,
I suddenly stopped feeling nervous.
I had finally
waited long enough for this day.
I finally became myself again.
Congrats.
On becoming yourself again.
May it inspire you, too.
When will you become
your real self again?
I've always been myself.
Stop lying to yourself.
You're drunk.
The moment you tell He Han
that you like him,
no matter how badly he has treated you,
that's when you'll finally
be honest with yourself.
Jeez.
Total lovesick idiot.
You do like him. That's a fact.
You can reject all his ridiculous logic,
say he's unreliable,
say you don't want to work with him,
or live with him.
But you can't deny
that you like him.
What's the point of liking someone?
Can it put food on the table?
All it brings is pain.
You're scared
you'll end up like your mom,
spending your whole life loving a man,
only to be pushed far away in the end.
I won't become my mom.
She has suffered too much.
They've been married
for decades.
Now that I'm grown up,
she still can't get close to my dad.
If I ever like someone,
I'll definitely stay by his side.
Very close.
Come.
Mr. Lin.
You've terminated
the lease on your place?
I have.
I know what you're trying to ask.
You're wondering what if I move back in
and can't get used to it anymore, right?
You've lived alone
for over twenty years.
Of course I won't be used to it.
I'll just have to put up with it.
Young people call it
"try and work it through"?
But honestly,
compared to most people,
I had an extra
twenty years of freedom.
I'm satisfied with that.
I always knew
one day I would have to move back.
I told Zhanqiao, too.
Whether her mom gets sick
or I do,
once that day comes, I'll move back.
No matter what,
you keep your word.
I really admire you for that.
Freedom always comes at a price.
Either you pay for it yourself,
or someone else pays for it for you.
Maybe Mrs. Lin doesn't resent you
that much.
It's not just Zhanqiao's mom.
Zhanqiao paid the price, too.
When parents can't even
get along normally,
do you think
the child doesn't suffer for it?
People always say
children learn by example.
She never had a good example.
All she learned were the bad parts.
That's why she can't properly
get along with you now.
No. That's because
I'm hard to get along with.
Not you. Zhanqiao is.
How could that be?
It has to be me.
No. She's the one with the problem.
She's my daughter.
Wouldn't I know her best?
(Exclusive Licensing Agreement
[Draft Termination Agreement])
(Proof of Contract Breach)
Hello, Ms. Lin.
I'm Mr. Wang Hai's attorney.
(Confidentiality Agreement)
You should know
that Mr. Wang Hai
is a contracted author under Chenxing.
Based on what we've learned,
during your collaboration,
Chenxing committed multiple
breaches of contract.
That has led my client,
Mr. Wang Hai, to consider
terminating the agreement.
(Demand Letter)
I'm meeting you
to discuss the matters
related to the termination.
There's an agreement here.
Please take a look.
Have you read these agreements yourself?
No.
But I know Dingqi was going
to approach you.
I know Mr. Fan and Zhao Lanxin
can give you a very good offer.
But at a time like this, hearing you
bring up termination with me,
that really hurts.
Mr. Fan said
they'll give you
the compensation you deserve.
You can take the money
and find a better author.
I thought our partnership
meant more
than just money.
Between us,
it's work and business.
It's all about money.
Or mostly about money.
Now that I've accepted that,
but you're turning around and telling me
not to talk money with you?
When it comes to work and business,
shouldn't people go
wherever gives them better opportunities
and a better future?
In the short term,
I do think Dingqi can give you
more exposure, more opportunities,
maybe even a higher revenue split.
But in the long run,
Zhao Lanxin won't be able
to help your writing
that much.
Nobody can predict the long term.
Back when I worked as
an internet cafe manager,
I never imagined
that one day I would be
writing novels with you.
And after I started writing,
I never imagined I'd rise
to the top so quickly.
But what I never expected most
was that I still wouldn't
get the recognition I wanted.
Authors go through
highs and lows.
Zhao Lanxin won't patiently wait for you
through those lows.
The moment someone else
can bring her more profit,
she'll move on to them.
She will.
Even on her wedding day,
she was still asking about my life!
As long as I need her,
she'll come see me anytime.
When I was writing the sequel to
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui,
she stayed up with me
night after night,
waiting for my updates.
She told me
I was the best author
she had ever worked with.
Maybe she can't help me
write better stories,
but she makes me
feel valued,
needed.
If that's what you want,
I'm sorry,
I can't give you that.
One more thing.
During the call with the lawyer,
he brought up details
from our past collaboration.
Like payments being delayed by two days.
Or disagreements over progress.
Did you tell Dingqi
about all that?
No.
I didn't say anything.
Mr. Fan said
they have an insider at Chenxing.
Alright.
As for the termination,
let the lawyers handle it.
I'll finish writing Drunk Old Friend.
Finish it well.
It's good
for you
and me.
Where are you, Ms. Zhao?
The cervical cyst surgery itself
is a minor procedure,
and we'll try our best
to minimize tissue damage.
But I should let you know this.
Your cyst is relatively large,
and the surgical area will also
be slightly larger.
After the removal,
there is a risk of scarring or adhesion,
which could affect your chances
of a natural pregnancy in the future.
(Liu Blind Massage)
Hello?
Lin Zhanqiao.
I was worried you would be upset,
so I asked Zhangzhu
to pass you a message.
Also, I recently took on a new project.
The houses are amazing.
Come take a look if you have time.
Doesn't matter if you don't have
money right now.
Looking at houses can lift your mood
and make you feel like
a new life is waiting for you.
Thanks.
If Chenxing goes under,
maybe I'll work for you selling houses.
Then I can look at homes
every day
and dream about a new life.
(Oncology Department)
Bed 31,
you're being discharged today.
Has your family arrived yet?
Yes.
Mom.
Thank you.
Didn't I say I would help you pack?
Why did you do it yourself?
It's barely anything.
No need to trouble you.
Give me a moment.
I'm going to make a payment.
Hello, Ms. Zhao.
You forgot your medical insurance card.
Thank you.
Where's your family?
They stepped away. They'll be back soon.
Make sure you rest in bed
for a couple of days after you go home.
Are you okay?
What a small world.
Do you need any help?
You don't look
very well.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I'll just sit here and rest for a bit.
How about you wait here for me?
I'll bring my mom downstairs,
and then I'll drive you home.
Thank you.
I'll be quick.
Sea cucumber.
Bird's nest soup.
Black chicken soup.
Fish maw pigeon soup.
Dining alone?
Would you like to add
vegetables or staples?
No, that's all.
Alright. Please wait a moment.
Excuse me, ma'am. Your meal is here.
♪After giving everything, I
couldn't wait any longer♪
♪The verdict was
already waiting in the future♪
♪Why bother confessing♪
♪Or thinking about what to say?♪
♪It's none of my concern♪
♪Even if it's unraveled♪
♪It had already fallen apart♪
♪Endless dependence♪
♪I really miss♪
♪All the beautiful moments together♪
♪I may seem to be alone♪
♪But I'm still waiting♪
♪Happiness feels like an accident♪
♪Why be overly generous♪
♪Beyond the limits of endurance♪
♪Living in humble silence♪
♪Who is it within the crowd♪
♪Gathering strength beneath the waves?♪
♪Who wasted their time
waiting for the wrong person♪
♪In despair?♪
♪Saving the love you once gave me♪
♪I don't need your pity♪
Why weren't you answering?
I was interviewing editors.
I couldn't take calls.
Didn't I come over right away
as soon as I finished?
You don't look quite well.
Really?
Maybe I didn't sleep well last night.
What did you want to see me about?
Did Lin Zhanqiao give you trouble again?
More like
I became her trouble.
Between you,
you're the one calling the shots now.
Back then, Lin Zhanqiao lost He Han,
and Chenxing fell into
a business crisis.
Luckily, she was prepared.
She had you to pull her out of the fire.
Now she has lost you, too.
No one will save her this time.
I hope the lawyer
won't lower the penalty fee,
no matter the reason.
Her problem now
isn't whether it's five million more
or ten million less.
She needs to reflect on herself.
She's too proud.
She needs to learn
how to swallow her pride.
But then she wouldn't be
Lin Zhanqiao anymore.
She refuses to bow her head,
so the only thing left
is for setbacks to crush her first.
And when that happens,
it'll only look worse.
If I compensate her more on my side,
it'll only delay the moment
she has to face reality.
She'll talk to you again.
She still has responsibilities
toward Chenxing.
She won't want to disappoint
her employees.
She'll definitely come again
and beg you.
I never imagined it.
Until yesterday,
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui
had been firmly holding
the number one spot.
But one hour after
Drunk Old friend updated,
its number quickly overtook it.
(Drunk Old Friend,
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui)
Besides,
Gu Yan's control over pacing
has improved.
He has started leaving hooks
in the story,
getting readers to discuss it
in the comments section.
From what I'm seeing so far,
all the data
looks extremely strong.
If Sansan really is Gu Yan,
then updating two novels
at the same time
was something He Han never managed to do
back in the day.
The consulting firm we hired
also believes Gu Yan has now entered
a phase of rapid maturity.
So they advise us
to keep Gu Yan with us, no matter what.
Only then will we have leverage
when negotiating with investors.
I went to see him.
Dingqi gave him extremely good offers.
There's no way we can compete.
So the chances of keeping him
are small.
And if we go by
the breach of contract terms,
with his current value,
we would definitely take a huge loss.
The main issue now is
he's not even willing to pay
the amount stated in the contract.
Instead, he's accusing us
of treating him unfairly.
I've never seen someone
so ungrateful
and opportunistic.
What do you call this?
Isn't he a total ingrate?
How can someone be like this?
- Alright. Enough.
- Ingrate.
Big companies exploit their talent.
Big talents push companies around.
That's how it works everywhere.
It's like agencies managing celebrities.
When you're not famous yet,
you're the one under pressure.
But once you become famous,
the company's under pressure instead.
What happened to basic human decency?
Tell me about it.
That's why
the consulting firm suggested
that if things don't work out,
we should compromise
and agree to Gu Yan's non-exclusive
open collaboration model.
Gu Yan would still maintain
a formal contract with us,
but we would allow him
to work on other projects with Dingqi.
What does that mean?
We worked so hard
to develop this author,
and now we have to share him
with someone else?
This is humiliating.
You think that's humiliating?
Gu Yan and Dingqi might not
even be willing to agree to it.
This is betrayal.
- This is humiliating.
- He might refuse?
I've never seen someone like this.
He never cared about us.
I'll go talk to him again.
What if
he still says no?
Then I'll beg him.
Ask him to help us.
Even if it's for Chenxing's sake.
Ms. Lin,
no matter what, you should
never have to use the word "beg".
Without you and Chenxing,
he wouldn't be where he is today.
Times have changed.
You adapt to the situation
and bend when you have to bend.
- Never seen someone this shameless.
- So frustrating.
Jeez.
If she begs you,
will you soften?
Of course I will.
And she knows that, too.
That's exactly why you mustn't.
Everything humble she's doing right now
is nothing but an act
to get through this rough patch.
At her core,
she's still the high and mighty
Lin Zhanqiao.
To you,
to me,
probably to everyone except He Han.
The moment you give in,
the moment you give her room to breathe,
she'll immediately go back to
how she used to be.
And you'll go back to being that Gu Yan
buried down in the dirt.
(Phantom Knight)
Only if you never compromise
and never back down
can you stay in control.
You mean
stay in control?
I've never thought that way.
You didn't dare to.
But I'll show you
that you can.
What about you and me?
Between us,
it's equal.
My job is to push you
as high as possible.
We rise together.
(Zhanqiao)
She's calling?
If she wants to come see you,
tell her to come later.
I'm taking you somewhere first.
Hello?
Do you have time right now?
I want to
come to your place again.
Tomorrow.
I'm busy today.
Other than Gu Yan,
pull together the editors
who handle the company's
three best-performing projects.
Set up a meeting this afternoon.
I'll oversee it myself.
- Okay.
- Understood.
Is she trying to create
another Gu Yan overnight?
Impossible. There's not enough time.
No way.
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Just desperate measures.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
To look at a place.
I think you deserve a better environment
for writing.
My place is fine.
I live alone.
I don't need that much space.
Take a look first.
Trust me.
You'll like it.
What's wrong?
Wasn't this the hotel
He Han used to stay at?
That's right.
Is this the place
you rent for me?
Hello, Ms. Zhao.
Your room is ready.
Please come with me.
This way, please.
This is the suite
He Han stayed in before.
It's the best room in the hotel.
Go in and take a look.
We'll look around ourselves.
Please wait outside.
Of course.
This suite is over 300 square meters.
Temperature-controlled,
humidity-controlled,
fully ventilated, and soundproof.
The living room overlooks
the busiest part of the city.
Convenient transportation.
Full facilities nearby.
Parks, malls, and stadiums.
Everything you need is here.
And most importantly,
the restaurant here is excellent.
This is the perfect environment
for writing.
Go take a look at the bedroom.
I don't want to stay here.
Why not?
It reminds me of He Han.
That means you still can't get past him.
Even though he has stopped writing,
you still feel inferior to him.
I want you to move in here
so you can see
that you've completely replaced him.
When this place slowly becomes yours,
when you sleep in that bed
without thinking about him anymore,
then whether you face
Lin Zhanqiao or He Han,
you'll finally feel
that you deserve the best treatment
and the highest respect.
Of course,
having you live here
is also a way of telling everyone else
that you've replaced He Han.
Please come in.
The manager heard you might move in,
so they specially prepared
the hotel's signature afternoon tea
for you.
One wine glass is enough.
I should get going.
I'm not drinking today.
When you move in,
I'll celebrate with you then.
You can leave whenever you want.
If you decide to move in, let me know.
Oh, right.
The building across from these windows
is Lin Zhanqiao's office.
He Han probably stayed here
because of that.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪