( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 29=
Welcome.
(Dida Ride Hailing)
Here.
Thank you.
Not off work yet, Mr. He?
I keep the regular spot for you.
Alright, thanks.
(The building across these windows)
(is Lin Zhanqiao's office.)
(Back when He Han stayed here,)
(it was probably because of that.)
(That's why I want you to move in here.)
(Once this place slowly becomes yours,)
(once you sleep in that bed)
(without thinking about him anymore,)
(that'll mean...)
You've completely replaced He Han.
Dida has assigned you
a passenger with
the last four digits 3118.
Please follow the navigation
to the pickup location.
Dida reminds you.
Please avoid driving while tired
and drive safely.
Sir, your car is here.
This one.
Sure. I'll walk you over.
Thank you.
Take care.
Hello.
What a coincidence.
Please fasten your seat belt.
We're setting off.
Do you usually drive around
this hotel area?
I know this area pretty well.
And I know the hotel staff outside, too.
He always saves me a good parking spot.
Do you know
why I came here?
How would I know?
Why?
I'm looking for a new place to write.
The room I stayed in
is actually pretty nice.
Yeah, it is.
And expensive, too.
Too expensive.
If I were you, I would switch hotels.
There are plenty of places
cheaper and better than that one.
Would it bother you
if I stayed here?
No. Why would it?
Other people stayed in that room
before I did, too.
After I leave,
someone else will stay there anyway.
I was more worried
you'd feel uncomfortable.
Like you said,
it's just a hotel,
right?
People are going to talk about you.
The person who'll probably
feel that worst about it
is Lin Zhanqiao.
She won't.
She'll just look down on you.
(Once this place slowly becomes yours,)
(then no matter)
whether you face Lin Zhanqiao or He Han,
you'll feel like you deserve
the best treatment
and the highest respect.
We're almost there.
Where do you want me to stop?
Pull over on the right
after the turn ahead.
Wait downstairs for me.
Don't end the trip.
I need to head out again later.
Sure.
About how long will you be?
I need to figure out where to park.
Pull over anywhere.
Let the meter keep running.
I'll tell you when I'm coming back out.
Got it.
(Market Influence Analysis)
From the current situation,
all three projects
have their own strengths.
Year of Blessings is a popular genre
with a stable readership.
Out of the three projects,
it's the safest bet.
Order of the Mountain Ghost
is a rare genre
in the current market.
I think it's a pretty risky attempt.
Of course,
it has caught readers' attention.
But it's still niche
and not very stable yet.
I think we should observe it
a bit longer.
As for Lord Cui Wei,
it's the first title
in one of our key series.
A very important starting point.
If this book succeeds,
it'll drive the development
of the entire series going forward.
Ms. Lin,
all three project editors
are here today.
Honestly, we're all worried
the company's going to cut
our promotion budgets.
Let me be upfront with everyone
about my plans.
If I can keep Gu Yan
at Chenxing,
then every plan we made before
will continue as scheduled.
But if he insists on leaving,
I'll receive a payout.
And the most important thing for us
will be using that money
to push one project
into becoming a top-tier hit.
So during this period,
I'll definitely cut the budgets
for the other projects.
Understood?
Year of the Blessings is the safest bet
with the quickest return.
But film studios have kept an eye
on Lord Cui Wei
and are actively following up.
There's a real chance
its adaptation rights
could be sold for a very high price.
Order of the Ghost Mountain
is my project.
I'm not just speaking up
for myself here,
but with how saturated the market is
with similar genres right now,
if we want to stand out, Ms. Lin,
I think you should give
Order of the Mountain Ghost a push.
But if Lord Cui Wei
successfully sells
its screen adaptation rights,
the licensing fee could also
be used to support other projects.
But Lord Cui Wei is in its early stages.
It'll need long-term
and consistent promotion.
Year of the Blessings is more
than halfway through serialization,
and the author's still going strong.
If we prioritize promoting
Year of the Blessings,
we'll see returns much faster.
There are too many similar titles
in the market for this.
Honestly, its story doesn't have
the strength to become a top-tier hit.
Pull over here.
I'm not denying
it can become a first-tier title.
(Gu Yan)
But the story itself
doesn't have the potential
to become a breakout phenomenon.
The payoff just isn't worth it
if you do that math.
I still think...
Hello?
Guys, I think we should prioritize...
I'm free now.
Come over.
I'll be right there.
Whether it's Lord Cui Wei
or Order of the Mountain Ghost...
I'm going to see Gu Yan first.
Wait for me to get back.
That's really a surprise, Wang Hai.
I never expected you
to do something like this
for my wedding gift.
I thought now that you've made money,
(Mengtong Internet Cafe Renovation Plan)
you would give us a red packet,
or maybe some gold jewelry.
I even thought
you might buy Er Jiu a car.
But you actually hired someone
to renovate our internet cafe.
This was from Zhao Lanxin?
Yeah.
She said you wanted to keep it a secret.
But since Er Jiu and I are the ones
using the internet cafe,
she thought we'd see the plans
in advance.
Before the design is finalized,
we can point out anything we don't like
and change it early.
She's thoughtful.
She also said you've made plans
for our future.
Like a chain of e-sports hotels
and building our own e-sports team.
Thank you, Wang Hai.
Why didn't you tell me yourself?
She said you've always
been planning things for us.
I should thank Zhao Lanxin.
I did have that wish.
She's the one who helped make it happen.
Take a look.
(Moments)
(Cai Zhangzhu: In the name of the Moon,
I'll punish the ungrateful one)
(three hundred times.)
(What happened?)
Hello?
Hello, Mr. He Han?
It's about Gu Yan.
Do you have time now?
Can we talk for a bit?
I'm seriously about to explode.
I'm very free right now.
Anyone can tell
you're talking about Gu Yan.
What happened?
Do you know
what he has done to Ms. Lin?
He summons her whenever he wants
and dismisses her just as easily.
He doesn't give her any respect at all.
Do you know why I have time
to call you right now?
Because Ms. Lin
went to beg Gu Yan
not to leave Chenxing.
Beg him? Can you imagine that?
What did you just say? Go on.
(Hello, when would you like to depart?)
(The driver
has been waiting for one hour.)
(Zhao Lanxin)
(Hello, when would you like to depart?)
You got here fast.
I came straight over
right after we hung up.
What do you want to tell me?
I take back what I said before.
I hope you'll consider
continuing to work with Chenxing
while also working
with Dingqi and Zhao Lanxin.
I'll probably need to discuss that
with Zhao Lanxin.
We haven't terminated our contract yet.
You haven't signed with
Zhao Lanxin either.
Whatever decision you make,
you don't need to discuss it with her.
She has done a lot for me.
Just today,
just now,
she was still making arrangements
for me.
She even considered
the guilt I feel toward
San Mei and Er Jiu.
Fine.
I admit Zhao Lanxin
has done a lot for you.
That's why you want to work with her.
I accept that.
Like I said,
I came here today
hoping that
for the sake of me discovering you,
for the sake of how hard
we worked together
to finally succeed,
you could continue working with Chenxing
for another year or two.
She still has responsibilities
for Chenxing.
She'll definitely come back
and beg you.
Lin Zhanqiao,
have you never begged anyone
like this before?
Did you rehearse this speech
over and over beforehand?
Zhao Lanxin predicted all of this.
I prepared more than this.
If I were a man,
I would probably
be pouring you drink after drink
until you agreed.
Too bad I'm not.
So all I can do is talk.
But honestly,
I don't have much more left to say.
No matter how I put it,
I'm just asking you to help me
and Chenxing get through this.
I'll owe you one.
I'll repay it.
Boss, I'm ready to order.
I'm not used to seeing
this side of you, Lin Zhanqiao.
I can't agree to it.
Because I already promised
Zhao Lanxin.
Everything you just said...
Zhao Lanxin heard it, too.
If she agrees,
I'm willing to discuss with you.
What do you mean?
(Zhao Lanxin)
How could you do this?
No matter how you treated me,
I could accept it.
I was prepared for that.
But why would you do something
this disgusting?
I was on the phone with her
when I came back.
She told me not to hang up.
She was afraid that if I saw you,
I would go soft.
Lin Zhanqiao,
Zhao Lanxin was wrong.
Do you realize
how shameless and despicable this is?
Zhao Lanxin also said
that if you cried in front of me,
I could agree to help you.
I won't.
You're not worth it.
Where's Lin Zhanqiao?
Why haven't you left yet?
Seriously?
How could I leave
before you end the order?
Where's Lin Zhanqiao?
She left.
Didn't you want to know
why Lin Zhanqiao came?
I'll tell you.
She came to beg me.
Didn't expect that, right?
Of course you should
help her when she asks.
Without her,
you would be nothing right now.
Now that she's in trouble,
why didn't she ask you for help?
If she begged you for help,
you would definitely help her, right?
But she would rather come to me.
Even if I refuse,
she'll still come back to me.
Do you understand
how worthless you are?
You and Lin Zhanqiao are the same!
Both of you are worthless.
I couldn't persuade Gu Yan.
I'm sorry.
Think about which
of those three projects
we're going to push.
Hello?
Yes, this is.
(Police)
(Ningping Road Police Station)
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why did you hit him?
Doesn't he deserve it?
Beating him up won't solve anything.
It does. It felt good.
I just wanted him to know there are
consequences
for doing something like that.
It'll teach him
some sense of right and wrong.
But you've been to
the police station now.
Can you still drive
for the platform after this?
I don't know.
Depends on how the platform handles it.
Maybe not.
Then what are you going to do?
If this platform doesn't work out,
there'll be others.
I'll figure something out.
I can drive for you.
No need. I'm fine.
If you can't drive anymore,
come back to writing.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself instead.
What are you planning to do next?
I'm betting everything on a project
that hasn't launched yet.
If it works,
then I'll have a shot
at getting funding from investors.
But if it fails,
then forget it.
That's it for Chenxing.
Doesn't Gu Yan owe you
compensation for breach of contract?
Yeah, but both sides are still
gathering evidence through lawyers
and filing lawsuits.
By the time everything's settled,
and the money actually comes in,
it'll probably take at least
another year or more.
Objectively speaking,
how's that new project looking?
It's the best option
among limited choices.
I mean how confident are you
that you can pull it off?
Seventy percent? Three percent?
Big rewards come from big risks.
What's the new novel called?
It's a novel about myth and revival
aimed at female readers.
You wouldn't be interested.
If Gu Yan gives you trouble again,
call me.
He won't.
I'm off.
(Ms. Lin, are you okay?)
(I'm fine. Good night.)
♪Like a drifting dandelion♪
(To this day,)
(Chenxing's downfall)
(is unavoidable.)
(I may be a good editor.)
(Organized,)
(planned,)
(hardworking, and resilient.)
(But none of those qualities)
(were enough to make me a good boss.)
♪Even spring borrows its fragrance♪
(Refusal to compromise)
(or take a step back.)
(My ego and stubbornness)
(left both Chenxing and me shattered)
(when we hit obstacles.)
♪Swaying in the shape of the wind♪
♪Not waiting for calm to come♪
Zhangzhu, what's the title
of that new novel
your company's planning to promote?
First is a welcome speech
and company introduction.
Second is the training plan.
Hello?
Have you reached the office yet?
I'm in a meeting.
Going over HR details.
What about you? Is Guangzhou hot?
I'm fine. I haven't been outside much.
I just met with an author
and got back to the hotel.
Have HR send me an email
about the new employees.
I want to take a look.
It's room service bringing breakfast.
My flight back to Shanghai
is tomorrow at noon.
See you tomorrow.
What?
You told Ling Yikai
you weren't in Shanghai?
I told him I was on a business trip
in Guangzhou for three days,
meeting an author.
I brought you some food.
Thanks.
Why didn't you tell him you had surgery?
He doesn't want kids.
He thinks I've been
taking birth control,
so I couldn't get pregnant.
You've been staying here
these three days?
You're the only person
I told about this place.
Lin Zhanqiao said she saw you
at the hospital.
She probably doesn't know
why I was there.
You didn't tell her, did you?
No.
I haven't seen her either.
Besides, this is your private business.
Thanks.
Right now, the person
she probably hates most is me.
But she should understand
that in any industry, if you want
to climb all the way to the top,
(Registration and Consultation Slip)
you run into countless competitors.
(Post-Hysteroscopy Care Instructions)
We just happened to be placed
on opposite sides by fate.
And there's only one trophy.
The trophy matters.
So does your life.
The doctor said you have
to rest in bed for three days
and no strenuous activity for a month.
I know.
But I'm not like you guys.
I'm tough.
If you need to go to the hospital
next time,
call me.
I'll go with you.
Next time I go to the hospital,
I'll probably be
for a pregnancy check-up.
I thought Ling Yikai didn't want kids.
I do.
(In the little town of Hulan River)
(lived my grandpa.)
(By the time I was born,)
(he was over sixty years old.)
(And when I was four or five,)
(he was nearly seventy.)
(We had a big garden at home.)
(In that garden, there were bees,)
(butterflies,)
(dragonflies,)
(and grasshoppers.)
(Everything.)
(There were white butterflies)
(and yellow butterflies.)
(Those butterflies were tiny,)
(not very pretty.)
(The beautiful ones)
(were the red butterflies.)
(Their wings were dusted
with golden powder.)
(The dragonflies were gold.)
(The grasshoppers were green.)
(The bees...)
You're here so early.
Mom.
I wanted to see you
before heading to the office.
Where are Dad and the caretaker?
She's at the market.
Since when did you start reading books?
I don't read.
Your dad brought it.
He reads to me.
While reading,
he explains things
like a storyteller.
He spent the whole afternoon reading.
If you like it,
ask him to keep reading.
It's not that I like it.
But the part he read yesterday
was actually quite interesting.
So I secretly recorded it.
Today,
I listened to it again.
If he doesn't sit beside me reading,
what else would we even talk about?
There's not much to say.
So reading's better.
Where did he go today?
I gave him the day off.
He can go wherever he wants.
He'll come home for dinner tonight.
That doesn't sound like you, Mom.
If you make him
stay beside me all the time,
don't you think he'd feel miserable?
And when I think about that,
I feel miserable, too.
Once you get better,
you two can go out together.
Whether I'll get better or not,
I don't know.
But if he had to
take me along when he goes out,
he would probably rather
not go anywhere at all.
That much I know for sure.
He's been like this his whole life.
He can't travel happily with anyone.
If...
there had to be one person,
it would be you.
When you were little,
he took you to the zoo,
to Suzhou,
and to Hangzhou.
Do you want to take your meds?
I'm fine.
Massage here for me.
Okay.
Here?
Here.
He's at the Western Suburb Hotel.
I didn't ask.
He sent it himself.
Whenever I let him go out,
he sends me pictures.
I feel like
that's his way
of repaying me for giving him freedom.
Mom,
I've been thinking.
Everyone probably has a different idea
of the most comfortable distance
in a close relationship.
Your distance
is very close,
and Dad's distance
is very far away.
This kind of thing
isn't like weight or height,
where there's a clear number.
If there were,
things would be much easier.
People who want to get married
can compare their numbers
like birth charts.
If it doesn't match,
don't get married.
Being friends is nice, too.
(Grandma also likes raising sheep.)
(The sheep ate all the fruit trees,)
(so the trees died.)
(By the time I could remember things,)
(there was only one cherry tree
left in the garden,)
(and one plum tree.)
(Because neither of them bore much fruit.)
Order of the Mountain Ghost.
Mr. He Han,
is there anything else you want to know?
Let's meet up when you're free.
Sure. Anytime.
Who is it?
Mr. He Han.
Seriously?
Do you have a superpower or what?
I was too embarrassed
to knock directly,
so I texted asking when you were free.
You said anytime.
Come in.
What?
I heard you beat Gu Yan up.
That was so satisfying for us.
I've always wanted to hit him.
Maybe don't learn that from me.
How did you know?
Did your boss tell you?
No.
Someone in our fan group
knows people at the police station.
That's how we heard.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What's going on with
Order of the Mountain Ghost?
Tell me about it.
What kind of person is the author?
The author
goes by Prefrontal Cortex.
A new author.
He writes day and night.
He works really hard.
But still not as good as you.
Ms. Lin, everyone knows the company is
promoting Order of the Mountain Ghost,
so naturally,
they have feelings about it.
Naobaijin has always wanted
to turn the Lord Cui Wei series
into a real brand.
I need to talk to her more about that.
There's a chance we might form
a joint studio together.
Chenxing can use
the IP value of Lord Cui Wei
as an investment.
What about our other projects?
I want to observe her a bit longer.
As for the other projects,
I don't want her
to get too deeply involved for now.
So you suspect Naobaijin
leaked our information?
There are two editors
in Zhao Lanxin and Ling Yikai's company
who used to work under her.
These are special circumstances.
Better safe than sorry.
Understood.
How long has it been
since you last wrote with a pen?
Quite a while.
I realized something.
Writing isn't like driving.
Even if you haven't been driving
for ten years,
once you get behind the wheel,
you still know how.
But if you stop writing for ten days,
your hands feel rusty.
Mr. He Han,
if I want to write novels,
will you teach me?
Why the sudden idea?
Well...
I used to be your fan.
I entered this industry because of you.
Back then,
I could still read your novels,
run errands for Ms. Lin,
and find excuses to see you.
But now
you've stopped
writing.
You don't come see Ms. Lin anymore.
You have no idea
how bored I've been lately.
Actually,
I've wanted to come for a long time.
I just couldn't think of a reason.
Have you really thought this through?
You know how hard it is
starting out as a web novelist.
There are over twenty million authors
in the country.
And the ones anyone actually knows
are less than a hundred.
If you agree to teach me,
I can learn slowly.
I can't.
I'm not a good teacher.
If you want to learn,
ask your boss.
A good editor makes the best teacher.
It's not like I have to become famous
or make money.
My dad doesn't expect me
to make big money.
You can just critique whatever I write.
If it's terrible,
you can scold me.
I'm not saying Ms. Lin is bad or anything.
I just hope
I can still see you often.
People who write novels
mostly only get to see themselves
and the characters in their stories.
But sometimes,
you need to see Ms. Lin, too.
Well...
Sometimes, maybe.
Do you ever want to see me
sometimes too?
No.
Because there's really no one
I especially want to see.
Right?
Other than your boss,
sometimes, I want to visit Mr. Liang.
And Dai Shan, too.
I'm curious what she has been up to.
I don't think people need to
meet every day or stay in contact.
If you run into someone, chat,
and have a nice time, that's enough.
If we run into each other,
I would be really happy, too.
And I'd love to hear
whatever you want to share.
Yeah.
True.
I understand now.
I should get going.
I'm heading back to the office.
Anyways,
Mr. He Han,
you're someone I really want to see.
Someone I want to see
and talk to every day.
♪I don't want to leave the memories♪
♪My mind's not over you♪
♪Girl, don't ask me♪
♪Why I cannot find♪
♪The way to forget you♪
♪I have battled♪
♪through the sleepless nights♪
♪All I think about is you♪
♪How I wish♪
♪that you could hear my voice♪
♪And know I won't forget you♪
♪Never forget you♪
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪