( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 30=
These are the winter clothes.
We'll donate them to rural areas.
Okay.
Please sign here.
Lin.
Show her a few different decor styles.
Okay, Mr. Cai.
Alright.
No problem.
Great.
- You have them all.
- Thanks.
I do.
Go over them carefully with her.
Mr. Cai, Ms. Mei is here.
You should talk to her.
Mr. Cai.
Zhou Mei.
Just tell me what you want,
and I'll make it happen.
Lin Zhanqiao's business is my business.
Your house is my responsibility.
Thank you, Mr. Cai.
Hello, Ms. Zhou Mei. Your parcel.
Thanks.
(Cordially invites Bei Wenqi)
(Groom: He Shunnan, Bride: Li Yuzhen)
Hello?
Hello.
On the 5th of next month,
it's a good friend's wedding.
I want you to go with me.
I want to
properly introduce you to everyone.
Well,
let me try
asking for time off from work.
Okay.
One more thing.
Your mom asked
to meet me this afternoon.
What?
I love Zhou Mei.
I fell in love with her
the moment I first saw her.
But at the time,
I was
still married.
Of course, I had to hesitate
and weigh my options.
I'm not a child.
I couldn't act on impulse
and ask my wife for a divorce.
But my love for Zhou Mei
is real.
So after some hesitation,
I decided to divorce.
Stop making excuses
for tossing the old for the new.
By your logic,
marriage has no binding power at all.
It might as well not exist.
Since the law allows for divorce,
it means marriage
can be trial and error.
If two people
aren't right for each other
and are miserable,
they should end the relationship
and start over.
Your actions
will make my daughter
a laughingstock to the world.
If Zhou Mei feels the same way,
I'm willing to face
this so-called ridicule with her.
How will you face it?
By being shameless together?
I probably shouldn't say this.
But I believe
Zhou Mei's biggest source of ridicule
has been you.
Brought upon her by her own mother,
not anyone else.
As her mother,
please stop hurting her.
Whether physically or verbally.
If you do it in front of me,
I will do everything to stop you.
If I hear about it,
I'll gather all the evidence.
And I will sue you if necessary.
This self-deception of yours
and excuses about finding true love
make me sick.
Of course.
Every shameful deed in the world
is always given
some grand,
high-sounding justification.
Zhou Mei.
Just in time.
Sit.
Just say it
right now.
If you insist on marrying
a man who's just like your father,
I will end my own life!
Let me ask her!
Ask her how she plans to die, and when?
When she gets my wedding invitation?
When I get my certificate?
Or at my wedding?
She's threatening you.
She wants you
to go argue with her right now,
and to explain yourself.
I'm her daughter.
Why won't she just let me be happy?
About getting married,
let's wait a bit.
I really want you
to marry me.
But under these circumstances,
I can wait as long as it takes.
If I don't go through with this wedding,
won't she think I'm scared of her?
She'll just keep
using her life to threaten me.
If there's no other way,
let's wait a bit longer.
I really didn't expect
to be the lucky one.
Come on, thank you for choosing me.
Here, I bought you some snacks.
- Thank you.
- Help yourselves.
- Let's pass these around.
- Thanks.
I saw you complain on Moments.
There hasn't been much promo.
We're basically
pooling all our efforts
to get you on the ranking.
- Keep it up.
- Here, have some coffee.
Thanks.
I'll give it my all.
Have some coffee.
These two are yours.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Chenxing had a star writer called He Han
and Gu Yan.
Next, it might be me, Prefrontal Cortex.
Ms. Lin.
Please, sit.
We finally meet.
(Destined)
But it's possible that the result
could be underwhelming.
Have you thought about that?
I have.
Did Mantou explain the situation
to you?
Yes.
I know all of this.
But
I still decided
to take a leap of faith with you.
What if we win?
I could become
a partner at Chenxing.
Then it's settled.
We're on the same page.
Your "Order of the Mountain Ghost"
is now riding with Chenxing.
We're going all in.
Mantou mapped out
a month-long promo campaign.
So starting now, I need you
to stick to the original character arcs
and your core outline,
and stockpile chapters.
We need explosive updates
ready to drop.
It'll help your ranking,
and boost our off-site promo.
Can you do it?
I can.
Are you free tonight?
Let's grab dinner.
I can't get away.
I'm swamped at work.
Talk to you later.
Stats for "Order of the Mountain Ghost".
Have a look.
The growth curve has actually
been flattening out since last week.
For a newly launched novel,
it's not good.
That's why we need to help him.
It's slowing down,
but it's still climbing, right?
We still have a week left.
If we go full throttle
and push harder,
we still have a shot.
Okay.
Mr. He.
Mr. He Han.
Why are you here?
I said
I didn't have time for dinner.
You don't, but I do.
So what do you want?
"Order of the Mountain Ghost".
Are you going all in on it?
I'm not going all in.
It's a hard push.
If it's not set in stone yet,
I'd advise you to drop it.
It's already set.
I read the novel.
I don't think it's a smart choice.
When did you read it?
Last night.
I even skimmed through his other work.
He's no Gu Yan.
Not even close.
"Order of the Mountain Ghost"
isn't a marketable concept.
But it's honestly the best shot
I have right now.
How good of a shot?
If other books have
a ten percent chance,
twenty percent still means
it's practically hopeless.
You're pouring
so much effort and money into this.
If it bombs, it'll be a massive blow
to you and Chenxing.
I still have some money
and plenty of fight left in me.
I have to use whatever I have left
to make one last push.
True, but couldn't you
pick a better project?
Mr. He Han?
He's the one?
I know "Order of the Mountain Ghost"
isn't a masterpiece.
But compared to the other projects,
it's slightly better.
The author is more cooperative,
and far more optimistic.
At a critical time like this,
that's a huge plus, right?
I'm out of options.
Alright.
As long as you know what you're doing.
You just seemed so dead set on it.
You could be blinded by it.
The author is the only one
who actually has faith in it.
But if I show any doubt now,
we might as well
just pack it in.
So I have to be the one
who goes all in,
and fights until the very last second.
Good luck.
If you stay and develop
a new one, I won't have to
push "Order of the Mountain Ghost".
I don't have the pull anymore.
You're still a heavyweight.
♪If the sky and the sea traded places♪
♪If a fish fell in love with a bird♪
It's not that I won't help.
I just can't write anymore.
I don't know how to start
a new series.
♪We wouldn't have
lost each other in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
It's alright.
I was just asking.
Maybe you'd say yes.
♪Let love surge like raging waves♪
♪Crashing over us, never fading♪
All the best.
♪Even if we're drenched in the rain♪
♪Even if time buries us away♪
♪At least we still have♪
♪This one eternal photo♪
♪But the sky can never
trade places with the sea♪
Gu Yan.
Coming?
Let me introduce you.
Ling Yikai.
Zhao Lanxin mentions you a lot.
We finally meet.
How are things?
Settling in okay?
Not really.
It's too big.
You really bring
that gaming vibe everywhere you go.
We'll all be colleagues from now on.
I figured you two should meet.
The company is paying
the rent for this house you're in.
That means the daily value you create
can't be less than the rent.
I'm not good at math.
Isn't that your job?
Let me make it simple.
We'll soon announce
that Sansan is your other pen name.
You wrote the top two
most-read works.
This will take you to the next level.
Your job is simple,
yet difficult.
Just maintain your current standard.
As for the stats,
they can only go up.
It's easier to conquer than defend.
Not to mention,
you have to hold two titles here.
And if the views drop?
Seems you don't know Zhao Lanxin well.
The moment your views drop,
you'll be moving out of here.
Is that so?
There's no free lunch.
You earned everything you have
right now.
Writers inevitably have
their ups and downs.
Zhao Lanxin doesn't have
the patience to wait.
She'll just pivot to other writers
who can bring her more profit.
It's not just this house, of course.
Your friends
are currently expanding
an esports arena.
It used to be an internet cafe.
I don't know if they told you,
but we signed an agreement.
The expansion funds
from Colorful Culture Media
count as an equity stake.
You guys still run the daily operations.
Nothing will change.
But if you choose
not to work with us,
I can't guarantee your friends
can keep this arena open.
What do you want?
We can wait for you until...
tomorrow.
(Exclusive Licensing Contract: Gu Yan)
I was thinking
we could consider
making the mysterious A'kong
the ultimate villain.
Any thoughts on this?
Yes, Ms. Lin.
I had the same thought.
I can use a secret identity trope
to hook the readers.
The plan was for A'kong
to oppose the female lead
the moment he appeared.
(Character Relationship Chart)
But actually,
we can give A'kong an alter ego,
put him beside the heroine,
and let him play dumb.
Introducing a new character
at such a critical juncture
is a bit risky.
So, if we do this,
we need to write it in a way
that gives the readers
an omniscient view.
Make them feel like
two masterminds are about to clash.
That way,
long-time readers won't have
their momentum broken.
Then, we introduce A'kong.
Exactly.
This way,
A'kong's identity
becomes even more crucial.
Everyone's entry point
into the web novel industry
is different.
There might not
be much common ground there.
And the process varies, too.
Some have smooth sailing
right from the start.
For others,
the hardest part is getting started.
Can't help that.
But I feel like
the total amount of hardship
is probably about the same.
Tired?
I'm alright.
You've worked hard.
Not at all.
I feel great.
Not a single day here feels wasted.
Finish what you're working on.
Send it to me.
This has
my edits and notes for the last section.
If you have time today,
finish it
and hand it over for formatting.
Send it in tomorrow morning.
Okay.
I'll go make you a cup of coffee.
Thanks.
"Order of the Mountain Ghost".
I read the novel.
I don't think it's a smart choice.
He's no Gu Yan.
Not even close.
"Order of the Mountain Ghost"
isn't a marketable concept.
You're pouring
so much effort and money into this.
If it bombs, it'll be a massive blow
to Chenxing and you.
That's it for today's episode.
I've prepared over ten episodes anyway.
They are all different lengths.
If there's not much to say,
I'll keep it short.
If there's a lot to share,
I'll talk a bit longer.
But the price is the same.
No refund if it's short,
and no extra fees if it's long.
It's all about trust.
Alright, that's all.
Good night, everyone.
(All edited. Looks okay to me.)
(If you think it's fine too,
the file is in your inbox. Just forward it.)
(From Your Lifesaver)
When did you get here?
Where's Prefrontal Cortex?
He left with you?
(Three Hours Earlier)
Prefrontal Cortex, right?
Mr. He Han.
Why are you here?
Sit down.
Where are you at?
Has the mysterious one
for the first climax appeared?
Yes.
Almost.
Mr. He Han, does this mean
you've read my novel too?
Very carefully.
Thank you.
Thank you for your valuable feedback.
Right.
These are
the first ten chapters I finished.
Based on Zhanqiao's suggestions,
I'll finish editing them tonight.
And, these
are the latest three chapters.
We'll review them when she gets back.
Let me see the first few chapters.
I'll edit the last three for you.
You'll edit them for me?
This...
Isn't this inappropriate?
Oh my.
This is such a surprise.
So what can I do?
Does Zhanqiao know?
I'll get her.
No, no, no.
She knows everything.
She asked me to help.
Thank you, Mr. He.
Hurry up and write.
Right away.
I'm just so excited.
♪I watch the stars in my eyes♪
♪Slowly drift away♪
These parts
are the same.
♪Died a little inside last night♪
♪Cause I'll never see you again♪
♪I'm waking up to silence around me♪
♪Heal, can I heal?♪
♪All I want is nothing more♪
♪Than to see your face someday♪
♪We were lovers♪
♪Till that very day♪
♪I'll remember♪
♪Us this way♪
♪How I wish♪
♪That you could hear my voice♪
♪And know I won't forget you♪
♪Never forget you♪
Fermented sparkling wine.
Zero alcohol.
But these bubbles
still give you a kick.
Cheers.
What are you so happy about?
Did your son come to you?
My son didn't come.
His friend came looking for me.
We chatted
for a long time.
Your son sent him, didn't he?
He won't admit it.
But from what I observed,
it was definitely my son
who sent him to spy on me.
Don't worry.
I can stand the test.
Did you show him your notebook?
Yes, he saw it.
It's been 2,237 days without a drink.
He even took photos.
He'll definitely report back to my son.
I realized
my son is going to come back.
With me turning over a new leaf,
he's bound to forgive me.
He will.
Cheers.
If your son does come back,
what about the shop?
Why would I keep it open?
I'm going to be a healthy old man.
I'll wake up at 5:00 AM,
and go to bed at 9:00 PM.
If my son
has kids,
I'll help him take care of them.
If not,
I'll help him walk the dog.
I'll be waiting for your good news.
Wait.
If I close my shop,
where will you go at night?
No need to worry about me.
There are plenty of people
with bad father-son relationships.
There's another old man
running a shop somewhere,
spending his days in misery.
I shouldn't have worried.
Your young friend is here for you.
It's sent?
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
If you hadn't dozed off,
you would've finished it.
So why did you come looking for me
so late at night?
To help.
I can't write long novels anymore,
but I can still help edit drafts.
Your account got suspended?
For a month.
That's a long time.
What are you going to do now?
I sell classes online.
What kind of classes?
Web novel writing.
Oh my.
You used to hate even doing interviews.
I'm not like you.
I know how to adapt, okay?
Give me a break.
Who hooked you up with this?
An old friend.
The so-called phoenix head,
leopard tail, and pig belly.
We start with the phoenix head.
Everyone knows
that readers will read
only three pages.
If they don't find the hook,
they'll just drop it.
Your characters, plot, and setting
have to be spectacular
right out of the gate.
Let's compare two novels.
One is mine.
The other belongs
to our course producer,
Ms. Mimi.
These two...
Mimi?
She reached out to you?
Is she not writing anymore?
No.
She got her courses recorded.
She's doing livestreams herself.
She's actually making a lot of money.
So, is she still...
Mr. He.
Actually,
my boyfriend is a fan of yours, too.
And he really wants to meet you.
Is that okay?
Is that a good idea?
We made quite a scene back then.
It'd be awkward.
It's fine.
The first time we met,
he asked me
if I was the Mimi who wrote
about He Han being a jerk.
But I told him
that for your course,
he has to promote it hard.
If he doesn't hit
five million views in a week,
I won't marry him.
Don't be so dramatic.
Thanks for today.
Hello.
This is my boyfriend.
Hi, nice to meet you.
I can't believe it.
I'm shaking Mr. He Han's hand.
Oh, please.
The hand that wrote
"Tao Yao: Dream of Wuchuan"
and "Shattered Six States".
Mr. He,
can I get a picture with you?
Of course.
Mimi, take a picture for us.
Sure.
Three, two, one.
What's on your mind?
The boss of that online course platform
is her boyfriend.
Lanxin, are you done?
Almost.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I just need a minute.
I've known you for years.
I've never seen you cry.
And this is the first time
you've hugged me first.
Lanxin.
Don't put so much pressure on yourself.
You're already doing great.
Think about it.
In a little while,
once Dingqi buys in,
and we secure Gu Yan,
we'll be the hottest
web novel site.
I can do even better.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
Stop crying. It's okay.
You're up early.
Didn't sleep well last night?
I slept for a bit.
Woke up again after 3 AM.
You can't sleep well,
and I can't get enough sleep.
Finding someone
who sleeps well these days
is really not easy.
Insomnia causes all sorts of problems,
but it won't kill you.
You keep
mentioning death lately, you know?
As soon as I close my eyes,
I see my mom
threatening to kill herself.
You weren't in a rush
to get married anyway.
Put it on hold for now.
Can't you buy some time?
No.
That's a retreat.
If she sees me retreat,
she'll advance.
How will you advance?
I'll marry Lawyer Bei.
Come on.
She's your mom.
You don't have to push her this hard.
She forced my hand.
But she's still your mother.
It's no excuse to abuse me.
Abuse?
Yes, abuse.
Emotional abuse.
Just because it's invisible,
and she's my mom,
makes it even more terrifying.
But I won't tolerate it anymore.
Since I've decided to fight back,
I'm not backing down.
Both of us are officially
in a state of war right now.
Compared to yours,
my situation is slightly better.
At least I have a game plan,
and a clear way to concede defeat.
Mine is a duel.
It's face-to-face
with knives drawn.
And my opponent is my mom.
Sometimes, I wonder
if I should just pluck her hair
and get a DNA test.
What if she isn't my mom?
That would solve everything.
You know what?
That might actually be a good idea.
Zhangzhu.
Time for breakfast.
She left this early?
She's been distracted lately.
It's a bit weird.
The company isn't doing well right now.
Maybe she went out early
for an interview somewhere else.
She doesn't seem like the type.
But when a girl is that distracted,
she's either in love or heartbroken.
Why don't you ask He Han
if he's seen her lately?
Zhangzhu likes He Han.
I'm sure you know.
I know.
But it's just
a young fangirl's
crush on a male author, right?
She's in her twenties
without a boyfriend.
Do you actually think
she has no interest in dating?
It made sense
when you and He Han were at odds.
But now that you are getting closer,
what does she think?
What could she be thinking?
She's jealous.
He Han and I
have been together for years.
We've spent so much time
and been through so much together.
She can't understand or feel that.
You mean you two
are like a married couple?
By the way,
with Chenxing in this crisis,
is He Han's help going to do any good?
I'll check the data later.
If it manages to climb at all,
we'll make a final push together.
(Dingqi Reading Platform Real-Time Data)
(Exclusive Licensing Contract: Gu Yan)
I can sign it, but on one condition.
Chenxing's prized Prefrontal Cortex,
and his "Order of the Mountain Ghost"
must not gain any traction.
Ms. Lin.
How's the data?
It's up.
Isn't that great?
Why do you look worried?
It only went up a little.
The rate
of growth is slowing down.
We should observe
before we make a move.
How are Gu Yan's two books doing?
Still the top two.
The cumulative data curve is stable.
If "Order of the Mountain Ghost"
could go a bit higher,
we could really push it.
Ms. Lin, Prefrontal Cortex is
in the conference room.
He seems highly motivated.
Probably stayed up all night.
I'll head over in a minute.
He asked
if Mr. He Han is coming again tonight.
You can invite him.
Okay.
Let's wait another two days.
Ms. Lin.
Morning.
I went for a run this morning.
Then I came straight to the office.
I'm here to report
that I saw people
in the fan group talking
about rumors
of Dingqi trying to poach Gu Yan.
I reckon it's Zhao Lanxin's way of
laying the groundwork
for an announcement.
We can't wait two days.
The video montages we prepared,
the promo clips,
and the blogger collabs
must be released now!
Isn't it too risky
to dump all that money now?
If it doesn't climb now,
it won't get any exposure later.
Ranking on the Dingqi charts
is the best start for a new story.
That's how its copyright value goes up.
If you wait any longer,
the same amount of money
won't even make a splash.
Tell Prefrontal Cortex
to prep bonus chapters for prime time.
And promise the readers
that if the ranking goes up,
do a big update tomorrow.
(Order of the Mountain Ghost,
Mythology Meets Infinite Flow)
(Nanhui Network: "Order of the
Mountain Ghost is a cultural trove)
(Order of the Mountain Ghost)
(Drunk Old Friend, Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui, Order of the Mountain Ghost)
Lin Zhanqiao made her move?
The promo companies said
she bought
all the top-tier promo resources.
I heard He Han
helped out as a favor, too.
Prefrontal Cortex posted on Moments.
He said he wouldn't let down
the top-tier author
and editor backing him up.
In our industry,
the worst thing is
having everything ready,
but lacking the talent.
True.
"Order of the Mountain Ghost"
is published on our platform.
We win either way.
Go tell Zhao Lanxin
to delay Gu Yan's promo
for a few days.
Okay.
Let's give Lin Zhanqiao a day.
Let her enjoy the moment.
I don't want to see
this Prefrontal Cortex
above me for even a day.
(Exclusive Licensing Contract: Gu Yan)
Give them some hope.
The higher the hopes,
the harder the fall.
(Dingqi Reading Platform Real-Time Data)
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪