( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 32=
I'll send you a WeChat contact.
Zhao Lanxin from Colorful Culture Media.
She likes Order of the Mountain Ghost,
and she reached out to me.
You said it yourself.
She's my rival.
So there's no way
she's taking over this novel to help me.
Throwing in the towel?
Yeah.
I didn't expect you to concede so fast.
You care about winning and losing.
I don't.
What do you care about then?
I don't want to live with regrets
or a guilty conscience.
You need to win first
before anything else matters.
I care about
my relationships with people.
I care about how others feel.
But you don't.
If nobody cared about how I felt,
why should I care about theirs?
No.
I care about people
who envy or are jealous of me.
Or maybe you do care,
but you pretend not to.
Don't need to worry about me.
I'm the winner here.
What are you going to do?
Drive ride-hailing cars with He Han?
I haven't figured it out yet.
There's a lot left to wrap up
at the company.
Why did you come to me?
I want to ask you for a favor.
How do you know I would help you?
You would enjoy helping me.
It makes you feel
you're above me.
What is it?
I want to hand Order
of the Mountain Ghost over to you.
I'm not interested.
That's why I'm asking for help.
After the novel is finished,
whether you renew his contract or not,
I won't interfere.
That's between you and him.
But right now,
I hope you can assign him
a good editor
and help him finish the novel properly.
I can't guarantee rankings.
Top ten shouldn't be a problem,
to be fair.
That means you owe me one.
I don't want him to know
you took on the novel as a favor.
An author's pride matters a lot.
Understood.
I'll say I took an interest in it.
Thank you.
Lin Zhanqiao,
you're a good person.
I'm genuinely envious of you for that.
It's not flattery.
It just means
you've been treated kindly.
Where's Dad?
I kicked him out.
He has nowhere to go.
That's exactly why
I kicked him out.
When he has nowhere left to go,
he'll regret
abandoning you and me
to fool around with those women outside.
Once he has nowhere to live,
he'll start coveting the apartment
you live in now.
This apartment's partly
under his name too.
The nerve of him
to ask me for that apartment.
Where's he going to stay then?
He...
He can come beg for
our forgiveness.
What do you mean?
Haven't we been waiting
for an apology and repentance from him
all these years?
Now he's old
and broke.
He should beg us.
That's what you want.
I stopped thinking that way long ago.
I didn't know
you still thought like that.
What have you been doing
all these years?
Waiting for him to come back?
I knew
this day would come eventually.
And then what?
You would forgive him
and live with him again?
That depends on
how sincere his apology
and repentance are.
He treated you badly for so many years,
and one moment of repentance
can wipe everything clean?
Other than us,
no one else is going
to take care of him.
In the end,
he'll only
grow old alone.
That's his own choice.
I don't need his apology or repentance.
And I'll never forgive him.
So when you say these things,
don't involve me.
Whether he comes back or not
has nothing to do with me.
Giving him a place to stay
doesn't mean I'll live with him again.
I'm not going to eat with him
or talk to him either.
I'll only support him in his old age
based on the standard of a nursing home.
After all, legally, I'm his daughter.
But I won't cry for him.
Do you have to oppose
everything I say on purpose?
Are you trying to rebel against me?
I'm not.
It's just that
we have different opinions
about Lawyer Bei and my dad.
You still have the nerve
to bring him up?
Is this dress
from him?
You planned to wear it
to Bali
and announce
your relationship, right?
I won't allow it.
Is this all you can do?
There are plenty of nice dresses
out there.
You can't tear them all apart.
Where are you going?
To buy a dress.
Did your mom leave?
I'll get you a hotel.
I'll pay for it.
What hotel?
Look at you now.
You can only stay somewhere
for around 200 yuan a night.
Then I'm not going.
Fine, stay here.
Zhou Mei!
Changed your mind?
Your mom called.
She said you wouldn't answer her calls.
And if you go to Bali,
she'll jump off the building.
Where are you, Zhanqiao?
Can you come over?
My mom's threatening to jump.
At my place.
Okay.
Taxi!
Sorry, can I take this cab?
I need to save someone.
She's not here.
Hello, police officer?
I want to report an emergency.
Mom!
Mom.
I've written my will.
When the time comes, everyone will know
I was driven to death
by my own daughter.
Mom,
come down.
I told you before.
If you stayed with Lawyer Bei,
I would die right in front of you.
She's trying to take her own life.
Give in to her now.
Is that man
more important
than my life?
(Emergency)
(Rescue Operation)
Don't crowd around!
Watch your step.
- What's going on?
- Alright. Stop looking.
Back up.
This looks dangerous.
Excuse me. Make way.
Excuse me, can I get through?
You can't go in.
It's dangerous.
What's there to be so upset about?
I won't be with him anymore.
You're lying to me!
I'm not lying!
I don't believe
anything you say anymore!
Only if I die in front of you
will you stop seeing him.
Because every time you're with him,
you'll think about me jumping today!
You forced me into this.
And you too, Zhou.
This is all
because of you.
You won't get to live in peace either.
Mom, I won't see him again!
You won't?
How are you going to prove it?
I'll prove it to you.
Come down first.
Come down.
This will never happen again!
You'll never have to worry
about this again.
If I come down,
and you break your promise,
I'll jump again.
I know.
That's why I'll prove it to you.
Come down first.
You're my mom.
And he's my dad.
I can't let you kill yourself
in front of him because of me.
You...
You finally understand now.
Mom.
Come.
Come here.
It's too dangerous.
You really understand now?
I do.
Come down.
Slowly.
You come down, too.
Hurry.
Mom.
You said that ever since
you married my dad,
you've never been happy.
But ever since I was born,
I've never been happy, either.
Zhou Mei!
(Emergency, Ambulance)
(Emergency Rescue Room)
She's your daughter!
What did you say to her? What did you do
to make her jump?
I've never seen parents like you before!
You don't deserve to be her parents!
Is she going to be okay?
Doctor.
The patient is awake.
How is she?
She sprained her ankle
and has a mild concussion.
Nothing serious.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I believe you now.
Let's just pretend
none of this ever happened,
okay?
Zhou Mei,
say something.
I spent my whole life
not understanding what family meant.
But...
when you jumped today,
I finally understood.
Maybe I realized it too late.
Talking to you about family now
would only burden you.
But I hope you'll live well from now on.
You're still young.
When you jumped just now,
if there hadn't been
an air cushion below,
I would've jumped
with you.
We've been through
everything together all these years.
Your daughter Zhou Mei
has already died.
I don't want to talk to
either of you anymore.
I want to see Lin Zhanqiao.
You really scared me, you know?
Even if they're your parents,
they're not worth this.
No one is.
You're absolutely not allowed
to think about doing something
like this again. Okay?
I won't anymore.
I've given
the old Zhou Mei back to them.
From now on,
I belong to myself.
You can't fight them
this way.
If anything happens,
you can come to me.
We'll figure it out together.
The last thirty years
may not have been good,
but we still have many more years
ahead of us.
We can live well together.
So now,
do you regret
what you did back then?
If you had another chance,
would you
still leave our daughter and me?
Yes.
Our marriage was a mistake.
So leaving us
for those women who deceived you
was the right choice?
Maybe that was a mistake, too.
Now you're broken and alone.
Where are you going to find a woman
who's willing to take you in?
How's Mei, Ms. Lin?
She has a mild concussion.
She should be fine
after resting for a few days.
Why did she...
She was trying to pull her mom back,
and then accidentally slipped.
That was terrifying.
Good thing you called
the fire department ahead of time
and got everything prepared.
Why have you been leaving early
these days?
What have you been up to?
I...
I've been out writing novels.
Writing novels?
Back when
I still had work at the company,
I was worried you'd think I wasn't
taking my job seriously
if I told you.
But now the company
is about to shut down,
so I figured
I should tell you.
You want to become a web novelist?
You've seen so many web novelists
rise and fall over the years.
And you know
most of them
just fade into obscurity in the end.
Why do you still want to do it?
Because
if I can write
really good stories one day,
maybe
Mr. He Han
will value me more.
Doesn't he already value you?
I...
I don't want to just be his fan.
I hope
one day I can stand on equal footing
with him.
Once the company shuts down,
I probably shouldn't stay here anymore.
This is your house.
Don't.
You can stay here.
I'll rent it to you.
I'll move out instead.
Who moves out of their own house?
Ask your dad
to help me find another good place.
Alright.
One bedroom?
Two.
I should leave a room for Zhou Mei.
I really envy Mei for having
a best friend like you.
She would envy you
for having a good father.
Are you okay?
Why didn't you tell me
something this serious had happened?
It's fine now.
You said it was an accident.
From what I heard, it wasn't.
It was an accident.
I was just lucky to survive.
By the way...
you should take this back.
You can't go to Bali with me
in your condition.
Keep the dress.
You can wear it after your foot heals.
I don't want to wear it anymore.
Why not?
We...
Whatever there was between us before,
I don't want it to continue anymore.
But...
But things
between us
are finally getting better.
Why...
Why would you give up now?
Before, I could never have had it.
So I always wanted it.
Family, parents, and love.
I always felt like everyone else
had a better life than I did.
I envied everyone.
My mom used to say my happiness
had been stolen by others.
So I became jealous of
everyone else, too.
And now, I've finally
won love for myself.
I know
that if I wanted it,
you could give me a family.
We could even have children.
Exactly.
Isn't that a good thing?
But I don't feel anything anymore.
What do you mean?
I've finally waited for this day.
You're telling me now
that everything I ever wanted
can finally be mine.
But I don't feel anything.
Or maybe
this is all the feeling there is.
So...
let's end this.
I want to be alone.
This must just be temporary.
Too much has happened recently.
You just need some time to yourself.
Once you're feeling better,
I'll come see you again.
Please lift your shirt a little.
(Early intrauterine pregnancy, twins)
What does "twins" mean?
It means twins. Literally.
We never said we wanted children.
Weren't you taking birth control pills?
How did you get pregnant
if you were taking them?
And twins on top of that?
Then take it as a surprise.
You never took birth control at all,
did you?
You call this a surprise?
This is a shock.
This is deception, you know that?
Your grandma is really happy.
She said she always hoped
she'd get to see your children someday.
I'm not ready for this!
And you never gave me the chance
to get ready!
Why don't you want children?
I can have children.
But this is something we're supposed
to face together in the future.
Did you discuss it with me?
Listen.
We can only have children
if I agree to it.
If you don't agree,
I'll go upstairs right now
and tell the doctor
we're not keeping them.
Zhao Lanxin.
I really hate you.
According to the contract,
we have two months left on the lease.
If a new tenant moves in
during that time,
our rent can be refunded.
If not,
we'll have to cover it ourselves.
Once you've sorted out the contracts,
give them to Zhangzhu.
I already gave them to her.
How are you holding up?
Feeling a little down?
You finally got the property management
to approve you for a parking spot,
and now the company's shutting down.
Parking spots are more in demand
than offices.
I can easily transfer it anytime.
It's fine.
Have you arranged everything
for what comes after?
More or less.
I transferred Prefrontal Cortex
to Zhao Lanxin's side.
So she'll probably let you take over.
I know after you leave here,
you'll probably join Zhao Lanxin.
Ms. Lin...
You were the one who gave
the new author list to her, right?
I'm really sorry about
the suspicions I had all along
about Fragile.
It wasn't until the day she resigned
that I realized it wasn't her.
Only four people had access
to the new author list.
You, her, Zhangzhu,
and Naobaijin.
But Zhangzhu
didn't know Zhao Lanxin.
Before that,
I even suspected Naobaijin.
I never suspected you at all.
Because at Chenxing,
you were the person I trusted most.
How did you figure it out?
You bought an insurance plan recently.
The salesperson was recommended
by Zhao Lanxin, right?
I happened to see her
when she came to the office
to see you.
Ms. Lin.
It's true.
I really did want to jump ship
to Zhao Lanxin's side.
I thought Chenxing's core
was its authors.
And the core of the authors
was He Han.
I thought you would give up
on Chenxing soon.
I'm the boss of Chenxing.
I'm the core.
Even now,
I still don't think of it as giving up.
It's only a pause.
And that's also why
I decided not to leave.
Ms. Lin,
I realized that you're
really tough
and resilient.
And also,
I...
I truly didn't expect you
to trust me that much.
Ms. Lin, after you found out it was me,
why didn't you expose me?
Because you pulled back in time.
You didn't leak the information
about Prefrontal Cortex
to Zhao Lanxin.
That's why the launch of
Order of the Mountain Ghost
went so smoothly.
If Zhao Lanxin had known,
she definitely would've
interfered somehow.
I have enough judgment to see that much.
After leaving here,
you've decided
to join Zhao Lanxin's company?
Dingqi?
No.
I'm talking with a new company.
You know the boss.
Who?
Dai Shan.
Didn't she already leave Shanghai?
She's back.
She went overseas before
to secure investment funding.
Alright then.
Wish you good luck.
I'm sorry,
Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin,
are you staying in this industry?
Of course.
I like this industry.
There are more people here
who love reading and writing.
And more people
with loyalty and tenderness, too.
(As much as I hate)
(seeing each of them off,)
(farewells still come.)
(So we might as well learn
from those free-spirited wanderers)
(and part ways cleanly.)
(The feelings will stay)
(until we meet again.)
This way.
How many students are there altogether?
Twelve.
How much are you charging each of them?
Twenty-six thousand.
Mr. He.
Hello, Mr. He.
Twenty-six thousand.
Ten-day intensive course.
Room and board included.
(Tian Ye, Student)
Web novel guru
personally guiding students
(Web Novel Master Class)
through creating a story outline.
Forget twenty-six thousand.
Even if you doubled the price,
people would still sign up.
(Web Novel Master Class)
And who knows?
Maybe the outline itself
could be sold to a platform afterward.
Besides me, who else
could teach the class?
None of the other instructors' classes
sells as well as yours.
Yours is the most expensive.
Ten days,
and you charge three hundred thousand.
I talk half.
That's fifteen thousand a day.
Of course.
If you're up for it,
you can rest for a few days,
and we'll open another class.
Over a hundred people signed up.
I had them each submit
a story outline first.
Then I screened them layer by layer
and picked these twelve.
Their ideas were the strongest.
I could probably handle
a few more students, too.
But let's try twelve first.
Alright.
Sorry to interrupt.
Class starts in ten minutes.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Come on.
These are the materials
you'll need to know.
And this is the presentation
that will be projected up there.
You need to control the slides yourself.
Clip this onto your clothes.
The mic.
- Like this?
- Yeah, right there.
Hello, Mr. He.
(Han Overdose, Student)
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
If I had told you,
it would've looked like
I got in through connections.
Submitting anonymously
is the way to prove my skills are real,
okay?
Over a hundred people applied.
If you got picked,
it means you genuinely earned it.
So you'll teach me properly, right?
When I make the rankings one day,
people will see my name
and know I'm your student.
A disciple of the Han clan.
Don't expect too much.
I'm probably not a very good teacher.
That's okay.
I'll surely be a good student.
I'll keep chasing after you
until you teach me.
Come on.
Break time is over. Time to start class.
♪First time in love♪
♪It tears my heart apart♪
♪Keep chasing on♪
♪Yet no one will ever know♪
♪For long time♪
♪Hope to lean on your side♪
♪And here you are♪
♪Calling my name in the air♪
♪Stay with open arms♪
♪I see you at the end♪
♪Now I cross the line♪
♪To be with you, my love♪
♪Love♪
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪