[Episode 27]
Miao Jing, over at Hongshen...
Miao Jing's been dealing
with a family emergency recently.
- Could I ask for two days off for her?
- Sure.
- May I ask how she's doing?
- You may not.
Sorry to trouble you.
No vehicles or refrigerated coffins available?
Then I'll arrange a vehicle myself.
We'll send her over today.
[Contact, Bo]
[Contact, Uncle Zhou]
[Call Home Phone]
Uncle Zhou.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you, Uncle Zhou.
Where did you borrow the vehicle from?
The owner of Final Stop.
We've borrowed their hearse
with a refrigerated casket before.
You've been up all night.
You must be starving.
Here. Have something to eat.
Eat even if you don't feel like it.
There's a lot of hard work ahead.
Don't wear yourself out.
Don't worry.
We're here with you.
Thank you, Uncle Zhou.
We'll take her to the morgue first.
Okay. Han. Thanks for the help.
- Okay.
- This way.
Family members, please confirm the body.
Then sign the handover paperwork
and the death certificate.
I'll go.
I can do it.
Have you confirmed it?
Then come sign here.
We also need your fingerprint.
Miao Jing.
[Soiled Utility Room]
My chest felt so tight just now.
Let's go.
[Hall of Remembrance]
[Farewell Ceremony for Ms. Wei Ming Zhen]
The farewell ceremony will begin shortly.
Family and friends, please come to the front.
Immediate family in the first row.
Today, we gather here with the deepest sorrow
to hold this farewell ceremony.
We mourn the loss of Ms. Wei Ming Zhen.
We bid Ms. Wei Ming Zhen a heartfelt farewell
on her final journey.
Moment of silence.
The moment of silence is over.
Now, let us bow three times
to Ms. Wei Ming Zhen,
to express our grief.
Everyone, first bow.
Wei Ming Zhen is dead?
Who are you?
You're Wei Ming Zhen's daughter, right?
Your mother owed us over 200,000 yuan.
Then she just dies and walks away.
Whatever the reason,
causing trouble at a funeral isn't appropriate.
Decency won't pay her debts.
If I don't corner you now,
I may never find you again.
I know people like you too well.
You think death wipes the slate clean.
Not a chance.
If you want to talk, do it outside.
Trying to run? Let go.
Don't push your luck.
- How much did she owe you?
- 230,000 yuan.
She signed the IOU last July.
It's two months overdue.
How did you find this place?
Her phone was disconnected.
The contract listed her daughter's information.
That means you.
How do we know you didn't hear the news
and plan to run?
Look, we really did lend the money out.
If we hadn't been unable to find her,
we wouldn't be here at a time like this.
Where is the contract?
It's okay. Just a copy. Give it to him.
[Loan Agreement]
Borrow one, pay back two.
That's loan-shark interest.
This contract is illegal.
And now that she's dead,
her debt has nothing to do with me.
It's illegal just because you say so?
Showing up to intimidate people.
Harassing the neighbors.
Making personal threats.
I know all your tricks inside and out.
I don't have time for this.
If you know what's good for you, get out.
You punk.
Who do you think you're pushing around?
- Boss!
- It hurts! It hurts.
Let go.
- It hurts!
- If you keep causing trouble,
we'll call the police.
Go ahead. Call the police.
I've got a promissory note and a contract.
You think I'm scared? That hurts!
- Boss!
- I am the police.
What's going on?
A promissory note and a contract.
This is loan sharking.
The law won't protect it.
You borrow money, you pay it back.
Officer, we're not running a charity.
Wei Ming Zhen may be dead,
but her daughter has to pay it back, right?
They can repay the principal.
The contract says borrow one, pay back two.
That part doesn't count.
Loan sharking is a civil offense.
I can't detain you right now.
But while collecting illegal interest,
if you endanger their safety or property,
the police can punish you under the law.
What? Want to come back to the station with me?
Uncle Zhou.
You should go home.
You have my contact information.
I'm not going anywhere.
We'll work out a plan later and settle this.
But if you come back and cause trouble,
I won't go easy on you.
Get out of here.
Contact me.
Go.
You should've hit him!
It's all right now.
A senior family member needs to be present
during the cremation.
I need to go in.
Not until I saw her portrait just now
did it really feel like she was gone.
Miao Jing.
Don't force yourself.
These past two days,
I've kept thinking about the past.
About how she picked me up
from my aunt's place,
and ended my days of living off relatives.
She brought me to Teng City.
Then I met you.
She gave me a home.
She bought me dresses.
She packed eggs for me.
She bought me gold jewelry.
It feels like all I can remember
is the good in her.
The bad parts of her...
I seem to have forgotten them all.
Do you think she came to me
because she really missed me,
or because she needed me to handle all this?
Miao Jing.
We're all ordinary people.
It's normal to feel upset
when something like this happens.
It doesn't prove anything.
What happened before,
good or bad, is already in the past.
The joy.
The pain.
Don't force yourself to choose.
The family can place the burial items
in this box.
After cremation, it'll be returned
with the urn.
[Trolley Forward]
I never had the luck to change my fate.
But now I have the power
to show you what it's like
to have more money than you can spend.
This is for you.
Zhai. There's one more thing I need from you.
Help me see this path clearly,
so nothing goes wrong.
Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Liu sent word.
He says once this blows over, we can
officially start shipping early next month.
- It's just...
- Just what?
The police have been watching closely.
What happened in Lingang was so sudden.
Do you think
the police may have found out something?
Sorry, Mr. Zhang. I spoke out of turn.
Six years.
Zhou Kang An hasn't taken his eyes off us.
Right?
I'm used to it.
Zhai.
This time, I took the hit for you.
Now I don't owe you anything.
[Kuangxia Real Estate]
Let me tell you. I used to eat inside a tent.
Never on the roadside.
What the heck...
If Mr. Zhai were still around,
they wouldn't stand a chance.
Who knew I'd end up like this?
Eat up.
It's got dust on it. I'm not eating.
Tomorrow I'll find a storage place
and leave the ashes there for now.
Then over the weekend,
I'll check out the cemetery here.
No need to go to all that trouble.
The ashes can stay here for now.
What are your plans?
What else can I do? I still have to go to work.
Cen Ye is back. There's a lot to deal with.
Maybe you should head back first.
It's fine. Get some rest.
If anything comes up, call me anytime.
- I'll walk you out.
- No, I'll take a cab.
[Melatonin Tablets]
[5:00]
Therefore, based on our investigation,
the third-party partner represented by Liu
has questionable qualifications.
- They may have engaged in business misconduct.
- Sorry.
We know Mr. Liu's situation.
But those are all legacy procedural issues.
We can definitely settle this within the month.
Could Hongshen hold off
on reporting this for now?
I understand your concerns.
But the audit procedure--
If we could speed up this process,
would we still need to sit here and talk?
That isn't their call.
Let's keep going.
I'll explain the details to you later.
This isn't part of your job, is it?
Let's keep going.
Okay.
Are things at home still difficult?
No. It's mostly taken care of.
You can take a few days off and get some rest.
No need. If there's nothing else for me to do,
I'll get going.
[Teng City Teng'an Cemetery]
[About Teng City Teng'an Cemetery]
You haven't been eating properly lately.
Cold drinks are hard on your stomach.
Have something warm.
You're not working overtime this weekend,
are you?
Why?
I booked the tickets.
I'm taking you out for a change of scenery.
Where to?
Jiang City.
- If you don't want to go--
- Let's go.
Come in.
Bin.
I'd like to take a couple of days off.
I'll make sure someone watches the route.
The emergency plans are all in place, too.
As long as work is covered.
Just don't drop the ball elsewhere.
Go ahead.
I'll be gone for a few days.
Keep an eye on Zhang Bin's people.
[Message, Uncle Zhou]
Mr. Zhang. The site is causing trouble again.
They even put up banners
and tried to protest downstairs.
It's been handled.
They were acting on impulse.
If loyalty could put food on the table,
he wouldn't be here causing trouble.
Remember this.
Never be the kind of person
who is blindly loyal
but not very bright.
Why does Chen Yi take a personal leave now?
Didn't you just see him?
Wasn't he supposed to lead the convoy
on the site visit?
And he just walks out now?
Just the opposite.
This is the perfect opening to draw him away.
This way.
I checked.
This bus route is the same one you took
when you first came to Teng City.
Only it gets there an hour earlier.
We'll arrive this afternoon.
Give me the bag.
After all, she was the one who brought me here.
Passengers for Jiang City,
line up here for ticket check.
Any passengers for Jiang City?
Anyone else for Jiang City?
Over there is fine too.
Both ticket gates are open.
Keep your hands to yourself.
How was I supposed to know
you'd bring an urn on the bus?
That is seriously bad luck.
Make way.
Sir, let go.
What is going on?
He was going through my bag.
I caught him red-handed.
I didn't.
Your identification and tickets, please.
Documents.
Okay. Let me find them.
Stop right there.
Trying to run? Stop. Come with us.
First thing in the morning,
I run into two people off to a funeral.
- Watch your mouth.
- What a nightmare.
Move.
What kind of people are they?
Seriously.
They even brought an urn with them.
What terrible luck.
[Teng City to Jiang City]
It's too crowded in there. I'll hold it.
You got up early. Get some sleep.
I'll wake you when we arrive.
You're awake.
Did you sleep well?
Very well.
Then this pillow could fetch a good price.
A really good price.
Have something to eat.
What's wrong?
You're so good to me.
One sausage, and suddenly I'm good to you?
This is already great.
All right. I'll bring you more next time.
Jiang City is huge.
We're almost there.
Does any of it look familiar?
I was too little when I came here.
I don't remember any of it.
Then I'll scout the way.
The exit is over there.
Slow down.
Need a taxi? Taxi rides here.
- Don't rush.
- Taxi!
Handsome guy, pretty lady.
Need a ride? Where are you headed?
- When was this place renovated?
- About five years ago.
I thought you were tourists.
You're locals? Back visiting family?
I stayed here for a while as a kid.
Can we go to Nanshan Cemetery?
Nanshan Cemetery is pretty far.
But don't worry.
We're not picky. We'll go anywhere.
Need a private ride?
Do you want to see your relatives here?
No. I only have an aunt here.
When I was little, my mother dumped me on them.
But they didn't want me either.
So to Wei Ming Zhen and to me,
they were never family.
Then it's better not to see them.
What made you decide
to come to Jiang City with me?
You went straight back to work
as soon as you returned.
Getting out for a while will do you good.
Besides,
everyone deserves to return home in the end.
You haven't slept well
these past few days, have you?
Bringing Wei back can put your mind at ease.
Thank you.
Don't be silly.
This is the burial plot you reserved.
It's quiet here, with a wide-open view.
The cemetery facilities are also very complete.
From custom headstones
to routine cleaning and upkeep,
we provide all maintenance services.
So you don't have to worry about that.
We'll seal the grave now.
Family members, please step back.
My condolences.
We'll get going.
In a way, she came home in the end.
Came home in the end.
[Beloved Mother Wei Ming Zhen]
[Erected by her devoted daughter, Miao Jing]
When I was little, I lived here.
It always snowed here in winter.
The snow would be ankle-deep.
In Teng City, winter was just endless rain.
So when I first moved there, it felt strange.
Why didn't they have winter there?
When I lived here,
winter was my favorite season.
In winter,
I could sneak out and play in the snow.
And once winter came, New Year was almost here.
Every New Year,
the other kids
would get new clothes from their moms.
But I didn't.
I remember always sitting on my aunt's doorstep
watching and waiting,
waiting for my mom to come get me.
But she never came.
Then one day,
when she finally did,
she said to me,
"Jing, I'm taking you with me."
"We have a home now."
You have no idea how happy I was.
But then,
she left me somewhere else.
[Garden of Grace]
Chen Yi.
I really don't have a mom anymore.
I'm here.
[Garden of Grace]
[Little Alley Restaurant]
Maybe we should stay.
Wouldn't it be nice to live here?
We could.
Then tell me what I can do here.
Nothing, if you want.
So you're supporting me again?
I'm not. I couldn't afford you.
In Jiang City,
we could open a little shop like this.
Open 24 hours a day.
You'd take the day shift. I'd take nights.
In the storage room, we'd set up a little cot.
We'd save on rent.
And have three steady meals a day.
Sounds good.
But what about you?
You said before that paying for my education
was a long-term investment.
You said that I had to move to a better city
and find a good job.
If we just stay here and open a little shop,
wouldn't your investment be a bust?
Did I really say
something that awful back then?
You said plenty.
Then I really was a jerk.
[Little Alley Restaurant]
[Answer, Decline]
What a pretty lady and a handsome man.
Are you two here on your honeymoon?
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival in a few days.
Young man,
buy your beautiful wife a gold necklace.
It'd be so festive.
Do you like it?
Can we really afford to buy gold
for Mid-Autumn Festival...
Why ask your wife?
If you buy it for her, she'll be thrilled.
I'm not in charge of the money.
Of course.
Just let me know if you need anything.
- Okay, thanks.
- Sure.
Let's go.