( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Over not making
loan payments on time?
Nothing to worry about?
It's all right. I'll sort it out.
Save, I like you.
Alright, from now on,
we're growing our own vegetables.
You'll take turns watering them.
Deal?
- Deal.
Louder.
Hurry up.
Hurry, Mabel. Come on.
Just open it.
Let's start.
Hey Snow, hold on.
I'm still reading that page.
You're such a slow reader.
Done?
Okay, next page.
What are you doing here?
Oh, my dear.
- Grandpa.
You've gone too far.
Cute, isn't it?
Run, run.
Hey.
Kids.
Shh.
Don't tell anyone.
"Until the Time is Right."
Uhm.
Must I write this kind of thing?
Mmm.
A big shock right from page one.
Gets worse in the middle. Hmm.
Save, I like you.
Like me?
Yeah.
I like you too.
Why else have we been friends
since seventh grade?
No.
Not as a friend.
What do you mean?
Are you losing it?
I like you, Save.
More than a friend.
Be serious.
You messing with me?
I'm not.
Are you... rejecting me?
No.
I just don't know what I did
to make you feel that way.
I don't know.
I just like being around you.
And I started feeling like
I wanted to be with you.
At first, I wasn't sure.
Thought I was losing it,
like you said.
But now, I'm sure.
You're more than a friend to me.
But to me, you're not.
Huh.
I kind of figured.
So why bring it up?
Because I've been hiding it
for too long.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Save.
Can I ask you something?
Can you just...
forget what I said?
Pretend I never said it.
Can you do that?
I still want to be your friend.
How's that supposed to work?
"Guy: Home yet? I'm already home."
"Why not reading my texts?"
"Taking a dump?"
"Hahaha."
"The broad frame growls
with a fierce rumble"
"like a crack of thunder."
"Burning lips press
along every tender spot"
"of the slender form in his arms"
"before sliding up
to meet the ice-cold lips."
"Tongue slipping in
to taste the sweetness within."
"As the slender form cries out
as if drawing a final breath"
"the young alpha bends down
and bites the omega's neck"
"to bind the two of them
together, forever."
Whew.
The most incredible scene of passion
I've ever read.
Father, it's Mart.
Come in.
Father, we have a problem.
Something bad has happened.
What happened?
Media rot is dragging our society
into the gutter.
No wonder kids are going
off the rails everywhere.
Calm down.
Tell me again, what happened?
The kids were reading a BL novel.
Explicit stuff.
What?
Where did they get it?
From a friend at school.
Return it. No more reading it.
But why, Grandpa?
Everyone reads BL novels these days.
That's right. The world's opened up.
People need their daily
BL fix now, Director.
Daily BL fix.
What does that even mean?
BL fix means consuming gay content.
Because it's adorable.
- Adorable.
Uhm-hmm...
You certainly have
a way with words.
There are actually
a lot more, Grandpa.
We can teach you if you want.
That's enough.
This is getting out of hand.
I said do not read it.
The content is simply inappropriate.
How, Grandpa?
Are you against LGBTQ people?
I'm not against that.
And I don't think it's wrong.
What's wrong is its 18+ material.
Are any of you that old yet?
Age is just a number.
That's enough.
As far as I'm concerned,
you're still children.
You don't yet have
the judgment to know
what's appropriate and what isn't.
So don't let me catch you
sneaking off to read it again.
Understood?
- Yes.
Wait.
Am I reading this right?
Men can get pregnant?
That's shocking.
Father, it's me. Here to clean.
Ah... come in.
Dad.
Hehe.
You could've knocked.
Sorry, Dad.
The tap's broken. I need some cash
to buy a new one.
Again?
It's necessary, Dad.
Unless you want to
just leave it broken.
Hold on. Maybe it can be fixed.
Hmm?
- Um.
- Let's go.
Probably not, Dad.
We'll need a new one.
You never even try to fix things.
Go, go.
Save, pass it over.
Pass the ball. Come on.
Save.
Why didn't you pass to me?
I zoned out for a second.
Is that a braised egg?
I got no egg.
And we paid the same price.
- Oh-ho.
- What is this?
Here, take mine.
Hey, scoot over.
What? There are plenty of seats.
Oh, Save.
Pheem, going to Siam tonight?
Yeah.
I want to try
that place you showed me.
Oh, right. Yeah, sure.
Hey, I'm coming too.
Up to you.
What about me?
- You guys don't want me?
- Up to you.
Hey, what's the deal?
Just come with us.
I don't want you talking
behind my back.
I know you, always buying new parts.
If it can be fixed,
you should learn how to.
Oh, who could ever
match your skills?
That sounds a little sarcastic.
No. I genuinely mean it.
Think you can fix that now?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Oh, a delivery.
I'd better get back to work.
Carry on.
- Oui.
- Yes.
Were you in my room just now?
No, Director. What's wrong?
I can't find something.
You should ask Mart, Director.
I saw her go in to clean.
Not heading out?
It was canceled.
But what are you doing here?
Well...
looking for that thing
you borrowed from me.
- Borrowed.
- Hmm.
What did I borrow from you?
That thing.
Which thing?
How do you forget so fast?
The whole house is
losing their minds.
Forget it. I'm done talking.
If you find it, just return it.
Hmm?
Uh.
What did I borrow from him?
Father, I found this in your office.
Did the kids get another book?
- Huh.
- Well...
Nice disguise.
They thought we wouldn't catch on.
We can't let this slide.
A real punishment this time.
It's not necessary.
I'll talk to them.
Father, please don't.
If we're lenient, there's no telling
what they'll pull next.
We have to nip this in the bud.
Calm down. It's not
that big of a deal.
Ah... it is, Father.
Let it slide once,
and they won't stop there.
It's okay. Give that to me.
Is this a good idea?
It is.
I don't think it is.
- Trust me.
- Father.
Please don't.
Please.
Let me keep this.
This time I'll talk to them.
Whose book is this?
Admit it.
It's not mine, Mom.
- Not mine either.
- Not mine.
So that's how you're gonna play.
Ow... it isn't ours, Mom.
What's there to admit?
You're lying.
If it's not yours, then whose is it?
Who in this house
reads this kind of novel
besides you kids?
Own up.
Well... ahem. Mart.
Just let it go.
I cannot. This is serious.
They'll all go down the wrong path.
What wrong path?
It's just about two men in love.
It's full of dirty scenes.
And you're still kids.
So nobody's going to admit it?
It really isn't ours.
That's right.
Fine. In that case,
no dinner tonight.
- What?
Auntie Mart, it's not ours. Honest.
- That's not fair.
- Mom, come on.
Mart. Mart.
Ahem.
Come here.
What is it, Father?
Just come here.
What is this?
- Oh come on.
- That's so unfair, Auntie Mart.
Hold on.
If it's not ours,
then who does it belong to?
Yeah, whose book?
- Father.
- Hmm.
Please don't make this
harder for me.
I have to punish them.
That's enough. Leave them alone.
But they broke the rules.
Let it go this once.
What is going on?
This isn't like you at all.
It doesn't matter.
They are getting punished.
Mart. Mart.
That book is mine.
I'm sorry.
This book. It belongs to me.
Leave the kids out of it.
You don't have to go this far
to protect them.
I'm not protecting anyone.
It's really mine.
Uh... but how could it be yours?
Since when did you
even glance at this?
Well... I'm planning
to write a BL novel
to pay off the debt.
BL novel? What is it?
Come on.
It's boys' love romance novel.
You can't write that, Dad.
That's not you.
I can. I just need some practice.
Dad, a great writer like you,
taking on this genre?
People are really
into it these days.
And if it sells,
the money's decent.
Please don't, Dad.
There has to be a better way.
You haven't written a novel
in over thirty years.
You think you can just
pick it back up now?
I said I can, didn't I?
Just sell the place, Dad.
Sun, how did you know about this?
I told him.
Why did you?
He is his son and your kid brother.
He's family.
He has every right
to know what's going on.
Dad, if you really can't hold on,
I think...
you'd better sell the orphanage.
It'll relieve you of this stress.
I'm not selling.
Then you'll need to open up
for more donations.
Or reach out to former residents
with the means to help.
Anything that can cover the debt.
That could work.
We've never once told them
that we're struggling.
If we put the word out,
I'm sure they would want to help.
No.
They have their own lives now.
I've raised these kids
hoping to see them thrive.
Not to have them repay anything.
Grandmother, please sit down.
Come, come. Right there.
Dad, we can't just keep
going like this.
You must do something.
I'm working on it.
The bank won't wait for that.
Sun, don't push him like that.
I'm just laying out the facts.
Dad, I don't see any other way.
The best option now is to sell.
Plain and simple.
No.
Selling is not an option.
Why not?
You may eat.
All right. Enjoy.
Luang (honorific), sir.
What is it, Phi Boonma?
Could I trouble you
to keep an eye on Tone?
Just through the afternoon.
I'll pick him up
when I'm done with work.
My wife just passed.
There's no one to look after him.
Of course. I'll take care of him.
Thank you, Luang.
All right, Tone. Greet him properly.
Hmm.
Come, just in time for a meal.
Luang, the villagers
raised this sum.
Please keep it.
It's a lot of money.
I can't.
Please take it.
We understand your dedication
to care for these children.
We all want to do our part.
You could purchase
the adjoining land
and build a proper house for them.
So they don't have to
put up with cramped living.
Please accept it, Luang (honorific).
I don't know how to...
thank you on behalf of the children.
We're happy to support
your dedication.
I promise I will use this land
for the good of these children.
Always.
The land isn't ours to sell
because the villagers
donated their money
to find a home for children in need.
Selling it
would betray that purpose.
It's not for sale.
But that was so long ago, Dad.
The donors are all gone now.
I'm still here.
I will never compromise
my grandfather's vision.
Honestly, I don't agree
with selling it either.
Stay out of this, Sun.
We'll find our own way.
Then I have nothing more to say.
Thank you for coming.
I'll head out then. Back to work.
Bye, Dad.
That's Sun for you.
Nevertheless, keep this
from Save and Snow.
They'll only worry.
Don't get there. Come on, quick.
Save. Hey, Save.
Pass it over.
Save, pass. Come on.
Ow.
- Oh, come on.
- Aw.
- What?
- Hate the game, guys.
Sorry.
- Unbelievable.
- Let's go. Go.
Try harder.
Nice. Jang, that was nice.
- Heh.
- Enough.
Dude, it wasn't my fault.
Hey.
- Ron.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Ron, you gaming tonight?
Sure, nine o'clock, yeah?
- Don't go dark on us again.
- He will.
All the time, this guy.
Never.
- Never what?
- Never?
- Haha.
So stuffed, man.
Yeah, up to here.
Can't do soccer now. Too full.
- So full.
- Still full.
Ugh.
- Hey, Jang, Pheem, free tickets.
- You got them?
- Hold on.
- Free to what?
Go ask him.
We need to talk.
I want to go to class.
Class? You?
Yeah.
Just talk to me.
Come on.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
You're not yourself.
I am myself.
You said you wouldn't act weird.
You think it's that easy?
Us the way we were?
After you told me you liked me?
You hate me now?
No.
I make you feel uncomfortable?
Huh.
Fine. I'm sorry.
I told you, stop apologizing.
This is on me.
I ruined everything.
From now on, I won't be around you.
Whew.
"1"
Oh, hi.
Hey, Save. Humor me this.
What's it like
when a boy likes another boy?
What kind of question is that?
Well, I'm writing a BL novel.
- Ha? A BL novel?
- Yeah.
You got nothing else?
I just want to try.
Help me out a little.
Tell me how it feels
when two boys like each other.
Oy, you got the wrong boy.
How should I know?
I'm not into boys.
Ow, you're a teenager.
Some of your friends
may be like that. Right?
None. Just don't write it, Grandpa.
Drop it. Quit.
You can't pull off a BL novel.
Huh.
Why got mad?
Okay.
Yeah, good.
Mart, I don't think
Dad can write that novel.
Hmm. That's what I figured.
So what do we do then?
Hmm.
We could try selling something.
Who's got money in this economy?
Well.
We gotta come up with
things they want to buy.
Like what?
Help me think.
I'm helping and thinking.
Even if we figure it out,
who knows if we can make them?
That's the question.
Oh, Grandmother.
Oh, stop, stop.
Hmm. You're at it again.
Sanae Chan, The Royal Recipe.
Phi Sorn. Phi Sorn.
Yeah? What is it?
Hmph. Are you deaf?
Didn't you hear me?
Grandmother, thank you.
You really came through for us.
Thank you.
What?
Oh, now it just clicks.
Dad used to tell me
that when Grandmother was young,
she studied confectionery
at the palace.
These recipes are
over a hundred years old.
Ah-ha.
Now sift.
All right.
Oh, hmph.
Oh, no. Like this.
Just tap.
- I see.
- Be patient.
Or it'll be all over the place.
- Got it.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Phi Sorn.
- Hmm?
Okay. Put this in.
100 grams.
Hold on.
And this.
Now... mix well.
- Phi Sorn, nice color, see?
- Oh, wow.
- It's coming together.
- Yes, yes.
Get the tray.
Here.
Okay. Ready.
Twenty-three.
That's ten.
Here. Here.
- Nice, huh?
- Here...
Oh, forgive its shape for now.
Let's get the flavor right first.
Oh, no. Grandmother.
Huh.
Um. Didn't we get the right flavor?
I guess it's really bad
that she spits it out.
Oh, Phi Sorn.
I did say it tasted strange.
I will try again, Grandmother.
Hey, Guy.
- Guy.
- Oh.
Didn't he see me?
He saw me, yeah?
He looked right at me.
- He did.
- Yeah, man.
Uh... oops.
Phi Sorn, what a mess.
Um...
- Phi Sorn.
- It happens. No big deal.
- Be careful.
- I'll just try again.
- It's a big bowl there.
- I don't want to break the yolk.
Ugh.
- I'm trying, okay?
- Oh?
We haven't made any money yet.
- But eggs are out.
- Mom, Dad.
What is all this mess?
Your mom wants to
make sweets to sell.
What? Selling sweets?
That's food, right?
Aw... a little encouragement
would be nice.
I hope nobody gets food poisoning.
You. Wipe that off.
- There you go.
- Oh, Dad.
Here. Check this out.
Hehe.
Ugh.
Hmm.
Huh.
Hmm?
Is it good now?
- Heh.
- Ha!
We did it, Phi Sorn. We got it.
Eh-haha.
I did great.
Careful.
- Oh, wow.
- Wow.
Go ahead. Try some.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Slow down. Slow down.
No need to fight over them.
They're all good.
Heck. Heck.
Mom, what did you give us?
Dirt mixed with sugar?
Ow.
A sweet is supposed to be sweet.
If it's bland,
can you call it a sweet?
Let's go find some water.
Hmph.
Is it that bad?
Mm-hmm.
The kids just don't
have the palate.
Royal palace confectionery
isn't for everyone.
Hmph.
Really.
Have a taste, Khun (honorific) On.
Hmm.
Throat-burning sweet, Khun Mart.
Really?
It is.
I can't get it down.
Water...
Here, water. Water.
Can I be honest with you?
Yes, please. I need the feedback.
It's very rough going down,
Khun Mart.
It's sticky. Can't swallow it.
I'm sorry. I really can't take it.
Have some water.
So how is it?
Hmm. I think the recipe needs
a bit of tweaking.
Yeah...
You used to make sweets, Khun Phon.
Could you advise me?
Of course.
Hmm... have you ever tried
Japanese sweets?
The texture is much smoother.
And the sweetness isn't as sharp.
You can apply that to your recipe.
Really? How would I go about that?
Is something the matter, Grandpa?
Snow, will you read this?
What is it?
BL novel.
Ump...
You wrote this?
Mm-hmm.
Awesome. That's my grandpa.
Good.
"Hew"? What does it mean?
That word is pronounced "wae."
Hor-wor-ae, Wae.
What does it mean?
Your nagging tone
when you chew someone out.
Have they never
covered this in school?
No... never heard it before.
Is it even Thai?
See... that makes it fun.
You find it fun?
Hmm...
You wanna get AI to help?
Let who help?
AI.
It's an app on the phone.
Can I borrow your phone?
Thank you.
Hello.
"Hello. How can I help you today?"
Help me write a fun BL novel.
"What novel did you say?"
A gay novel.
"I'm sorry. You like gay content?"
Huh... no!
No. You don't understand me.
Good. Serves you right.
Ta-da.
Mabel and Yoyo are here
to give feedback today.
Mm-hmm.
This paragraph reads a lot like
"Sick Crush on My Senior."
That part is just like
"Phi Nuea, My Undoing."
Did you yoink from other novels?
What does yoink mean?
You lifted it
from someone else's work.
I didn't lift anything.
It's just that...
I had AI help me.
That's not okay, Grandpa.
Hmm?
"Guy: Home yet? Not reading
my texts? Taking a dump?"
"Save: Hey..."
Save.
Yeah?
Oh, whew.
Getting ready to be fried?
Not funny.
Fetch me field trip permission slips
from Grandpa's room
and hand them out to the kids.
Sure.
"Demand for Repayment
and Notice of Legal Action."
"Balance: 530 baht."
Told you it wouldn't work.
You complain a lot,
and it doesn't help anything.
It's the truth.
This kind of sweet is out of style.
All that money down the drain.
At least we tried
to save the house
from getting repossessed.
This place is home to these kids.
A lot of them
have nowhere else to go.
We're the only family they have.
Phi Save, play with us.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Hurry up.
Mm-hmm.
- Ball.
- Yeah, catch.
How are you, Jingjai?
Wanna play with your friends?
Come. I will take you.
That's it, sweetheart.
Your friends are drawing something.
Grandpa...
How's the novel coming along?
Snow read it. Not feeling it.
The boy-boy energy just isn't there.
Beats me. I've never once
been in love with a man.
And none of my friends
have ever been that way either.
Grandpa.
You think your BL novel
will pay off our debt?
What debt?
Grandpa, you don't have to
hide it from me anymore.
I know what's going on.
Don't sweat it.
Leave it to the adults.
Grandpa, I'm a grown-up now.
Just tell me.
You think your BL novel
will save this house?
Of course.
I am an award-winning writer,
you know?
It's just that
I still can't figure out...
what it actually feels like
when a man loves a man.
I know I can do it.
You just add them up.
That's how you get these values.
We talk.
What do you want?
I need to talk to you.
What more do you want from me?
I already backed away.
Guy.
How about we give this a try?
What? You're seeing a boy?
Hey, Grandpa.
Don't tell Mom and Dad.
Keep this between us.
When you held hands,
did your heart race?
Not at all. More like a jolt.
I can't write this.
I just... can't write this...
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together, day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?