( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 17=
Your Majesty.
- We're switched back.
- Yes.
It finally happened.
Seize all suspicious people
at the altar.
Put out the fire
and rescue Their Majesties.
Yes.
Well...
Make it quick.
As you command.
How dare you hurt my husband!
Let's go.
Jinming.
What should we do?
They will be fine.
Come here.
Jinyun, Xu Yu.
Jinyun.
Your Majesty.
What's wrong?
- Your Majesty.
- Jinyun.
Your Majesty.
- Summon the physician!
- Yes.
Your Majesty.
Xu Yu.
If you keep pretending to be asleep,
I'll go find Jiang Tang right now
and get you more medicine.
No need for that.
My medicine
has always been only you.
Are you alright?
Jiang Tang already told me.
Your Majesty is fine.
You want me to always stay by your side.
That's why you were pretending.
Your Majesty is overbearing,
telling me that even in my next life,
I can only be with you
and marry no one but you.
I remember someone used to say
that if I died,
she wouldn't live on alone.
I meant it.
I meant it as well.
Well...
You take the medicine,
and I'll always stay by your side, okay?
Excellent.
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
Where did you get this?
Jinming got it for you.
It's sweet.
How is it?
Sweet?
Not sweet at all.
Try it yourself.
♪The same joys and sorrows
can't be relived♪
It is sweet.
You just got bitter decoction.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
So sweet.
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
It was
a miraculous experience.
We actually switched our bodies back.
The Grand Preceptor said
that lightning strikes
could make unusual things happen.
We could switch our bodies back
not just because of the lightning,
but also because we had intimacy.
So, if I get tired of being the Emperor,
can I just have intimacy with you
to switch our bodies again?
Sure.
After Your Majesty
roots out the traitors,
you can do it if you want.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
Your Majesty.
What are your plans now?
I need to know
who is behind Tao Kan,
and more importantly,
how deeply involved Uncle is with Dada.
Also, I wonder whether Huna is involved.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
I know
you trust her.
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
I believe in Huna.
But I trust even more
that Your Majesty
will make the wisest choice.
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
Foolish!
Regicide gets the entire clan killed.
His Majesty will seize this chance
to settle accounts.
If he learns that Tao Kan came here...
Isn't usurping the throne
exactly what you desire?
Don't you know that once it's exposed,
our entire clan is doomed?
There's no turning back.
Since His Majesty
already knows what we're up to,
no need to pretend anymore.
What exactly do you want to do?
I'm helping you contend for the throne
against Xiao Jinyun.
To make it happen,
we must fight fiercely
to the death
and brace for a bloodbath.
Isn't that exciting?
You never intended
to help me seize power.
You just wanted to see Xiao Jinyun
and me fight each other.
I am your father!
So what?
Now, all guards and servants
in this mansion
are loyal to me.
I respected you in the past,
not because I feared you,
but because I was
used to wearing a mask.
I simply didn't want
to make things ugly.
You're unfilial!
I...
The throne you covet
has never interested me.
What I want is
to plunge this world into chaos.
Why can't I subvert the imperial power?
You must be crazy.
I promise
my actions will only grow more insane.
(Fengyi Palace)
Your Majesty.
These memorials require your review.
(I've returned to my original body.)
(Why do I still review them?)
Take these memorials to His Majesty.
I'm exhausted and need to rest.
These were personally selected
by His Majesty.
They pertain to the harem affairs.
They require the Empress's Seal.
No.
Take them away.
Or else, spar with me!
Who are you challenging?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why have you come?
We've switched our bodies back.
What brings you here then?
Previously, you and I
toiled day and night here.
We had good times.
So,
after taking advantage of me,
you're turning your back on me?
It seems your chamber
is truly off-limits to me.
Who took advantage of you?
Who used their own body
to kiss me first?
Alright.
I came to tell you
that I've handled these affairs
for you long enough.
Starting today,
you must review every memorial
that requires your approval.
There's one more thing.
I have a question.
What is it?
When you were in Dada,
did you use my body
to do anything improper?
Queen of Dada, Huna,
will arrive in the capital soon.
Really?
She just wrote to me a few days ago.
I didn't expect it so soon.
Fantastic.
Answer me!
Your Majesty, are you still bothered
about that love letter?
Huna
is a woman from the desert.
She is naturally passionate
and unrestrained.
It's merely a friendship between women.
I swear,
in my heart, there's only...
Only what?
Anyway, Dada's allegiance is good news.
I am happy for Your Majesty.
Long live the Chen!
Long live Xiao Jinyun!
All hail to you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty is famous
far and wide.
All in my nation revere you.
Thus, bearing
the sincerity of my people,
I came to present the credentials.
We wish for a lasting friendship
with Chen.
We'd like to make a contribution
to Chen.
The interaction between nations
resembles that between people.
Thank you,
Your Majesty, for keeping your promise.
I hereby make you Queen Dada.
Henceforth, our peoples
shall be forever connected.
From this day forward,
The Chen and Dada
shall be mutually dependent,
share weal or woe,
and strive for peace,
prosperity, and good governance.
- Strive for peace, prosperity,
- and good governance.
Queen Dada came all the way over here.
It shows true sincerity.
Let's drink.
Without Your Majesty,
there would be no me.
Without Chen, there would be no Dada.
To Your Majesty.
Please,
be seated.
Queen Dada.
How do you find the liquor
from the Central Plains?
It's fine liquor.
I merely wonder
if Your Majesty misses Dada's liquor.
Strong liquor deserves big bowls.
Where one drinks doesn't matter.
What matters is with whom one drinks.
Someone!
Bring big bowls.
Your Majesty.
Can you handle it?
Strong liquor.
Even you can drink.
How can I not?
Your Majesty is as forthright as ever.
Your Majesty.
I drink in your stead.
This concerns the dignity of the Chen
and the royal house.
More importantly, it's for you.
I did not misjudge you.
Bottoms up.
- Good friendship.
- Eternal legacy.
To the friendship of Chen and Dada.
Fill it up.
(Again?)
This liquor is like water.
Come on.
Let us all drink together.
Your Majesty.
I'm in high spirits.
Again!
(In the desert, he never got drunk.)
(How come he seems drunk
after just a few bowls?)
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪