( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 18=
Again.
Again!
Your Majesty.
His Majesty has things to do later.
I shall drink with you now.
Thank you for coming.
I once heard from His Majesty
that you're an excellent woman.
Indeed, seeing is believing.
When it comes to drinking,
I like the way your people drink.
They drink heartily.
I heard from His Majesty
that you have great military abilities.
I guess your martial arts must be good.
Of course.
Women of Central Plains also possess
loyal hearts to defend our homeland.
Sit still.
Impressive.
- Impressive.
Fantastic!
Impressive!
Impressive.
(Xu Yu can both
wield a sword and drink.)
(Even her behavior is no different
from before.)
(In contrast, Xiao Jinyun
has reverted to his previous demeanor.)
(Could it be that the incident
at the altar)
(helped switch their bodies back?)
You mean
the Emperor of Chen values scholarship
and knows nothing of martial arts?
Yet the Empress
is the daughter of a general
and knows martial skills?
Exactly.
(Not just sword dancing,)
(even the way she drank is identical.)
(Can there truly be two people
whose behaviors are so similar?)
(Or perhaps...)
Your Majesty.
Queen Dada requests a meeting.
Huna?
Let her in.
Yes.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I'm here
to thank Your Majesty for exempting Dada
from tribute for three years.
Since we are allies,
no need to thank me for that.
Indeed.
After all, when you were in Dada,
Your Majesty guaranteed
that if Dada is in a crisis,
no matter when,
you will come to help.
Of course.
Since that is the case,
I have another request.
Speak plainly.
I wish to see the Majesty again
that I encountered in the desert.
You invited me to watch the flowers.
Yet you are not here.
Queen of Dada?
What brings you here?
I asked His Majesty to arrange this.
Why?
I wasn't sure
if I should invite His Majesty,
or Her Majesty,
whom I met in the desert.
How did you know?
I consulted our shaman.
Soul Silk is a treasure of Dada.
And the witchcraft is unique to Dada.
Coupled with your martial arts
and drinking habits,
I deduced that your bodies were swapped.
Since you already know...
Don't worry.
The people of Dada
will always be your friends.
Wonderful!
You're not even angry?
What's so great about Huna?
His Majesty is actually enchanted
by that seductress!
(They are hugging)
(and smiling so sweetly.)
It's a load off my mind.
From now on,
we can speak freely just like before.
Okay.
That's it.
You're doing much better than I did.
Such a large garden.
If it's filled with flowers in spring,
it must be like a paradise on earth.
These plants are deliberately planted
and can't compare to those
in Moon Valley.
Does it hurt?
When I first learned,
I got pricked many times a day.
It's fine.
Giddy up!
May our friendship last forever.
(Your Majesty.)
(You've never been this thoughtful
towards me.)
One, two, three, go.
Well done.
Don't move.
Good.
Go on.
One, two, three.
What are you doing here?
And what about you?
Must I explain to you?
You look suspicious.
You must be up to no good.
(Xu Yu.)
(You've been pretending for so long.)
(Still not satisfied?)
(Drop the act!)
Consort Zhao.
Consort Zhao, what brings you here?
I wish
to get close to Your Majesty's friends.
You also know martial arts?
Come on.
Consort Zhao,
are you alright?
won't you stay longer?
Try it. This is the best liquor
in our palace.
How is it?
Chen's wine is good
but somewhat mild.
The strong liquor is spicy,
intense, and direct,
while the mild one
is refined
and not bland,
with a long, clean finish
and balanced flavors.
Each has its merits.
It's just a matter of personal taste.
But I think you suit the strong liquor.
You suit the boundless grasslands,
instead of being trapped
by the palace walls.
You shouldn't waste energy
on being envied.
As the Empress,
I willingly wish to assist His Majesty.
As a wife,
I love my husband wholeheartedly.
After parting,
I dreamed of coming to Chen.
I'm grateful for helping me
reclaim the throne.
Unexpectedly, he is the Emperor.
These past few days, I've sensed it.
He's been secretly watching us.
Truly petty.
Listen, he's not really like that.
He's just naturally cautious.
He doesn't yet trust or know you well.
Xu Yu is right.
I truly don't know you well.
But can you give me a chance?
I believe
drinking capacity isn't key,
but one should know how to accept,
wake up to reality, and reflect.
Coincidentally, I know all these.
Come on, drink.
So this is Your Majesty's intention.
But persistence and resolve
are also crucial.
Drink up.
Excellent.
What a coincidence.
Let's eat together.
Come on.
Another cup.
(Why are they competing like this?)
Why must you drink?
I can drink.
Over here.
I'll get you some water.
Every time you're drunk, you kiss me.
Xu Yu,
if I could always kiss you,
I would rather
stay drunk forever,
and never sober up again.
Xiao Jinyun,
you are actually making me shy.
I can give up anything for you.
I never regret it.
All I hope is to stay with you.
Alright.
Enough.
Stop talking.
Xu Yu,
I said every word
from the bottom of my heart.
I'm serious.
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪All who believed love would never fade♪
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
♪Like a song, like a dream, like a play♪
♪This life is but a solitary boat♪
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
Your Highness.
It's a letter from Dada.
Water and fire suppress each other.
Yin and Yang merge.
Souls return to their places.
(My guess was right.)
(Xu Yu has returned.)
(And Xiao Jinyun wishes for peace.)
(So I can't let him get his wish.)
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪