( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 20=
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
It's so hard to survive the harem.
The Empress Dowager pressures us
to have an heir.
The Empress forces us to exercise.
But I haven't
even touched His Majesty's hand.
Back when His Majesty favored me,
he summoned me very often.
His Majesty did touch my hand.
I'm so envious.
I want that too.
But you and His Majesty
slept in separate beds.
What nonsense!
I thought I was unlucky,
assuming His Majesty just preferred you.
So you also noticed
that His Majesty has feelings for me?
Then... why?
Could it be
because His Majesty is impotent?
His Majesty has never slept in my place.
Yeah.
Shut up! Do you want to die?
His Majesty is healthy. Very healthy.
What's going on?
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I was praising
how strong His Majesty is.
Your Majesty.
See how well we've been training.
Then, you shall hold your horse stance
for an extra hour today.
Yes.
(Although I wish
Xiao Jinyun would only be with me,)
(Zhao Qiluo
and the others are innocent.)
(Should they be forced
into lifelong loneliness?)
I knew I'd find you here.
I can relax a bit
only when I'm with you.
You must have heard
about the situation outside.
It's sort of a state affair,
causing quite the stir.
I've heard about it.
They all have their eyes fixed
on my harem,
eager to have my heir come
from their own clan,
so they can partake in the royal power.
So, who in this court can I trust?
Your Majesty,
I can fight on the battlefield.
I also won't fear facing your subjects.
No matter what happens,
I will stand by your side.
Xu Yu.
They are pressuring me to depose you
and expand the harem.
As the Empress,
are you truly not jealous?
Who says I'm not?
It's just that...
They are right on some points.
So you mean I should
restart the concubine selection?
Xiao Jinyun.
We have no doubts about each other
and can face it together.
But I think
Consort Zhao and the others
haven't done anything wrong.
Must they be trapped
and wither away in the palace?
I wish to request that once Your Majesty
roots out the treacherous officials,
could you please
seriously consider their future?
No worries,
I have a plan for this matter.
Anyway,
I have something more important
to do with you right now.
What is it?
Xu Yu, how about you bear me a child?
What are you talking about?
Xu Ziping,
based on the Three-Pillar Method,
invented the Four-Pillar Method.
Interesting.
Your Highness, you...
Since Queen of Dada has left,
Jinyun should be able to sleep soundly.
As for me, I can finally get some rest,
no more being a spy and tracking her.
Your Highness.
If you are tired,
you can return to your place
and rest properly.
You're mistaken.
I'm in high spirits right now,
free from official duties.
I feel so good.
Have you heard?
His Majesty argued
with the subjects in court again.
He said there will be
no more concubine selections.
He will only have the Empress's child.
Then what about us?
Xu Yu is such a vixen.
Does she want
to have His Majesty to herself?
Exactly.
Now the Empress Dowager pressures us
to bear children. But how?
Actually, as long as they don't
lower our ranks or allowances,
I find the life here agreeable.
That's what you think.
His Majesty...
His Majesty once held me.
He held her.
I don't believe Xu Yu has His Majesty
to herself forever?
Everyone arrived quite early today.
- Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Your Majesty.
We've been practicing the moves
you taught us.
We've improved a lot.
Well done.
Today, we'll learn a new move.
Consort Zhao,
let's demonstrate it for everyone.
Shall we show everyone an example?
Okay.
Turn right, dodge.
Well done.
Your turn.
Good.
- Your Majesty.
- It wasn't me.
- I didn't even touch her!
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Jiang Tang, what's wrong?
Your Majesty, congrats!
Her Majesty is pregnant.
What?
Really?
Physician Jiang.
Is she truly pregnant?
I'm very sure.
This time, she truly is pregnant.
Heaven blesses us!
I will soon have a grandchild.
I'm already pregnant?
Someone, assist me to the prayer hall!
I must pray for Xu Yu
and the child she is carrying.
Mother,
the Directorate of Astronomy
will do that.
My grandchild deserves my personal care.
You stay with Xu Yu
and do not upset her.
Yes, Mother.
Xu Yu, rest well.
Yes.
Mother.
Let me help you.
Stop staring at me.
What are you doing?
I want some water.
I'll get it.
No need.
I'm not that fragile.
This isn't about fragility.
You're pregnant now.
Take care not only of yourself
but also of our child.
Xu Yu, thank you.
For giving me another family
in this world.
From now on, I will protect you both.
We've bought the supplements,
but without the jade
for the expectant Empress.
But with so many jade shops
on this street,
which one should we choose?
Your Highness,
Her Majesty's element is metal.
Today, the southeast is most auspicious.
Coral and tourmaline
are her lucky stones.
But there are no gold shops
to the southeast.
I also want to buy a longevity lock
for my future nephew.
May he live a long, healthy life.
Your Highness.
Longevity locks are usually gifts
from elders.
So what? I am an elder.
He will be my closest nephew.
He deserves the best.
Your Highness likes children?
Of course!
They're small, soft,
and smell nice. So adorable!
Today, you all came specifically
to congratulate me on my pregnancy
with precious gifts. I am deeply moved.
I hope you all can enjoy yourselves.
- Thanks, Your Majesty.
Take it.
It's yours.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
My mother is unwell and unable to come.
She sent me in her stead.
This is a top-grade red coral bracelet.
May it bring you peace and joy
wherever you are.
Thank you so much.
Your Majesty!
Xu Yu!
Virtuous Consort.
Your Majesty.
Summon Jiang Tang!
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Virtuous Consort is injured.
And Xiao Jinle.
Thanks to him,
Virtuous Consort and I were saved.
It was an honor
to protect Your Majesty.
Miss Sun, Count Cheng'en's daughter?
Why did you attempt to assassinate me?
A poison in her mouth.
She killed herself.
Your Highness.
Virtuous Consort.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪