( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 19=
Greetings, Queen of Dada.
Please be seated.
What brings you here?
We seek to collaborate with you
to overthrow the imperial power.
This would be a great benefit for Dada.
Previously, you conspired
with my brother to harm me.
And now you want to cooperate with me?
Do you take us for fools?
My father promised to offer your brother
three cities after seizing the throne.
I offer five cities.
My father has petitioned to retire
due to illness.
His Majesty has approved his petition,
and I now handle affairs in his stead.
Currently,
I'm in charge.
It's indeed a good offer.
Unfortunately, I am not interested.
You may take your leave.
What if I offer five more cities?
You are well-learned.
You must have heard this saying.
"How can a square peg fit a round hole?
How can
those on different paths coexist?"
I didn't expect you
to be so well-versed in literature.
In that case,
you may state any additional demands.
Dada is remote, with scant troops.
Therefore, every citizen is a soldier.
But it's just to defend our homeland.
We hope for peace.
Yet you
seek to exploit Dada to restart the war
and help you seize the throne.
I can also bring you peace.
You don't bring peace.
You just grant peace.
I do not trust you.
Finally caught you.
Huna did meet with Xiao Jinle.
I must let Jinyun know.
Jinming.
What a coincidence meeting you here!
Would you like me
to show you around the capital?
No need.
However,
I hope you can pass a message
to your brother.
One.
Two.
Hard!
Hold on!
I've reviewed your medical records.
Each of you is exceptionally frail.
Martial training
can strengthen your body.
Your Majesty, we are imperial consorts.
We serve His Majesty.
How can we possibly
manage martial training?
Her Majesty is right.
To serve His Majesty,
we must be physically fit.
I find Your Majesty is
particularly reasonable.
I learned it
after watching it just once.
Look.
One.
Two.
Well done, but...
Look.
Exert a force on the waist.
Tighten up.
Well done.
Look, all of you learn
from Consort Zhao.
Well done, Consort Zhao. Take a break.
Yes.
I had Xuan prepare cooling tea
for everyone.
Everyone, come have some.
This is delicious.
I love it, Your Majesty.
We've worked so hard.
Yet we only have a cup of green tea.
Only when parched
does one know water's sweetness.
Only when starving
does one know rice's fragrance.
The hardship you endure now
lays the foundation for your future.
Her Majesty is right.
Huna, what brings you here?
Those who exercise have firm muscles
and move agilely.
They're less likely to get sick
and remain composed in danger.
Knowing some martial arts
is better than being at others' mercy.
I'm returning home tomorrow.
I came specifically to bid you farewell.
You're leaving tomorrow?
In Dada, every citizen is a soldier.
Even my handmaids
can kill wolves barehanded.
You should be grateful
that you have a good Empress.
Otherwise,
when armies besiege your city,
you will be helpless.
Let's spar again.
That's all for today.
You may go back and rest.
Let's go.
No need.
Your Majesty.
Go ahead.
I will ensure they practice diligently
and never give up.
You will continue? That's very good.
Let's go.
It's been so long since I met someone
who can ride horses with me.
Riding and shooting arrows with you
reminded me of our days fighting
against the enemy in Dada.
But I feel you've improved
since then.
Our people are skilled at riding
and shooting arrows.
I am the Queen,
so naturally, I'm even more skilled.
What is this?
A gift.
This is...
Its name is Aqi. It's a gift for you.
When you need me,
no matter where I am, Aqi can find me.
Really?
Aqi.
Next spring,
come to Dada.
The tastiest meat, the strongest liquor,
and the fastest horse
will be yours.
I will keep my promise.
No matter how far, I will come to you.
See you then.
Aqi, so cute!
Aqi, my name is Xu Yu.
Wintersweet blooms in snow.
The stove fire warms a cold night.
This is Huna's riddle.
Yes, Jinyun.
Huna is quite cunning and scheming.
I fear their meeting today
was to plan something.
About what?
Xu Yu.
Try these.
Xu Yu, you know what?
Today I saw Xiao Jinle meeting
with Huna.
They talked for a long time.
Xiao Jinle allied with her brother
to seize her throne.
How could she possibly
cooperate with him?
Besides, I trust Huna.
Being wary matters.
But I feel the truth may not be so.
Otherwise, Huna
wouldn't have left you this riddle.
What riddle?
I know.
Wintersweet blooms in snow.
The stove fire warms a cold night.
Right?
Huna, did you enjoy your time in Chen?
Your Majesty sends me off so early.
It seems you truly dislike me.
Your Majesty, are you afraid
that I will steal your Empress?
Of course not. I should thank you.
After all, because of your arrival,
I've become determined.
I'll devote myself wholeheartedly
to Xu Yu.
I won't give anyone an opportunity.
Good luck then, Your Majesty.
It's getting late.
Take care, Your Majesty.
Take care.
Huna.
This is for you.
You're skilled with scimitars
and surely like this.
Thank you. I like it very much.
That's good.
Remember our promise.
I'll wait for you in Dada.
I'll miss you.
Safe journey!
Goodbye, Huna.
I often wonder
what it feels like to drink
and ride freely in the desert.
Could you describe that feeling
to me in detail?
Hearing others describe is boring.
Your Majesty should feel it yourself.
I can escort you there. What do you say?
Okay. Next spring,
I will definitely travel there.
(Tea)
I wonder why you have asked me to come.
Jinyun and Xu Yu
once switched their bodies.
You must be aware of it.
Last time, I made myself very clear.
I do not trust you.
So naturally, we won't cooperate.
(She's so calm,
so she must have known long ago.)
Follow your heart and ask yourself.
Will the Emperor's promise
remain forever unchanged?
Can the contract last forever unbroken?
If you have even a trace of doubt,
please hedge your bets.
It might not be a bad choice.
All we want is Dada's cooperation
on the border.
For you, it would be effortless.
Alright.
I will consider it carefully.
(Presented to Princess's Palace)
You submitted 318 memorials,
all urging me to have an heir.
Do you think
I won't punish you all?
Your Majesty, it's the people's will.
Moreover, Your Majesty has been married
to Her Majesty for years.
Yet she has not conceived.
Such a thing has never occurred
in Chen before.
We are anxious and worried.
We hope Your Majesty will understand.
Jinle, you are my cousin.
Will you also
meddle in my private affairs?
As your liege, I know the boundaries.
I have only two wishes.
Your Majesty will have children,
and our nation will become prosperous.
Well said!
I've heard that Your Majesty
often stays in Fengyi Palace
and rarely sees other concubines.
This is probably improper, isn't it?
Your Majesty is the ruler of the nation.
How can you value your romantic love
over offspring?
Are you going
to control which woman I see?
However, we heard
Her Majesty has never conceived.
We are deeply concerned.
Her Majesty
has difficulty having children.
How dare you!
How dare you judge Her Majesty!
Your Majesty,
a woman who cannot bear children
is considered an ill omen
even among the common people.
How much more so
for the Empress of a nation?
I beg Your Majesty
to restart the concubine selection,
as the imperial lineage is paramount.
Otherwise, you should
appoint a better person as the Empress.
- We beg you, Your Majesty,
- to put the nation first
- and continue the imperial lineage.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪