( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 24=
Prince Ning spreads lies
to usurp the throne!
Seize him!
Jinyun, leave our uncle to me.
Time to settle our scores.
Xiao Jinyun, I'm your opponent.
You imprisoned Xu Yu in the palace.
You caused her death.
Today, I will avenge her.
Xu Yu is here, at your service!
No one noticed, right?
No one noticed.
Not even His Majesty.
But...
Why keep it from even His Majesty?
I didn't.
I left him a letter.
The Grand Preceptor would hint to him.
(Xiao Jinyun, I finally tricked you.)
(I'm not going to die.)
(Jiang Tang got the herbs Jinming found)
(and developed the antidote first.)
(Now, the situation
in the palace is a deadlock.)
(One of us must break it.)
(I am the member of Xu family
and your wife.)
(Whether it's the empire,)
(the Emperor,)
(or my husband,)
(it is my duty to save them all.)
(That's why I staged this act)
(to deceive everyone)
(and leave Chen and join the Xu army.)
(Now, let Prince Ning
and his cohorts come out)
(and crush them at a time.)
Your Majesty.
Those two are gone.
How's it going?
Her Majesty and Huna
will follow your orders
and arrive on the day of the rite.
You lowlifes dare dream
of shaking Chen Empire?
Soldiers!
Seize the traitors!
Kill the rebels!
Xu Yu.
You're back.
I was careless.
You faked your death.
With villains like you still at large,
how could I possibly die?
His Majesty set this trap
just to expose
your vicious ambition to the world.
Xiao Jinyun.
I don't believe in Heaven's pity.
I only believe in our unwavering love.
My husband will be protected by me.
You infected the city for selfish gain!
Thanks to the antidote,
the people are safe.
My two brothers
have blocked your remaining mercenaries
outside the walls.
Prince Ning, if you don't surrender now.
I will execute you immediately
for those innocent lives.
A sacrifice to the people.
Don't celebrate too soon.
The armies of the Prince of Luoyang
and Prince of Zhennan will arrive today.
You still can't hold the capital.
Is that so?
Marshal Xu's victory report!
Working with Dada,
they crushed the barbarians.
The Prince of Luoyang and the Prince
of Zhennan returned to their domains.
How can this be?
The reason I stand here today
is not just the Xu army
guarding our empire,
but countless soldiers
who yearn for peace
and fear no death,
and our people who cherish every day
even in the simplest of lives.
Isn't a ruler yearning for
the people's peace and prosperity
and a world without war?
So, you will lose.
Xiao Jinyun!
10 years ago, I didn't seek
power against you.
Your father killed
my wife's family on false charges.
I begged him desperately,
but he still killed them.
Now, taking his son's life is only fair!
If anyone is wrong, it's you!
You wronged me first!
Absurd!
You and they clearly
fought for the throne.
Now, things happened,
and you wash your hands clean.
Pitiable is Princess Ning's family.
Each was loyal and righteous.
Not one named you, even in death.
But they faced extermination.
Your ambition killed them!
Y-You're twisting the truth!
Your letter of repentance
to my father is still here.
It clearly states you were coerced
by treacherous individuals
and were completely unaware.
Doesn't your conscience
trouble you even now?
Xiao Jinle!
Insane. You killed your father.
And now, you're laughing?
I got my revenge right this time.
Shouldn't I be laughing?
Xu Yu.
Back then, you saved me.
I vowed to rescue you
from this gilded cage of a palace.
I thought you were dead,
so I planted explosives here.
Today, no matter who sits on the throne,
everyone here must die!
They will all join you in death!
But now, you're alive.
We shall go to die together!
If we cannot live together,
we shall die together.
You're wrong.
No one will die today,
except you all.
Your Majesty,
all explosives here have been removed.
All is safe.
Another traitor.
Xiao Jinyun!
Do you think this was my only plan?
(As long as I kill
the Grand Preceptor of Chen,)
(the entire palace
will fall under my sorcery.)
Evil sorcery.
Your death won't be mourned.
Don't dirty
my place.
You small fry!
Her Majesty set the trap long ago,
just waiting
to catch you all!
Your Highness,
did we truly defend
Ci'an Palace on our own?
Of course!
We have trained in martial arts!
We are formidable!
Your Majesty,
I have fulfilled my duty.
I held the harem for you.
If you think you've sent men
to attack Ci'an Palace
and that the women
of the harem are all weak,
you are wrong again!
And you'll pay the price
for your actions!
His Majesty has decreed
to restore the consorts' freedom.
They will be returned
to their families as imperial sisters,
and they may marry as they wish.
Their Majesties
will see them wed with princess rites.
With such favorable terms,
why aren't you leaving?
You're no different.
You don't return.
What?
Still hoping His Majesty will favor you?
I am now a Female Secretary
personally appointed by His Majesty!
Her Majesty secured this for me.
I now manage palace affairs.
In the future, I will assist Her Majesty
in selecting female officials.
From now on, female officials
in Chen can also serve in government.
Men? Who needs them?
My father will need me
to bring honor to our family soon!
Dear,
how about giving me
a palace official position?
How about we build our careers together?
That's it!
The other feudal lords
did not object to confiscating
Prince Ning's estate.
The Chen Empire
now enjoys internal stability.
The northwest is pacified.
Huna is spreading
your majesty far and wide
to cow the tribes.
Now, the borders are secure.
Xu Yu.
We met as kids.
If I hadn't kept my distance back then
and instead remained close with you,
the court wouldn't have stood
for our marriage,
let alone making you the Empress.
What do you mean?
I mean,
if we had always been a loving couple,
the court would have viewed you
and your family as an eyesore.
I did not want that.
Are you saying...
I mean,
I might have started
paying attention to you in secret
when I first knew you.
Later, when you came to my palace
to see me time and again,
I became even more certain
that I liked you.
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
Xu Yu,
I treated you badly before.
I wish to spend this life making amends
and grow old together with you.
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
I wish
to grow old with you too.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪All who believed love would never fade♪
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
With a wife like you,
how could my empire not be secure?
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
♪The same joys and sorrows
can't be relived♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
Celebrating six years
of the imperial marriage.
May your bond stay eternal,
and may the Chen Empire flourish
for all ages!
- Flourish
- for all ages!
Everyone,
rise.
- Thank you.
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪
Bound as husband and wife.
No doubt in us.
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
♪Like a song, like a dream, like a play♪
(The end)
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪