( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
"I used to be just an ordinary girl."
"So plain that I couldn't be any plainer."
"Until I realized that, actually,"
"anyone can become beautiful."
"If you choose to invest in yourself completely."
"I no longer thought of myself as ordinary."
"I found out that, in fact,"
"you can be someone special, if you're willing to pay enough."
Let me borrow this, Dad.
Hello, you must be Nano.
Please take a seat and wait a moment.
It looks good. I'll come back to do it again.
Sure, please come again.
Will do.
The one I mentioned is a keratin treatment.
It'll help reduce frizz.
Thank you.
Thank you. See you.
So, is there any specific part you're concerned about today?
My cheeks.
I want my face to look smaller and firmer.
Hello.
Did you manage to grab it?
I got it.
I couldn't get it.
Oops, that's too bad.
But it's okay, I'll bring it for you to see.
She's so cute.
So pretty, right?
Yeah, really pretty.
Nano, I'm heading out now.
Hey, sis!
What?
Can I borrow some cash?
How much?
500?
5,000.
5,000? Aren't you spending way too much lately?
Stop complaining. I really need it.
It seems like you always "really need it."
Fine, I'll transfer it to you.
Once you get paid for your modeling gig, pay me back.
I will. Thanks!
Yeah.
"I've realized that making money"
"isn't actually that hard after all."
[Dream, Room A: Nano, no need to rush paying it back.]
Dan.
Can I borrow a hundred thousand baht?
[Dan: For you, Nano, always.]
"I can never go back to being ordinary again."
We are definitely not losing today.
If we do it just like how we practiced, we'll win for sure.
Come on. One, two, three.
Hey!
Good luck, you two.
Nano, have you seen this?
What is it?
[#FakeRichGreenCheerleader #APT]
[Owes almost 80k in total to the whole school.]
If she owes you, go get it back before it's too late.]
[That's just in school. Who knows who else she borrowed from outside.
Looking rich with other people's money lol]
[Is Nano cosplaying as a beggar?]
[I thought I was the only victim.]
[Wow, pretty but a scammer.]
[Someone tag the Mother Superior.]
No need to thank me.
For taking the trouble to sum up your debts.
That was truly amazing.
And next up is the show from our 3-time defending champions.
The Green Team!
No need to thank me.
For taking the trouble to sum up your debts.
What's wrong with her?
Did you see what they shared on the page?
I thought they practiced so hard.
This year isn't as good as last year.
Look, she's rushing off.
I thought you told us not to mess up.
Hey, calm down.
Nano, what the hell is wrong with you?
You were totally zoning out. You messed up the whole routine.
I'm sorry.
You're the head cheerleader, but we lost because of you.
Isn't "sorry" a bit too easy?
Do you even realize? You forced us to buy expensive costumes.
Paid so much for makeup.
My parents wasted their time
just to watch you stand stupid in the middle of the field?
It went right according to your best friend Shisha's plan.
Stop being a bitch. You screwed up all by yourself, Nano.
Stop blaming others.
Why are you quiet?
Don't give me those fake tears.
You always love to put me down, Nano.
Come on, do you want to slap me?
Slap me, Nano.
What gonna do?
Hey, that's enough.
Enough, enough.
Let's stop here for today.
I know you're mad.
But save the yelling for tomorrow. Enough.
Let's go, everyone.
Earn, we're here.
Let's go.
I'll take you to the registration desk,
then we'll get something to eat.
Can I borrow your bike for a joyride, uncle?
Aren't you going to wish me luck?
You didn't even come to see me off this morning.
Do you really have to hide like this?
I just don't want anyone to know I skipped class for this.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Don't lose to second place.
Ohhh.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Have I ever caused you any trouble, teacher Nalin?
I don't think I ever did.
So why did you do this to me?
For someone like you,
just getting fired means the Mother Superior was merciful.
You've got a smart mouth.
Look who's talking.
What kind of teacher are you?
Wanting to date a student who isn't even in college yet?
What were you thinking?
Can you really control feelings like this?
The kid liked me first anyway.
But you're a teacher.
Teachers shouldn't do that.
So what if I'm a teacher?
You keep judging others.
But you're not that different from me, Teacher Nalin.
Don't you agree?
Don't think people don't know.
About what you've been doing with students on the rooftop.
Teacher Thip told me everything.
About your preferences.
What kind of things you like.
You caused quite a scandal back when you were a student, didn't you?
You should know,
the reason you weren't charged with statutory rape
is because of me.
I didn't want the student's reputation ruined,
so I had the school cover it up.
Otherwise,
it wouldn't have ended with just you getting fired.
So, what do you say?
Do you want it to end at just getting fired?
So, is Sophie talking to anyone?
Is she?
Not at all.
Oh, really?
Really? You're secretly smiling.
Are you sure?
We wouldn't judge if you did.
She definitely is. Acting this suspicious, she definitely is.
[Amy: Is it really that easy for you?]
Three people on one piece and we're still not done.
Where are you going tonight?
Are you okay?
If you can't take it, just rest.
Have some.
You haven't eaten anything because of the outfit, right?
You can eat now.
Here, just a bite.
Chocolate,
eating it when you feel bad really helps.
Because it's so delicious.
I mean...
I still don't know what to do next.
Suddenly I'm the talk of the whole school.
And I don't know where to find the money to pay them back.
I think there's a way.
Don't worry, I'll help you.
It's almost 300,000. How can you help?
Those brand-name items... selling them should be enough, right?
But I love those things so much.
But in this situation, you don't really have a choice, do you?
If you can pay them back but refuse to,
it's no different from scamming them.
The people who lent you the money might really need it too.
If you still refuse to pay them back,
you'll just look even more selfish.
Fine!
How am I being selfish?
Then just let me handle this myself.
That's not what I meant. I...
Hello.
You're in front of the school already?
Okay, I'll be right out.
Hey, P'Nano.
Even if you didn't come out, I would've still lent it to you.
But thank you for coming out to see me.
Cheer up.
I saw the hashtag, so I figured you might want to borrow more.
You look really beautiful today, P'Nano.
I've transferred the money.
Thank you.
I'll find a way to pay you back as soon as possible.
P'Amy, is everything alright?
You look down. I'm worried.
If you want to talk to someone,
you can talk to me.
Thank you.
Do I look that bad?
I've just been sad lately.
Even though the match is coming up, I can't concentrate at all.
I'm afraid I'll make the team lose.
And I don't want anyone else to get in trouble because of me.
If you're not over it yet,
it's okay to just be a mess for a while.
No need to rush.
When we're sad, we don't know what to do.
So...
Just let it slowly get better on its own.
I think...
The more you force it, the longer it takes to heal.
And besides, you've been practicing hard all semester.
Even though you're sad, I still see you doing a great job.
Don't pressure yourself too much.
Even when you're sad, you can do this well.
So when you're fully healed,
you'll definitely be even more amazing.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
It's just words of encouragement.
I can always give them to you.
Not just for the encouragement.
Thank you for always secretly watching me practice.
And always checking if I was okay or not.
Can I have some?
I didn't buy any.
So forgetful.
You know you're not the only one who's good at caring for others?
I noticed everything.
Oh, shit!
P'Amy.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
Take it slow.
Does it hurt anywhere?
Are you okay?
Oh, where are you rushing off to, Nano?
I thought you said your family was rich.
Give me my money back.
Why don't you announce it on the school mic next time?
Don't think I wouldn't dare.
I just paid you back.
You lent me money was so I'd get you into the industry.
But sorry about that.
I tried to pitch you, but nobody wanted you.
What kind of person is she?
Hey Sophie, want some ice cream?
Wow, it's so hot today.
Here, have some.
It's okay.
You eat it, Jane.
Why are you sitting all alone like this?
Just taking a break.
The Green Team's stand looks amazing.
Even more beautiful than what you drew on paper that day.
Hey, thank you.
Out of all the Sports Days I've done in my life,
I put the most effort into this year.
Next year we have university entrance exams.
I didn't want to regret it later.
Didn't want to regret it later?
Yeah.
What if...
What if you're bound to regret it either way?
Bound to regret it either way?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
My mom used to say,
if you have to choose between what is right and what you like,
choose what you like first.
Wanna know why?
Because if you choose what you like,
at least it's good for your heart.
What my mom meant was,
we need to be much kinder to ourselves.
I think that's true.
I'm jealous of you.
Your mom is so lovely.
My mom has a lot of quotes.
Thank you, Jane.
No need to thank me.
Just remember to be kind to yourself.
It melts so fast.
The Little Prince learned that "to tame" is to establish ties.
After the Little Prince met the fox,
the fox told him that if he tamed it,
its boring life of hunting chickens every day
would become as bright as the sun.
The fox would recognize the sound of his footsteps,
and would not run away when it heard them.
An ordinary wheat field
would make the fox...
Did Earn forget?
Earn.
You can sit next to me.
I might be weird, but at least I'm not a jerk.
And...
I've never seen you as a bad person either.
We know best what kind of person we are.
Ever heard of that?
You can do it.
Don't lose to second place.
I think you might need to lean in a bit closer.
It looks sexier.
You got this?
Earn.
What is essential is invisible to the eye.
It is only with the heart that one can see rightly.
The Little Prince realized that his rose was important.
Because she was the only one.
That he had formed a bond with.
Even if they had to be apart.
This rose would still be the only one.
That was always special to the Little Prince.
The Little Prince might have thought that the bond gave the fox nothing at all.
And even brought tears on the day they had to part.
But in the eyes of the fox.
Its secret is hidden in this truth.
What is essential is invisible to the eye.
It is only with the heart that one can see rightly.
So every bond that is created.
Will be a thread that ties our hearts, making us responsible for each other.
Thank you.
And for the first prize,
I would like to announce the two schools
nominated for the first prize. They are...
Phraharuthai Metta School
and Anna Patronage Tipwan School!
Please come up to the stage.
And the winner of the first prize is...
Congratulations to...
Miss Oranichaporn Ruammitr
from Anna Patronage Tipwan School!
Let's give her another round of applause!
I won because of you, Belle.
Thank you.
You're exaggerating.
You won because you tried your best.
Good girl, Earn.
Why do I feel like a dog?
Here, your reward.
I wanted to buy it to cheer myself up before the competition.
I'll take this one.
Wow.
When did you buy this?
Thank you!
It's so cute.
Skipped class and came a long way, Belle.
I'm not mad. It's good that you came to cheer for your friend.
But next time, take a car. Riding a motorcycle is too hot.
Tomorrow night, I'm throwing a party at my house. You guys should come.
Consider it a thank you for everyone's hard work.
Supplies are here!
I'm sorry about earlier.
For being so harsh on you.
It's okay.
I already know you have a bad mouth.
Just kidding.
I don't know if you've checked the hashtag lately.
But...
I think things are starting to get out of hand.
If you don't do something, I'm sure it'll reach the Mother Superior.
I think so too.
Figured out how to fix it yet?
Probably your idea.
Selling the stuff I have.
Good thinking.
For someone like you, saving up to buy these things again later won't be hard.
Come on, let's start.
Which one first?
Let's see, which one should we do?
That one, or the one in the middle?
Let me get up and take a look.
Let's see. What do we have here?
Wow.
Just one person, but you have like 10 bags.
Oh, this one is pretty.
Here, I'll take a picture. Wear it like this.
This one, this one. Let's take 3 of them.
And the Best Cheer Stand award this year goes to...
The Green Team!
Mom.
I took the kids to the competition and we won first place.
Really?
That's amazing, sweetie.
So you don't have to worry about the medical bills anymore.
Nalin.
Can we talk for a bit?
What is it, Mom?
Nalin.
Mom is so tired.
I already told the doctor.
That I want to stop the treatment.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Mom.
I'm okay.
You don't have to cry anymore.
I loves you, sweetie.
Hey, hey!
Someone just messaged to buy it.
Really? Let me see.
[Can you lower the price a bit more? It looks pretty worn out.]
"Can you lower the price a bit more? It looks pretty worn out."
Oh, please.
This bag is worth over a hundred thousand.
Haggling this much, why not just ask for it for free?
You don't have to sell it yet, you know.
I'll help boost the post in case someone else asks.
[If you're ready, you can transfer the money now.]
It's fine.
Selling this one bag can pay off several people.
It's better to get the money and fix the problem first.
Aww, good job, little Nano.
Do we look like we're just playing around?
Nano did great. Great job.
Hello, Jane.
Hello, Earn.
Teacher Nalin is throwing a party at her house today. Do you wanna come?
Hey, I'm in. But can I bring Nano too?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, see you then.
Okay, see you.
Oh.
Inviting people over... did you ask for permission yet?
Teacher Nalin, can I invite some more friends over?
Inviting them before asking? Sure.
Thank you.
Teacher, can I invite my friends from the science class too?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
It's like that.
6 pieces.
Keep going!
We're here!
Hello, Teacher Nalin.
Come on in.
Come sit with us.
Wow, so many snacks.
Can I eat this?
Sure, go ahead.
Hey, Amy.
Ooh, who did you come with?
Who's that with you?
That person, of course. Don't you know?
Turns out it's just a minor bone fracture.
The person who brought it in said it got run over.
I was so shocked, but it was just a scrape.
[Nano, when are you paying me back?]
I think you should close the fundraiser now, Nano.
The amount should be enough now.
Doctor, I have to go now. My friends are waiting for me.
Amy, wanna play with us?
Okay, sure.
Can I have some too?
Sure.
Whoever loses is paying.
I'm going to the restroom real quick.
Anyone want to have some more fun?
Whoa, P'Som!
Teacher.
Are you okay?
There are so many people downstairs.
It's a party, of course there are a lot of people.
For me, a party...
can be just two people.
Can I have a drink too?
No.
You're still a kid. You can't drink.
And when was your first drink?
10th grade.
See? And you're lecturing me.
I thought you weren't coming.
I can't come to a party without bringing some snacks, right?
So...
who else is here?
You've already paid everyone back.
Why worry? It's going to be fine.
If anyone gives you a hard time, I'll slap them for you.
Slap them?
Clap my hands.
Everyone's waiting for you. You're the only one who's late.
Welcome drinks.
Have a sip.
It's a bit weak.
Wow, is this alcohol?
This is my first time.
I'm glad to be your first.
Come on, let's go inside.
Cheers.
Come on, cheers!
Anyone wanna play a game?
Let's play a game!
What's going on with you two?
What's the deal?
P'Amy.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Say yes! Say yes! Say yes!
No...
I can't let Aioon be the one to ask.
So... Aioon, will you be my girlfriend?
Hey.
Even though this isn't the rooftop,
if there's anything on your mind, you can tell me.
It's nothing.
[Hey, Mink posted a photo of a marriage proposal.]
[Friends are sharing it everywhere.]
What kind of crazy day is this?
What happened?
Why is life so tiring?
Well, we're tired because we're not dead yet.
I don't know what you're going through,
but I'm here for you.
Always ready to listen.
Thank you.
My eyes are as swollen as a frog's.
Let me see.
They're not swollen at all. You look beautiful.
Here.
Why did you take a picture? It's ugly.
You're beautiful.
Beautiful even when you cry.
Here.
I saw it and thought of you, so I bought it for you.
I'll take this one too, please.
Sure.
I think...
I like you.