( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Nano, I'd like to split the budget between the cheerleaders and the stand.
Can we do 50/50 like the other teams?
The cheer stand taking 20 is enough.
Our group usually wins the cheerleader trophy all the time.
But the cheer stand is always last, there's no need to invest in it.
20 is barely enough for welfare expenses alone.
There won't be that many people joining the stand anyway.
But then we wouldn't have enough money for cutouts.
Then scale it down.
Then can you give me a breakdown?
What exactly do the cheerleaders need, and how much budget?
Just for the costumes,
we always have to pay out of our own pockets every year.
Not to mention the hair and makeup artists.
All of that already exceeds 70%.
Then you scale it down.
You're determined, aren't you?
The highlight of our school's sports day
is the cheerleaders.
No one wants to scream their lungs out singing cheer songs.
Since you just transferred here, learn to adapt.
Don't be annoying.
Then I'll go ask the juniors who wants to be on the stand.
And I'll calculate the budget based on the actual numbers.
Try me.
This will be what our stand looks like this year.
Time Travel... it can go back in time, like
time machines, dinosaurs, or like
you could dress up as any character from the past.
So whoever wants to be on the stand or wants to help make props,
just let me know.
P'Jane.
If our whole class wants to be on the stand, will there be enough seats?
Wow, the whole class?
Yeah, of course there's enough! Definitely enough. Sure!
So many juniors want to be on the stand.
I guess the cheer budget needs to be doubled.
I don't think 50/50 is going to work anymore.
Hey everyone.
Thank you so much for joining the cheer stand this year.
But with this, we probably won't have much budget left to help the cheerleaders.
But I still want to watch P'Nano and the cheerleaders dance beautifully!
Yeah! The cheerleaders are the pride of our group!
We'll try our best.
But it might not be as grand as previous years.
P'Jane.
What is it?
My friends and I are backing out.
I have friends who are cheerleaders, and I want them to be able to do their best.
If we don't join the stand,
the cheerleaders will get their budget back, right?
Um... yeah.
I'm sorry, P'Jane.
Hello, P'Amy.
We're shooting a school promotional video.
Clip it nicely.
Hello, ma'am.
Oh, hello ma'am.
Hello, teacher. Hello, ma'am.
Thank you.
I just dropped by to say hi to Teacher Thip
and brought some snacks for everyone.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Amy looks very proper today.
Are you here to receive an award too?
Today, the school selected exemplary student representatives, ma'am.
Both from the academic and extracurricular sides
to shoot a promotional VTR.
Watawan here is the representative for outstanding extracurricular activities.
The song she composed herself is actually going viral right now.
Um, ma'am, excuse me.
If you're ready, could I interview you first?
Sure.
This way, please.
Please.
Ma'am, how important do you think the smart library
is to the education of students like us?
I think it's very important.
Because kids these days
can all find information online.
I probably can't compete with the younger generation when it comes to technology.
So, I'd like to make a contribution
towards purchasing and developing educational equipment.
I'll hand it over to the committee and the teachers
to allocate and purchase for the school.
For P'Sophie,
how should a proper young lady behave nowadays?
The most important thing for every student,
whether now or in the past,
is simply to know your duties
and fulfill them to the best of your ability,
without causing trouble for anyone.
That, to me, is considered being a proper young lady.
And how does this school help
further students' interests outside of academics?
Actually, our school supports extracurricular activities quite a lot.
But beyond that,
we have a parent association that constantly encourages students
and fully supports us with equipment.
Which I think is a really lovely thing.
Um, computers at other schools might be just for doing reports,
but our school's computers also have music production software installed.
So I consider this award I received today
to be mine and everyone's who helped vote for me.
Including you too, ma'am. Thank you.
Thank you.
This friend of yours is quite nice.
I see her coming over every day for you to tutor her.
I thought she'd be a slacker.
Amy is a smart person.
She might fall behind in class sometimes because she does a lot of activities,
but whatever she's interested in,
she excels at it.
How should we edit this?
There's a part where there's a lot of dead air.
Oh, P'Amy. I thought you had already gone home.
Wow, your answers today were so good!
If I were P'Sophie's mom, I'd be so thrilled.
Wow, really?
Yeah!
Hey, Aioon.
Why don't you let P'Amy help check the pacing of the edit?
I'm going to go lock the club room door first, in case I forget.
Okay.
I'll get going now.
Are you fully recovered?
You're even here helping shoot content today.
It still hurts a bit, but it's okay.
You're so hardworking.
Do you want to be the club president like Anna?
I just wanted to try shooting content, so I came to help.
I like filming when you guys are doing activities.
Really?
So among all the things you've filmed, are there any behind-the-scenes of me?
There's a lot.
You do so many activities,
and you're so talented.
Actually, I've had a crush on you too.
At first, I thought it was just like a regular fan admiring you,
like everyone else.
But...
after seeing you do so many things,
I felt like I wanted to get to know you better.
I'm glad you hit me in the face with that basketball that day.
It gave us a chance to talk.
And today you even came to talk to me first.
I just wanted to tell you how I feel.
Even if you already have someone you like, it's okay.
Thank you so much.
You're so cool, Aioon,
for being brave enough to confess to me directly.
I don't even have the courage to tell someone I like them directly like this.
From now on, if you need my help with anything,
or if you want some advice, you can reach out to me anytime, okay?
Don't hesitate at all.
Now, show me the video. I'll help you edit it.
Okay!
[@Nalin A student from Class 11C skipped school this afternoon.]
[Teacher Nalin, were you not aware of this?]
[Even though you are a new homeroom teacher,]
[please take good care of your students.]
"Whatever" again? Then you choose.
Not this one.
Let's have something Japanese.
May I speak with Belle for a moment?
If you're going to break the rules,
why do it in a way where you get caught?
Just in case you didn't know, teacher...
I'm the Mother Superior's biological niece.
That means...
no matter how badly I behave,
or how much I want to get expelled,
my aunt will never expel me.
So you don't need to care about me.
Just leave it between me and my aunt.
I don't care about your personal life.
But I pity your skills.
If you want the school to stop targeting you,
prove yourself in the right way.
I don't think I have to prove myself,
especially in this stupid school.
Do you really not know what freedom is?
If you really want freedom,
you wouldn't act in a way that makes people constantly try to control you.
The more you act out,
the more you're just demanding attention.
I know that at this school,
there are a lot of things that don't make sense.
It's very different from your old school environment.
Stop running away,
and try to actually beat the Mother Superior, how about that?
What do you mean?
If you agree to compete in the French contest and win,
I'll talk to the Mother Superior for you.
I'll suggest she transfer you back to an international school
where my friend teaches.
There's a scholarship to study abroad.
If you really want to escape your aunt,
this is a great option.
Or even if you don't want to go,
it's an excuse with enough weight to make the Mother Superior
accept you.
And who are you? Why would my aunt listen to you?
Before you can make the Mother Superior believe in you,
you have to believe in me first.
Do you have any plans for celebrating this Saturday?
This Saturday?
Don't tell me you studied so hard you forgot your own birthday.
Oh.
You're right.
If you don't know where to go yet,
should we go to my friend's resort? The one we went to last year.
Sure, if you want to go.
Invite Amy along too.
It's your birthday, invite your close friend so you can have fun.
And I can get to know Amy better too.
Okay.
I'm here.
I told the doctor we can start the targeted therapy.
And where did you get the money for that, honey?
I have some savings.
My illness is causing you so much trouble.
Don't say that.
What trouble?
When I was a kid, I was sick all the time.
And you never complained.
But now I'm a grown-up.
Anything I can do for you,
please let me do it for you, Mom.
I'll be getting a bonus from the school next month anyway.
As for your medical bills,
I can pay them no matter how much they are.
Don't worry.
Thank you, honey.
You're such a good girl.
Where's Teacher Nalin?
She's probably not coming today.
She said we'll start practicing when we have all 4 people.
So you're here because...?
Yeah, I entered the competition too.
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Just scrolling through my feed.
Is that Amy?
Yeah, she's singing a Marc-Flute song.
Marc-Flute?
Oh, the ship you like, right?
Yeah.
[Even without seeing your face, I can't take it anymore.]
You saw that, right?
Yeah.
Belle, can you please not tell anyone about this?
Who would I even tell?
I won't tell anyone anyway.
But you probably think badly of me now, don't you?
Why do you care how I look at you?
What kind of person you are,
you know yourself best.
Have you heard that?
In the end, whether people find out about this in the future or not,
I think
you know best what kind of person you are.
That's the most important thing.
And also...
I've never seen you as a bad person.
I've never met anyone who studies as hard as you.
In this school, you're probably the most frugal person too.
So I think...
you making sex content,
I think you must have your own reasons.
If in the future someone bullies you saying
you do this because you're hungry for money,
tell me.
I'll punch them in the face for you.
Promise me?
That you won't tell anyone.
On the honor of the Mother Superior.
And I'd be happy to hire you immediately.
If you promise me one thing.
What is it?
I want you to get close to the students.
Learn about their personal lives,
or any bad behaviors they are secretly doing.
And report back to me.
So that we can eliminate the problem early on.
But, Mother Superior,
if we use our position as teachers to approach students
with hidden agendas,
isn't that a violation of the students' privacy?
The parents have entrusted us to fully take care of their children.
Therefore,
if there's anything that could damage our school's reputation,
we won't consider it
a private matter for the students at all.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Will you accept my offer, Teacher Nalin?
Well, Teacher Nalin?
Are there any students at risk of ruining our school's reputation?