( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I have exams coming up.
Do you even study? Please, at least read a little.
By the way, what should we eat?
"Whatever" again? Then you choose.
Let's have something Japanese.
Not this one.
May I speak with Belle for a moment?
If you're going to break the rules,
why do it in a way where you get caught?
Just in case you didn't know, teacher...
I'm the Mother Superior's biological niece.
That means...
no matter how badly I behave,
or how much I want to get expelled,
my aunt will never expel me.
So you don't need to care about me.
Just leave it between me and my aunt.
I don't care about your personal life.
But I pity your skills.
If you want the school to stop targeting you,
prove yourself in the right way.
I don't think I have to prove myself,
especially in this stupid school.
Do you really not know what freedom is?
If you really want freedom,
you wouldn't act in a way that makes people constantly try to control you.
The more you act out,
the more you're just demanding attention.
I know that at this school,
there are a lot of things that don't make sense.
It's very different from your old school environment.
Stop running away,
and try to actually beat the Mother Superior, how about that?
What do you mean?
If you agree to compete in the French contest and win,
I'll talk to the Mother Superior for you.
I'll suggest she transfer you back to an international school
where my friend teaches.
There's a scholarship to study abroad.
If you really want to escape your aunt,
this is a great option.
Or even if you don't want to go,
it's an excuse with enough weight to make the Mother Superior
accept you.
And who are you? Why would my aunt listen to you?
Before you can make the Mother Superior believe in you,
you have to believe in me first.
Do you have any plans for celebrating this Saturday?
This Saturday?
Don't tell me you studied so hard you forgot your own birthday.
Oh.
You're right.
If you don't know where to go yet,
should we go to my friend's resort? The one we went to last year.
Sure, if you want to go.
Invite Amy along too.
It's your birthday, invite your close friend so you can have fun.
And I can get to know Amy better too.
Okay.
I'm here.
I told the doctor we can start the targeted therapy.
And where did you get the money for that, honey?
I have some savings.
My illness is causing you so much trouble.
Don't say that.
What trouble?
When I was a kid, I was sick all the time.
And you never complained.
But now I'm a grown-up.
Anything I can do for you,
please let me do it for you, Mom.
I'll be getting a bonus from the school next month anyway.
As for your medical bills,
I can pay them no matter how much they are.
Don't worry.
Thank you, honey.
You're such a good girl.
Where's Teacher Nalin?
She's probably not coming today.
She said we'll start practicing when we have all 4 people.
So you're here because...?
Yeah, I entered the competition too.
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Just scrolling through my feed.
Is that Amy?
Yeah, she's singing a Marc-Flute song.
Marc-Flute?
Oh, the ship you like, right?
Yeah.
[Even without seeing your face, I can't take it anymore.]
You saw that, right?
Yeah.
Belle, can you please not tell anyone about this?
Who would I even tell?
I won't tell anyone anyway.
But you probably think badly of me now, don't you?
Why do you care how I look at you?
What kind of person you are,
you know yourself best.
Have you heard that?
In the end, whether people find out about this in the future or not,
I think
you know best what kind of person you are.
That's the most important thing.
And also...
I've never seen you as a bad person.
I've never met anyone who studies as hard as you.
In this school, you're probably the most frugal person too.
So I think...
you making sex content,
I think you must have your own reasons.
If in the future someone bullies you saying
you do this because you're hungry for money,
tell me.
I'll punch them in the face for you.
Promise me?
That you won't tell anyone.
On the honor of the Mother Superior.
And I'd be happy to hire you immediately.
If you promise me one thing.
What is it?
I want you to get close to the students.
Learn about their personal lives,
or any bad behaviors they are secretly doing.
And report back to me.
So that we can eliminate the problem early on.
But, Mother Superior,
if we use our position as teachers to approach students
with hidden agendas,
isn't that a violation of the students' privacy?
The parents have entrusted us to fully take care of their children.
Therefore,
if there's anything that could damage our school's reputation,
we won't consider it
a private matter for the students at all.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Will you accept my offer, Teacher Nalin?
Well, Teacher Nalin?
Are there any students at risk of ruining our school's reputation?