( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
"Sophie's life was what you'd call perfect."
[Average grade point: 3.96]
Why didn't you get a 4.0?
"Raised to be..."
"...proper."
Mom, what's wrong?!
"It had to be absolutely perfect."
Sophie, what are you watching?
Why are you watching this kind of stuff?
Did I raise you poorly?
It's my fault. It's all my fault.
That's why you turned out like this!
"Sophie learned right then..."
I won't do it again, Mom.
I'll never do it again.
"...that she couldn't afford to make any mistakes."
I love you most, Mom.
Just stay within the lines I've drawn for you.
And everything will be fine, sweetie.
"Amy's life was never perfect."
Ugh, my daughter doesn't care about a single thing.
Yeah, I'm talking about Amy.
The youngest one who isn't good at school.
And lately, she's so addicted to social media.
She's always on her phone.
I don't know what she does all day.
I don't even know if she'll get accepted anywhere.
But thank goodness my son got into med school.
So that's one less headache.
But my daughter really stresses me out.
"As long as we're in the right place,"
"we'll be the right person."
Hi, P'Amy.
Hi.
See you later.
What?
Nothing.
Oh.
Should I wait for you?
It's fine.
Sorry I'm late. I was at practice.
Do you have a pencil I could borrow?
I forgot mine.
Thanks.
I didn't study.
I figured guessing the same letter gives me a better chance.
Hey, sorry for startling you that day.
What day?
The day you saw me kissing...
Oh.
I wasn't startled.
Really? I thought you would be.
Since you seem like such a proper girl.
Do I look proper?
I mean, you're the student council president.
Seeing something like that must have felt weird, right?
But thanks for not telling the teachers.
I'm not a snitch.
And I'm not a proper girl either.
True.
A pretty girl like you...
must have some experience by now, right?
What do you mean?
I mean,
you must have people hitting on you, or had a partner before.
And...
you probably have some physical experience, stuff like that.
Huh. I don't.
Seriously?
So what's the most physical contact you've ever had?
None at all.
I haven't even been kissed.
Really?
So that means you've never slept with anyone?
More like I haven't found anyone I want to try it with.
But honestly, I am curious.
About how it feels.
What do you mean?
When people actually have sex.
With this kind of thing,
you have to try it yourself to understand.
Just like this exam.
If you don't actually do the work,
you'll never understand it.
There, I helped you with your exam.
Now, I want to know how it feels.
You have to return the favor.
"And maybe the right place..."
"...is what leads us to the right person."
"The perfection that Amy never knew..."
"Finally,"
"Amy made it hers."
Wow, back with another love song today.
When are you going to reveal who's in your heart, P'Amy?
Honestly, you could reveal it today.
Go ahead, tell us.
The 'S' stands for...
Sabrina Carpenter.
Oh, come on, P'Amy!
I mean, it's still unrequited love right now.
Our students' standards are steadily dropping.
Just look at the radio show.
When Teacher Nalin was a student, it was all about general knowledge.
Look at it now.
Financial problems, romance issues.
And some are secretly doing inappropriate things behind our backs.
Nalin, do you happen to know anything about these issues?
I don't really like gossiping about students.
Teacher,
The Class C students are fighting!
Are you crazy, Belle!
Stop!
Belle!
Everyone, stop!
Hey, can I have some? I forgot to buy mine.
So forgetful.
Thanks.
If you keep forgetting, I'll buy you some every day.
What about us?
I can buy some for you guys too.
Stop teasing her.
Come on, guys, let's go.
Um, P'Amy,
I'm coming in for stand cheer practice on Saturday too.
Will you be here?
Oh, I won't be here tomorrow.
Going out of town for two days.
Oh, really?
Going with your family?
Oh, going with a friend's family.
I'm going to get back to practice.
See ya.
You've all explained how this happened.
I think we should discuss the main issue.
Even though this started because of Jiratchaya borrowing money,
the fact that you got physical
means you still have to be punished.
A 10-point deduction in behavior.
And 20 hours of community service.
And if there's any more insulting of your peers,
you know the punishment won't stop here, right?
Violence is strictly unacceptable here.
Violence
is never the right solution.
A 10-point deduction
isn't enough.
As agreed, if Nicharee causes any more trouble,
she will lose her right to compete in the French competition.
Is that correct, Mother Superior?
Belle! Wait, Belle!
You know you were wrong too, right?
For saying something that harsh.
Student.
Does Nano really have a problem with overspending?
Belle...
Are you okay with not being able to compete together?
I'm not okay with it.
But what can I do?
But I still want to help you win.
Wanna study tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, Belle...
But tomorrow...
can you help me with that other thing too?
There's a huge rumor going around among the students right now.
About inappropriate relationships within our A.T. school.
Doesn't Teacher Nalin have anything to report on this?
Actually,
I was just about to report it.
It's regarding a romantic relationship.
P'Jane, can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Well...
I feel bad for causing a problem between you and P'Nano.
About the cheerleading budget P'Nano asked for...
She actually let me borrow it to rent a costume first.
Because I really don't have the money.
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Did you really con me out of my money?
I gave you that to help the cat.
So you didn't use it to help the cat?
I really did use it for the treatment.
Well, I haven't seen any proof.
I heard your friend say you spent the money on other things.
I can swear to it anywhere you want, Sister.
It's not that I don't believe you.
But it is very suspicious.
But I can actually be a witness to that.
This is the X-ray of the broken bone.
I actually have photos of the treatment process too.
But they're not very pleasant to look at.
Nano, I'm sorry for misunderstanding.
It's completely fine.
Actually, Nano started a fundraising page to help cats.
At first, donors were very skeptical.
But Nano actually does it, and has proof of every step.
As for the leftover money,
Nano donates it to help other stray cats at the end of every month.
Are you really that good of a person?
But what I'm wondering is,
there's still a balance due on this case.
But I haven't seen Nano start a fundraiser for it.
Well, I actually want to keep this cat myself.
So I didn't open a fundraiser for it.
For the remaining treatment cost.
It's okay, Sister.
Consider it an apology from me.
Thank you, Sister.
You're welcome.
Are you going to stare all day?
Are you an angel or something?
Beautiful and charitable.
You sound so old. Major Gen Y vibes.
But I don't get it.
Why do you donate the money?
Couldn't you keep it to help other cats?
No way.
I'm a terrible spender.
If I gave in to temptation and spent the money,
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
So why did you suddenly decide to keep this one?
I guess we just clicked.
Hey, Nano, wait up!
How do you know where I live?
I know the Mother Superior's computer password.
So...
I got into the school's database a bit.
Teacher.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to cause so much trouble that I couldn't compete.
I know I let you down.
But I'll help Earn win no matter what.
Do you know where you messed up?
Messed up by not scattering before the teachers came?
You messed up by reacting like that.
I understand
that you were upset and wanted to retaliate.
But there are so many other ways to retaliate
without getting yourself in trouble.
This time, you chose the wrong way.
If something like this happens again,
I hope you don't make the same mistake.
Okay?
Okay.
And...
Does this mean you forgive me?
Phew. It was worth the cab fare then.
I'll call you a ride back. You can go now.
And give me my towel back. My hair is still wet.
Hey!
I'm leaving! Bye!
Hello, Ma'am.
Hello. Come on in.
It's fine.
It's fine. Allow me.
Thank you.
All set.
When did you two become friends? How did you meet?
I met her when I went to take a make-up exam, Ma'am.
Amy is very involved in extracurriculars, Mom.
So she had to take the exam later than the others.
I was proctoring for Teacher Thip at the time, so we met.
Very involved in extracurriculars.
What kind of activities do you do?
- She's a musician.
- I'm an athlete.
- an athlete.
- a musician.
Actually, Amy does almost everything, Mom.
The day you came to shoot the VTR at the school...
that's why she was chosen as a student representative.
Well, since you're so good at activities,
Sophie, you should invite her to play a round with me sometime.
Are you interested in golf?
I can give it a try, Ma'am.
Not afraid of the sun?
I'll just put on some sunscreen.
Let's paint a little more over here.
Is anyone else coming to help?
Yeah, the others will be here soon.
Don't worry about it.
You go focus on studying for your French competition.
Just bring home the win for us.
I got banned from competing.
So... because of Nano, you slapped Khaopan?
How did you come to that conclusion?
I mean, pretty much.
And I was hot-headed too.
But she was asking for it.
That sucks.
Someone as smart as you should be competing.
Don't feel bad. We still have our number one favorite.
This one... won't let us down.
I'm gonna go.
Hey, bye. Good luck.
Bye, Earn.
Hey, good luck.
Thanks.
Good luck to you both.
Bye.
Don't forget to win for us, Earn!
Might as well just show up tomorrow.
Well.
So crazy over a guy that you got in trouble, huh?
Don't let your behavior score drop too low.
Or the school will ban you from cheerleading.
And everyone else will suffer.
I don't need a lecture from someone like you.
What's wrong with someone like me?
At least I never sold out my friends like you did.
If you'd just paid me back, this wouldn't have happened.
I did pay you back.
You were the one who wanted to go bite Belle yourself.
I suggest you keep your mouth shut
and use it to borrow money like always, Nano.
Don't start with me.
Don't think I wouldn't dare.
I dare.
So what?
I dare too.
You said you dared.
You start then.
Bring it on if you dare.
Why?
And why?
And you?
I'm okay.
Jane.
Are you okay?
Idiot.
Did you really think I was gonna slap Khaopan?
Well... you look like the type.
Just kidding.
But honestly, I almost did.
Good thing you didn't. Good effort holding back.
Sports day is almost here.
Don't let a problem between two people ruin it for the whole team.
Just compromise when you can.
Think of the greater good.
You sound just like my grandma.
I'm gonna knock you on the head, Nano dear.
I'm not doing this anymore.
Ow, still hurts!
It's alright. Amy, please make yourself comfortable.
I've heard the song you wrote, Amy.
It's a lovely song.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Did you write it for your boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend yet.
Oh?
But that's nice.
You seem like a romantic, Amy.
It reminds me of when I was a young woman.
You still look very young now, Ma'am.
Actually, I'm not that conservative, you know.
Love isn't a bad thing.
My Sophie is almost a full-grown woman.
If someone really came along and courted her...
I wouldn't mind.
And if someone does try to win Sophie's heart...
I'd like you to help keep an eye on them, Amy.
I trust you.
Okay.
I'm going to go talk to my friend who owns the resort.
If you two want to take a walk,
or take some photos, feel free.
It seems like your mom would be okay with it now
if you had a partner, So.
At first, I thought we'd go to your place.
Well, if we're going to study...
and then I need you to help me take pictures after...
This place seemed appropriate.
How did you get into making this kind of content?
Actually, someone I know invited me.
Teacher Som.
You know her, right?
But you're okay, right?
There aren't any problems, are there?
Honestly, I don't really want to work with Teacher Som anymore.
She wants me to show my face.
Says the clients like it.
But I refused.
Well...
You have to tell her straight up. That's right.
It's completely your right to choose, Earn.
Don't be afraid.
Yeah.
So...
Let's get back to studying.
Actually, I made a bit of a summary.
So you wouldn't have to read too much.
And just in case it might earn some extra points.
So motivated.
It requires a great deal of patience
to build a genuine connection between two people.
You must gradually approach each other.
Sit far apart at first,
then get closer day by day.
Until trust is built,
forming a special bond.
When the rose began to bloom,
the little prince felt excited and watched over her closely.
He watered her every morning.
Shielded her from the wind with a screen.
And placed a glass globe over her
to protect her from the cold at night.
The rose often demanded attention
by complaining and acting temperamental.
Like complaining that the wind was too strong.
Or the air was too cold.
Therefore, the little prince quickly began to doubt her.
Despite the good intentions from his love,
he took insignificant words too seriously
and became very unhappy.
So.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah?
Do you... like me?
Like how normal people like each other?
I think...
I think about you all the time.
And...
I worry about you too.
I'm afraid you don't feel the same way I do.
I've never been like this with anyone before.
If you're with me...
I promise I won't get involved with anyone else.
And I'll never do anything to hurt you.
I love you, Sophie.
You know?
Before this, I never thought about love.
I felt like...
Just getting through each day was enough of a headache.
Why add love to the mix?
But once I got to know you...
I realized,
love really is a headache.
But it's a headache worth having.
Are you saying you love me?
You're so slow to catch on.
Then let's be girlfriends.
You don't have to give me an answer right now.
I know this is probably moving too fast for you.
But if one day,
I like you more than this,
to the point where I want to make things official,
I might ask you to be my girlfriend again.
And if you're still not ready then...
I think...
I might really have to give up.
Thank you for understanding.
Hello.
Hello, Ma'am. I'm calling from Anna Patronage Tipwan School.
From the school? What is it, teacher?
I've received a report about Sophie's inappropriate behavior.
Regarding her dating a female friend.
Are you sure, teacher?
That Sophie...
is dating a girl?
Were you already aware of this, Ma'am?
Thank you.
Hmm, this outfit is nice.
Not as revealing as the other day.
Does the pose have to be like this?
Well... the subscribers want this kind of thing.
An angle of you on top?
Hmm, don't talk.
Okay.
I think I need to lean in a little closer.
Sorry.
I think it looks sexier.
Let's look at the pictures.
Looks good.
Thank you.
How was swimming? Did you have fun?
Very relaxing, Ma'am.
Cherries are one of my favorite fruits.
They're sweet and a bit sour.
I could eat them forever.
But if you buy them from a regular market,
they might taste bland.
It's disappointing.
I'm lucky I have a regular shop.
No matter how many times I order, it tastes the same.
Never changes.
But there was this one time,
I asked Sophie's father to buy some cherries for me.
I specifically told him to buy them from the usual shop.
Even though that shop had been closed for a long time.
But her father...
brought them to me and said
he bought them from the same shop.
I hate liars.
Liars who think I'm stupid.
Sophie, you know I don't like liars, right?
People who think I'm stupid.
You know I hate them, right?
I don't have to talk about your father.
Because today is your birthday, Sophie.
And it's time for an important moment.
Happy Birthday, sweetie.
Happy Birthday to you.
Happy birthday... Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, honey.
I wish for my daughter...
to be a good girl for me forever.
As my daughter grows up,
I wish you a good, happy life.
A good life partner.
A warm family.
I might be a bit old-fashioned.
I know people these days might accept and support
their children being whatever they want.
But for me... my daughter,
dating someone of the same sex... I don't think I could handle that.
I'd rather die.
Blow out the candles and receive my blessing, dear.
Happy Birthday, sweetie.
She'd really rather die?
That's just how my mom is.
Hey, don't cry.
So... what do we do now?
Well...
Nothing.
Just be friends like before.
It's fine, Amy.
It's been okay so far, right?
We just won't be open about it.
I don't have a problem with that, So.
But I will have a problem
if we have to hide this from your mom for the rest of our lives.
Right, So?
I'm sorry, Amy.
The rose tried to hide her feelings.
Even though she felt sad, the rose refused to show her pain.
The rose said she had been foolish,
and apologized to the little prince,
wishing him happiness.
Ma'am.
It's late. You're not asleep yet?
The song I wrote... I wrote it for Sophie.
I love Sophie.
And no matter what happens, I won't give up.
Sophie loves me too.
Did Sophie tell you that?
Please give Sophie and me another chance.
Ma'am!
What's wrong?
Ma'am... Ma'am, calm down.
Go back! Go back!
Calm down, Ma'am.
I said go back!
Go back! Go back!
Go back! Go back! Do you hear me?!
So! I don't know what's wrong with your mom.
Mom, stop.
Just go.
Mom.
Please go back now.
So, I'm trying to help you!
I'm here now, Mom.
So, Som, what are you doing these days?
I'm a teacher now. Tutoring. I have a lot of students lately.
You're so hardworking.
I actually have to look for more teachers right now.
Oh, Earn.
You're back just in time. Som is here to see you.
She came to ask if you're still tutoring.
She wants to give you some students.
I told her you're still doing it.
But you already tutor a lot.
Why did you do this?
We promised not to tell my mom about this.
I wasn't going to tell her.
I was just making conversation.
Then why are you here?
You weren't answering my texts.
So I had to come see you.
You just keep asking me to show my face.
I'm not doing it.
Earn, I'll be honest with you.
I'm really strapped for cash right now.
And what the clients requested isn't that hard, is it?
It pays 150,000, Earn.
Then go find someone else to do it.
When you were in trouble,
I was there to help you, wasn't I?
And now that I'm in trouble, you won't help me?
Show some sympathy, will you?
I don't want to do this forever, you know.
Hit it, hit it, hit it!
Where are you going? You can't go.
[The cheerleading outfits are ready. Please transfer the remaining 50% to this account.]
So cute.
Sis.
Are you gonna borrow money again?
Pretty, smart sister, can I borrow ten thousand?
Huh? Ten thousand?
I don't think this is funny anymore. You haven't even paid me back for last time.
And recently I saw you had some work done on your face. Where did you get the money for that?
Do you have a sugar daddy?
Ugh, nonsense. What sugar daddy?
If I had one, why would I be borrowing money from you?
Who knows?
Yeah, yeah.
I borrowed money from friends.
Several of them, to tide me over.
I'm gradually paying them back.
Nano, if your friends...
suddenly wanted all their money back at once...
Wouldn't you be screwed?
Probably not.
I'm paying them back.
What are you spending all this money on?
I see you shopping like crazy on IG, then getting work done on your face.
Ugh, Sis, you ask too many questions. Never mind.
Hey, you brat.
[- Can I have my money back now?]
[- Mine's a small amount. Pay me first.]
[- Are you okay, Nano?]
[- Isn't this a bit much?]
Why is everyone asking for it back at the same time?
I have some secret to tell you.
Actually, I have a birthmark on my forehead.
Don't I get any of your smile?
Hey. How are you doing?
How am I doing about what?
About your mom.
Well...
Nothing much.
She's my mom.
I've lived with her since I was born.
Anyway...
I'm sorry.
For scaring you.
You don't have to carry everything by yourself, you know.
What you're going through...
It's too heavy for one person to bear alone.
But I've carried it alone my whole life.
And I've always gotten through it.
You know what, Sophie?
From the day I met your mom...
until right now...
There hasn't been a single moment where I felt like walking away from you.
So...
Please don't push me away.
Let me be by your side when you're not okay.
Be my girlfriend, Sophie.
Don't make this any worse than it already is, Amy.
With anything else, I could probably think of a way out.
But I really can't see my mom as the problem.
I don't want to live my life feeling like...
I hate my mom.
I feel like...
The only way out for me...
Is to be reborn. Or for one of us to die.
No one can help me with this anyway, Amy.
I can, So. I can help you.
If you don't want the issue with your mom to be a problem for you,
then it won't be a problem for me either.
Or if...
You want to keep our relationship a secret forever,
I'm okay with that.
Just as long as I can still be by your side.
Thank you, Amy.
I've been really happy with you.
But I want you to go back to living your life.
Without having to worry about me anymore.
Okay...
Please. Don't go.
I'm done lying to myself.
And you shouldn't lie to yourself anymore either.
Finally, the moment everyone has been waiting for!
The show from the cheerleaders of all four colors!
Let me tell you, this year is going to be fierce.
Every color is giving it their all.
Alright, let's start with the first color. The Blue Team!
We are absolutely not losing today.
If we do it like we practiced, we'll definitely win.
Ready? One, two, three.
Hey!
Good luck, both of you!
Nano, have you seen this?
What is it?
[#FakeRichGreenCheerleader #APT]
[Total of 293,000. Better ask for your money back before it's gone.]
[Getting rich from other people's money. lol]
No need to thank me.
For taking the trouble to sum up your debts.
It was you.