( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Die!
I'm going.
I don't know since when,
Yes!
I started questioning,
what was I born for?
I used to think
maybe I was born to be my mom's happiness.
Then I realized,
that wasn't me.
Dad.
Will you take me back to France?
I get sick often, you know.
Maybe it's cancer, like your mother's.
No, it's not that.
I miss you so much.
Don't talk like that.
Your aunt is nice to you, right?
Nice?
She leaves me in this house all the time.
She's always the way she is now.
She has to sleep at the convent.
And besides,
she's giving me less and less money.
I might not even be able to send you any more.
And you want me to come see you? How?
Under these conditions?
That's enough! I'm hanging up.
Dad! Dad!
I gave you money to come see your daughter here,
but you spent it all on drugs.
I'm done with you.
If then you tell that shit,
I'm not gonna talk to her anymore.
Fuck you.
I decided to throw away everything about him.
Even if throwing it all away...
...would hurt like hell.
You saw that, right?
Damn, I haven't even done anything yet.
I know.
I mean, you're so... you.
It'd be weird if they didn't look at you.
Hey,
why did skipping class to walk around here used to be more fun?
Now it's just... whatever.
Yeah, true.
Wanna try something new?
Hey, kids.
Can I see your bags?
Stop!
Come here!
I said stop!
Hey, stop!
After her!
Front guards, intercept the runner!
Teacher, Film told me to do it.
So what exactly happened?
I didn't do anything.
I just went along with Belle.
Parents.
This clip has been shared all over social media.
It's severely damaging our school's reputation.
We have no choice
but to expel them.
I hope you understand.
Whatever you think is best.
Belle, let's go.
Stop lying!
Tell the truth!
What the fuck is your problem?
You're so stupid!
Say it!
What is wrong with you, you idiot!
You bitch! You liar!
You're awful!
The question I always asked myself,
what was I born for?
I finally have the answer.
The answer is,
I shouldn't have been born at all.
Hey.
I think this is the kid who shoplifted at the mall.
Look at this clip.
She used to have red hair, but she changed it.
I'm pretty sure it's her. Just watch the clip.
So aggressive, even attacking the guard.
Yes.
It was me, the kid who shoplifted at the mall.
And I'm also the Mother Superior's niece.
Got a problem with that?
In the Gospel of Luke, chapter 15,
Jesus told a parable.
The parable of the prodigal son.
When the lost son returned, his father ran and embraced him.
That is the model of love He gives us.
In the name of the Lord,
He gives me the strength to never give up on the children.
With love,
and mercy.
I believe this is the mission
that God has entrusted to us.
It's my first day teaching.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Sure.
Can I get one, though?
Yeah, sure.
I'm so bored.
When am I going to graduate?
Have you thought about what you want to do after graduation?
Not really.
I just want to get out of here.
Just far away from that aunt of mine.
You don't need to graduate to get away.
You just need money.
But first,
tell me something.
Do you like guys,
or girls?
What kind of question is that?
I don't know, but...
definitely not guys.
Then,
let's get you some quick cash.
So what exactly am I doing here?
You're going to be an actress.
Just...
touch and stroke me.
Don't worry about showing your face.
Because I don't want to show mine either.
Uh, I'm not against it or anything, but...
if it's this kind of stuff,
I'm out.
Class, stand up.
Good morning, teachers.
This is a random check.
To see if any students are engaging in inappropriate behavior.
Everyone, take out your phones.
And write down your passwords.
I'll give them back this evening.
That's personal property. What right do you have to check them?
If you haven't done anything wrong, why be afraid?
Tell you what.
To set a good example,
we teachers will also hand over our phones to be checked.
How about that? Fair?
What are you waiting for, Teacher Som?
Yes?
Your phone.
I don't think that's necessary.
If the school says it's necessary, then it's necessary.
Password?
Never thought I'd see a student come up here to smoke.
By the way,
why did you start smoking?
I don't know.
I guess I just didn't think things could get any better.
Teacher Nalin.
Hi. You're not home yet?
I'm just about to leave.
I'm glad
you both decided to join the competition.
So, when do we start practicing?
Tomorrow.
Oh.
Hello.
Done tutoring already? That was fast.
Normally, when the science kids tutor for the Olympiad,
it's pitch dark by the time they finish.
We start tomorrow.
I see. Here.
I brought Shisha specifically to see you.
I'd like Shisha to be a representative for
the French competition as well.
Even though she's not in the French-Arts program,
her foundation is very strong.
Her mother has had her tutored since she was young, right, Shisha?
I apologize,
but my team is already full.
Oh, really? Well, that's a shame.
At first, I thought you were short on people.
Because it seemed like you had to take kids who are
far from the cream of the crop to compete.
If we're judging by language proficiency,
everyone on my team is considered top-tier.
You don't need to worry, Teacher Thip. Thank you.
Alright, no problem.
Then I wish you the best of luck.
I hope your students
don't step out of line,
or do anything to disgrace the school,
until the competition day.
I believe I've chosen capable and suitable students.
I didn't just pick them because I had no choice.
But thanks again for your concern.
Good luck.
Well.
Yes, and you?
Stop playing the innocent good girl.
Or I'll spill your secrets.
That you are such a jealous one.
And everything else you've been doing too.
So watch your back.
Good luck.
Guess she hasn't studied much.
Why did you do that?
I like this pair better.
But I like this one. It's more stylish.
This one is more stylish.
But the other color teams are wearing the exact same pair, you know?
Earn, a sub just asked about showing your face again.
They're offering a lot more money this time.
This one looks cheap, right?
Yeah.
Earn.
Which pair do you think is prettier?
This one or this one?
I think this pair looks nice.
Don't you think it's a bit too expensive?
It's 4,000 baht a pair.
I'm picking this pair. It's prettier.
If you want me to pay right now,
I don't have the money.
Earn, did you get paid for your tutoring yet?
Can Pan borrow some first?
Our allowance comes in two days.
Pan will pay you back then.
Sure.
By the way, Earn.
Don't you want to be a cheerleader again?
This is our last year.
Um, no thanks.
Okay, that's fine.
But let me know if you change your mind.
Did you know I'm not the only one she borrowed money from?
She keeps borrowing from everyone.
It's so freaking annoying.
I don't know what her problem is lately.
Earn, wait for me a sec. I need to reapply my lipstick.
Do I look good?
Want some?
Hey, is Nano really not going to pay us back?
The fan meet ticket sale is coming up.
And the cheer outfits are expensive too.
It's okay, Pan.
If you really don't have it, you can borrow from me first.
It's fine.
I'm just a bit annoyed.
I don't know what's up with Nano lately.
Take that.
Ow, that hurts.
Watching the sunset alone?
Can I join?
Sure.
But it'll cost you.
I was the one who picked the lock to this rooftop.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be up here.
Are you bragging?
You even chased me down once, remember?
That was because you were skipping class.
And you were smoking.
Okay.
Quit if you can.
Don't do things that are bad for you.
I'm not addicted. Just once in a while.
Just to clear my head.
You're so young.
What's there to think about so much?
Well...
Growing up alone is lonely.
Anything that brings comfort, I consider a friend.
Something like that.
I understand.
My mom raised me alone too.
I just found out
she's been smoking secretly this whole time.
Found out last year.
And now she has cancer.
I'm sorry to hear that.
When I warned you,
I did it as an older sister.
You still have a long life ahead of you.
It's not too late to quit.
So...
You became a teacher here because of your mom?
Is the money that good?
The benefits are good.
And I have time after work to see her.
Also,
I get a bonus if my students compete.
So asking me to compete...
It's because I'm part of getting your bonus?
I'd be lying if I said it wasn't.
But I truly believe in you, Belle.
I know.
You've said it many times.
Even in front of Teacher Thip.
My aunt has never even said that.
Just do your best.
And in the meantime, behave yourself.
Or you might not get to compete.
You finally got moved to a normal class.
Instead of detention.
Try to stay there.
Are you worried as a teacher,
or as a sister?
Let's do this.
On this rooftop...
there's no Teacher Nalin.
And no student named Belle.
Just an older and younger sister.
If...
you're stressed or need to vent,
tell me.
No need to smoke anymore.
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
P' Nalin.
Honestly, before this...
I didn't care much about life, to be real.
But right now,
maybe things can get better.
If you're using me...
I'm willing.
As for first place,
I'll bring it to you.
And I'll hold it over you later.
Or if there's a zeroth place,
I'll get that for you too.
Once this is done, let's cut it and continue.
Is this okay?
Okay.
Then let's split it up like this for now.
Sure.
P' Jane.
Our color's water is gone.
What?
But we just bought several packs to refill it.
Now I know why we run out of water so fast.
Can you stop taking the stand's water?
The kids don't have enough to drink.
Can't we even share this much?
We're on the same team.
But you took 3,000 of our budget.
The cheerleaders haven't bought anything to share with the stand.
One bottle. Is that enough?
Or do you want the whole pack?
I'm not trying to start a fight.
But what did you do with the 3,000 budget?
Stop being so nosy.
We didn't even ask how much your stupid cutouts cost.
We have receipts for everything. Wanna see? I'll show you.
What did you do with the money?
Whatever we do with it is our business.
You're only working here because we chose you.
Don't take yourself so seriously.
I'm working here
because our friends chose the theme I came up with.
You tell me, what did you do with the money?
Paying off debts? Huh?
Isn't that you?
Hurry up and graduate so you can pay off your mom's debt.
I never told anyone about my mom's debt.
How do you know?
It was you?
You're the one who tore my notebook? Huh?
Hey, hey.
It was you who tore my notebook?
It was you who tore my notebook. Why?
Stop.
Don't mess with me.
If you're so tough, hit me.
Let go of me, I will.
You picked the wrong person to mess with.
Shit.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Need a ride anywhere, little girl?
My house is far, old man. Can you handle it?
Whoa, calling me an old man? Isn't that a bit harsh?
So why the sudden invitation?
Usually, when I ask for a ride, you say no.
Well, I need a favor.
But don't worry, there's definitely compensation.
Uh-huh.
Hey Belle, do you believe in lucky charms?
Yeah.
They say
a four-leaf clover means good luck.
I wanted to buy one as encouragement before the competition.
Never mind.
I'll buy it for myself as a reward after we win.
Let's go, before I change my mind.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, it's hot. I just warmed it up.
Eat a lot, Belle.
I will, thank you.
Does your mom usually cook at home?
My mom has never cooked for me, not even once.
Uh, I mean...
I don't have a mom.
Oh, uh...
My mom passed away when I was little. So...
I grew up with nannies, and mostly eat out.
My regular customers always say my cooking
tastes like a mother's home cooking.
I used to give Earn some to share with her friends at school.
I did bring it once.
But nobody ate it. Such a waste.
Then bring it to me next time.
Okay, next time, I'll pack some for Earn to give you.
Eat up.
Okay, I'll leave you two alone.
I'll go now.
Since it's just you two, make sure you lock up properly.
And turn off the lights.
Okay.
So, do you like the compensation?
Um, yeah, it's good.
But I still don't know what you need me to do.
Well...
I want you to help me take some pictures.
I need to post some sexy photos.
It's a request from a sub.
I figured if someone else took them, they'd look better.
But, the photos...
Let me show you.
It has to have ears and a tail like this.
Is it that bad?
Ugh, I don't want to do it anymore.
Wait.
No, no, I mean...
The outfit is cute, but...
I just imagined you in it and felt...
Isn't it a bit too revealing?
But...
You've seen me in more revealing things before.
I mean, I've shown you a bunch of them.
Oh.
Okay, yeah, right.
You go ahead and eat. I'll go change.
Come upstairs when you're done.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
Why are you...
looking at me like that?
Like...
what?
Never mind.
Do I look like a cat?
You look cute.
Hm?
Uh... I mean...
Yeah, you look like a cat.
Um...
So...
Wait a sec.
Okay.
I'm going to take the picture now.
1... 2...
1... 2... 3...
That should...
be enough. So...
Okay, I'll get going.
Wait.
Wanna get scratched by a cat?
Sit down.
Where are you rushing off to?
We're not done taking pictures yet.
Take it again.
Okay.
Should we keep taking pictures?
How are you?
You did very well today. My mom really appreciates it.
Thank you
Should I get my rewards then?
Hey.
When I reply fast, she disappears.
Oranicha, 19 points.
Nicharee.
20, perfect score.
Quit if you can.
Don't do things that are bad for you.
Our school...
has a unique wai unlike anywhere else, Nicharee.
See, you can do it if you want to.
And there's no smell of smoke today, either.
Do you have a cold, Sister? Is that why you can't smell it?
Suddenly getting compliments like this is creeping me out.
Surprise!
[Sophie: You can stay over today. My mom's not home.]
[Sophie: As many rounds as you want, before midnight.]
Here are some snacks from our color's stand.
Share them with everyone.
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
Jane.
How are you doing? Did Nano slap you yesterday?
Have you told Teacher Thip yet?
I didn't get slapped. Just almost.
But it's fine.
Jane confronted her about the money, so she lost her temper.
I'm just glad Jane's okay.
Here's the thing.
Nano runs a fundraising page for stray cats.
But no one knows if she actually uses the money for the cats.
A friend in Class D asked for proof once.
But she couldn't get it.
And Nano yelled at her.
So Jane confronted her about the cheerleader budget, right?
And it turned into this mess...
Based on what we volunteered for last time,
I'll have Belle and Earn compete in the French storytelling.
Goi and Wan, you need to study more.
Because you'll be answering general knowledge questions.
This part of the competition is in Thai.
I think it suits you two better.
Because you'll probably do better than Belle.
How many colors are on the French flag?
Three.
In what order?
Red, white, blue.
Vertical or horizontal?
Horizontal.
Please give this homework to Wan too.
Finish all of this.
Shit, wrong.
Vertical!
What horizontal?
Hey, let's go home.
I'm leaving now, P' Jane. Bye.
Sure, get home safely. Bye.
The poor thing is badly hurt.
I saw your cat rescue page. Let me help with the medical bills.
Thank you, Sister.
I'll go now.
Nano runs a fundraising page for stray cats.
But no one knows if she actually uses the money for the cats.
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I followed you.
I didn't think you were actually bringing the cat to the vet.
Just because you think I tore your notebook,
you thought I was scamming the Sister too?
Something like that.
So now you know I didn't tear it?
Wait, if you didn't do it, who did?
You don't need to know. Just consider this an apology on their behalf.
Because it's my fault I didn't stop them.
I'm sorry too.
For saying all those things to you.
I knew it...
Someone as pretty as you wouldn't scam anyone.
Uh, I gotta go now.
See ya.
Oh, Nano.
Don't forget to do the sports day accounting for me. Bye.
Can we take a break?
What's wrong?
I just can't do it lately.
Can we not do this?
Let's just go back to taking pictures like before.
We can't, Earn.
It's not like when we first started.
Pictures alone just don't sell anymore. It has to be videos.
Earn.
Like... it just has to be videos now.
The girl-on-girl market isn't even that big.
Especially with our faces hidden like this.
But if we show our faces,
we could get 100,000 right from the first time, Earn.
P' Som.
I told you I'm not going to show my face.
Please, I really can't do this.
Aioon.
Wanna try shooting?
But I don't know how to play.
It's okay. I'll have my friends teach you.
Hey, teach her how to shoot.
Here.
Have you ever played?
Never.
Do it like this.
Here, hold it.
Like this.
Like this?
And then aim, and throw it into the hoop.
Almost made it. Try again.
One, two, three.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Does it hurt anywhere, Sophie?
If something is bothering you, you can tell me.
I was just walking too fast.
So I wasn't careful.
I was watching the basketball practice earlier.
I totally understand why everyone adores Amy.
Things are great these days.
If you want to scream for someone, you can, and no one will judge you.
But back in my day, oh my.
Screaming like that would get you punished.
Not to mention dating.
And...
In your day, were there many students who liked each other in school?
In any era, there are always students who like each other in school.
Parents...
often think that sending their kids to an all-girls school
will keep them away from romance.
Because there are no boys.
But the truth is,
love doesn't discriminate.
My first love...
happened right here in this school.
Back then, I could only wonder...
If love is a good thing,
then why is our love considered wrong?
I still think that way now.
Yes, P' Title, what's up?
Nano, I've transferred the money for last month's event.
Thank you so much.
If there's more work, I'll take you to the casting. Okay?
Sure.
Call me anytime. I really want to work.
Okay, thank you.
Wow, really?
Has Nano sunk so low as to borrow from Khaopan?
Yeah, Khaopan told me the other day.
That's just sad.
Borrowing from someone poorer than her?
If she's actually poorer.
I heard Class B talking the other day too.
Nano borrowed from them as well.
What's going on?
Is she going to borrow from the whole world?
Did you come see me at the basketball court earlier?
Yeah.
So why didn't you come say hi?
You just disappeared.
I saw you were busy.
Jealous?
Why would I be?
I'm just one of the people you're talking to.
Look at you, all jealous
and feeling neglected.
I was just annoyed
that I texted and no one replied.
My phone was in the locker.
Because I was practicing.
Right.
Whatever you say.
Hey.
You're not just one of the people I'm talking to.
Since I started talking to you,
I haven't been with anyone else.
You're the one who leaves me on read.
I waited so long last night I couldn't sleep.
I never leave you on read.
I'm sorry.
My mom came in to check if I was asleep.
So I had to turn off my phone.
Oh, and about coming to the court...
Did you need something?
Well...
My mom invited you to come hang out with us this Saturday.
But I told her you have basketball practice.
Nah, I'm not practicing.
Why would I?
It's your birthday this Saturday.
Like I'd forget Sophie's birthday.
Isn't basketball practice important?
If you lose, your fans will be disappointed.
Nothing is more important than how you feel.
Forgot.
There's a camera.
It's been broken for ages.
I haven't reported it yet.
So it hasn't been fixed.
Hey, can we just get the 4,500 zone today?
Let's just go for VIP. It's just a little more for a signed poster.
Here, Earn, here.
Can you pay me back today?
How much?
Ten thousand.
Hey, hey, it's starting.
Okay.
Refresh now.
Damn it! Mine is still loading.
This is bad. Shit!
It's not loading at all.
What do we do?
I want this zone.
If you're free, book it.
Yay! I got 3 VIP tickets.
Awesome. Transfer the money to our friend at 7-Eleven to pay.
Okay.
Earn, can Pan borrow from you first?
Earn, you don't need to.
I'm seriously asking you.
Do you have money problems lately?
You've put me off so many times.
Well, if you became color president, you would've gotten your money back long ago.
But you lost to that Jane.
And you gossiped about me to other classes, right?
Don't try to change the subject.
What you need to do right now,
is transfer my money back.
Transferred.
Go spend it on your boys.
Thanks.
Did you tell her?
That I was talking about her to other people?
I didn't.
If it wasn't you, then who was it, Earn?
You're the only one I told.
Hey, guys.
If you're done getting tickets, I'd like to get back to studying.
Because we can only use this room until 6.
Belle.
I'm really asking you.
Since when did you start paying attention in class?
Or is it...
since Teacher Nalin started teaching?
Belle, she's totally your type, right?
Just like Teacher Som.
Get out.
I'm not leaving.
Why, Belle?
Or are you going to run home and cry to your mom?
Say that again.
I said, run home and cry to your mom!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Don't...
Shit!
What the hell are you saying?
So what, motherless freak!
Stop!
Everyone, stop!