( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
I used to wonder if my life
was already a happy one.
Yes, please wait a moment.
What can I get you, ma'am?
Hello, welcome! What would you like?
Sure, please take a seat first.
Tell them to wait a bit.
Some say money can buy happiness, if you have enough of it.
I'm home!
Hey, sweetie.
Hello.
Hi.
My grades are out.
How is it?
Mom!
Huh?
4.0!
I have your reward ready. Who's favorite is this?
Here's a reward for my smart girl.
But I'm lucky that I can make my parents happy
without spending a single cent.
Do you still want to study here, sweetie?
I was just looking, Dad. The school is beautiful.
But as for my own happiness,
it might be too expensive for my family to afford.
Wow, this is amazing, sweetie!
Let's take a picture together.
Sure!
Give me 16 poses! 1... 2... 3!
But I guess that didn't matter,
because I believed I could create my own happiness.
Hey!
Is Flute your bias?
Yeah.
Marc is my bias!
1... 2... 3...
Marc-Flute!
Exactly! It has to be Marc-Flute!
So true, it has to be this ship!
Aww, so cute.
Making new friends
was easier than I thought.
I need everyone to close your eyes.
Alright, everyone. You can open your eyes now.
Congratulations!
You two have been selected to be our cheerleaders for this year!
Give them a round of applause!
Could you two please introduce yourselves?
Hi, my name is Earn.
When I count, answer together, okay?
Ready to cheer?
Ready!
3... 4...
Earn, you're not keeping up.
Earn, you're a bit slow. Turn back and look at your friends.
You're the only one turning back.
Watch your friends. Okay, everyone, hands down.
Ready to cheer?
Earn can't really keep up, huh?
That's how it is. Did the seniors just pick based on looks?
But I don't even think Earn is that pretty.
Right?
I think Shisha is much more charming.
I feel like Earn tries too hard.
Well, Earn comes from a different background than us.
She has to try harder, that's normal.
I think...
It's pitiful.
3... 4...
Okay, take a break.
Oh, Shisha, new bag? It's so cute!
Really? It wasn't expensive at all, just a bit over ten thousand.
Should we all get one?
Earn, what color do you want? White?
Um, I think it's a bit too expensive.
Hey guys, the car's here. Let's go.
Where are you going?
We're going to sleep over at Shisha's house.
We'll get going now.
You've seemed busy lately,
so we didn't invite you.
Maybe next time.
That was the first time I admitted that
not having enough money might mean some happiness can't be bought.
And it might mean the word 'us' that my friends used,
no longer included me.
Oh, Shisha. You haven't gone home yet?
Yeah, I lost my wallet.
Have you looked carefully? Need help?
Here, I'll help you look.
Try looking in your own bag.
For a poor person like Earn,
stealing a friend's wallet wouldn't be surprising, right?
Shisha! Shisha, stop!
Why are you doing this to me?! Don't hurt me!
Shisha, stop!
Shisha, stop! What are you doing?
Shisha, that's enough! Stop right now!
Shisha, stop!
Stop!
What's going on?
What is happening here?
I lost my wallet,
and I found it in her bag.
I asked for it back nicely, but she wouldn't give it back.
And then she hit me!
I asked nicely!
Why did you have to get physical?
I didn't do it, teacher!
Why are you like this?
You're the one who stole my junior's wallet, right?
Did you think just returning it would end this? Huh?
Come here!
Bow down to her right now!
Shisha, please help me.
Shisha, aren't we friends?
Ugh, you're so slow.
I told you to bow. Bow!
Huh? You won't bow? Huh!
I told you to bow, and you refuse?!
I said bow! Won't you bow?!
I told you to bow!
Get back here!
What did you say? You don't want to ruin the school's reputation?
And what about my daughter?
They said if you drop the charges,
they won't press charges against Ornnicha for stealing the money either.
Is this true, sweetie?
Teacher,
we don't have any proof.
But kids this age are just like this.
They fight, it's normal.
You don't need to take it too seriously.
Just let it go,
so it doesn't become a big deal.
Honey,
if Earn moves out of the science-math track, she'll lose her scholarship.
We can't afford the tuition fee.
Earn.
Putting the bullying aside,
are you still happy at this school?
It's okay.
I know how hard you worked to study here.
Now it's my turn to work hard for you.
Ugh! I told you not to walk behind me!
Are you blind? I'm filming here!
Hey!!
You're so damn loud!
Go dance somewhere else. I'm trying to sleep.
What's her problem? Damn it.
You can sit next to me.
I might be weird,
but at least I'm not an asshole.
What the hell is your problem?
And what the hell is YOUR problem?
Why did you throw that at me? What did I do to you?
I can feel that you wrote it.
Forget it. She is weird.
Just ignore her.
Let's keep watching.
I thought that if I just tried hard enough like always,
maybe everyone could be happy.
Which answer did you choose again?
I think it's C.
Wow, you're good!
Help me clean up, sweetie.
Okay.
But when it comes to money,
sometimes no matter how hard you try, it's never enough.
[The school break starts next week.]
[We'll cancel the tutoring for now, Earn.]
P'Som!
P'Som, I can't afford this.
It's okay, just eat. It's my treat.
Why is it so delicious?
Of course, expensive stuff is delicious.
Chef, you can make the next one.
So, how is it?
Is the dream school life what you expected?
It's... good.
The teaching is much better than my old school, and the activities are grand.
I've only been teaching here for a few days, and I've already heard everything.
About you having to change classes.
But you know, bad people are bad no matter what.
No matter how expensive the tuition is, it doesn't really screen the kids.
The good kids here are too good.
As for the assholes...
they're scarier than poor kids.
Just being able to study here,
without having to worry about tuition,
isn't that enough for them?
Not necessarily.
If one day money isn't an issue,
other issues will just become more apparent.
Hmm, Teacher Som sounds so mature now.
Are you sure you're the same P'Som who cried over a breakup
and asked to sleep over at my house?
Oh, stop.
I just broke up with my boyfriend.
Why did you guys break up?
What do you think about people who do sex content?
You mean people who sell porn videos?
Well, nothing much.
As long as they're not causing trouble for anyone, isn't that fine?
My boyfriend dumped me because I make sex content.
But I understand him.
Back then, I really had financial problems.
Just like you do now.
Aren't you afraid of
your digital footprint?
I only make faceless content.
If there's no proof it's me, what's there to be afraid of?
If you're interested in joining the industry, let me know.
Just doing it for fun, I can make over a hundred thousand a month.
Over a hundred thousand?
To be honest,
with your body and skin,
just posting some slightly revealing photos,
you don't even have to be naked.
People will subscribe, and you can easily make 20-30 thousand a month.
But...
I've never slept with anyone before.
And nobody has ever told me I'm sexy before either.
The reason they say you're not sexy
is because they've never seen you undress.
So?
Do you want me to teach you how to undress?
I'm so proud to have you.
Pun, why are you turning the sound on? Just watch the video.
Are you stupid? We're going to get caught.
I can't see their faces.
But maybe we can recognize the voice of a student from our school.
Ugh, I've scrolled so much my eyes hurt.
I still haven't found any videos with our school uniform.
I thought they said she were fired for making a video with a student from our school?
Or maybe it was a kid from another school?
Hey, is this it?
Yeah, it looks like our school uniform.
Shit, probably not.
Hey.
The fan meeting seating plan is out.
Should we go for VIP? It's close to the stage.
Yeah.
Let's use the French room, the internet is fast.
Earn can definitely get them.
She's the ticket-buying champion three times in a row, right?
P'Som, could you hide the content where we're in school uniforms first?
I think my friends are getting suspicious.
I might not be able to yet, Earn.
The engagement is really good right now.
Don't overthink it. No one will know.
I'll transfer your cut. We made a lot this round.
Once you see the money, you'll stop worrying.
By the way, when will you agree to do face-reveal content with me?
Fans are sending requests.
If you agree, we can make four times what we did with the uniform video.
Maybe not yet.
Hey, Earn.
Nano borrowed ten thousand from me.
She said if I became the color team president, she'd get the money to pay me back.
But since I didn't get the position, she hasn't returned it.
And the fan meeting ticket sales are coming up.
If she doesn't pay me back...
Earn, do you have some I could borrow first?
Yeah.
I do. Don't worry, Pun.
Has Nano ever borrowed money from you, Earn?
Yeah, she has.
But not that much.
How much is not that much?
About the same as what she borrowed from you.
And has she paid you back yet?
I really want to know what she's doing with the money.
It's been a month, man, and she still hasn't paid me back.
Her family seems rich too, right?
I've seen Nano taking care of a lot of stray cats.
She also mentioned that cat food is really expensive.
She feels sorry for them and doesn't want to leave them on the street.
And her family doesn't support her buying cat food.
Is it really just for raising cats?
Guess who?
Hey, shouldn't I be the one asking that?
I just said it for you.
So you wouldn't have to tire yourself out.
If I didn't want to get tired,
I probably wouldn't have come to see you, right?
I'm really busy today.
I need to hurry up and go.
You're busy every day.
More like you're bored of me.
I'm not bored.
Normally,
I never really think too much about you.
But I don't know why, lately my feelings have been strange.
I mean, we've had this secret thing going on for so long.
And I only do this kind of thing with you.
I think...
I'm catching feelings.
And you probably feel the same way, right?
What you said on that show...
My name is Sasikamol.
It starts with an 'S' too.
Did you mean me?
Earn.
Where's Belle?
She probably went to the restroom.
In the restroom for the whole period?
Here, at the end of the period,
please collect everyone's exercises and leave them at the front of the room.
I'll be right back.
And please hand these out too.
Why aren't you in class?
I don't feel like it.
Smoking is not allowed here.
I know.
But I don't care.
Rules aren't meant to be followed all the time, right?
Learn to follow your heart sometimes.
Do you know how? If not, I can teach you.
Before you try teaching me...
go back to your class.
[Did you transfer money? 20,000 baht?]
[It's my savings from tutoring.]
[I'll give it to Dad for the car repair first. Don't worry.]
Jane.
Are you here to read?
No.
My notebook got torn.
I thought I'd come borrow some tape from the teacher around here to fix it.
I don't know where they are.
Jane, you can tell me anything.
Even though I might not be able to help much,
you can really talk to me.
Thank you, Earn.
I really don't know what I did wrong.
Why do they have to bully me like this?
You're not wrong, Jane.
The people bullying you are.
Don't be discouraged.
Let me see.
It's torn up so badly.
I think I'll go find a big book to press it flat.
Hey, it's okay, I'll go look for one myself.
The encyclopedias are over there.
Oh.
Okay, okay, I'll be right back.
Hey, someone's coming.
Run!
What?
What the...?
What are you doing?
Oh, hi.
Amy, right?
Oh, I went to hear you sing the other day.
Wow, you were really awesome.
Thanks.
Oh, this is my friend.
She just went through a breakup, she's crying.
Cry!
She doesn't really want anyone to see her face.
Okay, okay. I won't bother you guys then.
I'll get going now.
Cheer up!
Your hair is a mess.
Did it look natural?
Maybe.
Sorry I'm late. I ran into someone I knew.
Hmm, you have a friend now, Jane?
We just met.
By the way, Earn,
how do the cheer stand and the cheerleaders usually split the budget?
Actually, other color teams usually split it evenly.
But our team usually wins the cheerleader more than the cheer stand.
So we split it 60/40.
But sometimes even 70.
Whoa!
Why do cheerleaders have so many expenses?
I'm not exactly sure, but from what I've seen,
it's mostly for off-campus practice venues, costumes,
or hair and makeup on the sports day, things like that.
But I don't know about the rest.
Then it's okay. I'll go talk to Nano myself.
Need my help?
Hey!
Watch out!
Shit!
Hey, I'm so sorry.
Does it hurt a lot?
Hey, go get some ice for a cold compress.
It doesn't hurt much now.
And I don't feel anything at all.
Do you want to go to the doctor?
Keep the compress on, it won't heal.
Nano, I'd like to split the budget between the cheerleaders and the stand.
Can we do 50/50 like the other teams?
The cheer stand taking 20 is enough.
Our group usually wins the cheerleader trophy all the time.
But the cheer stand is always last, there's no need to invest in it.
20 is barely enough for welfare expenses alone.
There won't be that many people joining the stand anyway.
But then we wouldn't have enough money for cutouts.
Then scale it down.
Then can you give me a breakdown?
What exactly do the cheerleaders need, and how much budget?
Just for the costumes,
we always have to pay out of our own pockets every year.
Not to mention the hair and makeup artists.
All of that already exceeds 70%.
Then you scale it down.
You're determined, aren't you?
The highlight of our school's sports day
is the cheerleaders.
No one wants to scream their lungs out singing cheer songs.
Since you just transferred here, learn to adapt.
Don't be annoying.
Then I'll go ask the juniors who wants to be on the stand.
And I'll calculate the budget based on the actual numbers.
Try me.
This will be what our stand looks like this year.
Time Travel... it can go back in time, like
time machines, dinosaurs, or like
you could dress up as any character from the past.
So whoever wants to be on the stand or wants to help make props,
just let me know.
P'Jane.
If our whole class wants to be on the stand, will there be enough seats?
Wow, the whole class?
Yeah, of course there's enough! Definitely enough. Sure!
So many juniors want to be on the stand.
I guess the cheer budget needs to be doubled.
I don't think 50/50 is going to work anymore.
Hey everyone.
Thank you so much for joining the cheer stand this year.
But with this, we probably won't have much budget left to help the cheerleaders.
But I still want to watch P'Nano and the cheerleaders dance beautifully!
Yeah! The cheerleaders are the pride of our group!
We'll try our best.
But it might not be as grand as previous years.
P'Jane.
What is it?
My friends and I are backing out.
I have friends who are cheerleaders, and I want them to be able to do their best.
If we don't join the stand,
the cheerleaders will get their budget back, right?
Um... yeah.
I'm sorry, P'Jane.
Hello, P'Amy.
We're shooting a school promotional video.
Clip it nicely.
Hello, ma'am.
Oh, hello ma'am.
Hello, teacher. Hello, ma'am.
Thank you.
I just dropped by to say hi to Teacher Thip
and brought some snacks for everyone.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Amy looks very proper today.
Are you here to receive an award too?
Today, the school selected exemplary student representatives, ma'am.
Both from the academic and extracurricular sides
to shoot a promotional VTR.
Watawan here is the representative for outstanding extracurricular activities.
The song she composed herself is actually going viral right now.
Um, ma'am, excuse me.
If you're ready, could I interview you first?
Sure.
This way, please.
Please.
Ma'am, how important do you think the smart library
is to the education of students like us?
I think it's very important.
Because kids these days
can all find information online.
I probably can't compete with the younger generation when it comes to technology.
So, I'd like to make a contribution
towards purchasing and developing educational equipment.
I'll hand it over to the committee and the teachers
to allocate and purchase for the school.
This contribution I'm making
will hopefully help the students
further their education.
Ma'am, do you have a message for students
who are considering enrolling here?
This is a school that teaches students to be well-mannered
and to be proper young ladies, as they should be.
Come join our Anna Patronage Tipwan family.
For P'Sophie,
how should a proper young lady behave nowadays?
The most important thing for every student,
whether now or in the past,
is simply to know your duties
and fulfill them to the best of your ability,
without causing trouble for anyone.
That, to me, is considered being a proper young lady.
And how does this school help
further students' interests outside of academics?
Actually, our school supports extracurricular activities quite a lot.
But beyond that,
we have a parent association that constantly encourages students
and fully supports us with equipment.
Which I think is a really lovely thing.
Um, computers at other schools might be just for doing reports,
but our school's computers also have music production software installed.
So I consider this award I received today
to be mine and everyone's who helped vote for me.
Including you too, ma'am. Thank you.
Thank you.
This friend of yours is quite nice.
I see her coming over every day for you to tutor her.
I thought she'd be a slacker.
Amy is a smart person.
She might fall behind in class sometimes because she does a lot of activities,
but whatever she's interested in,
she excels at it.
How should we edit this?
There's a part where there's a lot of dead air.
Oh, P'Amy. I thought you had already gone home.
Wow, your answers today were so good!
If I were P'Sophie's mom, I'd be so thrilled.
Wow, really?
Yeah!
Hey, Aioon.
Why don't you let P'Amy help check the pacing of the edit?
I'm going to go lock the club room door first, in case I forget.
Okay.
I'll get going now.
Are you fully recovered?
You're even here helping shoot content today.
It still hurts a bit, but it's okay.
You're so hardworking.
Do you want to be the club president like Anna?
I just wanted to try shooting content, so I came to help.
I like filming when you guys are doing activities.
Really?
So among all the things you've filmed, are there any behind-the-scenes of me?
There's a lot.
You do so many activities,
and you're so talented.
Actually, I've had a crush on you too.
At first, I thought it was just like a regular fan admiring you,
like everyone else.
But...
after seeing you do so many things,
I felt like I wanted to get to know you better.
I'm glad you hit me in the face with that basketball that day.
It gave us a chance to talk.
And today you even came to talk to me first.
I just wanted to tell you how I feel.
Even if you already have someone you like, it's okay.
Thank you so much.
You're so cool, Aioon,
for being brave enough to confess to me directly.
I don't even have the courage to tell someone I like them directly like this.
From now on, if you need my help with anything,
or if you want some advice, you can reach out to me anytime, okay?
Don't hesitate at all.
Now, show me the video. I'll help you edit it.
Okay!
[@Nalin A student from Class 11C skipped school this afternoon.]
[Teacher Nalin, were you not aware of this?]
[Even though you are a new homeroom teacher,]
[please take good care of your students.]
I have exams coming up.
Do you even study? Please, at least read a little.
By the way, what should we eat?
"Whatever" again? Then you choose.
Not this one.
Let's have something Japanese.
May I speak with Belle for a moment?
If you're going to break the rules,
why do it in a way where you get caught?
Just in case you didn't know, teacher...
I'm the Mother Superior's biological niece.
That means...
no matter how badly I behave,
or how much I want to get expelled,
my aunt will never expel me.
So you don't need to care about me.
Just leave it between me and my aunt.
I don't care about your personal life.
But I pity your skills.
If you want the school to stop targeting you,
prove yourself in the right way.
I don't think I have to prove myself,
especially in this stupid school.
Do you really not know what freedom is?
If you really want freedom,
you wouldn't act in a way that makes people constantly try to control you.
The more you act out,
the more you're just demanding attention.
I know that at this school,
there are a lot of things that don't make sense.
It's very different from your old school environment.
Stop running away,
and try to actually beat the Mother Superior, how about that?
What do you mean?
If you agree to compete in the French contest and win,
I'll talk to the Mother Superior for you.
I'll suggest she transfer you back to an international school
where my friend teaches.
There's a scholarship to study abroad.
If you really want to escape your aunt,
this is a great option.
Or even if you don't want to go,
it's an excuse with enough weight to make the Mother Superior
accept you.
And who are you? Why would my aunt listen to you?
Before you can make the Mother Superior believe in you,
you have to believe in me first.
Do you have any plans for celebrating this Saturday?
This Saturday?
Don't tell me you studied so hard you forgot your own birthday.
Oh.
You're right.
If you don't know where to go yet,
should we go to my friend's resort? The one we went to last year.
Sure, if you want to go.
Invite Amy along too.
It's your birthday, invite your close friend so you can have fun.
And I can get to know Amy better too.
Okay.
I'm here.
I told the doctor we can start the targeted therapy.
And where did you get the money for that, honey?
I have some savings.
My illness is causing you so much trouble.
Don't say that.
What trouble?
When I was a kid, I was sick all the time.
And you never complained.
But now I'm a grown-up.
Anything I can do for you,
please let me do it for you, Mom.
I'll be getting a bonus from the school next month anyway.
As for your medical bills,
I can pay them no matter how much they are.
Don't worry.
Thank you, honey.
You're such a good girl.
Where's Teacher Nalin?
She's probably not coming today.
She said we'll start practicing when we have all 4 people.
So you're here because...?
Yeah, I entered the competition too.
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Just scrolling through my feed.
Is that Amy?
Yeah, she's singing a Marc-Flute song.
Marc-Flute?
Oh, the ship you like, right?
Yeah.
[Even without seeing your face, I can't take it anymore.]
You saw that, right?
Yeah.
Belle, can you please not tell anyone about this?
Who would I even tell?
I won't tell anyone anyway.
But you probably think badly of me now, don't you?
Why do you care how I look at you?
What kind of person you are,
you know yourself best.
Have you heard that?
In the end, whether people find out about this in the future or not,
I think
you know best what kind of person you are.
That's the most important thing.
And also...
I've never seen you as a bad person.
I've never met anyone who studies as hard as you.
In this school, you're probably the most frugal person too.
So I think...
you making sex content,
I think you must have your own reasons.
If in the future someone bullies you saying
you do this because you're hungry for money,
tell me.
I'll punch them in the face for you.
Promise me?
That you won't tell anyone.
On the honor of the Mother Superior.
And I'd be happy to hire you immediately.
If you promise me one thing.
What is it?
I want you to get close to the students.
Learn about their personal lives,
or any bad behaviors they are secretly doing.
And report back to me.
So that we can eliminate the problem early on.
But, Mother Superior,
if we use our position as teachers to approach students
with hidden agendas,
isn't that a violation of the students' privacy?
The parents have entrusted us to fully take care of their children.
Therefore,
if there's anything that could damage our school's reputation,
we won't consider it
a private matter for the students at all.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Will you accept my offer, Teacher Nalin?
Well, Teacher Nalin?
Are there any students at risk of ruining our school's reputation?