( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
He had the same look in his eyes as you.
What's the fun
in doing the sensible thing?
Doing what no one else can
is what makes you a badass.
This guy might be a good fit for us.
It was the final years of the Edo period.
Gathered at the Shieikan dojo
home of the Tennen Rishin-ryu style...
We'll have another match, Toshizo.
...were ten fearsome warriors,
including Hijikata Toshizo.
After all, the one thing that really
gets a man's blood pumping
is good old-fashioned violence.
Ain't that right?
I swear, I'll never lose to anyone again!
This was a turbulent era.
This is the story of men
who lived and died by the sword.
Tennen Rishin-ryu: Sword of No Light!
SONG OF THE SAMURAI
FEBRUARY 1863
February 1863.
The men of the Shieikan dojo came to Kyo,
seeking to become the strongest.
But they were unable
to find a way to make a living
let alone make a name
for themselves with their swords.
Meanwhile...
You bastard! You're a manslayer!
DIVINE RETRIBUTION
Aizu clan samurai, shogunate allies
were being attacked one after another,
spreading terror across the city of Kyo.
ONE MONTH LATER
This is good.
This isn't enough.
By the way, Eisaburo,
what were you up to last night?
Huh? Hmm? Well...
You smelled of face powder
when you came back.
Don't tell me you were doing this?
You're more of a player
than you look, you sly dog!
No, that's not it!
Where would I get the money for that?
Gosh, that's suspicious.
It's not like that.
If we had that kind of money...
Did you want to go with him too, Yamanami?
Of course not!
I'm hungry.
If we don't find a way to make
a living today, our savings will run out.
Fine.
Hello? Anyone home?
Hey!
Still stinks like a bunch
of sweaty guys in here.
Sasaki Tadasaburo?
What are you doing here?
Hey.
Please calm down.
Mr. Sasaki was also a shogunate official
involved with the Roshigumi.
He got screwed over
by Kiyokawa, same as us.
What gives?
An official who is officially useless?
Seriously? Don't talk to me, you monkey.
The only ones here worth talking to...
are you and you.
I presume you've heard the rumors about
manslayers targeting shogunate retainers.
Yes. We've heard they're assassins
sent by the Imperialists.
Naturally, we can't just let
scoundrels like that run wild.
And so, an order has come down
from the powers that be
to gather all swordsmen of skill.
Does that mean we have a chance
to serve the shogunate?
Precisely.
Giving this job to savages like you...
- Personally, I was against it.
- Is that true?
You're not so bad after all!
This is why I hate you savages!
What?
- Sasaki.
- Yes?
Is what you just said true?
Will the shogunate really take us in?
Yes, but there's a catch.
- The Aizu will test you.
- The Aizu?
That's right.
To see if you're actually of any use.
And what if we fail
to get the Aizu's approval?
Then you had better be prepared to starve.
Bring it on!
They're more than a worthy test!
We'll show them what we've got!
KYOTO MILITARY COMMISSIONER
AIZU DOMAIN HEADQUARTERS
What the hell are they doing here?
Serizawa Kamo, Niimi Nishiki,
and Hirayama Goro.
Word that they defied Kiyokawa Hachiro
has reached the ears of the shogunate.
They're considered men of real grit.
Especially Serizawa Kamo.
The man is a monster in a fight.
And where the hell is Kamo?
Master Serizawa went out last night
and has yet to return.
The nerve of him.
Toshi... Toshi! Don't go in there.
They are really fired up.
The Aizu are called Japan's strongest.
The strongest in Japan?
That's right. The Aizu Domain,
ruled by the Matsudaira of Aizu
is a prestigious clan renowned for its
unwavering loyalty to the Tokugawa family.
Their lord, Matsudaira Katamori, was named
the Military Commissioner of Kyoto
and 1,000 of his hand-picked men
are keeping the peace in Kyo.
Line up!
Who is that?
That's Sagawa Kanbei.
Sagawa...
What is a samurai?
That's him.
They call him "Kanbei the Demon."
The greatest in all of Aizu...
No, it wouldn't be an exaggeration
to call him the greatest samurai in Japan.
A samurai is...
The greatest in Japan, huh?
He is the very embodiment of a samurai.
SAGAWA KANBEI
It has been a while, Sasaki.
You seem to be in very high spirits.
I'm glad.
You're from the former Roshigumi?
Yes.
I'm Kondo Isami, the fourth master
of the Tennen Rishin-ryu school.
Yes, I was told you were the ones
with the backbone to defy Kiyokawa.
Hey, he says we've got a backbone.
When, really, we were just broke.
Whatever. It's a minor detail.
How insolent!
I'm here.
SERIZAWA KAMO
Serizawa.
So you're the greatest in all of Aizu,
"Sagawa the Demon," huh?
The one and only.
I like it. He reeks of pure mayhem.
The finest vintage.
All I smell on you is face powder.
So cold.
Hey, move.
Then let's not waste any time.
Show me what you're made of.
We humbly accept.
I shall be your opponent.
If you are victorious
I will recommend you to our lord,
Matsudaira Katamori.
We're going to face
the Demon Chief himself...
He's Japan's greatest samurai.
- Bring the gear.
- Sir!
Hold on a minute.
What's the problem?
We don't need that junk.
Toshi, stand down!
Anyone who would get cold feet
just facing you
isn't someone you would want
in your ranks anyway, right?
Judging by your tone
I take it you'll be my opponent?
That's right.
I'm going to beat you senseless.
- Hijikata, what are you doing?
- You had better be ready!
You!
Such incredible spirit.
- Hey!
- I like this man.
It takes one to know one.
Hey.
- Thank you.
- Stop it!
Stop it now! Creepy!
Tell me your name!
What is your name?
Go.
Hijikata Toshizo.
Hijikata.
That's a great name.
My lord!
Kanbei.
Sir!
What is the meaning of this charade?
That's Lord Matsudaira of the Aizu Domain!
Hurry up and bow!
You're not
planning to fight them
with a stick, are you?
LORD OF THE AIZU DOMAIN,
MATSUDAIRA KATAMORI
You think you can tell if they're
real samurai, risking their lives
with something like that?
Use this.
A real sword.
Cut the crap. If we use a real sword,
the loser is going to die!
Get a hold of yourself.
Then you can die for all I care.
All right, listen up, bastards!
Sooner or later
the shogunate is going to fall.
Kyo is a battlefield now!
It's kill or be killed.
That's all there is to it.
In this Kyo, we Aizu were told
to become the sacrificial pawns
of a dying shogunate!
My lord.
And yet, why did you accept the post
of Protector of Kyoto?
It's obvious.
Because I'm...
Matsudaira Katamori.
But listen.
I don't intend to let
these men die for nothing.
Losing without even putting up a fight
is not Katamori's way, no...
It's not the Aizu way of the samurai!
If we're going to fight
we'll fight to the bitter end,
even if the shogunate itself surrenders.
That is the Aizu way!
My lord!
- My lord!
Understand?
Every last Aizu samurai here
is a damn fool prepared
to die alongside me.
That's what it means
to fight with us.
I like it.
If they're told to die, they would
gut themselves. Look at their eyes.
Are these guys insane?
Look.
In times like these, you need it
to stay true to your convictions.
A little bit of madness.
Now
let's see...
this so-called resolve of yours!
Well...
You are something else.
Interesting.
A duel to the death.
I accept.
Hijikata, there is something
I would like to ask you.
What does the way of the samurai
mean to you?
What a pointless question to ask.
To bloom brilliantly,
then gracefully fall.
That's what it means to be a samurai, no?
I knew I was fond of you.
But
that's precisely why...
I'll fight with everything I have
as a samurai.
Bring it on.
As expected of the greatest samurai
in all of Japan.
Is Toshi going to be okay?
Your path as a samurai...
I hope this is not
the best you can muster.
Now my blood is boiling!
This is where the real fight begins.
Oh?
Hiraseigan.
So he's ready to stake everything
on a mere duel. Not bad.
It'll be over quickly.
How can you tell?
Yamanami, you can't even figure that out?
From the start,
defense wasn't even on their minds.
When the force of ten collides against ten
they'll shatter.
Then the outcome of this match is...
A mutual kill.
They are both going to die?
Hey, Sagawa.
Let us bloom with all our might.
Hold it!
The match is over.
What are you talking about?
This fight isn't over yet!
My lord, let us fight till the end...
You bastard.
Are you screwing with me?
Hey, you bastard!
Did you suddenly decide that dying here
wouldn't do Aizawa any good?
Don't you dare go on the defensive!
That's how you die.
I have no excuse.
Hijikata.
Your desperate, all-or-nothing style
is magnificent.
I welcome you as the fools
who are ready to die alongside the Aizu!
You all got that?
From now on, we live and die with them.
We share one fate!
There will be no objections.
- Yes!
And so, we were officially taken
under the wing of the Aizu clan
and the Mibu Roshigumi
which later became
the Shinsengumi, was born.
Kamo.
I just remembered.
What?
I can't stand that guy.
He was the same way
when he fought me. Utterly reckless.
He has absolutely no fear of death.
Maybe that just means
you don't have enough resolve, Tada.
Rise!
Bow.
The time has finally come,
has it not, Takechi?
Now that Shogun Iemochi
has traveled to the capital
the shogunate has no choice but to promise
the emperor they'll expel the foreigners.
But the Aizu are a problem.
I hear a group called the Mibu Roshigumi
is hunting the Aizu Hunters.
The most dangerous one
is Serizawa Kamo,
a rogue from the Mito Domain.
And Kondo Isami from the Shieikan, too.
And there's one more.
The man who is rumored to have
defeated Sagawa Kanbei of Aizu.
Just a rumor, of course.
No matter who it is,
if they dare stand in our way...
You understand what must be done, Kusaka.
Rest assured.
I know their every move.
Someone is coming.
It could be that killer.
So, you boys are from Aizu, huh?
This pathetic? You're hardly a challenge.
You bastard!
Is it us Aizu that you're after?
I'm an Aizu Hunter.
Aizu Hunter?
I'm here to hunt down every last one
of you rotten shogunate dogs.
You had better be ready to die.
Blink and you're a dead man.
Enjoy.
Aizu Hunter, my ass. Damn it!
There were six men last night alone.
Who the hell is doing this?
Hey, Toshi. Take it easy.
Our men were killed!
How the hell am I supposed to be calm?
The expulsionists have to be the ones
pulling the strings.
Those sons of bitches.
Judging by the sword work,
it's all the work of a single man.
Hey. What do you want?
You seem to be enjoying yourself, huh?
No, I would say there are two of them.
On what grounds?
How can you not even get that, huh?
The Aizu men in Kiyamachi were all hit
with a single killing blow from the front.
But the ones in Uradera
were ambushed from behind.
All right. Now we're talking.
You've got good eyes.
Look, it doesn't matter who the killer is.
They're the ones who picked this fight.
They are mocking us!
So enough with the chatter.
We just need to cut them all down. Right?
Do whatever you want.
What's so damn funny?
There are two Aizu Hunters,
and both are master swordsmen.
They could show up at any time.
Don't let your guard down for a second.
Wipe that grim look off your face.
I'm telling you, I'll take down one or two
of these Aizu Hunters myself.
Talking big, aren't we, Hijikata?
That's what's great about him.
I would say he's more likely
to get seriously hurt.
Don't you worry.
I'm a man who always delivers.
Who says we're counting on you?
I believe in you, Hijikata!
Whoa, where did that come from?
Ever since he saw you beat me,
he has been your biggest admirer.
Why don't you ask him
about that thing, Hironojo?
I'll see you later.
Hey.
What did you want to ask me?
I... I couldn't possibly ask.
Don't be shy! Need me
to take care of someone for you?
Oh, no.
It's just that my son was born
the other day
and I was hoping you would name him.
You want me to name him?
I want my son to grow up
to be strong, just like you.
- Hiyah!
- Boss!
Wait!
The Aizu Hunters, huh?
I carry out...
divine retribution.
Took you long enough.
All right. Bring it on.
So you're Kondo Isami.
To think you dodged my surprise attack.
You're just as good as they say.
Were you going after our boss?
He's still breathing!
Boss, go and help him. This one is mine.
I'm telling you, he's a master swordsman.
Yeah.
I won't forgive him.
Let's go!
There's no point in running away now.
I'll cut you down and then chase them.
Bring it on!
It has been a while
since someone has managed to wound me.
But for some reason, I don't like you.
What's with that look?
Those eyes say
you've thrown everything away.
That's some boring violence.
Oh well. Before you die,
give me your name, Aizu Hunter.
Okada Izo.
At least now, those eyes
have some life in them.
Hey, Hirayama.
What are you, a moron?
Stay out of my fight.
Interfere and I'll kill you.
My apologies.
You're slow.
You too.
Or might you be the one?
The one they say defeated Sagawa Kanbei?
Your name?
Hijikata Toshizo.
That way!
I'll remember you, Hijikata Toshizo.
I'll kill you myself.
- Hijikata!
- Are you okay?
Hey!
It's me.
Boss, how is he?
He's safe.
He said he can't die
until you've named his son for him, Toshi.
Good.
So?
Are you sure the ones who attacked you
were Aizu Hunters, too?
Yes.
A two-sword style ambush.
From his accent, he's from Satsuma.
My guy is from Tosa.
His name is Okada Izo.
Okada Izo?
What? Do you know him?
An old sparring partner from Edo.
I see.
It has to be a mistake.
What kind of nonsense is that?
He just tried to kill Master Serizawa.
And your leader's life, too.
The fact that both of our commanders
were attacked at the same time...
No matter how you slice it,
something isn't right.
What are you getting at?
Someone on the inside
leaked our movements to the enemy.
You're saying a traitor is among us?
I am.
For an old friend, perhaps.
- Are you picking a fight?
- Toshi would never do that.
Niimi, that theory doesn't hold up.
If Toshi were a traitor, it doesn't
make sense that he's wounded.
What if he got wounded just to deceive us?
Why the hell would I do
something so stupid?
Can we really trust you?
What gives? Not you too, Yamanami.
In Tosa
I heard of the Tosa Loyalist Party.
They're radical imperial loyalists.
Okada Izo may very well be one of them.
Are you serious?
So, what is it going to be?
What are you going to do if that killer
turns out to be your friend Okada Izo?
When he comes to kill you,
what are you going to do?
If you hesitate, you die. Right?
That's going too far, Serizawa.
Now that's the look I wanted to see.
Hey, Kondo, do you want a match?
I don't mind doing it right now.
I don't fight my own men.
Is that right? Still as cold as ever.
Whatever. All right, let's go for a drink.
A damn shame
letting that man get away.
Do you mean Kondo Isami?
No, the man I crossed swords with.
The one who is rumored
to have defeated Sagawa Kanbei.
His name is...
Hijikata.
Right, Hijikata Toshizo.
Toshizo?
Have you met Toshizo?
So you know the guy.
That man is a real piece of work.
The more you cross swords with him,
the stronger he gets.
If he fights like that, I want to see
just how strong he can get.
That man is my prey.
Next time, I'll be the one to finish him.
If you do
I'll kill you.
What is that supposed to mean?
Because I made a promise.
That he and I would fight one more time.
So you've crossed swords
with Hijikata, then.
We fought
and became friends.
Friends?
This is war, you fool!
It's kill or be killed! Becoming friends?
That isn't war.
It's nothing but child's play!
He's the enemy!
You're wrong.
Toshizo is the exception!
We cut down our enemies.
That is our way. We are manslayers.
So he's the traitor.
Sasaki
is that really true?
Yes.
He's the one who tracked him down.
There's no doubt about it.
My lord, what are your orders?
You're way too jumpy.
Toshi!
Hajime?
Hajime!
It's not like you to lose your composure.
It hurts to suspect one of our own.
Yamanami! Sanosuke! Hurry!
Get over here, quick!
Hajime? Yeah, it really is you!
Whoa! Hey, Eisaburo!
How have you been?
Hajime!
Do you have any idea how worried we were?
No, really. Where the hell have you been?
After leaving Edo, I've been getting by.
Actually, more recently,
I heard the Mibu Roshigumi
was making a name for itself,
and that you guys were a part of it.
I knew you missed us.
That's not it!
Then what brings you all the way out here?
I happened to see some tense-looking idiot
I knew heading this way.
Don't use me as an excuse, you jerk.
Whoa! Hajime! When did you get here?
Hey, enough already.
Gotcha!
- Go, Heisuke!
- Hey, go for it!
Crap.
Hey, Heisuke, hang in there!
- Go on!
- Hang on!
- Take him down!
Give it back!
Show him!
Enter.
Hajime.
You... What is the meaning of this?
Saito Hajime is a criminal
who has taken a man's life.
We can't just let him run loose.
On my authority, until things cool down
I've decided to place him
in the Aizu Domain's custody.
I'm sorry that I didn't
say anything, Boss.
Now, back to business.
It's about the Aizu Hunters.
As you know, our moves are
being leaked to the enemy.
Yes.
I've identified the traitor.
The one who uncovered him was...
Boss.
Hey, Boss.
What's wrong?
Are you all right? You look pale.
Hey, Shinpachi! Heisuke!
The traitor has been identified.
Who is it?
Spit it out.
I'll beat them to a pulp myself.
Hey, Eisaburo.
Hajime.
I'm so surprised. I can't believe
you were in Kyo this whole time.
Hey, have you tried the mitarashi dango
from the Shimogamo Shrine yet?
We would sneak out of training to eat them
all the time back in Edo, remember?
We could only ever afford one,
so we would always have to split it.
They taste just like I remember.
You haven't changed a bit.
What is that supposed to mean?
Why did you betray us?
What are you talking about?
It's no use playing dumb, Eisaburo.
I was under orders from Aizu
to investigate the Choshu clan.
Why did you betray us?
You're the one who always said
everyone at the Shieikan is family.
I had no choice.
They said they would tell me where he was
if I fed them our information.
"Where he was"?
The man who murdered my brother.
Keep at it, Eisaburo.
You have a real gift.
Do you really think so?
Yes.
- Mine!
- Brother!
- Come on, catch me!
- Hey!
Brother!
I heard a rumor that he was in Kyo.
It was around that time
when we all went to Kyo.
I searched all over for him
in my free time.
I heard he was spotted
in the Shimabara pleasure district
so I checked every corner.
That's when I met him.
A man from Choshu.
Kusaka Genzui.
You've been looking for someone
in the pleasure district, haven't you?
I happened to see you the other day.
As a matter of fact, I may know
the person you're looking for.
The man with the Asura tattoo, correct?
So, just to find your brother's killer,
you sold out your own comrades?
Why would you go that far?
If it lets me avenge my brother...
I'll do whatever it takes.
Are you going to strike me down?
This should be fun.
Go on, try it.
I kept my promise. Isn't it enough now?
Where is the man who killed my brother?
Tomorrow, at dusk...
The man you want
will be at Gokuraku-ji Temple.
Is that really all your conviction
amounts to?
If you're so desperate to go,
you'll have to go over my dead body.
Not even a single day.
Every night, every single night.
Night after night. I dream about it.
About what happened that day.
Running away, I felt so pathetic.
So damn pathetic.
I kept thinking I should turn back,
cross blades, and die. Over and over.
But my legs...
My legs just wouldn't listen to me.
Then I started hearing voices behind me.
"Coward. Why did you run?
Aren't you ashamed
you're the only one who lived?
You should've died.
You should die!"
So please, Hajime, let me go!
Honestly, I don't want to let you die.
But...
it's better that you die by my hand
than by anyone else's.
Eisaburo!
My brother...
Abiru Seiichiro
was a retainer
of the Tsushima-Fuchu Domain
and a master
of the Hokushin Itto-ryu school.
Was it you who murdered my brother?
I was.
I'm going to avenge
my brother.
The Asura.
So that cowardly brat
has grown a spine, has he?
Niimi?
I knew from the very beginning, Abiru.
That you were the same
cowardly brat from Mibu.
Were you working for Kusaka and Choshu
this whole time?
You've got it backwards.
I was the one using him.
All so that Serizawa could
seize control of the Mibu Roshigumi.
Everything was for Serizawa?
Oh, please!
That violent meathead
is just a figurehead.
He's nothing without me
pulling the strings.
What do you mean?
Do you still not get it, you stupid hick?
Fools dance in the palm of my hand,
and history moves at my command.
I can't get enough of this!
You, your brother,
and those idiots at the Shieikan
exist just to be used by me.
Hiraseigan stance?
You think you can take me down with you
with a pathetic stance like that?
Niimi
you bastard!
Let's be careful now.
You'll ruin the priceless sword I stole.
No, it can't be my brother's.
Secret Sword: Poison Scorpion.
It's coated with aconite poison.
Works like a charm
on hot-headed idiots like you!
And you call yourself a samurai?
Samurai? Please!
These days, the ones
who are weak up here are called samurai.
So long, you fool.
What a thrill!
Dusk, huh?
You are in a good mood.
Did something good happen?
I wonder.
All right! I'm going to sing too!
Eisaburo!
Toshi! Any luck over there?
No. How about you guys?
He's nowhere to be found.
Nothing over here, either.
Where the hell did Eisaburo go?
Hey! Something terrible has happened!
This was in Eisaburo's belongings.
A NOTE
Eisaburo.
Hey, Eisaburo! Hey!
To my fellow members of the Shieikan.
Crap.
- Nine years ago
- Eisaburo.
my brother was murdered by thugs.
Let's go back.
Not a day has gone by
that I haven't thought about it.
I have lived for nothing else
- Let's go. Eisaburo, wake up.
- but to avenge my brother.
- Hold on!
- In my long search for his killer in Kyo
- I met Kusaka Genzui of the Choshu clan.
- Don't die! Hey! Don't die!
And so, I betrayed the Aizu...
"...and all of you
by leaking your movements to Kusaka.
All so he would reveal
my brother's killer.
I know my betrayal is unforgivable.
But it was something
I had to do, no matter the cost.
Whether I succeed in my vengeance or not
by now, I am no longer of this world.
Kondo.
Yamanami.
Gen.
Sanosuke.
Nagakura.
Heisuke.
Soji.
Hijikata.
Hajime.
The Shieikan was my home...
and my family.
Thank you
for everything."
Look.
Eisaburo.
Hajime.
Hajime!
Eisaburo!
The Choshu?
So the Choshu clan killed Eisaburo!
Let it go, Toshi. Not now.
The hell I will!
Toshi...
I'm begging you.
For now, can't we just
let him rest in peace?
Eisaburo...
finally managed to surpass himself.
Listen. Did any of you know? This guy...
Abiru Eisaburo.
Abiru Eisaburo...
was one hell of a fighter.
Well done.
On April 6, 1863, Abiru Eisaburo fell.
He was 21 years old.
His murder was covered up.
His death was officially ruled an illness.
Good for you, Eisaburo.
He would be known
as the first member of the Mibu Roshigumi
and the first to fall in Kyo.
Sorry, Eisaburo.
I'm borrowing this for a while.
What's with that getup?
These are for you guys.
Light blue-green?
Apparently, Serizawa had them made.
It was the color of the 47 Ronin's coats
when they committed seppuku.
He's telling us to be ready
to die at any moment.
His death will not go unanswered.
I will see to that.
Hajime...
I'm not letting anyone else die
on my watch again.
If we fall, we fall together.
Because of Eisaburo's betrayal
our boss was knocked out of the running
for the leadership of the Mibu Roshigumi.
And so, Serizawa Kamo was made
Chief Commander.
Hey, Niimi.
Looks like you like drawing things out.
Well, dancing on them isn't so bad either.
Right?
Was this really the right decision?
I couldn't save Eisaburo.
I'm not cut out to be a leader.
But...
I will get revenge for Eisaburo,
no matter what.
Even now, it is seared
into the back of my mind.
That hateful American merchant ship,
squatting in the Kanmon Strait.
And our Choshu cannons firing upon it!
Boom... Boom! Kaboom!
It was a truly exhilarating sight!
Our preparations against the Aizu
are proceeding splendidly.
However, it is not yet enough.
Do you have a plan in mind?
The assassination
of Lord Anegakoji Kintomo.
You want to kill one
of the emperor's own aides?
Lord Anegakoji, once a passionate advocate
for expelling the foreigners
has now switched his allegiance
to the pro-opening faction.
If we let this stand...
But if we're the ones to carry out
his "divine retribution"
we would make an enemy
of the Imperial Court.
Precisely.
I have a plan for that.
JUNE 17, 1863
Lord Anegakoji Kintomo,
face divine retribution!
Hear ye, hear ye!
At Sarugatsuji Crossroads,
in the Flower Capital, Kyoto
Anegakoji Kintomo was cut down!
The culprit? Shocking!
A ruthless, bloodthirsty villain slays
shogunate retainers night after night!
Want to know who it is?
Come and buy your copy!
I want to know!
Tanaka Shinbei! Get him! Hold it!
Where did he go?
Tanaka Shinbei!
This time, I will kill you!
How did you fellas figure out it was me?
Because you left your sword behind.
My sword?
You didn't notice?
So that's it, huh?
Even if you kill me,
Hijikata will hunt you down without fail.
Hijikata?
You mean Hijikata Toshizo?
Damn. Failed again.
You've gotten better, Hijikata.
Hey, Soji. Don't give me that crap.
You got distracted and lost
your footing, didn't you?
No, really.
You have gotten better, Hijikata.
You never would have noticed that before.
If you've got something on your mind,
spit it out.
It's about Serizawa Kamo.
Right.
He has been taking the new recruits out,
and they drink nearly every night.
Welcome.
- Welcome.
- Hey.
- Welcome. This way, please.
- With that guy as our commander-in-chief
while Kondo gets treated like dirt...
I just won't stand for it.
Soji, I appreciate the sentiment.
But what's important isn't
who is in charge.
It's protecting Kyo
from the extremist imperialists.
Tanaka Shinbei has killed another one!
This way!
Brutal.
Hironojo!
- Hironojo!
- Are you all right?
- Yes. I...
- It's all right.
I'm glad you're alive.
- No, that's not it.
- Don't speak!
No, you don't understand!
He let me live.
Hijikata, it was so I could
deliver a message to you.
What do you mean?
Tanaka Shinbei is waiting.
He's...
waiting for you
Hijikata.
Where?
Sanbonmatsu.
Hold it, HIjikata.
- We're going with you.
- We're coming too.
No, I'm going alone.
You can't take him on alone.
If we go together, he'll just run.
Besides, I won't stoop
to such cowardly tactics.
I'll go with him.
- Boss!
- Sagawa.
Please let me go.
If anything happens to Hijikata,
I swear I'll take him down.
Boss, stay out of this.
I know.
Tanaka Shinbei!
So you only brought Kondo Isami with you?
I figured you would bring more men.
Hijikata, I have to admire your guts.
So they threw you away, just as I thought.
What do you mean?
Something about it
never sat right with me.
Why would a master swordsman
like you leave his blade behind?
But seeing your two-sword style,
now I'm sure of it.
The sword you "forgot" at Sarugatsuji
was a fake.
The imperialists framed you to avoid
being branded enemies of the court.
So what?
I still did it.
That doesn't change a thing.
Draw your sword, Hijikata.
Why the fixation on me?
I decided that you, and you alone,
would be the one I cut down.
Now, let's settle this.
Bring it on.
You kill people
just because you're told to
then get tossed aside
when you're no longer useful.
That makes you nothing more than a puppet!
I don't understand a thing about politics.
But I have killed
in the name of my own justice.
Shogunate or Court,
if something is rotten, I'll set it right.
That is the cause I fight for.
What kind of justice is that?
I don't care what you call it.
You're still just a murderer!
Isn't a fight
supposed to be honor against honor
something more passionate than this?
I was born poor, the son of a boatman.
All I ever wanted was to be a samurai!
To be called a killer
is an honor
not everyone can claim, isn't it?
So a boatman's son can't become a samurai?
Just watch me.
I'll cut them down,
again and again and again.
And if that changes the course of history
our names will be remembered forever
as the true samurai
who set this rotten world right.
I get it.
But it's all so pointless.
I'm the son of a farmer!
We're not so different, you and I.
The thrill is in doing what others can't.
I feel the same way.
But I couldn't care less
about leaving a mark on history.
I just want to fight strong opponents!
As long as I can fight someone strong
that's all that matters.
It's the only time I feel truly alive.
Like right now, fighting you.
My blood is pounding in my veins.
We're a couple of fools, aren't we?
Both of us.
This is my defeat.
I see now
why Izo saw something in you.
Izo?
Do you know him?
Yeah. He said you two were friends.
I've never had a friend in my life.
That's why I wanted to kill you.
Maybe I was even jealous of Izo.
I'm glad my final opponent was you.
Shinbei!
That could have been me.
If I hadn't met all of you guys.
Tanaka Shinbei.
I have etched your name upon my soul.
I can't believe Hijikata was the one
to take down Tanaka Shinbei.
I like it.
He just keeps getting more interesting.
This is going to be fun.
Satsuma clansman Tanaka Shinbei's body
was given to the magistrate's office
and his death was officially
ruled a suicide during questioning.
This was to appease the Satsuma Domain
which had friendly ties to the shogunate.
998!
999!
1,000!
You're still at it, I see.
It helps clear my head.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Back in Edo
I didn't need to do practice swings
to keep my mind clear.
Will our family
end up disappearing one by one someday?
Like Eisaburo.
I wonder what Izo is up to.
Once they decide he's no longer useful...
will they just cast him aside?
Like they did with Tanaka Shinbei.
Damn it!
At first, all I wanted was
to be stronger than you, Kondo.
Toshi
the times are changing.
In this chaotic era...
what can I really accomplish
with my sword?
I want to find out,
together with everyone from the Shieikan.
We've finally made a name for ourselves.
This is just the beginning, Toshi.
For our family
this is just the beginning.
But...
if it's too much,
you can always walk away.
Like hell I will.
I'm not quitting until I've beaten you.
Damn!
Impressive.
You always push me to get stronger.
But you won't be smiling for long.
Look who's talking! You're smiling too.
All right!
Hiya!
- Hiya!
- One!
- Two!
- Hiya!
- One!
- Two!
- Hiya!
One!
Two!
- Hiya!
Pardon the intrusion.
Yeah! Awesome!
Kondo Isami.
For your patriotic service
and sincere loyalty
as a member of the Mibu Roushigumi
you are hereby appointed its commander.
We expect you to continue to serve
with the utmost diligence.
Hold it! Found him!
Excuse me. Where exactly are we going?
1912, HAKODATE
How much longer is this going to take?
What? For someone so young,
you're pathetic.
What's with that old geezer?
It has been a while, Toshi.
I've brought a guest today.
She wants to hear about the Shinsengumi.
Your story, actually.
She came because she wants
to hear Hijikata Toshizo's stories.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Ichikawa Makoto.
Who gets nervous in front of a grave?
Sorry.
Honestly, I'm surprised.
What Nagakura told me
is so different
from my idea of the Shinsengumi.
The story changes
depending on who is telling it.
True.
Why aren't you asking me any questions?
You don't know anything about me,
other than that I came from Tokyo.
So why did you decide to tell me?
You are Toshi's granddaughter, aren't you?
How?
When?
That snowy day when we first met.
You have the same eyes as Toshi.
No one in my family would ever
tell me about my grandfather.
Of course they wouldn't.
We, the Shinsengumi, were called rebels,
enemies of the Imperial Court.
Hijikata Toshizo was the vice commander.
If anyone knew you were related to him,
who knows what you would've faced?
Even so, I have to know
about my grandfather.
His blood, the blood of Hijikata Toshizo,
flows through my veins.
So that makes you
a "thorny brat", just like him, huh?
Now then, please go on.
To bloom in battle
and to fall in battle.
Samurai are flowers that bloom
in full splendor, unafraid to fall.
The Shinsengumi were
the last flowers to bloom
in the dying twilight of
the Bakumatsu era.
Charge!