( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Dad!
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I have to get into 3C.
No matter who tries to stop me.
INCOMING CALL - AIKO
I can't read their name.
The assistant at your father's boutique
in Japan called.
Cosmic Central wants you
to design their clothes.
It's all thanks to me.
Those photos I uploaded of you
are so cool that whoever sees it
can't help but fall in love.
I also uploaded them to show
that you're here on vacation in Bangkok,
so, of course, they'd want to see you.
Go. Go ahead.
Now Cosmic Central
has paved the way
for you to walk right in.
It's an honor to have you here
at Cosmic Central, Mr. Taiga.
I don't visit Thailand much,
but I know your company is number one.
Thank you so much
for considering the Kenji brand.
Pardon me.
He's just a designer.
Does he really need a grand welcome
from me downstairs, Atinuch?
It was Ms. Nun's idea, sir.
Actually, this designer's quite special.
His brand is very popular.
If he agrees to design our uniform,
there'll be hashtags,
the internet will praise us,
and we'll get hit tweets globally.
I'm busy.
Let whoever's in charge
of the project handle it.
THE PRESIDENT IS NOT GOING
Mr. Taiga,
my father's talking to a CEO from Europe.
Let's just start talking.
I'm the one who wanted to work
with a leading brand like Kenji anyway.
Thank you for working so hard
for our company.
This is to show my gratitude, Rin.
I like people who are straightforward.
On the day of the fire,
I saw your bravery.
From now on, no more traffic control work.
Report to the office upstairs.
What is it? Go ahead.
I'd like to take a picture with you.
It'd be an honor.
One, two, three.
Smile, please.
3C Group…
Let's see how I can crush you.
The news about the fire alone
shouldn't have decreased
our stock with 3C-coin this badly.
Did you check if there's a team of IOs
spreading fake news, Techut?
Don't worry about it, Dad.
We just need a team of bots
to pump and dump.
Let's just do a wash trade,
then it'll go back up.
I'll pass. I'm busy with our rebranding.
If you can't do anything to grow my money,
don't ever come see me again.
You've agreed to work with Cosmic Central.
How come you look so unhappy?
I didn't get to meet who I wanted to.
The president,
Naruban.
One of the three co-founders.
But the names of the other two
have been removed, vanished like ghosts.
Mr. Naruban's the only
major shareholder now.
You're designing their uniform.
You'll get to see him eventually.
My design will take a while,
not just a month or two.
Maybe six months if I'm lucky.
I can't wait that long.
Just the usual, please.
Sorry.
Do you need some company?
You look pretty stressed.
I'm just stressed about work.
I traded 3C-coins
and got only a few million baht.
I was thinking about
buying a private island.
Sounds great.
Where's the island?
My dad loves Thailand.
I'd love to visit sometime.
I own a resort near the island.
If you're interested, I'll have
my driver take you tomorrow.
Or we can go together tonight.
One glass, please.
I'm so sorry!
Sorry.
I'm so drunk.
Sorry, I need to use the restroom.
Oh?
I'm so sorry.
Anyway, I hope you get some tonight.
See ya.
What's up?
Looking for a bad boy tonight, huh?
My body, my choice.
You must not know
who you're flirting with.
Back off before I call the cops.
Before they come,
you'll be in pieces, with nothing left.
And maybe
you'll get a leaked live video
for your profile.
Run while you still can.
That rich handsome guy's got a crazy past.
He's assaulted women countless times.
If his dad weren't rich,
he would've spent many nights in jail.
What?
The lady said she's going home early, sir.
Naruban's eldest son is a total playboy.
Let's have some fun, okay?
That's my reward.
Cosmic Central is a front for Fire Phoenix
to launder money.
Fire Phoenix.
One of the top five secret organizations
wanted by Interpol.
I'll kill their members one by one
until I reach their ringleader,
Damon.
I know
that it's wrong,
but for me,
you are the only exception.
I'll help you.
Hello, Mr. Taiga.
Hello.
My driver has food poisoning,
so she's his substitute.
What's your name again?
It's Rin, ma'am.
So Rin's his substitute.
3C-coin's taken a nosedive,
yet your sister's going to the beach.
She's just crazy over her guy.
That designer guy is clever.
Nun's desperate.
He only has to please her a little
for her to give her body.
Don't worry, Dad.
I'll make sure both our stock
and 3C-coin will skyrocket!
How will you do that?
News, of course.
If they used it to manipulate the price,
we can use it too.
Those stupid investors love bagholding.
They consume the news for food anyway.
Where's Taiga?
Use your phone.
I called him. He wouldn't pick up.
Well, don't call him so often.
Men can get annoyed sometimes.
You're rich, you're pretty,
but your personality's not it.
Careful, or you'll stay single, madam.
Finding a guy is no trouble for me.
However,
you crashing at somebody else's place
like this
speaks volumes about your manners.
I'm only here because Taiga wants me here.
I'm here to do my job.
A job that someone
with a bubble brain like you…
can never understand.
Taiga's off to work.
Everybody's got a job,
except you.
Whenever you're free
and tired of living off your dad,
you should find something to do.
Try to look employed.
Then people might stop
posting with that caption,
"Pretty but dumb."
Learn to shut up sometimes.
Got it?
Wait! Madam!
Come take care of me!
That was a hard blow! Madam!
Damn, she's tough!
You look tired. Let's head back.
No, I'm still having fun.
I want another round.
Careful, Ms. Nun!
- Ms. Nun!
- Mr. Taiga!
- I've got a cramp!
- Hey!
Ms. Nun!
Ms. Nun.
Ms. Nun. Ms. Nun!
Thank you so much
for saving me, Mr. Taiga.
If it weren't for you,
I would've been a goner.
I didn't save you.
Rin did.
I'll take you to your room.
Careful.
Let's go.
It's not exactly your style,
but you look good.
Ms. Nun gave it to me.
Sure.
It's almost not work-appropriate.
Then what is?
Aren't you a little too judgmental?
When I was little,
my dad would tell me fairy tales.
Once there was a poor man,
a fisherman named Urashima Taro.
He saved a turtle's life,
but he didn't know it was a princess.
So he went from being poor
to getting married
and living in an underwater palace.
One day,
he wished to get back to shore.
He was very eager, no matter
how the princess would try to stop him.
Once he finally got back,
no one knew him anymore
because 300 years had passed.
He opened a present the princess gave him
before he would resurface,
even after the princess
had kept warning him not to.
Once he opened it,
the young man suddenly
turned into an 80-year-old.
In the end, he died on the beach.
How do you say it in Thai again?
Right!
The moral of the story is,
disobedience is the beginning of misery
and disaster.
I hope you're not like that.
I trust no one. I only trust my instincts.
No matter what you'll have to face?
At least it's my choice.
I won't argue with you.
You'd give me a headache.
Don't worry, I never wanted
to be near you anyway.
I'm an employee who wants to keep her job.
Cheers.
It's late, Ms. Nun. If you'll excuse me.
Wait, Mr. Taiga!
You still haven't finished your drink.
Stay here and drink with me.
Good night, Ms. Nun. See you tomorrow.
Don't go, Mr. Taiga. Stay with me.
Mr. Taiga!
Mr. Taiga, come play in the water with me.
Come on! The water's really warm.
I tried to stop her,
but she wouldn't listen.
That's why I had to call you.
Can I have your number?
- My number?
- Yeah.
So I can check in on her.
She's just drunk.
She'll sober up in no time.
It's not like she's badly hurt.
Who the hell's drunk?
Mr. Taiga,
you're my hero, you know.
You can get off of me.
I need to take care of Ms. Nun.
We got to know each other better
during this trip.
Is this what they call
"intimate"?
No.
What did you achieve
by speaking to a designer at the beach?
Stop giving people a reason
to talk behind your back.
It's only natural
I date someone on my level.
In fact, Mr. Taiga's known
at an international level.
We're aiming to go global
anyway, aren't we?
It's not like I'm taking it out
on lowly people.
You sure use your mouth well.
That's why the designer likes you.
I use my mouth well for work,
not just for cheap lust like you do.
What a waste of money and fame.
- Nun!
- Te!
- Mom!
- Hey!
Act crazy all you want,
but this is your mother!
Why'd you get in the way, Mom?
Dad, relax!
- It's okay.
- It's not okay!
You keep spoiling them,
never blaming them for anything!
Soon, they'll lose all respect for you!
What kind of mother are you, Giranun?
Why can't you raise them
to be normal like everyone else?
They're always causing trouble!
I'm rich, yet I can never be happy
because I don't have
a good child to show off!
Don't cry, Mom. I'll go see Dad.
What are you looking at?
If you didn't step in,
Dad wouldn't have yelled at me.
I only want what's best for you.
Stop it.
You're always defending me.
That's why he thinks
I can never be responsible.
When I make any small mistake,
he remembers it forever.
Yes, I slapped those girls.
What? I just like doing it.
Stay still! Got it?
Stay still! Stop moving!
Let's have some fun, okay?
What are you taking pictures for?
What the hell?!
All reporters outside,
please stop taking pictures.
Please give my client some privacy.
Why are you crying?
You didn't cry like this on the bed!
Te,
your dad has high hopes for you.
Everything he gave you
was for your own happiness.
If you tarnish my family's name,
you won't get a single penny.
But I've done nothing wrong.
- Dad!
- That's enough! Enough!
Stop!
He's our only son!
Are you badly hurt? Are you okay?
No one ever asked me what I want.
Te…
1089 PEOPLE - 1183
Sun!
Sun,
you were gone because
you were busy with work, right?
You have to take care of many people,
like your parents and your sister.
I'm back now, Sun.
I'll get a job too.
I'll help make ends meet.
I'll help you with everything, Sun.
Sun!
She thought I was someone else.
No, I didn't!
How could I forget my boyfriend?
Stop it! You're confusing me
with someone else!
What a waste of time.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
It's been a while, Taiga.
- I don't know you.
- But I know you so well.
You're not actually Mr. Kenji's son.
What are you, the son
of Blazing Tiger's yakuza boss,
doing at Cosmic Central Group?
I…
used to know your real parents.
And the one who saved you
is me.
You have to take our kids to Khanin.
He'll take you all to a hiding place.
‪-Mom!
‪-No!
Dad.
Dad, look out!
If you want Fire Phoenix
to help you, it'll cost you.
They can take my life.
We'll hunt them down together.
Even if they're hiding in the shadows,
Fire Phoenix needs to be exposed!
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya