( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Ugh!
Taiga.
I'm working on a new collection.
Want to try designing?
Maybe the clients will see
something new from you too.
I don't want to be like you, Dad.
Taiga.
You can be whatever you want to be.
Fire Phoenix is forcing us
to sell everything to them.
They're expanding their power worldwide.
If anyone resists or defies them,
they have ways of dealing with it.
This place is for tigers,
not for lowly birds like Fire Phoenix.
Taiga, remember this.
With a single cup of tea,
you can be happy anywhere.
I'll go refill the tea.
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
After the funeral of the boss, Kenji,
Fire Phoenix won't have
a single breath left.
I'll hunt them down myself.
Stay out of it. Restoring our pride
is the duty of the Blazing Tigers only.
Does that mean, as his son,
I'm not part of Blazing Tigers?
Don't dream about things
that are impossible and shouldn't be.
The position of leader
isn't for an orphan
from Thailand like you.
The position of leader
isn't for someone
who's incompetent either.
- Hey!
- Ugh!
- What?
- Argh!
Ugh!
Do you know who everyone
must listen to now?
When you come across these two things,
it means I was killed by the enemy's hand.
From now on, being the head
of the Tigers is your job.
Taiga, move forward.
Don't trust anyone but yourself.
Code 144.
A robber is fleeing the convenience store,
heading for the front exit.
Back off! Get out of the way!
Well done, Rin.
You've been here less than a month
and already delivered results.
Go home and rest for now.
I can keep working.
Let's go buy the stuff we need.
We are working tonight.
Who are you here to see, sir?
Are you meeting someone in the office?
Which department are you trying to reach?
I can inform them.
I'm lost.
This is good.
Excuse me. I need to go to the bathroom.
Follow her. This is your chance.
- Okay.
- Go for it.
She's good, huh?
Rin!
- Let go!
- Stop resisting!
If you stop, I'll pretend
this never happened.
No, I won't stop.
You won't stop, huh?
Damn it!
I've summarized in the meeting.
The global rebranding project for our CCC,
Cosmic Central Corporation,
includes many activities
planned throughout the year.
We're changing all employees' uniforms,
launching a new app,
"Hi, boost up your world of joy".
You can buy everything in the world
through our app.
We'll have influencers
releasing viral content for each project.
Dad, you're okay with it?
Then I can move forward.
How many more tens of millions do you need
for this image-selling project?
My ten million is probably more worth it
for Cosmic Central
than the money you spent
closing the case for beating a woman.
If you're not doing anything,
stop barking.
Do you bark as well as I do?
I make money with my words.
With just a few words, how much
trading volume does 3C Coin have?
Tens of billions, huge profit.
I use my words to make money
for our father, the CEO,
so he can own this universe.
Not like you, who spends all day
thinking about projects and image.
Numbers are logic, not emotion.
I'm just following Dad's orders.
He wanted to rebrand Cosmic Central,
and I've done it for him.
- Nun.
- Te started it first, Dad.
Nun, you're the younger one.
Learn to be patient.
You always side with him.
THE SUCCESS STORY OF COSMIC CENTRAL
THE IT BUSINESS LEADER
FROM THREE CLOSE FRIENDS
I've had PR remove all the old information
from social media.
Prin and Chanchai are not the founders.
I don't know why the magazine
decided to use this photo.
Remove all the ads.
So they will have it ingrained
in their minds
that Cosmic Central
is the empire of Naruban Asawawong
and no one else.
The Hi app must reach
a million accounts in three months.
3C Coin must be usable
to purchase all items in the app.
You two need to work together
to ensure the Hi app
generates over 100 million
in profit in its first year.
Isn't the timeline a bit too short?
You hired a PR team to promote yourself
as a new-generation manager.
Talented people don't have problems.
Guess you're a fake.
Whether I'm good or not,
I've never made the family
spend money to cover up bad news.
- Techut!
- Te!
Te, let go!
- Let go!
- That's your sister! Let go!
- Hey!
I said let go!
This little sister, if she keeps barking,
she can die for all I care.
You should learn
to understand other people's pain.
Fire! Which floor?
Let's hurry down, Dad.
You go down now.
I need to go to my office.
No, Dad. Your office is on the top floor.
If the fire spreads,
you won't be able to get down.
I need to go to my office!
Hurry up!
Are you okay?
We should go downstairs.
In case of fire, no elevators.
Use the stairs.
Are you crazy? Dad has a heart condition.
How can he get down this tall building?
Are you okay, President?
I'm fine.
This way, please.
Get out!
Hurry up!
Oh no, fire!
I've called an ambulance
to wait for you outside the building, sir.
I need to check
on the others inside first.
- Fire!
- Let's go, Dad.
FOR EMERGENCY EVACUATION ONLY
Stop.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Let go!
Ugh.
I have no obligation
to answer anyone's questions.
Dear.
I'm glad you're okay.
Worry about the company first.
Do you know how the fire started?
Some idiot started the fire
in the bathroom.
Who? Have you checked
all the security cameras in the building?
I was with you, Dad.
What about you, Te?
What have you followed up on?
I forgot. You were busy
running away like a scared dog.
If I were with Dad, I wouldn't be dumb
enough to run and make his heart worse.
Quit arguing! I'm asking
who started the fire.
Dear, please calm down.
I'm not talking to you, Giranun. Shut up.
I'm warning you because I care about you.
Why do you have to be so serious?
The building isn't damaged,
and no one died.
You must be hoping that next time,
I'm the one who dies, right?
INCOMING CALL
FIRE PHOENIX
If 3C's stock drops any further, you know
whose life will be held responsible.
What's your name?
Just the usual.
Hello. I'm Techut.
We met at the 3C Group client party.
I think you're mistaken.
Then this is the first time
I've mistaken a beautiful woman like you.
Your name is…
You think you're so pretty?
You can't just walk away from me.
Probably prettier than your mother.
What did you say?
Hey! You're asking for it?
- Hey!
- What's your problem?
You want some of this too?
Do we have a problem here?
Hello.
Come here.
Ugh!
You bastard!
Well? I'm kind of bored right now.
Want a couple of good ones?
Don't worry about your dads.
I can clear things up
at any police station.
What do you say?
Let's go.
Hey! Hey!
Did you forget something, beautiful?
Here.
Hm?
Do you know how to say thanks?
I only talk to people on my level.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Do you know who that is?
Whoa, Tat. She's the daughter
of the major shareholder here,
Miss Ratee.
Really?
- Never seen her before.
- She flies around like a bird,
barely comes around.
Thanks. Go back to work now.
Ratee. Beautiful,
but got such a bad attitude.
I've missed you so much.
This time, I'm staying for a long while.
I'm not leaving you alone anymore.
Oops.
Hey, you!
Hi, madam.
Taiga, why is this guy here?
Well, I'm a friend of Taiga,
just like you, madam. Taiga.
I've missed you so much.
This time, I'm staying for a long while.
Not going anywhere.
- Hey!
- What?
Since when have you
been friends with Taiga?
Thank you so much.
This bag is everything to me.
- Arigato.
- Are you okay?
I didn't know you were Thai.
I'm not okay with this.
You don't pick your friends well at all.
But I've known him for a long time.
My name is Dhammatat.
And you, Ratee,
Rateerungsri Clay,
daughter of Mr. Robert,
the famous media mogul,
owner of oil wells,
telecom shares, and many other
secret businesses
across over ten countries. Is that right?
How do you know about me?
I can read. Even though
you keep a low profile,
your name is still easy to find.
No way.
Someone like you couldn't possibly
know so much about me.
Who are you, really?
Just an ordinary, poor guy.
But…
I'm quite something.
Once you try,
you'll be calling for me day and night.
"Dhammatat. Dhammatat."
You jerk!
Ow.
I'm not coming back here
until you get rid of this guy.
Whoa, madam. This is a person,
not some wet garbage. Got it?
Whoa.
I'll leave now.
I'll come back to see you later.
Good news you need to know, Taiga.
I've deleted all the footage of you
during the fire
at 3C Tower. It's completely gone.
The problem is,
when I deleted the footage,
someone was watching it at the time.
You were watching
from the security server, right?
Yeah. How did you know?
Every time I go to 3C,
there's always a security guard
who tries to block me.
Yes!
You want to get into 3C
because it's a money laundering hub
for Fire Phoenix.
Dhammatat, you can still back out
if you don't want
to get caught up in this.
You're acting like we just met yesterday.
You know that risky stuff
always gets my instincts going.
I have to get into 3C.
No matter who tries to stop me.
This brand is trending.
I think it would be perfect
for the new uniform you want.
I already have a brand in mind.
The one you chose is too basic.
What kind of style do you want?
I can help find it for you.
Smart and elegant.
Both smart and elegant.
That's a good choice.
Perfect for our company.
How about this brand?
The designer, who's the father,
just passed away.
Now, his son is taking over.
I heard he's also started
a women's clothing brand.
Nun!
What's his name?
Mr. T, Taiga.
3C Group, let's see
how I'm going to crush you.
If you tarnish my family's name,
you won't get a single penny.
I will kill its members one by one
until I reach the big boss.
It's good to finally meet you, Taiga.
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn