( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
AN ADAPTATION OF THE NOVEL BY HUDANAJWA
I told you, darling.
Just do whatever you want.
Plus, I believe in you
and I love you so much.
You are a woman.
Women are special.
A woman has no limit
to her love for someone.
I'm not upset.
I'm thankful. Thankful for you.
Dear.
Yes.
I'm pregnant.
My goodness.
Darling, do you know that you are
the most special person in my life?
When I married you,
it was like a dream come true.
I don't really think about children,
but when Auntie's family
and yours said that you were barren,
I felt upset.
I pray every single day.
I pray to God
that He will let you get pregnant.
No one in this world
can humiliate you, darling.
Thank God. You are pregnant, darling.
Yes! I'm going to be a father!
I...
I can't wait to see the baby's face.
I'm sure it'll be cute like you.
But when I found out back then,
I really wanted this baby
to look like you.
Tall, handsome, fair.
Back then?
Are you serious right now?
You knew you were pregnant
and you didn't tell me?
I...
- I forgot.
- Forgot?
Am I not important in your life?
You forgot to tell me something like this?
No. No, dear.
Now I know. I understand it now.
Dear.
Dear. Please open the door.
Please open the door.
Honey, please.
Hey, dear.
- Why did you follow me?
- Hey!
- I'm not important, right?
- Dear, no.
Dear, okay, fine.
I didn't tell you that time
because I was angry with you, dear.
That's it.
I know, dear.
I shouldn't have kept this from you.
I know it's my fault
and I'm sorry. Okay? Please.
It's my fault.
I was too busy working
to know you were pregnant.
I'm sorry.
I should be taking care of you
at this early stage, but I wasn't around.
What if something happened
to you or the baby?
I would regret it.
My baby.
Let me tell you this.
Your father is the strongest man
in the world.
I don't want you to be scared
of anyone or anything, okay?
Papa will take care of us.
Please promise me, darling.
We will take care of our baby together.
God willing, darling.
I love you, Thariq Ridzuwan.
I love you too, my treasure.
Congratulations to Adrean,
Thariq, and all the members
of the Holy Dragon, for successfully
suppressing the Gajah Hitam syndicate.
Thank you, sir.
How about Farez?
His last location was in Yangon, Myanmar.
We will watch him closely.
If he crosses the border, we will know.
Permission, sir.
My wife is pregnant.
Thank God. Congratulations, Thariq.
Thank you, sir.
I'd like permission to work in the camp
throughout her pregnancy
and until delivery, sir.
Won't you miss working in the field?
I will,
but if I'm far away from her,
I'll miss her more.
Very well.
I approve your application.
Thank you, sir.
All the menus here are delicious.
Is it your first time?
No, I've been here two years.
I eat here every day.
Two years? Every day?
So 365 times 2 equals 730.
That's 730 days straight.
Seriously, bro?
So what? I want to think before ordering.
Sure, but don't do it
when you're already in front.
She's right.
We've been waiting for 15 minutes.
Please be considerate.
Others want to eat as well.
Miss.
Think first, then get in the line.
You're so well-built,
but you have a small brain.
What would you like?
One spicy set, one original set.
Add on cheesy wedges and one sundae cone.
- Okay.
- Give everything she ordered to me.
Make two sets, please.
One for him and one for me.
I'll pay for him. Win.
He pushed me.
Bro, sorry.
My wife is pregnant. So her mood is like--
Don't think I'm stupid.
She's short like a schoolkid.
And she's pregnant?
Isn't she too short for that?
Hey, she's my wife.
Ever heard of a hormonal imbalance?
This isn't an imbalance. This is crazy.
- Thariq...
- Stay quiet.
Now you apologize.
He pushed me, calling me crazy and short.
Now I have to apologize?
My principle is that
if we made a mistake,
it's still our fault.
Just apologize. It's as easy as that.
No.
Darling, please apologize,
so I have a reason to talk to him.
He's all brawn and no brain.
I can beat him up.
Go apologize. Now.
Bro.
Sorry, I shouldn't have cut your line.
I'm really sorry.
You're not only short,
but you're also rude.
What did you say?
Don't call my wife short.
Don't call my wife crazy.
Most importantly, don't touch her.
Hear me?
- Did you?
- Yes.
Okay, it's ready.
Please count for everyone.
I'm paying. How much?
I'll use my QR. Is 1,000 enough?
I paid 1,000. Thank you.
Let's go.
Yes, darling.
I want to say thank you.
Why?
For defending me at the restaurant,
even though it was my fault.
It's my job to protect you.
Whatever the reason is.
What should I do
if you're not around, dear?
If you don't want me gone,
don't go anywhere.
I won't go anywhere.
But if I die...
My God. What are you saying, darling?
I pray for you and our baby
to be healthy every day.
Please don't say that.
What were you thinking?
A prayer is an effort,
but we can't change God's fate.
We hold on to this saying,
"Whoever strives, achieves."
But we still have to believe this too.
"Be, and it becomes."
God responds to the way
His servant perceives Him.
If His servant thinks positively,
positive things will follow.
I love our child.
I've never
and will never think negatively of God.
So,
don't stop praying.
Okay?
Dear God, please. Please.
Dear, come here.
Still have something to say?
- Yes.
- I thought--
Come here. Come.
Okay.
Yes, what is it? What?
Do you know
that you're extremely handsome?
I know.
- What do you want?
- Can I ask for something?
Darling, come on.
I'll do anything for you.
What do you want?
I have a craving, dear.
What is it? Have I ever not given you
anything you want? No, right?
Just tell me what you want. Tell me.
I want to ride in a tank.
What?
A tank.
A...
A tank?
That's rather hard to get.
Have you heard the viral news
about a woman who has a craving?
She wanted to eat soap. Ever heard of it?
That's crazy, right?
Okay, so?
You should eat soap because a tank is--
You want me to eat soap
so the baby and I die?
Metaphor.
Dear, I just want to ride in a tank.
I didn't ask for soap.
Darling...
Can't you do it?
If you can't, sleep outside tonight.
Don't hold the baby or me in your sleep.
- Darling--
- Sleep outside.
She planned to sulk for a long time,
but I didn't notice it.
Don't play with me, dear.
I'm a woman of my word.
Where can I find a tank
at a time like this?
You're in special forces.
You can't take me for a ride in a tank?
Plus, the baby wants it, not me.
Have you ever seen a pilot
bring his plane home?
If you refuse to indulge me, just say so.
No excuses!
You sleep outside tonight.
Don't try to sneak in.
Darling.
Darling, please open this door.
Okay, listen.
Why don't we go for a ride in my car?
I need permission
to take the tank out, darling.
No! I didn't ask for much
and it wasn't difficult.
It's not difficult for you,
but it is for me.
Listen to me. Why don't we...
watch YouTube?
No!
Darling, please don't cry.
Okay, I'll take you.
I'll go and get it, okay?
Really?
- I didn't say anything.
- What did you just say?
- Yes, you said you'd get it.
- I said that?
- Yes.
So you'll take it home?
I guess I will.
Yes!
Get inside. Stop crying.
I won't.
Dear.
What else do you want?
Please look at me.
I love you.
Yes!
Good job, baby.
Darling.
Do you think it's funny?
With your red lipstick and all.
You look all, but you're a coward.
Anyway, where's the tank?
Whose lipstick is that?
Here it is. Ta-dah!
- Did you buy it?
- Of course.
Didn't you say it?
If you can't ride on it, that's fine.
As long as you get to look at it.
This is the last piece.
Limited edition. The biggest.
- It does look big.
- It is.
How much is it, dear?
Asking about the price?
Come on. It's 20,000.
How much?
20,000.
- Dear, you're joking.
- No, I'm not.
- What?
- It's so expensive. Such a waste.
Darling, it's more wasteful
if I buy a real tank.
You want to know why?
It's hard to park. What if we're going
to KLCC? We can't use the parking space.
If we park it by the roadside,
it'll get clamped.
If we use the valet, the attendants
won't have a license for a tank.
If we're on the highway,
how do we get through the toll?
We can't go to our hometowns.
Darling, it's a waste.
We can't be at war
with our children every day.
- Are you asleep?
- Are you done?
No. Want to hear more?
Gosh, dear.
I hope you like it.
This is 20,000?
I didn't say it was in ringgit.
It could be in rupiah.
Pregnant women are so rough.
- What?
- Huh?
Okay. You can go back to sleep, dear.
I want to play with this.
Darling.
Darling, hey!
How are you going to play it?
It needs batteries.
Now she's going to the pool. Darling!
7 MONTHS LATER
"What are you cooking?"
Wait.
Chicken chop
and carbonara.
I will deliver it later.
Love, love.
Posto! Posto! Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
"Chicken chop and carbonara."
"I will deliver it later."
That's cute.
You haven't eaten yet,
but you're already full?
You little thing.
WHY AREN'T YOU EATING?
Just say it. It'll be easier.
Don't you miss my voice?
I can speak?
You're just trying to make me angry.
You wanted the silent treatment.
I thought I could only speak
in seven or eight months.
Apparently, it's just a week.
No thrill at all.
You want it? After the baby is born?
No, no. I was just kidding.
There you go.
Luckily, I'm missing you, dear.
Otherwise, you'd have
to sleep outside, by the pool.
I can't swim. What if I fall in?
- Special forces, but can't swim?
- No, I do.
- I forgot about it.
- You forgot?
I want to sleep upstairs.
Darling.
- Dear.
- Yes.
I am so happy right now.
I've never felt this happy before
in my life.
Can we stay like this forever and ever?
Yes. Yes, we can. I want that too.
We'll live like this forever.
- Forever?
- Forever.
I'll check.
I'll come back and accompany you.
Make it quick.
We received reports of pirate activity
on land that's threatening public safety.
Two of our men were sent to Sabah.
Simple mission. Go wander.
Gather intel on their activities
and report back.
They should have been back three days ago,
but we haven't heard from them.
We lost all contact
and the villagers said that they're...
missing.
Captured by the pirates?
Yes, but we don't know
whether they're still alive.
But you know it, right?
I'm on leave now.
Radwa could give birth at any time now.
Yes, Ridz. I know.
The intel said that those pirates
are on the Sabah border,
near an Indonesian village.
Their temporary camp, Ridz.
Mr. Omar wants you
to lead this rescue mission.
Bring those two men back.
Dead or alive.
There are other soldiers.
Ridz, this is
not a regular rescue mission.
Mr. Omar wants the best to lead.
And you, Ridz, are our best.
I won't go on a mission
till Radwa finishes her confinement.
- That's my deal with Mr. Man.
- He's on sick leave.
Mr. Omar has taken over everything.
This is a non-negotiable order, Ridz.
Bring our men back.
In case Mr. Omar doesn't know,
Adrean is there.
He should've told Mr. Omar about this.
Megat.
Who are
those two missing men?
Adrean.
Oh God!
Who's the other one?
Haider.
- It's okay, dear.
- It's not okay.
- They need you.
- You need me too, darling.
I have to be with you. I promised you.
They are your brothers.
But you are my everything.
I don't want to go.
You have to go, dear.
I love you so much.
I love you more.
Ridz, please bring him back.
Please save him.
Dear.
I know this is not the right time
to say this.
There will never be the right time.
But if
this is the last time I'm seeing you,
I want you to know that you are
the best gift God has given me.
I really love you.
More than my own life, dear.
I know I made a lot of mistakes with you.
I've troubled you.
Please forgive me, dear.
Please consider me free
of any debt to you.
I forgive you.
You're free of any debt to me.
Forgive me for all of my mistakes.
You've never made
any mistakes with me, dear.
I'll always be with you, darling.
My baby.
Wait for me to come home.
I want to accompany your mom
when you come out.
Darling,
I'll see you when I see you.
Boys, let's go.
- Two barns. One cadet, another's clear.
- Got it.
Megat, cover me!
Okay.
I thought it was just Braxton Hicks.
So I held it in.
The opening of your cervix is 7 cm.
Get ready for delivery.
Nurse, take her to the labor room.
Doctor, can you wait?
I want to wait for my husband.
Ma'am, it's 7 cm. Get ready for delivery.
I want my husband!
In the name of God.
Okay. Push, ma'am!
Bastards.
Hey. Hey, Adrean.
Adrean, I'm here.
I'm here. I'm right here with you.
I'm here.
Let's go. Hurry. Faster.
Adrean, come on. Megat, cover!
It hurts. I can't.
Take Adrean.
Get them out of here. Don't stop. Go.
Now!
Daniel, cover them.
And you?
I'll cover here.
I'll make sure the enemies are delayed.
Go and rescue them.
You go. I'll cover here.
Daniel, go.
Radwa's waiting for you.
Why are you still here?
- This is an order!
- You're still my brother, Thariq!
My brother!
It hurts.
Dear. It hurts, dear.
You saved me from Zahid before.
I owe my life to you.
Now it's my turn.
Radwa is waiting for you.
Now, go.
Go!
Promise me you'll be safe.
I'll be fine.
Now go.
T.
H.
A.
R.
I place my trust in God.
Time to go to work.
I.
My child hasn't met
the crazy Uncle Daniel.
Let's go.
Q.
Darling.
I promised I'd be with you.
I can't wait to see our child.
Push more, ma'am. A bit more.
Just a bit more, ma'am.
Congratulations, ma'am. It's a girl.
Dear.
Our baby has been born, dear.
Hurry home.
Thariq. Get up, Thariq.
You're going to be a dad.
Oh, God!
God, help me.
Thariq, wake up, please. Thariq!
Thariq!
Thariq, please wake up. Ridz, come on.
You have your dad's eyes.
So pretty.
If I'm not here,
please take care of your dad for me.
Madam, the doctor asked me
to inject some medicine for you.
Take the baby.
Bye, Tia.
What did you say?
Tia Radia.
The daughter of Thariq Ridzuwan.
Such a pretty name.
- Mom.
- Sweetie.
Darling. Haider.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, darling.
I'm at the hospital now.
Thank God.
Darling, where's Ridz?
Radwa is giving birth now. She needs Ridz.
He has to come now.
He has to come and accompany Radwa.
Ma'am.
I'm so sorry.
Mrs. Radwa couldn't be saved.
Thalia.
Lia...
Darling.
Radwa is gone. She's gone.
The bullet went straight through.
Order a CT scan as soon as possible.
Radwa.
Doctor.
Can we transfer this patient
to a hospital in KL?
His wife is due any time now.
- Let me check on him first.
- No. Make it happen.
Thank you.
How are you? Okay?
Radwa has given birth.
Thank God. I'll tell Ridz.
Radwa is gone.
Hang on, Ridz. Hey, come on.
Just a bit more.
Radwa?
Where's Radwa?
Radwa has given birth, Ridz.
It's a baby girl.
Thank God.
I want to see Radwa.
There was
a complication during birth.
Radwa...
Radwa's gone, Ridz.
Let me see Radwa, Dad.
- Don't joke around.
- Ridz.
Radwa is gone.
From God we came, to God we shall return.
Don't joke around, Dad.
Please don't joke around like this.
No, Radwa is here.
No.
No!
Get out.
Get out!
- Darling.
- Ridz.
Darling.
Please don't leave me.
Why did you leave me?
- Ridz.
- Darling.
Wake up, please. Wake up.
Ridz.
Ridz!
Help!
Thariq.
TO BE CONTINUED
I've always wanted her to die.
God has granted my prayers.
She's dead now.
You promised to be with me
when I deliver the baby,
but you never came.
You were not there when I died.
Let's take her child.
Hey! Over my dead body.
I don't want her descendants
to live in my house.
Let me stay here! Why not?
There's no problem here.
No mission, no work.
No Farez, no Aina. Nothing!
Just the two of us.