( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Darling, I swear
I didn't do all that, okay?
Why was I so stupid to trust you?
I gave you my whole life!
And you did this behind my back?
Be angry all you want.
Let's go to the clinic.
Divorce me,
Thariq Ridzuwan.
I'm sorry, treasure.
Darling.
Hi, darling.
Are you okay? Do you want to drink or eat?
Are you hungry?
Darling?
Okay, I'm sorry for asking
so many questions.
I know you just woke up, but...
I just want to know
what really happened.
Did you meet up with anyone?
Did someone visit?
Do you remember anything?
I do.
I want you to divorce me.
Divorce me.
Ridz.
What happened?
How's Radwa doing?
See you downstairs.
Take leave
until Radwa gets well.
What is it?
Radwa.
She wants me to divorce her.
What?
Why?
Someone sent a CCTV photo
of me carrying Raudhah into the hotel.
Oh my God!
Didn't you say
we were all there at the time?
Do you think she'll believe me?
Did you try explaining?
I told her, but she refused to listen!
Okay, look. Try to talk to her properly.
- But wait for her to cool down.
- It won't make a difference.
I made her feel betrayed twice.
First, five years ago,
when I broke it off with her.
Now, it's about Raudhah.
Ridz, neither of them is your fault
if you think about it.
But I'm still the cause.
Then open up everything.
Until she understands you're innocent.
Ridz.
Tell her the truth
about Raudhah
and what happened five years ago.
Okay?
So? Is everything enough?
Yes, Datin.
I'll make sure to settle it tonight.
Good.
One more thing.
You know Thariq
is investigating all this, right?
Be careful. Don't get caught.
All right, Datin.
Darling.
How do you feel?
I trusted you.
I trusted you with all my heart.
Treasure, what do you mean?
Swear to me.
Promise you'll be honest.
Okay, I promise. What's the matter?
Raudhah.
She said you're the father of her child.
- So do you believe her?
- No!
I won't believe it until there's evidence!
You were in that photo!
Clear and obvious!
Answer me, Ridz!
I'm so stupid.
Stupid to believe
I'm the only love in your heart.
- Darling, I--
- Don't touch me!
Can I explain now?
I trusted you.
I loved you.
I cared more about you than about myself.
And this is how you repay me?
- Can you listen to what I have to say?
- No!
Divorce me.
- No, right now--
- Divorce me.
And take responsibility
for what you did, Ridz.
Okay, fine!
Fine. That's me in the photo.
But I did nothing, Radwa!
Get out! Get out now!
- Get out!
- Darling, listen.
- What else do you want me to believe?
- Listen!
Darling, I won't do that to you.
Why should we continue with our marriage
if we keep hurting each other?
Darling, no.
I'm the one who's been hurting you.
You've never hurt me.
- Can you not be like this?
- No.
- I hurt you when I can't control myself!
- Darling, I...
I understand.
I understand, but please trust me.
Yes, that's me in that photo.
But I was on a mission, okay?
I saw Raudhah that night
and she didn't look okay.
I didn't do anything. I swear, darling.
Please.
This time,
let me go.
I'm sorry.
Bless the food and drinks
while I was your wife.
God won't promise something
stronger than prayers.
In fact, God makes prayers
stronger than fate.
Give me a week.
I'll prove I'm innocent.
I can't wait that long.
You only have an hour.
If you can't do this within an hour,
divorce me.
I promise I'll come back
in an hour.
I know my husband.
He wouldn't do anything stupid.
Get out of my house. Go!
I have evidence.
Damn it!
Ridz, is everything okay?
Thalia, look after Radwa.
I have something to do.
Hey.
Sorry to hear what happened to your wife.
Let's go and eat.
I don't have time.
I have to find Zafir now.
I'll follow you.
Me too.
You don't need to.
Come with me to take care of Radwa.
It won't take long.
We'll just look for Zafir.
It's not about Zafir.
I know when he makes that face,
something bad will happen.
- Just stay.
- Dear, don't think that way.
- I can handle my brother-in-law.
- I don't feel good. Understand?
Then you can add some flavors.
I don't have time! I only have an hour.
Please don't waste my time.
Follow me if you want.
Otherwise, stay here.
Sorry, darling.
I can't just let the two of them go.
Adrean can't stop Thariq alone.
No!
You can't.
I'll let you know if anything comes up.
Don't worry, okay?
Still not okay?
Hold on.
Take this and look after it.
I'll take it back when I return.
Okay?
Be careful, darling.
If you feel you're in danger,
press this button.
I'll come.
What's wrong?
- It's Fateh.
- What's the matter?
He pressed the emergency button
of the watch I gave him.
He's already far away.
You know you only have
40 minutes to find Zafir, right?
Should we send Megat
and Daniel to rescue Fateh?
No, we'll...
We'll follow this GPS.
You're running out of time, Ridz.
If anything happens to Fateh,
Radwa will never forgive me.
You lied.
You said you'd be back in an hour.
Dear...
Hi.
- Come on.
- Ridz.
- Be patient. We have to plan first!
- What plan?
I only have one hour.
Radwa gave me an hour!
Our gear isn't complete. Don't be rash.
Be patient, Ridz.
We don't want to harm others.
Hurry up!
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Damn it. Fateh.
- Ridz! Be patient!
- Let go!
Can't you see Fateh?
Move it!
- Quickly!
- Help!
Always fighting back!
Help!
- Get inside!
- No!
Be quiet!
- Hurry up!
Silence!
Let's get out of here!
Ridz!
Haider!
Oh no!
Haider.
Haider!
Here.
Thanks.
Do you think I'm selfish?
For hoping he's the one
who entered just now.
No.
But I'm sure God responded
to your question.
What's the answer you see?
If it's true,
he would've arrived two hours ago.
What do you think?
Maybe he has a mission.
What mission is more important
than your feelings?
No, you're not selfish at all, Radwa.
There are a lot of soldiers
in this country.
Commandos, police,
the Royal Malaysian Navy.
But you, Husniya Radwa,
you only have your husband
to take care of you.
And he can't even fulfill
his responsibilities.
Maybe my request was ridiculous.
I was being too emotional.
One hour. That's not enough.
Ten minutes is enough to solve a problem
if he really tries.
But he chose to neglect you.
His responsibilities for the country?
Bullshit.
Do you think my decision is right?
To divorce him.
Yes.
As it should be.
So many problems to handle these kids!
- We even got ambushed.
- If the kids are healthy, it's fine...
We could've sold them.
Hey!
Come.
Hurry.
Come on.
- Let's go.
- Help!
Help me!
Fateh, come this way.
Slowly.
Come.
Shut up!
Get inside! Follow me.
Get in!
Sit down.
- Guard them.
- Be silent!
Bastards.
All right.
Fateh.
Fateh, you wait here.
Where are you going? Don't leave me.
Fateh. It won't take long.
I'm scared.
Fateh, dear. Listen.
If a bad man comes here,
run.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'll come back.
I promise. Okay?
- Okay.
- Wait here.
You're a boy. Be strong.
Come with me.
Go.
Thariq Ridzuwan.
We finally met face-to-face.
Say your last words.
Because today
is the last day
you'll breathe on this earth.
Fateh, get up. Fateh.
Boys, find the other kids.
Megat, find the kids and rescue them.
Kevin, Daniel.
Check everywhere
and make sure everything is clear.
Fateh?
Fateh, wake up.
The hospital.
Sorry if you're uncomfortable
with what I said earlier.
I didn't mean to instigate you
to divorce Thariq, but...
Logically,
your love for Thariq
should've turned into hatred.
The truth hurts, right?
Yes.
Love is blind.
We have to be smart to realize that
we're just their backup plan.
But he said he loves me.
Do you mean
after he left you five years ago
and got engaged to someone else?
But he came back.
And?
He made your sister pregnant.
Radwa, please open your eyes.
Are you sure
your husband can change again?
What your husband did
isn't a regular mistake.
But it's the ultimate betrayal
of his wife,
who loves him with all her heart.
But I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
Of being alone?
Nobody to protect you?
I'm here, Radwa.
I can take care of you,
keep you company,
and protect you.
Why?
Because
I believe in fate.
It was fate that made me
rescue you that night.
Not your husband.
Fate made us listen
to each other's problems.
And I believe
fate has determined
I'm the man who'll protect you.
We just met.
Yes, I understand that you don't know me
and I don't know you.
But I may have fallen in love with you.
Farez.
I won't force you
to fall in love with me, Radwa.
Whatever you feel toward me,
it's your right and I respect it.
But I'll wait.
I'll wait for the time
when you fall in love with me.
I believe
that fate has determined
that the time will come soon.
I'll wait for you, Husniya Radwa.
I swear.
I'll wait.
Is Haider here?
Keep an eye on Fateh.
What are you doing here?
See what your stubbornness did?
Forgive me, Thalia.
I told you I had a bad feeling!
What did you do to him?
You pressured him and told him to decide.
Look at my husband, Ridz!
He's in the ICU!
It's all because of you!
Thalia.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
No!
You're selfish!
This is my husband, Ridz!
Where is it? You said you'd protect us!
Where is your protection?
My Haider, Fateh, and Radwa!
Enough. Get out now! Get out!
Darling, wake up!
Wake up, darling! Wake up!
I'm here.
Wake up!
Please wake up.
I'm sorry, Fateh.
Fateh?
Similar, isn't it?
Now I understand why
you're always at Teduh
and treat Fateh like your own brother.
I feel like Raiza is close by
when I'm with Fateh.
So what's the status?
Holy Dragon entered our vicinity.
They took all the kids.
Fateh?
Fateh as well.
But he's in the hospital now.
I don't care! You must take care of Fateh.
Take him from there, and then sell him.
If it's too difficult, just kill him.
Okay, boss.
We can't wait too long.
Don't let that boy talk!
Okay, boss.
I can't do it now.
He's under strict control.
Well, you can't wait until I get caught!
If I get caught,
all of you will be hanged.
Do you want that?
I know who can go in without restriction.
He'll take me inside.
I'll take care of him.
See what your stubbornness did?
Look at my husband, Ridz!
He's in the ICU!
It's all because of you!
Fateh.
Things happen, Ridz.
I'm stupid, aren't I?
You're not, Ridz.
You just love the people
around you too much.
I quit.
I want to resign from the Holy Dragon.
Ridz.
Calm down.
- Don't decide while you're like this.
- No.
I've thought it through.
And this is the best for me.
What happened to Haider
wasn't your fault, Ridz.
- It's not.
- Then whose fault is it?
Whose fault is it
that Haider's in the ICU?
I'm a burden and the cause of all this. I...
Let me end all this. Please.
I'm exhausted.
Husniya Radwa.
I'm disappointed in you.
I don't really care if you have evidence.
I was just hoping
you'd appear after an hour.
For the sake of our marriage.
But you failed to do even that.
I'm sorry.
I've failed.
Be honest with me.
You went on a task
with the Holy Dragon, right?
I don't want you to choose
between work and me.
But once in a while, Thariq Ridzuwan,
I want to feel prioritized.
I just want
to make you happy with all my heart.
I just want to love you
with all my heart.
But I don't understand.
I only gave you pain.
Maybe it's written in fate
that Thariq Ridzuwan...
Thariq Ridzuwan can't make
Husniya Radwa happy.
If you truly cannot bear
the pain any longer,
I'm willing to let you go.
I'm sorry.
Ridz, where's Fateh?
What happened to him? Is he okay?
He's okay. The doctor said he's okay.
Okay.
Which ward is he in?
I really need to see him.
He must be scared.
- Do you want to see him?
- Yes.
- I'll take you.
- It's okay.
You look tired. You should go home.
I can go by myself.
Datin. No.
No, Fateh is under strict control now.
If you want to see him,
you have to follow me.
Okay. I'm sorry to trouble you.
But I have a bad feeling.
I need to see him.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
How are you, brother?
I hate having a sissy son like you!
Why didn't you fight back?
Dad.
- Please don't hit me.
- You should've died back then!
You have to fight back.
It doesn't matter how.
Play dirty or rough.
Just do whatever you can.
As long as you win.
Thank you, friend.
You're welcome, friend.
I have the love of my life.
I'll ask her to come to the tournament.
- Okay?
- Okay.
"Please make Husniya Radwa my wife."
I pray for that every day.
I'm sorry, Husniya.
Your future fiancé, Thariq Ridzuwan,
is dead.