( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Dear God, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful,
I beg and plead to You
let not even the thought of divorce
cross my heart
or mind from this day forward.
May my marriage to Thariq endure
until the end of my days.
And if the time has come,
let me be the one to go first.
I am too weak to continue life on
this earth without him by my side.
Dear God,
grant me the chance and the strength
to win back the heart of Thariq Ridzuwan.
Amen.
All right, ma'am. I've received
the result from your blood test.
Everything looks normal.
Thank God.
Ma'am,
you didn't tell us that you're expecting.
- Expecting?
- You didn't know?
What?
You're seven weeks pregnant.
All praise to God. Congratulations, ma'am.
- I'll excuse myself.
- Doctor.
Can I ask you a favor?
Please don't tell my husband.
May I know why?
It's just...
I'm actually really angry
at him right now.
- All right, then. I should get going.
- Sure.
All praise to God.
Thank you, God.
Baby,
help me win Dad back.
We can't see the face.
- Are there other angles?
- There aren't.
He knows all the camera locations.
Which means, he knows the CCTV angles too.
This man isn't ordinary.
Daniel, what about the hotel's CCTVs?
Unfortunately, every single footage
from that week has been corrupted.
So, yeah. Nothing.
Damn it. It must be Farez.
I did some digging on
Radwa's sister's social media.
And it seems like
there are quite a lot of DMs
from this particular guy.
Lots of flirting and sexual talk.
What else do we have, Kevin?
Actually, all the footages
from all those hotels.
And look at what I found.
So, we have proof.
Raudhah checked into this hotel
with the same guy.
And she bumped into Thariq at this hotel.
This is still not enough
to clear his name.
Megat, can you replay
that video of the accident?
Stop.
He looked at the driver.
He was facing the car's dashcam.
I think we can see his face
from the dashcam.
If we can match the guy in the dashcam
with the guy at the hotel...
Checkmate.
Megat, Daniel, find the car.
Kevin, keep digging on the hotel guy.
Where's Haider?
That's a great tactic
to make someone pass out.
- What do you want?
- I want you to apologize.
- No.
- You ran away from the hospital.
You didn't even let me know.
Do you like making me worried?
I went to work. Not playing futsal.
- You could have told me.
- The mission is P&C.
I don't care. Apologize right now.
- No. I didn't do anything wrong.
- Apologize now!
Why should I?
Apologize, or else...
Or else what?
I've been through torture
with all kinds of bad men.
There's nothing you can do
to break me, Thalia.
- Nothing.
- I'm pretty sure no one
- had ever done this to you.
- Sure?
I am.
Try me.
Dear.
- Don't do this.
- No!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
- I was just kidding.
- I'm your wife, Haider.
Of course I'd be worried if the guy
I love the most went missing.
I didn't go missing.
I'm here right now.
Don't cry. I can't do this.
I can't handle tears.
If even the Great Wall of China
can collapse, I'm even worse.
I looked for you like a crazy person.
I thought you were dead!
If you die, I want to die too!
- Don't.
- Don't?
I can't. Don't you love me?
- Why?
- Not me, it's Thariq.
- Thariq?
- Ridz.
He said not to answer the phone
if you called.
It's Ridz.
Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
It's been a while.
I know.
Lately, I've been a little grumpy,
I forgot to include you in my prayers.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
I made fried rice.
I was about to serve it and you came home.
It's been a while since I last fed you.
I have good news about your sister.
You don't have to.
You don't have to prove anything to me.
I trust you. Since then, now, and forever.
What else did I do wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Watching you heals me.
Are you mixed or something?
- You resemble someone.
- What do you mean?
- I'm sure you are.
- I don't.
Half me, half you.
You look a bit like our future child.
What?
I miss you, Thariq Ridzuwan.
I miss you even more, darling.
I want to go home, please.
Please.
Darling, this house is safe enough.
I will be safe wherever you are.
Please, dear.
I promise I will stick with you
all the time.
I will do everything by your side.
- Please, dear.
- You're so annoying and short.
What did you say?
- What did you say?
- No, I was saying
- you're short on...
- On?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Right.
I have all the money.
This must be how you see me.
My feet hurt.
So, can I go home?
My body feels sore. I feel dizzy.
It's okay, dear. I'll give you a massage.
Yes.
Dear, I missed you.
Dear.
I said I missed you!
Yes, I missed you too, treasure.
Okay.
- What now?
- Dear, I'm hungry.
You just ate.
That was then.
I'm hungry again.
You eat like you're eating for two.
No wonder you're chubby.
What?
What did you say?
Nothing. I said nothing.
I was just scrolling on my social media,
and it was nothing.
I'll go and get you some food. Wait here.
It was nothing.
Do I look chubby?
So close.
Chicken rice.
- What now?
- I don't want you to leave.
I'm not going anywhere. I'll be here.
Go on and eat.
Feed me.
If you won't, never mind.
- I can feed myself.
- I'll do it.
Don't make that face.
- In the name of God...
- The Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Sorry.
Dear?
I...
- What is this smell?
- Dear?
Dear!
Dear...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I don't know why I'm like this today.
I can't see or smell chicken rice.
I feel nauseous.
Why didn't you tell me?
I can eat it by myself.
It's okay.
Even if I were on my deathbed,
I would still feed you.
As long as you're happy.
I wonder what I did for God
to send you to me as a gift.
Me too.
I wonder what I did
to be given a strong wife like you
as a gift from God.
Thank you for staying until now.
I hope all your pain will be replaced
with happiness.
- Amen.
I'm sorry.
- What else do you want from me?
- Don't you dare ask me that.
This is all your fault!
You know you can't conceive,
but you still want to get married.
Your husband took advantage of your sister
because he wants a child so badly.
- It wasn't Ridz's child!
- Hey!
Raudhah told me everything!
Now, I want him to be responsible.
It's not his responsibility.
If he has a child, it should be with me,
not another woman!
You're not only barren,
but you're also rude!
Mom! Don't touch my wife.
I can do whatever I want.
She's my daughter.
I can do whatever I want to her.
- Who are you?
- I'm his husband. Why?
Since when did you consider me
your daughter?
- Darling, go upstairs.
- I won't.
It's not your fault.
Why do you have to be responsible?
Darling, go upstairs.
I'll settle this with Mom.
No! I don't want you to marry Raudhah!
Stop your drama!
Listen, even if you bleed tears,
do you think I'll pity you?
Mom, go home.
I'll come over to your house
to discuss tonight.
Leave. Go.
I'll go.
But if you don't come, you're done!
- Dear.
- It's okay.
Listen to me. It's fine.
Forgive them.
- Just forgive them.
- Forgive them?
- It's not a big deal.
- It is a big deal.
Forgive them. Please.
That's okay.
I'm coming with you.
Darling, stay here.
No. I don't want you to marry Raudhah.
Me marrying Raudhah?
No way. It's disgusting.
You don't understand.
They would do anything for Raudhah.
And you don't understand
that I'd do anything for you.
All right? Okay?
Thariq Ridzuwan!
You kidnapped my husband
from the hospital!
You stopped him
from answering my calls too, right?
Who said that?
It was Haider.
It was true. I told him to.
I apologized. So, it's fair.
What?
What do you mean by fair?
There's no such thing.
But I'll let you go.
Because Radwa is cute!
- Peace be upon you.
- And peace be upon you.
Why did they get to come?
Because if they're not there,
I can't prove my innocence.
Radwa, Kevin and I
will keep you company at home.
Where's that guy?
In the car, sleeping.
Darling,
I promise, after tonight,
your family won't disturb you.
Okay?
Boys, let's go.
Okay, girls! It's girls' night!
Ridz!
What are you doing here?
- Ridz.
- Raudhah.
- You're here.
- What are you doing?
I didn't expect that to be Raudhah.
Because the Raudhah I know
doesn't wear sexy clothes.
And she's not drunk.
Your name doesn't suit your behavior.
I wanted to take her home.
But she refused.
She didn't want you
to find out that she's drunk.
That's why I took the initiative
to book a room for her.
What?
And that was when
you took advantage of her, wasn't it?
She was drunk!
That's rape! You're an animal!
Where's your brain?
Rape?
It wasn't.
I left her at the lobby.
The hotel settled everything.
Do you have proof
that it wasn't your child?
Ma'am, what's the proof
that it was Ridz's child?
Mom, ask your daughter.
Raudhah,
is it Ridz's child, or someone else's?
Yes, he raped me that night!
Did you hear that?
What else are you denying?
You're lucky Mom only asked you
to divorce Radwa and marry Raudhah.
If it was me,
I would've made a police report
so you'd end up in jail, you animal!
- What do you want?
- I was wondering if this is
what evil looks like, disguised as human.
So ugly. What an eyesore.
Enough.
Why do you hate me so much?
I don't care if you do this to me,
but you're dragging Radwa into it,
and I don't like it.
It's always Radwa!
You're giving me a headache!
What does she have
that you can't leave her?
Because she...
is my wife.
No one can replace her. Do you understand?
Listen.
I don't know how she manipulated you
into becoming like her too.
My mom said not to say filthy words
unless you want blisters.
What's your problem?
Mom and I have made our decision.
You have to divorce Radwa
and marry Raudhah.
What are you saying, Dad?
Don't make me lose my respect for you.
You can't even prove
that it's not your child.
So you have to marry her!
I won't let it happen.
Mr. Husaini, what made you think
I would let my husband
marry that woman?
Why are you so rude?
Do you want to be a rebellious daughter?
My husband is my heaven. I obey him.
He said he doesn't want to marry Raudhah.
Don't you understand?
Dear, I'll clean this mess tonight.
After tonight, I don't want to have
anything to do with this family.
You saved me. You healed me.
Now, they're taking you away from me?
No. I'll never let that happen.
I don't want to lose you again.
I've hurt enough. Enough.
Listen to me, darling.
No one can take me away from you.
Darling, never be controlled
by your money,
your past, and people.
Put your trust in God.
Whatever your decision is tonight,
I will follow.
I believe in you, my treasure.
Okay?
Go.
When I was young,
I've always been scared of ghosts.
But now that I'm older,
I realize that humans
are far scarier.
But the saddest part is that
the humans are my own family.
- Rude!
- Radwa, help me.
I'm your sister. Don't you pity me?
You're heartless.
You didn't think
of saving your family's name?
Then why didn't you protect
the family's name in the first place?
Ask your husband
to divorce you and marry her.
Enough!
Listen to me!
Thariq Ridzuwan is my husband alone!
That's final!
Find another man to be responsible.
You keep saying that!
Right now,
he can't even prove it wasn't his child!
- Do you understand?
- Boys.
Get the monkey out.
Just wait.
Baby?
Oh, God. You're hurt.
Baby, what happened to you?
Tell me who did this to you?
Your baby is the father of that child.
Don't be rude!
Because he couldn't get you pregnant,
he got your sister pregnant.
You call someone barren,
you don't even have a child yourself.
- You!
- Enough!
Touch her and I'll break your arms.
Ask her to watch her mouth!
All of you!
Do you have proof that the child was his?
Auntie.
Just look at your daughter. She's pale.
Only guilty people look like that.
Baby,
you didn't do it, right?
You didn't do it, right?
It wasn't your baby, right?
No, dear.
They're accusing me.
- See, it was an accusation!
- Accusation?
- What's this?
- The proof.
It wasn't just a one-time thing.
They sleep together every month.
Baby.
Baby?
What have you done?
- What have you done?
- Stop it.
- Enough!
- What do you mean, enough?
Stop it! Don't hit her!
Are you crazy, Mom?
Are you crazy? Or am I crazy?
I don't know.
Stop!
Do you have anything to say?
Do you? You don't?
Okay, let's go.
Hey, happy divorce.
And congratulations.
Don't invite me to your wedding.
Disgusting!
No!
Darling, are you going to eat all these?
I need to let go of all my feelings
by eating this chicken.
No one can lay a hand on you anymore.
You have me.
What about Farez?
Just don't think too much about it.
He's going to get what's coming to him.
- Do you need my help?
- Thanks, but no.
I don't want you to be involved
with anything related to him.
Let me handle it alone. Okay?
All right.
Fateh is awake.
That's good.
The police contacted me
to help with the investigation.
Isn't it nice
when all your plans work out?
Tomorrow's the press conference.
I will announce that Thariq Ridzuwan
is the leader
of the Gajah Hitam syndicate.
The mastermind who's been selling
the kids from Teduh.
Brilliant, Datin.
Tomorrow, Husniya Radwa
will hate Thariq so much.
Farez,
when are you going to let go of my family?
Maybe...
tomorrow.
After the press conference.
I'll be saying prayers tonight.
I feel so at peace.
When I marry Husniya Radwa,
I will repent.
Do you think God will accept
my repentance?
Amen.
- Do you have work today?
- I do. Why?
Just asking.
Darling, I'll send you to the camp today.
No need.
Can I just stay home?
It's dangerous.
Farez is still free.
What if he kidnaps you?
Dear, if he wants to kidnap me,
he would have done it already.
Especially when he came
to see me all the time.
Okay? Don't worry.
I'll be fine. I promise.
Do you love me?
Do you trust me?
I do.
Then, let me decide
what I'm doing today. Is that okay?
The thing is, I'm...
I'm worried.
Because I can't protect you.
Do you know that you're always
protecting me with your prayers?
No prayer
returns empty-handed.
You always know what to say.
Tell me something good.
Every hurt and wound
we accept with sincerity
will one day be exchanged for joy.
Leave everything to God.
Let the plans and affairs
of heaven do their work.
Look at all these pictures of these women.
They're all the same height
and the same weight as Husniya.
Why are you smiling?
Because I'm happy.
What do you mean?
Because maybe we don't need them anymore.
What are you trying to say?
Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
I was looking for you at the cafe.
You weren't there.
Why were you looking for me?
I just need a friend to talk to.
I need to vent.
Where's Thariq?
I don't know.
After I asked for a divorce,
he got really angry.
He wouldn't talk to me. It's unfair.
He was the one at fault,
but I was the one he was mad at.
Didn't he say anything to you?
He didn't. Why?
Where are you right now?
At home.
Why didn't you come
to the hospital anymore?
Did you know that I was discharged
from the hospital without him?
He's been so mean to me.
That's enough.
Don't be upset.
Can I see you?
- I want to vent again.
- Sure.
Let's have dinner tonight.
Sure, just let me know.
Okay.
Bye.
Radwa.
Yes?
I miss talking to you.
Me too.
I can't wait to see you.
Bye.
Freaking psycho!
Boss, Thariq is here.
Go to hell, friend.
Hi.
How are you?
How did you know
Razi got Raudhah pregnant?
You said you're not talking
to Thariq anymore.
I lied.
So, you know everything about me?
I love you, Husniya.
I know your mother and your sisters
hurt you all the time.
So I stalked them until I found out
that your sister
was having an affair
with her own brother-in-law.
What a psychopath.
I was stupid.
For sharing about my marriage
to someone I barely knew.
I was weak and vulnerable.
I needed a friend.
- And I was your friend.
- You took advantage of me!
You used my problem
with Thariq to ruin him!
And it doesn't change the fact
that you and Thariq weren't happy.
Don't you understand? Listen to me.
Even if I divorce Thariq,
I will never ever go to you.
I may not be Thariq
Ridzuwan's wife anymore,
but my love for him will never change,
and will never stop.
If I had known that you would hurt Thariq,
I should have let you die back then.
I, Datin Zizi Abu Samah,
as the founder
of the shelter for kids, Teduh,
would like to confess that
I have been working
with the Gajah Hitam syndicate,
which has been trafficking
the children under my care
to be sold overseas.
And the person responsible
for leading the syndicate,
the largest child trafficking
syndicate in Asia,
is...
You're a psychopath!
I respect your love for Thariq.
But loving people blindly
is dangerous.
It can make you
blind to their mistakes and ugliness.
Thariq is a perfect man.
The kindest man.
Someone you will never be,
even until the day you die!
Tonight,
you will find out who Thariq really is.
Muhammad Farez.
Because you know my Mom,
and I have so much respect for you,
I will let you go.
Yes.
I lied. I will never let you go.
You are...
the cruelest person
I've ever met in my life.
Now,
tell me.
Are you going to help me
arrest the leader of Gajah Hitam?
Farez.
What did he take from you?
You're not talking
because he threatened you, right?
What did he do to you?
Hurry up!
- Is it done?
- Boss, Holy Dragon saved Zizi's family.
Radwa!
You'd rather watch me die
than live with Thariq, right?
So kill me!
Kill me now!
Boss, we have to leave.
We got caught.
Datin Zizi exposed us
at the press conference.
She said you're the leader of Gajah Hitam.
Now, everyone knows.
Are you angry that I went out?
Do you want to know where I went?
Then why are you waiting out here?
Because I wanted to make sure
that you're safe.
Why aren't you angry?
I told you, darling.
Just do whatever you want.
Plus, I believe in you
and I love you so much.
You are a woman.
Women are special.
A woman has no limit
to her love for someone.
I'm not upset.
I'm thankful. Thankful for you.
Dear.
Yes.
I'm pregnant.
TO BE CONTINUED
Have I ever not given you
anything you want? No, right?
Just tell me what you want. Tell me.
I want to ride in a tank.
Two of our men were sent to Sabah.
They should have been back three days ago,
but we haven't heard from them.
I'm on leave now.
Radwa could give birth at any time now.
This is a non-negotiable order, Ridz.
Bring our men back.
I don't want to go.
You have to go, dear.
I love you so much.
I love you more.