( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Get rid of all the evidence.
IN FATEH'S ROOM NOW
Should I just kill you now?
Without you,
it'll be easier for me to talk to her.
Are you ready to die?
One.
Two.
I place my trust in God.
I was just testing you.
Datin Zizi wants to visit Fateh.
Sorry, nobody is allowed to visit him
without Mr. Thariq's permission.
I'm akin to his mother. He needs me!
I need orders and authorization
from Mr. Thariq.
How could you
separate Fateh
from the only mother he knows?
Be patient, Datin.
This is a hospital.
Don't make noise.
We don't want people to know
we'll make a scene here.
Okay, sir. We understand.
We'll be back later.
Datin.
Do you want to see Fateh?
Yes, please.
Of course. Come on.
Fateh!
Radwa.
Do you know that
Fateh is like a son to me?
I feel so sad to see him
unconscious like this.
I feel so helpless.
And Radwa.
She's been protecting
and taking good care of you.
Let's pray for him, Datin.
I believe Fateh will wake up.
He has to wake up.
- Radwa.
- Yes?
Can you give me
some time alone with Fateh?
Of course, Datin.
Thank you.
Fateh, take my secret to the grave.
When you're there, pray I'll go to heaven.
Datin, what are you doing?
I'm adjusting his pillow.
He looked uncomfortable.
What were you doing
with the pillow, Datin?
Like I said, I was trying
to make him comfortable!
Tell me what you were doing to Fateh!
I told you, right? I was just trying
to make him comfortable!
Is that wrong?
You were trying to kill Fateh,
weren't you?
How dare you accuse me like that?
I know what I saw!
If you try to do anything
to Fateh or try to hurt him,
trust me, you will not get away with it!
What's going on?
Datin Zizi tried to kill Fateh.
My goodness.
I wouldn't do such a thing.
Fateh is like my son!
I know what I saw.
You're ill, Radwa.
That's why you're hallucinating.
I'm not ill!
You are. That's why you slapped me!
Radwa.
Did you slap Datin?
She slapped me first.
You slap my wife?
She accused me of doing such nonsense.
It doesn't make sense!
She was trying to kill Fateh.
Ridz, you have to trust me.
No, Ridz. You have to trust me.
You've known me since you were a kid.
I would never do something like that!
You've got to trust me, Ridz.
You believe me, right?
Go home.
Go.
From now on,
I don't want anyone to visit Fateh.
Let's go.
I've known Datin Zizi since I was a child.
Datin Zizi is Mom's friend.
She was the most suitable patron
when Mom started Teduh.
She gave so much to Teduh.
Time, money, and energy. Everything.
And she took those kids as her own.
Your accusation is severe.
You're willing to say Datin Zizi
wants to kill the kids.
Where's the proof?
You don't have any, do you?
You have no idea how much it hurts me
when the person I love and trust the most
doesn't believe me.
Radwa.
From now on,
you'll be with me all the time.
You'll eat, drink, sleep,
pray, and shower with me.
Understand me?
Please kill Fateh
before he gains consciousness.
When I tried to kill him,
there was a witness.
And please kill Radwa as well.
Don't touch Husniya Radwa.
If you do,
you'll die.
But you must help me.
You got me involved in this syndicate.
You were eager to become rich.
I have the market.
You have the product.
We do business and gain profit together.
Okay, for this business to be profitable,
you must help me.
If I get caught,
all of us will be done for.
Do you know why
I chose you to work for me?
Because I can supply the kids
and you can sell them?
There are plenty of suppliers out there.
But why you?
Because you handle Teduh.
Teduh belongs to Datin Tiana.
Thariq Ridzuwan's mom.
I don't understand. What do you mean?
It's time to execute our final plan.
Plan? What plan?
You were caught red-handed by Fateh
and Husniya.
That wasn't in my plan.
But I'm happy
because my plan has become more solid.
Yes, but what's the plan?
Don't kill Fateh.
Wait for him to gain consciousness.
Let him tell the police that you're
the leader of the Gajah Hitam syndicate.
Are you mad, Farez?
The police will look for you.
Obviously.
I want you to organize a press conference.
Call all the media and everyone.
At the press conference,
I want you to confess you're involved
in selling the homeless Teduh kids.
But
you must announce that
you're working with Datin Tiana.
The real leader
of the Gajah Hitam syndicate
is Datin Tiana and her son,
Thariq Ridzuwan.
You want me to turn myself in?
No!
Just say
you'll provide all evidence
that shows Thariq is guilty...
to the police.
But what if I don't have evidence
that he's guilty?
It doesn't matter
whether Thariq is guilty.
Because society will punish him.
And the most important thing is
Husniya Radwa won't trust him anymore.
You're doing all this
for the sake of stealing
Radwa from Thariq?
Husniya will finally understand
that I've always been a good person.
And I'm trying to save her
from the real bad guy.
Thariq Ridzuwan.
You're mad, Farez.
You're doing all this for a woman.
Yeah.
You want your family to die?
Do as I say.
I didn't know you were a vlogger.
Is there a problem with that?
Back then...
Do you remember
when you uploaded the videos
and someone commented on them?
He said he wanted to die.
And you made a special video for him
so he won't commit suicide.
Correct?
What are you trying to say?
You saved him.
He owes you his life.
Well, I couldn't have let him die.
Do you remember
saying you dreamed of marrying a commando?
He knows that.
He joined the special forces to marry you.
No.
No. Not me.
- Do I know that person?
- He'll introduce himself.
And he'll ask you to marry him.
- Is he crazy?
- I know.
While we were training,
he knew I was dating you.
Remember the guy who fought me
during the finals?
Ever since then,
he's been telling me
to break it off with you.
But I refused.
He called me.
He said he'd rescue me.
But you said
you had me to protect you.
He was furious.
He tried to stab me.
And he was expelled.
But he called and threatened me
every day to leave you.
Otherwise, he would hurt you.
He stalked you every day.
Then, I went to see him.
He was adamant.
He wouldn't let me be with you.
He threatened to kill you.
So neither of us can have you.
He told me
he'd rather see you die
than marry someone else.
Is that why you said
you were engaged to Anita?
I love you so much, Radwa.
I couldn't bear to leave you.
My love for you is not as strong
as the fear of losing you.
I'd rather we break up
than have you die.
I could watch you from afar anyway.
Five years, darling.
I watched you from afar for five years.
I saw you getting angry and sad.
I was mad at myself
because I couldn't take away your sadness.
Why?
Because I promised him.
As long as I'm not near you,
he won't even try to.
But now?
He...
broke that promise.
He kidnapped you, Radwa.
And you saved me
once again.
Hey!
I thought I had killed him.
But apparently not.
As people say,
bad people are hard to kill.
Now,
he has come back
to steal you away from me.
He told Zafir to give you
the picture of Raudhah and me.
Because this is his plan.
To get us to divorce.
And yeah...
I don't have proof
to tell you I'm innocent, darling.
With only words,
you won't believe me.
You said that
I don't know what it feels like
when someone we love
and trust doesn't believe us.
Just so you know, darling, I do.
I know what it feels like
when the person we love and trust
doesn't believe us.
I told you I didn't make Raudhah pregnant.
You didn't believe it.
You asked me for a divorce.
Dear.
By the way,
the person who wants us to divorce
is my old friend.
His name is Farez.
Stay here tonight, okay?
Someone will look after you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to regain
my treasure's trust.
Haider.
I'm in trouble,
but you're lying on this bed.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Wake up, Haider.
I promise I'll do
whatever you want if you wake up.
Sing "Dia Dok Kata."
Did you just...
I woke up this morning.
You said you're willing to do anything.
Sing "Dia Dok Kata."
Are you serious?
Yeah.
You promised.
Dance as well.
People call me Demonio for a reason.
Okay.
- Nobody's here.
- Over there.
No one's here.
Louder.
- Okay, enough.
- I'll slap you.
That's enough.
- You like that, huh?
- Yeah.
I've recovered.
Thalia told me she scolded you.
If I could turn back time,
I'd do the same thing.
Even if it happened ten times,
I'd do it again.
Thankfully, Fateh is safe.
- We even managed to rescue other kids.
- Yeah.
This is our duty,
mandate, and responsibility.
A little pain is normal.
Let it be purposeful.
As long as we don't sin.
You've done me no wrong, Ridz.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
But my heart will be more at peace
if you forgive me, Haider.
I forgave you long ago, Ridz.
- Love you, brother.
- You too.
- Yeah.
- So?
Did I miss anything?
A lot, actually.
Farez.
- Farez?
- Farez.
The guy who defeated you
at the tournament.
Farez.
- He's still alive?
- Yeah.
Do you have a plan?
You said you cared about me, right?
I have another request.
What have you done?
What's all this?
Come here.
Sit.
This is for all the pain you caused Radwa.
So please...
Please don't die yet
because I haven't finished beating you up.
Okay? Did you hear me?
Peace be upon you.
We're from
the Conflict Prevention Department.
You're still alive!
Calm down, Ridz.
You don't want him dead, right?
I'm still not satisfied with this bastard.
Got it?
Yes, I know, but you have to calm down.
You're pretty when you smile.
But it's a pity.
You look sad.
I hate people in uniform.
My dad was a soldier
who was willing to sacrifice
for the country.
But he's a failure as a father.
And a husband who's very good
at neglecting his wife.
Do you think I'm selfish?
For hoping he's the one
who entered just now.
No, you're not selfish at all, Radwa.
But he said he loves me.
Do you mean
after he left you five years ago
and got engaged to someone else?
But he came back.
And? He made your sister pregnant.
Radwa, please open your eyes.
There are a lot of soldiers
in this country.
Commandos, police,
the Royal Malaysian Navy.
But you, Husniya Radwa,
you only have your husband
to take care of you.
And he can't even fulfill
his responsibilities.
What your husband did
isn't a regular mistake.
But it's the ultimate betrayal
of his wife,
who loves him with all her heart.
Do you think my decision is right?
To divorce him.
Yes.
As it should be.
I swear
I won't let you
disrupt my life with Ridz anymore.
What's the matter, Datin?
I don't want my family to die.
But I don't want to go to jail.
What am I going to do now?
We'll kill Fateh.
Leave the country.
Escape to a faraway place.
Start a new life.
What about my family?
I understand you love your family.
You've sacrificed a lot for them too.
Now, let them sacrifice for you.
Hey! They're my flesh and blood!
My family! My children!
You won't survive in jail!
You'll die.
Right now,
make a choice.
Your family or yourself?
I understand this is
a very difficult decision for you.
If you can't decide,
let me.
But after what happened to Radwa that day,
Thariq would tighten security.
We won't get to see Fateh!
I'll kill Fateh with my own hands.
What about the police?
I'll just crash into them
with the kids inside.
The most important thing is that
Fateh has to die.
And your secret will be safe.
What if you get caught?
I will never say anything.
What if you get shot to death?
Then so be it.
But I'll ensure that Fateh dies first.
You've sacrificed a lot for me, Datin.
I'll be proud
if I die saving you.
You caused problems for Thariq.
So you are stupid. Got that?
Where did you get that photo from?
You're doing this,
gathering up your friends,
just for Husniya?
Where did you get that stupid photo?
Why? Did you have a fight with her?
Where...
did you get that stupid photo?
She must've asked for a divorce, right?
I knew it.
Women who overthink like Husniya
are easy to woo.
But destroying them
is easier.
Do you want to know why?
Because your wife is a madwoman.
What did you say?
Your wife is a madwoman.
Say that again.
- Your wife is a madwoman.
- My wife is not mad, bastard!
Do you want to die? Huh?
Demonio!
If I shoot this,
you might not die.
But you won't be able
to use it anymore.
Do you want that?
So answer me.
Where did you get that photo?
Do you want it damaged?
I'll ask you one last time!
Where did you get that photo?
I don't know. Someone gave it to me.
Who?
Who gave it to you?
I don't know. All I know is that...
It was already in my car.
I swear I don't know.
All these women
look similar.
But they're not the same.
I want her to have
the same height as Husniya Radwa!
The bone structure,
size, and everything
must be the same! Understood?
Okay, boss.
We'll find out more later.
Why are you nervous?
No, boss.
Our men
didn't get to kill Zafir.
The Holy Dragon saved him.
Didn't you tell us to find and kill him?
Let it be. He knows nothing.
No point in Thariq having him.
So why were you so eager
to kill him that day, boss?
Just for the sake of it.
Because I hate seeing his face.
Because he likes Husniya.
He deserves to die anyway.
Anyway, I have a task for him.
What is it, boss?
To distract Thariq and the Holy Dragon.
They'll focus on Zafir.
My plan for Zizi will proceed
without interruption.
You are an intelligent mastermind, boss.
A genius.
To qualify as Husniya Radwa's lover,
the greatest woman in the world,
you have to be smart.
Well done, boss. Well done.
All right.
Leave.
Go to sleep. You're exhausted.
Farez is planning something right now.
With each second I sleep, I'm giving him
a chance to expedite his plan.
So you want to keep beating up Zafir?
Farez has been planning this for years.
He won't be stupid enough
to show his face to Zafir.
Someone else must've been
meeting him all this time.
I've asked our team to check
all footage from Zafir's housing area
and from the hotel
where you met your sister-in-law that day.
There must be a loophole somewhere.
What are you thinking?
We all know that Chi Beng
and Zahid worked with Gajah Hitam.
And Farez used them to distract you.
So that he can see Radwa.
So that means Farez
is the head of Gajah Hitam?
Chi Beng.
Chi Beng and Zahid are dead, right?
But Farez seems relaxed.
So that means
someone else is carrying out his plan.
But it's not Zafir.
We must find out who it is.
Datin.
Why do you want to see me?
I just want to say I'm sorry.
On behalf of Radwa.
She shouldn't have accused you like that.
And I'm sorry for what Radwa did to you.
She slapped you.
And I hope...
I hope you can forgive her.
Do you want to see Fateh?
Okay.
I forgive Radwa.
And thank you for believing in me.
All right, I'll handle something first.
Sure.
Okay.
Change of plans.
Thariq allowed me to see Fateh.
I'll kill him.
You may enter, Datin.
Just you.
Okay.
I knew it.
I knew Radwa wasn't lying.
And now I have proof
of you attempting to kill Fateh.
I'm sorry, Ridz.
Please let me go.
But why?
Why do you want to kill Fateh?
Because you sold my friends
at Teduh.
Ridz, I swear I won't do it again.
Please let me go.
I'm sorry, Ridz.
Please. I don't want to go to jail.
Please, let me go.
Since you're a friend of my mom
and I have so much respect for you,
I'll let you go.
Fateh is fine.
He's gained consciousness.
Thank goodness.
Darling, I want you to understand this.
We need proof to take action
for such accusations, okay?
I understand, dear.
I was just being emotional.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
So what will happen to Datin Zizi?
Don't think about that.
Let me settle it, okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you miss me?
When you told me about Datin Zizi,
it's not that I didn't believe you.
Darling.
Even if the whole world didn't trust you,
I'd be with you.
And I'll always believe in you.
Thank you, dear.
I...
I might be selfish sometimes, but...
But why can't you believe me
the way I believe you?
No, dear. You're not selfish at all.
I'm the selfish one. I'm...
I overthink that...
- No, you're not wrong. At all.
- If I'm not...
If I'm not wrong,
why would you ask for a divorce?
No, dear.
No.
I don't want to divorce you.
We'll never ever separate.
We'll be with our love, Thariq Ridzuwan.
Forever.
TO BE CONTINUED
Half of me. Half of you.
You look a bit like our future child.
I don't know why...
I don't know why I'm like this today.
I can't see or smell chicken rice.
I feel nauseous.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Mom!
Don't touch my wife.
Ridz. What are you doing here?
I will announce that Thariq Ridzuwan
is the leader
of the Gajah Hitam syndicate.
That's enough. Don't be upset.
Can I see you?
I want to vent again.