( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
How are you, brother?
I'm touched.
You looked relieved that I'm not dead.
Is it because you feel guilty?
You tried to kill me.
Your good friend.
Like brothers.
It was all because of
a woman.
What do you want?
I want to rescue Husniya Radwa.
She doesn't need rescuing.
She's not in trouble.
I'm her husband and I'm here for her.
Aren't you getting a divorce?
You were not here
when she really needed you, bro.
When she was almost kidnapped,
you didn't rescue her.
Luckily, I was there.
She's always sad.
She's depressed because of Aina,
your aunt,
and Zafir.
She just needs someone
to talk to, you know?
But you were not there, bro.
You're always busy with your mission.
Her husband doesn't care about her.
And then
you impregnated her sister?
You're a psycho, bro.
You said that you love her till paradise,
but you hurt her every day.
That's why I'm here now.
To rescue her.
I understand.
So this was your plan all along.
So Radwa hates me.
Good effort.
But Radwa is my wife.
Move on, Farez.
No way in hell am I moving on!
Husniya Radwa is mine.
She has never
and will never be yours.
She doesn't even know you.
She didn't use to,
but now she does.
She knows me
and maybe even loves me
because I'm always there
when she really needs someone.
You have to accept the fact, my friend.
Husniya Radwa is fated to be with me
since the time she saved me.
- Where are you running off to?
- Hey.
Farez, where's my money?
I gave it to you yesterday.
I gave you everything.
That was yesterday. What day is it today?
Yesterday was Monday. Today is Tuesday.
Hey, listen to me.
I only asked you for 50 ringgit.
Is it so hard to find?
I'm sorry.
Sorry? Sure. This is your forgiveness.
Stop lying to me.
- Why did you go to school? Check his bag.
- There's nothing in there.
If you don't dodge, you'll get hit.
Luckily, you did.
You look so smart, but you're so stupid.
- If you don't have money, earn it.
- Nothing.
There's nothing.
He doesn't have a single cent.
I'm sorry.
I was bullied starting
in my first year of secondary school.
I don't know why,
but they kept it up until my final year.
Husniya went through the same.
She was bullied from her first year
of secondary school to graduation.
Today, I was bullied at school again.
As usual, it's because I'm short.
The story goes like this.
I came out of the library, looking for
my shoes, but couldn't find them.
I was looking for them and I found out
that they hid them on top of a cupboard.
I couldn't reach them.
They laughed at me
when they saw me jumping like that.
I don't know what's so funny.
After that, they came out of the library.
They put on their shoes, but I pulled
the shoelaces before they could tie them.
They were upset.
If only I were brave enough like you.
So they took my shoes back.
I put them on and left.
Serve them right.
Who told them to bully me?
But it did cross my mind.
I was definitely going
to be beaten the next day.
I'm sorry, Dad. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad. Don't hit me.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Hey, I hate having a sissy son like you.
Why didn't you fight back?
Dad.
- Please don't hit me.
- You should've died back then!
Such a sissy boy.
Hey, come here.
Stay here.
I asked for money,
but you said you didn't have it.
Where are you going?
To the shop.
Oh, you're hungry?
Where's your wallet?
Hurry up. Faster!
Sorry, that's all I have.
- Just this? Just 4 ringgit?
- Yes.
- Please.
- No need for a wallet then.
What's wrong with you? Come.
One more.
Take off your shirt.
Take it off. I don't trust you.
You're a liar! Take it off.
Take it off!
- Your pants.
- Take off your pants now.
Hurry up.
- No. No, please.
- Take it off.
Let's go.
I'M NOT BRAVE ENOUGH
TO FIGHT BACK AS YOU DID.
I hate having a sissy son like you.
-Please don't hit me.
- You should've died back then!
I CAN'T STAND BEING BULLIED.
I CAN'T STAND IT
AND I'M SCARED TO GO TO SCHOOL.
EVEN MY DAD WANTS ME DEAD.
Hi, everyone.
Sorry, I made a last-minute video.
It's because I read a comment on my video.
It was from an anonymous person.
They talked about being dead.
So this video is for my anonymous friend.
Please don't hurt yourself.
Please.
Okay?
I understand you're tired.
I understand that you don't want
to be scared every day,
but when you feel like killing yourself,
it's as if...
Okay, listen. Try to understand this.
When you feel like committing suicide,
this part is dead.
Your heart is numb.
So you don't feel pain anymore.
You're not afraid or ashamed anymore.
So you have nothing to lose, actually.
So don't give up.
Please don't give up.
Okay?
They can't hurt you or scare you anymore.
They can't embarrass you anymore
because you're "dead."
They can't hurt someone
who has died. Right?
Most importantly,
you have to fight back.
It doesn't matter how.
Play dirty or rough.
Just do anything you can.
As long as you win.
Farez.
You, come here.
All you want is money.
Farez!
Yes, Dad.
My son is no longer a sissy.
You're not a sissy.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, Dad.
Believe me.
Even if you lose,
you'll still win.
Yes! You're right.
You're right, Husniya.
I won earlier, Husniya.
I won. I won because I listened to you.
Thank you for rescuing my life.
Even my dad is proud of me.
He sent me to a Muay Thai class.
Guys.
I dreamed that I got married last night.
Want to know who I married?
Yes, I do.
I married a soldier.
Me with a soldier?
Okay.
What's your objective?
You said you were going
to defend the country.
Yet you failed this small test.
Only two of you passed.
- What's your name?
- Farez, sir!
- You?
- Thariq Ridzuwan, sir!
This is my last warning.
If you do it again, you'll pay for it.
How many times have I told you?
Do you understand?
- You...
- It hurts.
What?
- Are you trying to be a gangster?
- That's not your business.
- You can go.
- Okay.
- Burhan, let's go.
- Hey.
Are you trying to pick a fight with us?
Do you know who my dad is?
Yeah.
An exemplary father
who lives full of regrets.
For having a stupid son like you.
Your dad said that
rather than keeping you,
he should keep a monkey.
Monkeys are not stubborn.
They're smart and good-looking.
I really hate bullies.
Hey!
I hate bullies too.
Let them start.
So we have a reason
to report to the warden.
Self-defense.
You and a monkey.
- Who's more handsome?
- The monkey, of course.
Hey, monkey.
Come on, monkey.
Hey!
What are you smiling at?
No, it's nothing.
- Is it a girl?
- No.
So you have a girl. If you don't invite me
to your wedding, I'll jab your face.
Of course I'll invite you, bro.
You're my brother.
- Be my best man, okay?
- Of course.
How long have you known her?
It's just me. She doesn't even know me.
What?
- We have never even met.
- What?
But she was the one
who saved my life before.
If it wasn't for her, I think
I would've been dead a long time ago.
I came here because of her too.
After we graduated and started working,
I wanted to see her.
I want to propose to her.
You are such a gentleman.
You've never even met her,
but you want to propose to her.
A wise man.
Yeah, mean...
I know that she had a tough life too.
So I'm proposing to her
because I want to rescue her.
You know what?
For me...
If we talk about love,
I'm...
I'm not well-versed.
Your story was cringey, but it was smart.
I like it. It's smart.
And you? With such a pretty face,
don't tell me you're single.
Not single? Am I handsome?
I do.
I have the love of my life.
I'll ask her to come to the tournament.
Okay?
Okay, sure.
- What?
- Show me her picture.
- No.
- Come on.
- Why are you so stingy?
- Hey. Look.
- What?
- Look there.
Hey, is your girlfriend there?
I'm alone down here.
Hey, you said you'd introduce me
to the love of your life.
- Right.
- Where is she?
She'll be here.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Hey.
The love of my life.
Husniya Radwa,
my future fiancée.
Hey! When did I become
your future fiancée?
When you agree later.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is my friend, Farez.
Hi, Farez.
Fiancée?
Husniya is mine.
Husniya is really mine.
Husniya is mine!
Mine!
We've known each other.
We've met.
I'm sorry, Husniya.
Your future fiancé, Thariq Ridzuwan,
is dead.
Let's get married, honey.
So,
when will you agree to be my fiancée?
Are you ready?
I'm ready to be your husband.
Are you sure I'm your soulmate?
Why are you so sure?
- Because...
"Please make Husniya Radwa my wife."
I pray for that every day.
Every prayer we make
will be answered.
Okay, we can get engaged,
but with one condition.
I agree.
I haven't said anything.
Listen to me.
I can even buy you a tank, you know?
Why should I ask for a tank?
Then? What's your condition?
In the final match tomorrow,
you have to win.
Then we can get engaged.
What if I lose?
If you lose,
it means you're not sincere
in being my fiancé.
No, listen.
I promise you.
In the final fight,
I will win.
That's my promise to you.
- Promise?
- I promise.
I promise. Easy fight.
Okay, we'll see.
- Okay, let's go.
- You'll get it if you lose.
- Okay, but what if I win?
- I'll be your fiancée.
Did I do anything wrong?
Why are you upset with me?
I was
bullied from my first year
to my last year of school, Ridz.
They called me stupid,
soft,
and a sissy.
When they were tired of calling me names,
they'd prank me.
They threw my shoes in the toilet.
They spat on my food and cut my hair.
They stripped me off in front of everyone.
You report to the teachers?
I did.
I was beaten up every day
because of that, Ridz.
Your dad?
I told him,
but he'd beat me up too.
He was embarrassed.
To have a sissy son like me.
He was the one who called me sissy.
For my entire life, Ridz,
I was a loser.
I've never won anything.
I've never achieved anything.
But for the first time in my life,
I know what I want.
I want...
I really want
to win the tournament tomorrow.
We're friends, right?
I'm your brother, right?
I hope you can help me, Ridz.
You want me to withdraw?
No, don't.
I want us to fight,
but I want to win.
Can I?
Ridz, if you
really take me as your brother,
I hope you'll let me win tomorrow.
Please.
Let's invite
our special juror, Mr. Adrean.
The first finalist is Farez!
His opponent will be Thariq Ridzuwan!
Thariq!
Boys, let's have a clean fight.
The rules are easy.
Do not hit the back of his head.
Do not hit his neck
and his groin.
And no elbow.
Always protect yourselves, boys.
Touch gloves.
Friends forever?
Ready?
Fight.
Ridz, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Ridz.
- Just stop this fight, please.
- Hey.
- I'm okay.
- Ridz.
- Can you continue?
- Yes, I can.
You promised to win, right?
Yes.
How are you going to win
if you don't fight properly?
Okay, okay.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Fight.
Stop. Stop!
Farez!
Last warning.
No elbow.
Good, my friend.
Let Husniya see that you're a softy.
Like a sissy boy.
Ready?
Fight.
Stop.
Ridz, stop.
- I'll stop this fight.
- No, I'm okay.
I can still fight.
Please don't stop this fight.
I will win.
Ridz.
Farez's ribs could be cracked,
if not broken.
Farez. Hey, stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
You don't want me to win, do you?
Because you promised Husniya you'd win.
I won't let you marry her, Ridz.
You stole her from me.
You betrayed me, Ridz.
The girl who saved your life...
is Radwa?
Farez, please. Please stop. Enough.
You took her away from me, Ridz.
Farez, she doesn't even know you.
You haven't even met her.
What are you talking about?
In my whole life,
I want nothing but Husniya.
I'm alive now
and I want to keep living for her.
I love her, Ridz.
Farez, enough.
- I love her, Ridz.
- Farez.
Whether you win or lose,
she'll never choose you.
It's enough.
- Stop it.
- I don't just want to win!
I want you to die.
What are you doing?
I called Husniya, Ridz.
I told her that she was the reason
I didn't commit suicide.
She saved me, so I want to save her.
You know what she said?
She said you can save her, Ridz.
You will take care of her.
- What are you doing?
- Husniya is mine, Ridz.
- Farez!
- Ridz!
- Husniya is mine.
- Are you crazy?
Husniya is mine. Let me go.
Come with me.
Get out now.
- I will kill you, Ridz.
- Get out.
What happened to Farez?
He was dismissed.
They escorted him out.
This is for you, Ridz.
I'll go first.
I'M OBSESSED WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND...
Long time no see, my friend.
Farez.
Stay away from Radwa.
I want her, Ridz.
Why do I have to stay away?
Because she's my future fiancée.
She's my future wife.
I love her way more than you do.
Leave Husniya now
or I won't hesitate to hurt her.
If you really love her,
you won't hurt her.
This is not love. This is an obsession.
Don't be a psychopath.
Is there a difference
between love and an obsession?
Most importantly, she's mine.
I'd rather have her dead
than have her date you, Ridz.
Come on, Farez.
Radwa hasn't done anything wrong to you.
She made the biggest mistake
when she chose you, Ridz.
For that, she should die.
What do you want me to do?
As long as Radwa is safe.
Leave her.
Let her hate you.
And then don't ever see her again.
Okay.
I'll do it.
But you must promise me.
Don't ever see Radwa.
Okay.
I won't get her.
Neither will you.
Honey.
To me,
you're dead.
I know I was wrong,
but there are some things we can only love
and not own.
Damn you, Farez!
You hurt Radwa!
It doesn't matter
if I hurt her or anything.
The problem now is,
you broke our deal, bro.
We agreed before.
We won't get Husniya Radwa, but you...
- You married her, bro.
- Who are you calling stupid?
Who broke the deal?
Who kidnapped Radwa?
Right?
I planned it so well.
I even bought a house for Husniya.
I just needed to propose to her,
but you came and ruined it!
You wanted to take her away.
And you want to kill me?
I'm waiting for you to divorce Husniya.
Then I'll marry her.
What the hell are you talking about?
You impregnated her sister, bro.
Husniya Radwa will never trust you
until she dies.
What? You want to have a DNA test?
No need.
I can swear that the baby
her sister is carrying will die
before you take a test.
You'd kill a baby in the womb?
Stupid? You're stupid too.
If we want to do something bad,
we have to do it cleanly.
Get rid of all the evidence.
You mean you want to kill Zafir?
Where are you going?
The boss said thanks
and you can go and die.
TO BE CONTINUED
From now on,
you'll be with me all the time.
Understand me?
It's time to execute our final plan.
Plan? What plan?
My love for you is not as strong
as the fear of losing you.
I'd rather we break up
than have you die.
You all can stop trying to make me stupid.
You caused problems for Thariq.
So you are stupid. Got that?
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW