( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
That is not necessary.
I want her to be present.
Mom, can you let me
discuss with her first?
I want you to make a decision today.
What's all this? What's going on?
Radwa. I've come here
to tell Thariq to divorce you.
And marry Raudhah.
If you think you love your family,
and respect me
as the mother who gave birth to you...
- Let Thariq go.
- Mom, that's enough.
Shut up! I want an answer now!
Look at her. She can't wait anymore!
Soon, everyone will notice
her growing belly.
Okay, then. You should leave first.
We can discuss this another day.
I won't leave
until you make your decision.
Radwa.
I want you to agree.
Say it!
I agree.
I do.
But I'm asking you to go back first.
We'll discuss tomorrow, okay?
Are you sure?
If you don't come,
I will come here.
Mom, please.
Dear...
Do you want to die or stay quiet?
Treasure.
If you want to cry, then cry. Let it out.
Don't keep it. It'll make it worse.
Just cry. Go.
Darling, aren't you angry?
Mom forced me to divorce you
and marry Raudhah instead.
Don't you feel angry?
If I were you, I'd be really mad.
I know you're mad. Let it all out.
Scream if you have to! Just scream. Go!
Go!
How could Mom do this to me?
I know I was wrong.
But I'm still her daughter!
Since I was young, I never felt her love.
No hugs, no laughter, no tenderness.
When I grew up,
I no longer cared about all that.
I still supported them. 100%!
But why are they taking away
my only happiness?
And you agreed to it!
You agreed to marry Raudhah
because she can conceive.
- She can. And I couldn't!
- Darling.
Listen to me.
I don't even want children.
And I didn't agree.
I only did that because I don't want
to see you hurting like this.
Darling.
No matter what,
I won't ever leave you.
It's okay.
Falah?
Where are you?
Falah!
Where are you, Falah?
You said you won't leave me again.
- Hello?
- Hello, Ridz.
It's Fateh.
What's the matter?
It's Falah, my friend. He's gone.
- Gone?
- He was sleeping next to me.
But when I got up, he's suddenly gone.
Listen, Fateh. Go back to sleep.
Tomorrow, I'll come
and we'll look for Falah together.
Okay, Ridz.
Ridz, that night,
he was sleeping next to me.
- Okay.
- But when I woke up, he was suddenly gone.
Maybe he ran away?
He wouldn't do that at night.
He's scared of the dark.
Maybe he's staying
somewhere else, not here?
Not possible. He loves it here.
He promised me he won't go anywhere.
- Ridz.
- Yes.
Falah was kidnapped,
just like the other kids.
Wait.
Kidnapped?
Fateh, take this.
Don't ever take it off.
If you feel you're in danger,
press this button.
- I'll come.
- Okay, Ridz.
What's your problem?
Mom did it her way, but nothing changed.
Now let me teach you a lesson.
You're rude. You humiliated Mom and Dad.
Just agree with their decision.
What's so hard about it?
What do you mean? That's enough!
Don't you think Mom's idea was ridiculous?
Divorce me?
- And then he has to marry Raudhah?
- That's the perfect idea.
You don't deserve your husband.
There are other men out there.
Why does it have to be my husband?
Because you're too dumb!
You can't even use his money
for your own family.
- Just give him to Raudhah.
- Come on. It's 2025.
Not even kids in dramas
fight for money like you.
Don't touch me!
I don't care.
I want you to make
your husband divorce you.
- Okay, fine. I agree.
- Okay.
But with one condition.
Ask your husband to divorce you first.
Then, I'll marry him.
- Are you stupid?
- Yes, I am.
Too stupid to entertain
your stupid requests.
I don't care. I will make sure
you divorce him willingly.
Get lost!
Don't ever come here.
Leave!
Ridz, pick up. Please.
A child went missing
from Teduh last night.
Under the care of...
Datin Zizi.
A friend of Radwa's adopted sister.
Fateh said before he went to sleep,
that kid was in the room.
But he woke up at 1 a.m.
He saw the other kid is gone.
Kidnapped?
It's not confirmed yet.
Okay.
Go to Teduh.
Make sure your theory is right.
- Then, we can plan what to do.
- Sure.
Wait. If Zahid's dead,
and children are still going missing,
maybe someone else is involved.
I think there's someone else above Zahid.
What about his phone?
Could you trace who sent the message?
We just got the lab results.
It's empty. Clear.
Nothing's left.
That's a long sigh.
Why?
What do you mean?
Why do men in uniform
always turn out to be failed fathers
and husbands who neglect their wives?
Do you want to know why?
But they're not all like that.
It's fine. I still want to know.
As you know,
my dad used to be in the military.
They don't have fixed working hours.
They go on operations and are always busy.
I know all that.
But as a son,
I never had any memories with my dad.
My mom managed everything at home.
But I know she was suffering inside.
But do you think
he failed as a husband
and as a dad because of that?
Because he didn't have time
for his family?
I wouldn't hate it
if that were the only reason.
But killing his own wife and children?
- I can't accept that.
- What do you mean?
Did you know that depression
can kill someone?
Mila, do you know Falah?
Falah? Yes.
The one who's always with Fateh.
Did you know that
he went missing last night?
Missing?
I didn't hear anything.
But that's normal around here.
Whenever they get bored of staying here,
they run away.
So, you're saying he ran away?
Not missing?
I don't know, Ridz.
Ever since I started working here,
I've never heard of children
going missing.
That's what happened to my mother.
She kept everything inside,
even when she's angry, sad, or sick.
It was disguised under her smile.
She didn't want us to worry.
She knew she's the only one we had.
One night,
around 2 a.m.,
my brother had a high fever
and my dad wasn't home.
He was in the middle of an operation.
Mom called him. She was having chest pain.
He didn't pick up.
She was worried about my brother.
So, she took him to the hospital.
On her way,
she passed out while driving.
The car skidded and crashed into a tree.
They both died on the spot.
Did you know what was the worst part?
My dad only came back after three days.
Only for half a day.
Later that day, he went back to work.
Did they not give him
any compassionate leave?
They couldn't be that mean.
It turned out
that while he was away on operations,
he wasn't actually serving his country.
But it was for his lust.
He had a second wife, secretly.
They were in the same unit.
I've been keeping all this
to myself for a while.
It feels good to be able to talk about it.
My husband and I are not the same.
Do you think I can be happy with him?
Why are you asking me that?
Did something happen at home?
- I don't think he ran away.
- Then, he must be missing?
I'm not sure about that.
I heard that missing children
at Teduh often went missing.
Is that true?
They come and go all the time.
I don't think anyone ever went missing.
Saifuddin, wait!
Ridz, how are you?
He wanted to know
if there's a kid missing from here.
Did you hear anything about it?
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not here all the time.
I should get going. I have things to do.
My mom asked me to divorce Ridz,
so that he can marry Raudhah
because she's pregnant.
I don't know what else to think.
I can't even make a decision.
But do you want to divorce him?
And let him marry Raudhah?
Even though he wasn't the one
who got her pregnant?
It seems like that's the only thing
that will make everyone happy.
Okay. But will you be happy?
Psycho.
No, sorry.
Toxic.
Did you know that your family is toxic?
- I do.
- How did they even think of that?
Because they are after his money.
So, it's true then. They're psychopaths.
Should I just give in?
I feel like my marriage
has been through so much.
Give in?
What do you gain from giving in?
I don't know. Probably nothing.
Then, don't.
You should only give in
when you have something to gain.
Before I send you to meet the Grim Reaper,
you'd better tell me
where the children are.
I don't know.
All I know is that this place is just
a transit point for them.
Transit?
Where to?
Answer my questions!
I think they've been sold off to Thailand.
To be beggars.
Damn you...
Why didn't you answer my call?
What for?
To listen to you cursing at me?
You've been acting worse
since you got married.
You're doing this
to your own family on purpose.
You're a useless daughter!
You're brave enough to fight me back now.
Hey, listen to me!
I want you to agree to divorce Thariq
and ask him to marry your sister!
No way. Never.
Why do I have to sacrifice
the only good thing in my life?
Don't you want me to be happy at all?
Happy?
Now, you'd better choose
between happiness and my forgiveness.
You will forgive me about...
Yes, about that incident 15 years ago!
I will forget everything!
What happened 15 years ago?
I don't want to hear
anything else right now.
Now, I want you to agree.
I'll be waiting for your answer.
Darling.
Darling, tell me.
What happened 15 years ago that
you wanted her forgiveness so badly?
Darling, please.
Darling, how am I going
to help if you won't tell me?
It's like I'm doing this on my own.
I'm trying to protect you,
but I don't know from what.
This is my problem.
Mine! This has nothing to do with you.
So, please. Stay out of this.
You're my wife.
Your problem is my problem.
Your pain is my pain too.
No, you're wrong! You have nothing
to do with this. So, please.
Why is it so hard to tell me?
We're husband and wife.
There should be no secrets between us.
Please, don't push me.
Do you think acting like this
can solve my problem?
Yeah. You're right.
I'm sorry.
I won't ask anything anymore.
Yes, about that incident 15 years ago!
I will forget everything.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You came too early.
The cafe is not even open yet.
Here's your favorite coffee.
The other day, you told me not to give in
unless I had something to gain.
Yes, that's true.
What if by giving in,
I gain something that
I've been wanting for so long?
What do you mean?
My mom offered me something
that I've always wanted.
For a long time, even before I met Ridz.
But if I want it, I have to let Ridz go.
Is it worth it to let Ridz go
just to have that?
I don't know.
Have you ever heard
that if we love something,
we have to let it go?
Should I let him go?
You want my answer?
I'll give it to you tomorrow.
Why tomorrow?
If I answer now,
you might not want
to see me again tomorrow.
Seriously, I didn't expect this to happen.
I've heard news about children
being kidnapped and forced to beg.
I didn't expect this.
I should have been more alert.
- I failed to save them.
- Okay. It's not your fault.
It was Zahid's fault.
He's been using you and Teduh
for his dirty work.
Then what are we going to do
if this keeps happening?
Calm down.
Don't worry.
From now on,
my team and I will monitor Teduh.
Please.
Darling?
Where is he?
This is my problem.
Mine! This has nothing to do with you.
So, please. Stay out of this.
You're my wife.
Your problem is my problem.
Your pain is my pain too.
I'm sorry, dear.
I was too much.
- Do you want coffee?
- I want your answer.
My answer is...
if you really love someone,
don't let them go.
Fight.
Don't ever give up.
Fight until you don't love them anymore.
When love turns to hate,
maybe only then can you let him go.
If you really love Ridz,
settle with him.
Tell him.
Not me.
Thank you.
But you could have answered me yesterday.
Why insist on doing it today?
Because I know if I did it yesterday,
I won't get to see you again.
Why would you think that?
You once told me that
you felt guilty for coming to see me.
So I hope
I will never have to save you
from any unfortunate events anymore.
Thank you.
Bye, Radwa.
Don't ever come again.
Dad, what's so important
that we had to meet here?
We could have just met at home.
Also, does Mom know
you're meeting me here?
No.
Actually, I missed you so much.
That's why I wanted to see you.
Radwa,
I want to apologize.
We shouldn't have done this to you.
I don't even know how this happened.
Raudhah won't even say who the father is.
And the way your Mom behaves.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not defending you.
It's fine, Dad.
Too many things happened all of a sudden.
Sometimes, you have to choose
the easiest way.
What do you mean?
Didn't Ridz tell you?
I saw him last month.
I'm sorry
for asking this from you.
I don't have a choice.
Mom was pushing me.
Who was the father?
I don't know.
I asked her many times.
She never said anything.
Ridz,
help us.
You're the only one
who can help our family.
I hope you won't tell Radwa about this.
Let me tell her myself.
Is that okay?
Okay.
No, he did tell me. He did.
I'm not trying to pressure you.
But if possible,
please consider.
Aren't you eating with me?
Are you feeling better?
I'm asking you. Are you feeling better?
Husbands and wives shouldn't
keep secrets, right?
But you are keeping secrets from me.
What do you mean?
Have you been keeping
too many secrets from me?
Darling, what's this?
Why didn't you tell me that
you already knew about Mom's plan?
A month ago, Dad already told you
that Raudhah was pregnant
and that they wanted you to marry her.
Let's not do this in front of the food.
It's not nice.
I didn't tell you...
because I don't want you
to be sad, angry, or stressed.
Look at you now.
You're mad at me.
I only did that to protect you.
I don't want to hurt you.
What difference does it make?
I found out anyway.
Didn't Dad tell you?
How I rejected Mom's plan?
That's why I didn't tell you.
But why did you keep it a secret?
Can you not play the victim now?
You were the one keeping secrets from me.
You didn't tell me
about what happened 15 years ago.
Your secret is like cancer
that's slowly ruining our relationship.
I won't push you.
I offered you space, to help you.
But if this space hurts you,
I'm sorry.
This is my problem.
Mine! This has nothing to do with you.
So, please. Stay out of this.
You didn't tell me
about what happened 15 years ago.
Your secret is like cancer
that's slowly ruining our relationship.
If you really love Ridz,
settle with him.
Tell him.
Not me.
Peace be upon you.
I'm sorry.
I know I was wrong.
I shouldn't have pushed you.
No.
You were right.
This secret is ruining our relationship.
I'm ready...
to tell you what happened 15 years ago.
Actually,
I had a younger brother.
His name was Raiza.
It was the night before Eid.
Dad and Mom hadn't managed
to buy their clothes for Eid yet.
All of us went out together.
At the boutique, Ridha
and Raudhah wouldn't stop fighting.
Dad tried to calm them down.
Mom was busy picking clothes.
My brother was asking for her attention.
But she ignored him.
While waiting, he ran away.
- Look at her.
- Dad, look at her!
Raiza?
Gosh!
When I went after him,
I saw him being kidnapped.
Raiza!
Help!
Radwa, where's Raiza?
Raiza?
- Why did you let him go?
- Where is he?
He was kidnapped!
Kidnapped?
You couldn't even
look after him for a while?
What's wrong with you?
Now, do you understand
why I didn't want to tell you?
I'm a murderer.
I killed my own brother.
You're not a murderer.
I'm sure you regret marrying me.
If you want to leave me, I'll accept it.
Darling, listen.
Not even a little bit.
Don't you hate me?
Why would I hate you?
I already heard the truth from you.
And now I know how to protect you.
Darling, listen.
I swear
and promise,
as long as you want to be my wife,
I won't leave you.
I am...
yours.
Forever.
Dear.
One more thing.
I want to apologize
for leaving the house
without your permission.
I forgive you.
- It's not a big deal.
- No, dear.
- I'm really sorry.
- Darling, listen.
I forgive you.
Unless you went out and didn't ask
for my money, then that's weird.
That's dangerous.
Okay? Now, it's late.
Let's pray together.
Come on.
Don't cry anymore.
Forget about it. It's okay.
I understand.
Hurry up.
They're complaining about the shortage.
They've been stuck
at the border for a few days.
Make sure this thing settles tonight.
Follow the route I just told you.
Let's go!
So? Is everything enough?
Yes, Datin.
I'll make sure to settle it tonight.
Good.
One more thing.
You know Thariq
is investigating all this, right?
Be careful. Don't get caught.
All right, Datin.
Praise be to God.
- Dear.
- Yes?
I want to apologize
from the top of your head
to the tips of your toes.
You did nothing wrong, darling.
But wait.
Why my feet?
What do they have to do with it?
Because my legs are short.
So my legs are long then?
I see.
Dear, do you want to see Raiza's picture?
Of course.
Fateh?
Similar, isn't it?
Now I understand why
you're always at Teduh,
and treat Fateh like your own brother.
I feel like Raiza is close by
when I'm with Fateh.
Answer it.
Go on.
Hello.
Okay, I'll be on my way.
- Operation?
- Yes, operation.
I have to get ready.
Okay? Let's go.
Come on.
Peace be upon you.
Radwa?
Darling?
Come with me.
Goodness.
Slowly, darling.
Don't touch me!
Darling, I swear
I didn't do all that, okay?
Why was I so stupid to trust you?
I gave you my whole life!
I was loyal to you!
And you did this behind my back?
Be angry all you want.
Let's go to the clinic.
Divorce me.
Thariq Ridzuwan.
Darling?
Darling...
- Sorry, sir. Please wait outside.
- Nurse...
TO BE CONTINUED
I don't have time! I only have an hour.
Please don't waste my time.
Follow me if you want.
Otherwise, stay here.
You're running out of time, Ridz.
If anything happens to Fateh,
Radwa will never forgive me.
Dear?
Oh, God!
Haider!
And I believe
fate has determined
I'm the man who'll protect you.
See what your stubbornness did?
Forgive me, Thalia.
No.
You're selfish!