( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
- Yes.
- All right.
- And you're taking your time.
- Peace be upon you.
- And peace be upon you too.
- What are you cooking?
It smells so good.
Radwa.
I missed you.
If I can't have Ridz,
neither can you.
What's going on?
- Oh my God!
- Aina, what have you done?
Oh my God.
Aina!
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Dear.
Yes?
Will Aina and Auntie be there later?
As far as I know, I didn't invite them.
Okay.
Okay?
All right, wear your seatbelt.
Grandma!
Ridz is here!
- Grandma, peace be upon you!
- And peace be upon you.
My dear granddaughter!
Grandma, presenting
the proposal entourage
for your beloved granddaughter.
Proposal, huh?
You're suddenly getting married.
You didn't even give me a heads-up.
Sorry, Grandma.
Let me introduce Haider,
who has captured
your granddaughter's heart.
- He's the one who wanted to get married.
- Yes.
- Scold him instead.
- Grandma, are you well?
Praise God, I'm well.
Be patient. This is normal.
She loves to mess around.
- Peace be upon you, Grandma.
- And peace be upon you.
I missed you very much.
Sorry for showing up all of a sudden.
It's okay. I'm glad you are here.
How are you?
Praise God, I am fine.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
Are you doing well?
Radwa!
Radwa, I want to apologize
for the other day.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Darling.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why did you push Aina?
Look, get up. The floor is dirty.
For your information,
it was because of this woman.
She's the reason we were kicked out
of Tiana's house that day.
Yes, Grandma. That's right.
I've heard more bad things
than good, Grandma.
Is this true, Ridz?
Grandma, of course it's true.
Why wouldn't it be?
That day, Aina slandered Radwa
about wanting to kill her.
She even put a needle in the cake.
That's why Mom and Dad went berserk.
Maybe she even faked her fall.
You and your nonsense.
That's enough.
I've prepared a few dishes today.
I cooked, so come in.
Come on in. Don't just stand around.
Radwa, for your information,
Alia, Aina's sister,
has a rather strange husband.
It's your first time here, right?
It's better not to come here.
They're all the same.
Okay. Dear, let's go inside.
Let's go!
Come on, Ridz!
Dear God.
Forgive my sins, dear God.
And the sins of my wife.
Please protect my wife and our marriage.
Amen.
Radwa, I want to apologize
for the other day.
Your sister said you can't have children.
Just wait until Ridz divorces you.
Amen.
What are you thinking about?
Come on, tell me.
It's nothing.
I'm just a little tired.
Darling.
I'm sorry
about Auntie and Aina.
I didn't know they were here.
If you're uncomfortable,
we'll pack our things and book a hotel.
Don't. It's okay here.
Don't waste money.
I'm okay. Don't worry.
Of course I'll worry.
I know what happened earlier.
Nothing happened.
Enough. Don't think about Aina, okay?
Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
Okay.
Sure?
Okay, come on.
Have some sambal.
I cooked this.
So have you bought everything?
Everything is settled except for the cake.
Good.
The guest list is done, right?
I invited Dad, Mom and Thaufiq.
But Thaufiq is out of town.
So it's just Dad, Mom and you.
Just a small group for the solemnization.
- Haider?
- I was thinking
of inviting my friends and superiors.
Around 50 people.
You're thinking about it?
What's there to think about?
Fifty?
What? That's too many.
Thalia, you're already raising your voice?
That's enough. Just accept it.
As you wish!
I'm full.
Why is she upset?
- This girl...
- I'll check on Thalia.
Yes, go on.
- Everyone is still eating.
- Kids these days.
Stubborn.
How can she be a wife?
She always does as she pleases.
It's suffocating.
Why are you bothered by what she's doing?
Whose child is this?
It's Mrs. Farida's grandchild
from next door.
She asked me to look after her.
This is Laila.
She has to attend a lecture
at the mosque tonight.
Aina loves kids, Mom.
Just like Ridz.
Do you want to hold her?
She likes you, dear.
Come to me.
Radwa.
This baby isn't used to strangers.
So if you want to hold one,
you need to have your own child.
Only if that's possible.
What's the point of having a wife
if she can't get pregnant?
Right.
Ridz has always loved kids.
But pity him.
He has a barren wife.
Since when was there
a doctor in this house?
Are you a doctor talking about my wife?
That's enough, darling. Come on.
It stinks here.
There are many spiteful people here.
Come on, darling.
Can you move aside?
- Are you okay?
- No!
You know I don't want a big reception.
Well, you chose the solemnization venue.
Let me invite my friends.
Meet me halfway.
Are you saying I don't?
No, I prefer a lively reception.
- Give me a chance.
- Give you a chance?
Okay. Invite everyone.
Invite everyone,
even the woman from the next village,
the gravedigger, and even stray cats.
Make the occasion lively!
What a mess!
Surely, you want children, right?
Don't think about all that, darling.
But they're right.
It has only been six months
since we got married.
A child is the last thing on my mind.
Because all of that is God's will.
But what if I really can't get pregnant?
Or if I never have children?
Will you be okay?
Look at me.
Face me.
Darling.
God has laid out our path.
I'll come to terms with
whether we have children or not.
I'll still be happy.
Now,
let me focus on you.
Let me pamper you.
When we do have children,
I'm afraid you will have
a hard time juggling
between me and the baby.
So now,
let me spend time with you.
Can I?
You're so full of it.
Okay, I'm going to get water.
I'm thirsty.
You're sighing deeply.
Don't overthink what they said earlier.
They're just talking nonsense.
I'm Airil.
You can call me dear Airil.
It's better for you not to get pregnant.
When you get pregnant
and your body changes,
you won't be pretty anymore.
Hey, my hands don't have poison.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
Please, move aside.
I'm going to my room.
Make a drink for me.
Just a simple one.
A tongkat ali coffee will do.
It's okay if you can't.
I can't even ask for a small favor.
The coffee is in the bottom cabinet.
Oh, yes! I just remembered.
Coffee is up there.
Grandma put it there.
Never mind, I'll help.
Darling, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Why is your face red?
I'm okay.
Darling.
Dear, I want to ask again.
If I really cannot get pregnant,
- will you leave me--
- Wait.
What are you saying?
You're always overthinking.
I already told you.
Don't think too much.
Dear.
Have Airil and Alia been married for long?
Yes.
But they have no kids.
What's the matter, darling?
Did Airil harass you?
No.
Dear, let's go to bed.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Darling.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
Let's go and eat.
I don't want to.
Do you not want to go on a date with me?
Darling.
If possible,
I want to be like that chicken.
You want to become a chicken?
You can't. It's a sin.
Why is it a sin?
Gosh, my wife is dense.
She's also a bit slow.
- Say that again.
- Okay, no.
I mean I don't want to be a chicken.
I want to be like chicken
because it cheers you up
when you're sad, angry or crying.
You're happy when you eat chicken.
So I want to be like one.
Are you stingy?
You don't want to buy me fried chicken.
Are you saving money?
Saving? I can afford
plenty of chicken with my salary.
Darling.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
What happened at home yesterday?
Nothing.
Last night?
Nothing as well.
Don't lie.
I'm not lying. I cannot lie.
Lying to your husband is a sin.
Darling.
Tell me if you have something to say.
There should be no secrets between us.
Okay? Promise me that.
- We'll see.
- Promise.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I've thought it through.
I agree to have a small wedding.
The important part is getting married.
Are you sure?
Yes.
In that case, I want to apologize too
because I got emotional and scolded you.
You're cute when you're mad.
- I'm cute when I'm mad?
- Talking back now?
This is done.
- Did you make a lot?
- Just a bit more, Grandma.
The event crew asked
if you want to sit on the dais.
If so, they want to give
a discount for the dais.
No need for a dais, Grandma.
It'll be too much.
Why? You only get married
once in your life.
Sure, you only get married once,
but a simple gathering is enough.
I want a reception.
Calm down.
As you wish.
But I don't want it.
So are we just taking photos
at the dining table later?
There will be prawns
on the pineapple display tray.
And the photos will show leftovers.
- Is that what you want?
- No.
Not that way.
- But...
- But?
No exceptions, Haider.
You're always doing what you want.
We only get married once in our lives.
The same goes for you.
You always do what you want!
- I've given in too many times.
- Did you say give in?
So what about me?
You wanted to get married earlier.
You're afraid
you'll be going for an operation.
I'm following your wish.
Do you think I want to get married
in haste like this?
Not hastily.
Why are you getting emotional, Thalia?
What did you say?
If I'm emotional,
go out and find an unemotional woman!
I'm troublesome
and I don't tolerate you, is that it?
Find another woman
because I don't want to marry you!
What are you saying?
I'm saying this wedding is canceled!
This girl...
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
Are you packing to go back to KL?
Radwa, when I think again,
I don't know Haider at all.
How am I going to marry him?
True.
If we don't know that person,
or what they want,
how can we live with them?
Yes and we're always arguing.
We both want different things.
How can we get married
when we're not compatible at all?
The problem isn't compatibility.
She doesn't tolerate anything at all.
Here's the thing, Haider.
Communication is very important.
You have to always discuss and share.
The most important part is to be honest.
- Don't keep secrets.
- Right.
But not her.
Does she think I can read her mind?
I'm not expecting him to read my mind.
If he truly knows me, he'll understand
without me saying anything.
That's true.
We can't tell them everything.
We don't have to tell everything, right?
Yes.
It's not that I don't love Haider.
But if we argue like this every day,
how can we get married?
We get married to be happy.
Be happy?
Of course we get married to be happy.
But she has to be fair.
Let me win sometimes.
I...
Actually, I don't like you
marrying my elder sister.
You understand why, right?
But deep down...
I feel really relieved.
I'm relieved you're the only one
who can take care of my elder sister.
With that, I have one piece
of advice for you.
What is it?
The key to happiness
isn't tolerance,
but yielding.
As a husband, you must give in.
Okay?
That's strange advice.
Who's the one who's already married?
You're making that face.
- You're making that face again.
- Are you speaking in an accent?
Don't ask.
Do you want me to slap you?
Don't be stubborn with me.
- Okay.
- You'll understand when you get married.
Where are Thalia, Haider and Aina?
Thalia is in her room.
Haider went out for a while.
Let him cool down.
Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
Why do you always bring this baby over?
Maybe Aina is babysitting
part-time, Grandma.
You're funny.
It's not funny!
- That's insolent.
- Is it really, Mom?
I laughed.
Ridz.
I'm not doing this part-time, Grandma.
But Laila misses Uncle Ridz.
Poor Ridz.
He can't have children of his own.
Darling, hold her for a while.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Why are you whispering?
Look at that, Mom.
She's holding the baby like a doll.
It's a good thing she's barren.
The child would die
if she had one of her own.
Right, Mom.
People get married to have children.
Maybe she married because of lust.
I'm just respecting Grandma here.
Don't undermine me.
Jeez, she's just kidding.
No need to be upset.
Right, Radwa?
Just kidding?
There's a limit to joking around.
Well, look at that! How insolent.
- I seek forgiveness from God.
- Take this baby.
Don't show your brainless attitude here.
Darling.
Did Airil bother you?
No.
Go to the room and rest.
- But I haven't washed the dishes.
- Let me do it.
It's okay. Go to the room and rest.
Please.
- Radwa.
- What's this?
- Where are you going?
- Let go!
The more you refuse,
- the more I like it.
- Move it!
What's with you?
Dear!
You're very pretty.
Not suitable for Ridz at all.
You should find a man
more compatible with you.
Dear!
What are you doing, asshole?
What are you doing?
Do you want to die?
Enough. Why are you doing this
to someone else's child?
- Oh my God!
- Ridz, stop it!
- Let him die!
- Dear?
Dear, please stop it!
Dear.
Take your husband out of here.
Get out of my house!
I don't want to see you ever again!
- Leave!
- Enough. Alia!
Go back.
I said go back!
Dear.
Are you mad at me?
- Dear, please say something.
- No.
I'm not mad at you, but at myself.
I feel like I've failed you.
No, it's not your fault.
It's all my fault
for not telling you earlier.
Why didn't you tell me?
- Don't you trust me?
- No.
No. I didn't want you
to fight with your family.
That's all.
Dear, I'm so sorry.
From now on, promise me
you won't keep secrets from me. Okay?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry, my treasure.
I'm sorry.
Dear.
Yes.
I can't live without you.
The past two days
have been frustrating for me.
I don't know how to live without you.
We're not compatible, Haider.
You're north and I'm south.
You want black and I want white.
We can't be arguing like this
throughout our marriage.
I apologize for always opposing you.
I promise to follow everything after this.
This isn't about opposing.
We, you and I...
are not compatible. Understood?
I don't want to be the reason
you don't get what you want in life.
We're too different.
Never mind, I'm willing to give in.
- How long will you give in?
- Forever.
You're crazy!
I'm crazy. Crazy about you.
If compatibility matters to you,
we'll go and check.
Check?
What is there to check?
We'll check.
Okay, Thalia. Close your eyes.
I'll go and choose the cake you like.
If I get it right,
you won't have to doubt anymore.
You'll definitely like it.
- For sure.
- Okay.
- Agree?
- We can't. We're not married yet.
Agree. I'll close my eyes.
But make sure it's correct.
Don't waste my effort
of coming here, okay?
Yes, I promise not to waste it.
- Promise.
- Okay? One, two, three.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hold on.
Okay, done.
Open your eyes.
You've had them closed for a while.
No, I'm afraid you got it wrong.
Okay, on the count of three.
I'll count and open my eyes, okay?
- One, two, three.
- Correct!
- Correct?
I told you we're compatible.
Right?
I love you.
What? What did you say?
- I love you?
- You love me?
Thalia, I love you too.
Let's get married.
Next time. We'll wait.
We need a date.
- But we're getting married?
- Yes.
Okay, eat up.
We'll get married.
Hey, barren woman!
You came here and ruined my family.
You seduced Alia's husband, right?
Be silent if you know nothing.
Don't harass me.
I want you to divorce Ridz!
Even if we get divorced,
there's no guarantee he wants you.
You need to understand
that it takes two to tango.
Snap to your senses.
You don't deserve Ridz.
You're barren!
Is that all you have against me?
Do you know Ridz was destined
to be with me since childhood?
I was supposed to marry him!
But you appeared suddenly
and stole him from me!
You're crazy.
Don't disturb me.
Aina!
Stop it, Aina!
Aina, have you lost your mind?
You drove me crazy.
Don't!
Don't hit me!
What's going on?
It hurts!
What did you do to my daughter?
She slapped me.
Radwa, did you slap Aina?
No, Grandma. I swear, I didn't.
Oh dear. Why, child?
You don't deserve Ridz!
You don't deserve to marry him either!
- Insolent!
- You're mad!
What's with you?
Just marry Ridz to someone else!
Ridz is in the uniformed services,
so he can't practice polygamy.
But he must divorce this barren woman!
- Just divorce her!
- Divorce.
Then let him marry someone
who can give him children.
- Ridz wants children!
- Enough!
Enough!
Oh my God.
Ridz is in the uniformed services,
so he can't practice polygamy.
But he must divorce this barren woman!
Just divorce her!
Then let him marry someone
who can give him children.
Come to me, sweetie.
You wouldn't need to hold my child
if you had your own.
Don't say that.
Radwa will be hurt if she hears that.
I was just kidding.
If possible, I don't want
to hold someone else's child.
I want to experience having my own child.
But that's the thing. I...
I don't want to pressure Radwa.
Don't.
It's fine if we do.
It's okay if we don't.
By God's grace, I'll be okay.
Who are we to question God's will?
Right?
Ridz, what about Radwa?
Is she still traumatized
from that incident with the heart?
I don't know.
I brought her here for peace of mind.
But it's getting worse.
Do you know what's the saddest part?
What?
She tries to be strong in front of me.
And I feel useless.
Because I'm not able to protect her.
What about that heart?
Did you find out who did it?
Not yet.
Your CCTV footage wasn't helpful.
Adrean.
Don't you think that...
No, not possible. He's dead.
Ridz.
Where's Radwa?
- No, Radwa's not with me.
- Okay.
When I went to the kitchen
to look for her,
Grandma said
- Radwa argued with Aina.
- I seek forgiveness from God.
Go and look for her now.
An argument?
You!
You're desperate to marry him, right?
Confident you can give him kids?
What's wrong with you?
Radwa?
Jamilah? Aina?
What's wrong with all of you?
- Enough!
- Well, ask this woman, Mom.
Ask her!
She won't be satisfied
until our family is destroyed!
You should just die, mad woman.
Your mother surely regrets
giving birth to you.
That's right! You're right!
My mother regrets giving birth to me.
My life is a burden to everyone.
I burden Grandma.
I burden Mom and Ridz!
Especially, you.
You can't have Ridz as your son-in-law.
You don't get to steal
his dad's wealth too, right?
Insolent!
Crazy!
Crazy woman!
Darling, please.
Radwa?
Radwa, love.
Please, put the knife down, love.
I'm here, treasure.
Put the knife down, please.
You must be disappointed in me, right?
Because I have yet
to give you a grandchild.
I didn't even think about that, love.
Ridz.
You must regret marrying a woman like me.
No, darling. No.
Radwa, all of us love you.
That's a lie!
You!
You want him so bad, right?
- Marry him!
- I won't marry anyone else but you.
- Why do you still want this mad woman?
- Just shut up!
She's my wife, not a mad woman!
You'll never marry me!
Just shut up!
You're desperate for kids, right?
Just marry her!
I know everything!
I heard everything!
You misunderstood. I didn't even say that.
Please, put the knife down.
Please, I'm with you, darling.
Shut up!
Shut up, crazy!
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have brought you
back to Grandma's house.
I know.
No.
All this is my fault.
I...
am bad luck.
Aina is right.
We shouldn't have married anyway.
Darling.
Don't say that.
Just a second.
Darling, go upstairs now.
Let me discuss with her.
That is not necessary.
I want her to be present.
Mom, can you let me
discuss with her first?
want you to make a decision today.
What's all this?
What's going on?
Radwa.
I've come here to tell Thariq
to divorce you.
And marry Raudhah.
TO BE CONTINUED
Have you ever heard
that if we love something,
we have to let it go?
I want you to force your husband
to divorce you, okay?
Okay.
- Okay, good.
- Fine. I agree.
But why the secrecy? Why?
Can you not play the victim now?
Who's being secretive?
You've been keeping a secret from me.
When love turns to hate,
maybe only then can you let him go.
Divorce me.
Thariq Ridzuwan.