( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Hello, my favorite flashlight.
Hello, my favorite black bat.
Are you well?
No.
I miss my treasure.
Are you ready
for the happiest day of your life?
What are we doing?
We will do everything
that we've never done before.
Ready?
Yes, my treasure.
Darling.
This place is beautiful.
- Beautiful, right?
- Yes.
It's as if we're in heaven.
Heaven's beauty is indescribable, darling.
It's our forever after.
Our home.
Promise we will meet there?
I'm happy here.
I'll stay here forever.
Forever, yes.
But not here.
In heaven.
You must be strong.
You must fight to live on.
To live with my treasure.
I'm happy here as it is.
Right?
Darling, tell me.
Don't you like it?
Dear, I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
Anything for my treasure.
But this time, I'll cook.
Okay, my love.
Darling, we've been living together,
but this is our first time
cooking together.
Dear.
How's my cooking all this time?
Super delicious.
Really?
Is it really delicious or are you trying
not to hurt my feelings?
They're delicious. Have I ever lied?
Okay, in that case,
taste this.
Is it salty?
No. It's okay.
I would like some more.
- More? Okay.
- Yeah.
- Is it that good? Here.
- Darling, hold on!
Are you happy?
- Happiest day of your life?
- Absolutely.
Good.
Now, lie down.
- Why?
- Go.
Okay.
Here?
Good night, dear.
Close your eyes and sleep.
You must return.
Wait.
Well...
I can't sleep and I won't sleep.
If I can only see you here,
then I will stay here forever.
You can't. This isn't your place.
Listen here.
The love between Husniya Radwa
and Thariq Ridzuwan is so strong.
So, nothing can stop me from being here.
You understand me now?
Okay, fine. You win.
- I know.
- It's true.
Husniya Radwa really loves
Thariq Ridzuwan.
So, we'll stay here together.
Forever. Okay?
I will be here for you.
Forever.
Wherever you go, I'll be there.
I promise.
We have something to tell you.
Please brace yourself.
What is it?
Radwa...
She's gone.
Where did she go?
She's passed away.
Passed away?
Let's head to the hospital
and make arrangements for the deceased.
How did she die?
She suffered complications
during childbirth.
You mean...
Radwa was pregnant?
Radwa.
Forgive me, Radwa.
I didn't take care of you.
I didn't protect you.
I didn't...
I didn't even know you were pregnant.
Oh, God!
What kind of father am I?
Where are you going?
Out.
Where to?
To Radwa's funeral.
I won't allow it.
Since when does a husband
need a wife's permission?
She's our daughter.
What's wrong with you?
Don't ask me.
I've always wanted her to die.
God has granted my prayer.
She's dead now.
She's your flesh and blood!
You are heartless.
Don't berate me.
If you leave, we're over.
Do you dare?
She's mad.
Dato', is her family coming?
It's okay, Imam.
Let's just proceed.
Sure, Dato'.
Radwa.
I'm sorry, Ridz.
I couldn't wait for you to wake up
to bury Radwa.
We will run a few tests soon.
2 WEEKS LATER
What happened to Thariq, doctor?
Did we miss something?
Physically,
Mr. Thariq is almost fully recovered.
His bullet wound is healing.
His breathing has stabilized.
His blood test showed positive signs.
He is healthy.
Doctor, I have a question.
If he's healthy, why hasn't he woken up?
He should be.
But...
It seems like Mr. Thariq
has lost the will to live.
If there's nothing else,
I'll excuse myself.
- Okay, doctor.
- Yes.
- Wow, this place is huge!
- It's huge.
Darling, why is it that
when we were dating, got married,
and we were apart,
I didn't think about taking you here?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
I've been busy with work
and haven't had time for you.
It's your duty to do your job.
I'm very proud to be your wife.
That's all in the past.
I no longer have to think about work.
I want to spend all my time with you.
Wherever, whenever,
I'll be with you.
Would you like that?
Come. Let's go there.
Come.
- Are you happy today?
- Happiest.
Good.
Go to sleep.
No.
- Go to sleep.
- No.
Do whatever you want. I will not sleep.
Why are you here?
Because...
Because of you.
Or is it out of guilt?
You promised to be with me
in the delivery room,
but you never came.
You were not there when I died.
So, which is it?
Are you here because of love
or guilt?
Mom,
Radwa didn't leave anything for us?
That useless girl had nothing.
Dad said she had a child.
Her husband is in a coma.
Nobody knows when he'll wake up.
He could also die. Right?
Mom, let's take her child.
Hey! Over my dead body.
I don't want her descendants
to live in my house.
Mom, think about it.
It's done, right?
Mom, we take her child
and demand monthly child support
from the family.
We could get at least
5,000 ringgit a month.
You're dumb.
Do you think
they would simply give you money?
Just say that before Radwa gave birth,
she came to our house
and sought your forgiveness.
She asked for blessings.
And she professed her wishes.
She said that if something happened
to her and her husband,
she wanted you to care for her child.
Do you think they would fall for that?
Who will take care of the child? You?
You can't even take care
of your own child.
Don't dream of taking care
of someone else's child.
Mom!
We don't need to take care of the child.
We'll hire a sitter
using her in-laws' money.
This is easy money!
That's a better idea.
I told you.
I can't wait.
Ridz.
I've never blamed anyone
or myself,
but whatever happened was fate.
If I hadn't come to see you that day,
none of this would've happened.
When you are ready, wake up.
I love Thalia, Ridz.
But I know
it's incomparable to your love for Radwa.
I don't like to blame others, Ridz,
but in this case,
it's my fault.
All this happened
because of me.
If lying here, sleeping like this,
could ease your pain of losing Radwa,
don't wake up yet.
Take as much time as you need.
Ridz, it hurts.
I can't bear all this.
Wake up, Ridz.
You're the Holy Dragon's strength.
We understand.
We would do the same
for the people we love.
When I was captured
and tortured,
it was the first time
I came close to death.
I was afraid at that time.
But not of death.
I was afraid to leave my family.
Leaving Rania and Adriana.
I swear I couldn't, Ridz.
What would happen to them
if I weren't around?
What if they miss me?
Who would put my child to bed?
Who would finish off
Rania's salty chili fried rice?
Even if it was fate,
that fear would still haunt me.
But the feeling quickly faded
when I was reminded of you, Ridz.
I suddenly felt strong
because I was sure
you would come save me, Ridz.
And I would not die
because you were around.
And you really came to save me.
Because of you,
I still get to see my family, Ridz.
But because of me,
you couldn't be with Radwa
when she needed you.
Wake up, Ridz.
I want to apologize to you.
I miss you, Ridz.
Wake up, Ridz.
You promised to be with me
in the delivery room,
but you never came.
You were not there when I died.
So, which is it?
Are you here because of love
or guilt?
- I love you, Radwa, but--
- Please don't feel guilty.
I died because it was my time to die.
Even if you were around,
you couldn't have done anything.
But at least I'd be by your side.
I was always by your side.
When you really needed me, I wasn't there.
It's all my fault.
No, dear.
It's not your fault.
I'm at fault.
I was arrogant.
I was smug with God.
That night,
I was so confident
I could save Adrean and Haider.
And then go back
to be with you during delivery.
I was so cocky.
I forgot to seek God's protection.
I didn't even say my prayer.
I thought I could complete
the mission alone.
But when I really needed God,
I had forsaken Him.
I was shot.
I drowned and nearly died.
But instead,
you died.
This is all my fault.
I was arrogant with God.
You think I died
as a punishment from God?
You died because of me.
No.
But it's all in the past.
I don't want to be sad anymore.
This is our happy place
and will forever be our happy place.
It's nice having a movie night like this.
All we did was argue back then.
I love you.
I love you...
more.
Mira Filzah looks like you.
But of course you're prettier.
Of course, we are beauties.
But short.
What?
The lizard wants us to watch the TV.
Gosh.
How do we assemble this thing?
It's such a hassle.
Mom, read the instructions
before starting.
What a headache. Call your dad.
- Let him do it.
- No, Mom.
If he knows, he might ruin our plan.
He doesn't dare to go against me.
- Call him.
- Dad!
Where's that old man?
Dad!
This.
Put this together. I don't know how to.
Why is there a baby crib?
I want to take in Radwa's child.
Are you mad? I won't allow it!
How dare you call me mad?
You dare go against me now.
Are you not done torturing Radwa?
Now, you want to abuse her child?
What?
You want to threaten me with divorce?
Do you think I'm scared?
I can make it happen anytime.
If you want a divorce,
I can make it happen! Get it?
- Don't be rude, Dad.
- Don't be rude to me!
Insolent child.
Hey, I want to know.
Don't you want to take care
of your grandchild?
Don't you want to care for Radwa's child?
Tell me. Where's her child?
At Radwa's house or Thariq's mom's house?
Hey!
How's the baby?
Getting better. The jaundice has subsided.
But she refuses milk.
How's Ridz, darling?
Ridz...
He's the same.
Poor Tia.
She lost her mom and Ridz is unconscious.
Death can make us question fate.
I have 1,0001 reasons to love you.
You know what the first one is?
You always put God first.
Whatever you do, you do it for God.
You love me for God too. Correct?
Yes.
But if your love for me
distorts your judgment of God,
stop it.
Stop loving me!
I don't want to be a wife who ruins
her husband's relationship with God!
Why are you mad? Don't be sad.
- I told you this is our--
- Stop it!
Enough! Wake up!
That was her last wish to me.
I hope...
Dato' and Datin could help
fulfill her wish.
Look, ma'am.
If that was her final wish,
then it's a responsibility
she's entrusted to you.
We will fulfill it.
Dear.
Thank you, Dato'! Thank you, Datin!
You see...
She's also my first grandchild.
I really wish to care for her.
What should we call her?
Call her?
What do you mean?
For instance, we call our son,
Thariq Ridzuwan, "Ridz."
What about our granddaughter?
- What's the name?
- What's her name?
My goodness.
You don't know
your first grandchild's name?
Look.
Give us some time
because Tia is still in the hospital.
The hospital?
Is she ill?
Jaundice. Don't you know?
You can take care of her first.
Once she's healthy, send her to us.
Please have a drink.
Why are you eager to get rid of me?
Don't you love me?
- Honey, don't be like this.
- Don't you care about me?
I'll be heartbroken
having lost you forever.
Let me stay here! Why not?
There's no problem here!
No mission, no work.
No Farez, no Aina. Nothing!
Just the two of us!
You don't love me, do you?
Honey.
Do you hate me so much
that you're eager to be rid of me?
Why are you so mean?
Can't you love me
the way I love you, Radwa?
I...
regret marrying you.
I regret loving you.
I regret knowing you.
You want to get rid of me?
Fine.
I'll leave.
You will never see me again.
I...
hate you.
I honestly hate you, Husniya Radwa.
Darling.
Tia can't stop crying.
She's been crying for a long time.
The doctor is giving her a blood test.
Calm down.
Take a deep breath.
Now tell me what happened.
This morning, the doctor came by
and said she was okay
and could go home.
I was excited and called Mom.
But she said not to.
I have to send her to Radwa's mom.
They will take care of Tia.
Why? That can't be.
That's the issue.
They said that if something happened
to Radwa and Ridz,
Radwa's last wish was
for them to care for Tia.
Ridz wouldn't allow it.
Do they have proof?
No. But Dad said we have nothing
to prove otherwise.
So, if we refuse to fulfill Radwa's wish,
we're wrong.
Okay, I understand.
But why can't Tia stop crying?
I don't know.
After speaking with Mom,
I talked to Tia as usual.
I told her she's healthy and can go home,
but she can't leave yet.
Then we have to send her
to her evil grandma's house.
After I said that,
she's been crying nonstop.
I pity her.
She's been crying for quite a while.
What should we do?
This is not real, dear.
I am not real.
The real Radwa will tell you
that she loves you very much.
That she was happiest
when she was with you.
You're the best gift for her.
And she's proud to have given you a child.
This is not real, dear.
In reality, you would never yell at Radwa.
You would never think badly of me
and say those things to me.
Because you are a nice person.
That's why you can't be here.
I can't bear to lose you.
I can't live without you.
I...
I don't have the strength.
I'm not strong without you.
I'll always be with you.
In here.
For as long as you need.
You are strong.
You're my Thariq Ridzuwan.
Do we still have money for shopping?
Look, we spent thousands.
Of course we do.
Just use the credit card.
Just claim the expenses from Ridz's dad.
If he asks what we spent so much on,
just say we bought baby stuff.
Create more soppy tales for them.
Say, "Uncle, Dad is retired."
"Mom is a housewife and has never worked."
"Radwa left us with no money.
We're penniless."
Who knows, after hearing that,
he'd give us 20,000 to 30,000 a month.
It would be worth it.
Radwa's child. Hey.
- Come with me.
- Where to?
Let's go to the hospital
and visit Radwa's child to see
if she's really sick and in the ward.
If that's the case, once she's healthy,
we'll take her under our care.
- You're right.
- Let's go.
Tia.
Baby Tia misses her dad.
My baby.
Darling.
I would do anything
to hug and kiss Baby Tia.
But I can't.
It's okay
because you're around.
You can comfort me
when I miss my child.
But you must comfort me all the time
because I will always think of her
and worry about her.
Because she's alone there.
She has no father or mother
to put her to sleep,
feed, hug, and kiss her.
When she's grown,
other kids would have their parents
to send them to school.
Other kids would have parents
to celebrate their birthdays.
But not her.
Other kids would have parents
to say "I love you" to them.
Radwa would do anything
to hug, kiss, and smell her
for one last time!
But I can't!
You could! Only you could do that!
Thalia.
Mom.
Come, Tia.
My goodness!
Gosh.
My grandchild is so cute!
What do you want?
I just wanted to say
that my granddaughter is cute.
Okay, look, Dato', Datin.
Since our granddaughter is healthy
and can be discharged,
as we've agreed,
I will take her home and care for her.
No!
Why not?
Her dad is here. He'll take care of her.
Look at Ridz. He's in a coma.
How can he take care of the baby?
For all the pain you've been through,
I'm sorry.
For all the pain you're going through,
I forgive you.
I love you, Thariq Ridzuwan.
Good night.
Now, wake up, dear.
Ridz can take care of her.
What's the problem?
Her dad is in a coma.
He's as good as dead.
Rude!
Mom!
Don't you touch my daughter!
Your daughter was rude.
You should advise her.
Rude! Hey, she's not your child!
She's my brother's daughter!
She's my sister's daughter!
She's my child.
Thank God.
Tia Radia binti Thariq Ridzuwan.
My precious.
TO BE CONTINUED
I will kill Thariq Ridzuwan.
I promised Radwa
that I'll take care of Tia a thousand
times better than I ever took care of her.
Aina! Tia!
Aina took Tia away, Ridz!
I'm Farez, your husband.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW