( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
until the day I understand.
When it comes to resilience,
I am someone forged from losses
I was never ready for.
And I've come to believe
that loving someone is simply
another name for the courage to lose.
I'm glad she's finally asleep.
She wouldn't let go
of this toy tank until she fell asleep.
I feel sorry for her, but...
But thank God.
Thank God. You did a great job.
When the time comes,
it will be our daughter.
Sure?
Pray for us
that we'll have a daughter as cute as her.
Of course.
Well...
But...
I miss Radwa.
So much.
We all miss her.
But your brother
misses his wife even more.
We have to be strong
for Ridz.
Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too, Ridz.
I took this toy tank
because Tia wouldn't let it go
until she fell asleep.
She was crying. I felt sorry for her.
No, Ridz. I was the one who took it out.
- Sorry.
- Sorry, Ridz.
Thank you for looking after Tia.
You guys can go back now.
I've ironed your clothes for tomorrow.
They're in the closet.
Come on.
Ridz, I'm sorry.
Darling, I can't lose you.
I love you so much.
And I love you too, Thariq Ridzuwan.
I miss you so much.
Happy tenth anniversary, darling.
For our family.
Tia was playing with your toy tank.
She loves it. Right?
She's just as weird as her mom.
Darling.
I'll officially be replacing Dad
as the hotel's CEO today.
You're fine with me quitting, right?
There will be no mission
and no risky job.
So I can focus on Tia
more than I did on you.
I miss you so much, my treasure.
And our precious Tia misses you too.
Even though she will never get
to see her mom,
I will make sure
that she knows who her mom is.
And that she will love her mom.
Every moment of the day.
Want to chat with me?
Do you?
Listen.
You must remember our words.
Live well.
Be a humble person.
Have patience.
Hold back your anger and disappointment.
Accept every fate that God has determined.
May God
ease everything for Tia Radia
binti Thariq Ridzuwan.
I won't forget what you said to me.
Thariq Ridzuwan,
your shoulder is
my favorite place to rest.
Your warm embrace feels just like home.
Even a single smile from you
can heal a thousand of my wounds.
I'm sorry if I've ever fallen short
of being the good wife you deserve.
I'm giving you the gift
of a child, my love.
Hold her close and love her
just as deeply as you have loved me.
I promise
I'll take care of our precious Tia
a thousand times better
than I took care of you.
No one can ever harm her.
I promise.
Peace be upon you, darling.
Let's go. Come with me.
Say goodbye to your mom. Bye, Mama.
Yes, baby. I'm here.
I'm here.
Hold on.
Usually, the Megah Holding CEO
would come walking
with at least five bodyguards.
But our Thariq Ridzuwan
came with a stroller.
Gosh. While carrying a bag of diapers.
That's rare.
Yes, baby.
Hi.
See? She's happy to see me.
Everybody's happy.
Of course she is.
Kids love monkeys. Right?
Don't say that. It's not nice.
Look at your ears. Just like monkeys.
Peace be upon you. In the name of God.
- My gosh.
- What a cute little girl.
Why do you want to hold her so much?
You have your own child.
So what? I miss my baby.
Right?
Ridz, sorry.
- Ridz, about the toy tank, I--
- Thalia.
Thank you.
Thank you for ironing our clothes.
Guys, thank you
for always being there for me.
Are you ready?
Dad couldn't wait to make you the new CEO.
His speech is really short.
Ready.
- Baby Tia!
- No.
I just want to hold her. Don't get mad.
What do you mean?
Your face is annoying.
Your voice is too loud.
Can you get lost?
I said
get lost.
Thank you for supporting
our company all this time.
I hope you will give the same support
to my new replacement.
So, without further ado,
let me introduce my replacement.
Thariq Ridzuwan.
Yeah!
New CEO. Let's go, Ridz!
Let's go!
Ridz!
Let's go, Ridz!
Did I miss anything?
What are you doing here?
Let me hold her.
Tia? Aina! Tia!
- Where's Tia?
- Ridz!
Aina took Tia away, Ridz!
Two of you. Kevin, check the CCTV.
Upstairs.
Megat, check the back seat.
Haider, check the trunk.
- Clear.
- Bitch.
Nothing?
Where's Tia?
Where's my daughter?
I gave her to him.
Who is he?
He said if I help him,
he won't bother us and we can get married.
Who?
He asked me to kidnap Tia.
- Who is it?
- Radwa!
Guys, I found it.
Farez!
Kevin, check the CCTV footage
and traffic cams.
Track Farez's car.
Got it.
I will get Mr. Nasir's approval.
Haider, go to the camp.
Standby gears and weapons.
Daniel and Megat,
get our informers in KL.
Get some info.
KL isn't that big.
Someone must have seen him.
Ridz, follow me.
Ridz.
Today
is my anniversary with Tia
and Radwa.
Today
is the day that I finally accepted
that Radwa is gone.
Today...
For almost a year,
I tried to smile again.
I finally feel strong enough
to live again.
But Farez came
and took Tia away from me.
I promised Radwa
that I'll take care of Tia a thousand
times better than I ever took care of her.
No one can touch her.
That was my promise.
Now, I'm trying to understand.
What have I done wrong?
What is going on in my life?
What have I done
that God is testing me this much?
Be honest with me, Ridz.
You're the one who was on the prayer mat.
You're the one who prostrated.
You're the one who prayed.
You were the one crying,
pouring your heart out to God just now.
So tell me.
Do you think this is a punishment
or a test from God?
My eyes
and my brain
believe that this is a punishment.
But my heart
believes that this is a test.
Eyes can see it wrong.
Our brains
aren't smart enough
to understand God's greatness.
But the heart...
of someone kind like you
will never lie.
So, you have to keep believing
that this is all just a test.
Keep trusting in God.
With every hardship
comes ease.
I was proud before God.
I doubted Him.
I will never repeat the same mistake.
This is my test.
Truly,
with every hardship
comes ease.
We'll save Tia today.
We'll save my daughter.
There is no deity except You.
Exalted are You.
Indeed, I am among the wrongdoers.
There is no deity but Allah.
Muhammad is His messenger.
Where is he?
Contact.
Megat,
call Adrean now.
- Hello, sir. On the move.
- Okay.
Lead the way, Demonio.
I think they're heading to the airport.
We're heading that way.
He can't be taking a commercial flight.
He might be taking Tia out of the country.
There's an area in KLIA2. Head there.
Check over there.
There's a flight scheduled
to fly off from the hangar tonight.
Really?
Kevin, Haider, have you blocked
the road they'll be taking?
Yes, it's blocked.
Adrean, stop.
Why are we stopping here?
I know Farez. He must have a backup plan.
You can go first.
- I'll catch up.
- Ridz.
Are you sure?
Just go. I promise I'll come.
All right?
Be careful, Ridz.
If God wills it.
CAUTION
ROAD CLOSURE
What's going on?
Roads are closed.
Have a look.
Yes, sir. Come.
Why are you blocking the road?
Let us pass.
Will you let us pass or die?
Hey.
Don't start shooting here.
My daughter wants to sleep.
That's not your daughter!
It's Thariq Ridzuwan's!
They're playing us!
Change of plans.
Meet me at the location I just sent you.
I'm fleeing overseas.
Treasure?
I came here
to kill you,
Thariq Ridzuwan.
But when I found out
that you have a daughter,
I found the most painful revenge.
Dying is too easy for you.
I want you to feel what I feel.
I want you to feel how painful it is
to lose a child after you killed mine.
Now, release my husband
if you love your daughter.
But Tia is our child.
How are you, my friend?
Long time no see.
You look like you lost weight.
Like someone who just lost his wife.
Like someone who craves love.
Damn!
Damn it.
You tried to kill me back then.
You failed.
I never tried to kill you.
Farez,
control your emotions.
We...
We're not angels
who never make mistakes.
We're also not demons
who have no kindness at all.
We are humans.
We have our own strengths
and weaknesses.
Farez.
Every prayer we make to God
will be answered.
Enough. Farez, enough.
Your dad...
His existence in your life
was your test.
This is my test. And I accept it.
You want to shoot me?
Shoot.
Just go for it.
But just so you know,
Radwa...
will never love you.
Ever.
Shoot.
Shoot me, Farez. Go.
My dad was right.
I live in this nightmare every day.
This life doesn't suit me.
Thank you, Ridz.
Thank you for listening.
Farez...
Goodbye, friend.
Be happy.
And if I can't have Radwa,
neither can you.
All these women
look similar.
But they're not the same.
I want her to have
the same height as Husniya Radwa!
The bone structure,
size, and everything
must be the same! Understood?
Can I really be an idol?
A great singer?
I will take you to South Korea myself.
I know the owner of one of the agencies.
Korea?
Thank you. I'm so happy.
But there's a condition.
We have to fix your face.
Is it okay?
We'll make you look more beautiful.
Add dimples.
We can also polish your voice.
I mean, you have to sacrifice
to be an idol.
Thank you!
Are you ready?
Perfect.
OMG.
So pretty!
Honey, you haven't told me
why we're back in Malaysia.
I mean, I can't be an idol here.
What about my training?
And then, why do I have to wear this?
It's suffocating, you know?
I've never seen idols wearing this.
Your voice disgusts me.
Your face is perfect.
Beautiful.
But your voice isn't.
Make sure you leave no scars
after stitching.
Don't get caught.
Clean.
Also,
freeze her.
Okay, boss.
For the labor wound, do it properly.
They have to believe
that Lily was Husniya.
Understand?
Understood, boss.
Husniya will deliver anytime.
Did you speak with the nurse?
All done.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
If she dies,
you die.
Please don't.
Do what you have to do.
- Now!
- Nurse.
Good morning, darling.
Where am I?
Our home.
Who are you?
I can't remember anything at all.
I'm Farez, your husband.
We look so happy together.
But why did he do that to me?
He loves you.
But you love me.
That's why he tried to kill me?
To him...
He can't see you with someone else.
If he can't have you, no one can.
He'd rather watch you die.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving me.
I love you, Husniya.
Thank you.
I've asked you many times!
Why is it so hard to tell me?
Radwa, please. Listen!
I'm asking you one more time.
Is it true that I gave birth?
Where's our child?
Where's our child, Farez?
Answer me!
She's dead, darling!
Our child is dead.
Thariq killed our baby.
I will kill Thariq Ridzuwan.
Farez!
- Farez. Help me.
- Hey.
Listen. Hey.
I...
I am your husband,
Thariq Ridzuwan.
This is our daughter.
Tia Radia binti Thariq Ridzuwan.
You...
You gave her the name.
Darling. Hey...
Every...
The pain we make peace with today...
will be replaced
by something more beautiful.
Leave everything to God.
Let the divine take care of the rest.
Darling...
Do you remember me now?
TO BE CONTINUED
Our destiny is shaped
by the choices we make.
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
A.
R.
- Mom!
- Raudhah!
- Please.
Help me, Mom!