( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
- God is the Greatest.
If Farez had been with us,
together with Holy Dragon,
we would've been much more unstoppable.
He was a good man.
He only made one mistake.
Falling in love with Radwa.
But if it weren't for Radwa,
he would've died long ago.
Falling in love isn't wrong.
Being obsessed with something
that was not his
was his mistake.
The fate of our lives
comes with a choice.
Come to terms with it.
Let Radwa be happy with Ridz.
Farez had that choice.
I'm sorry, Farez.
Goodbye, friend.
DEBT 100K
Husziya Raudhah Binti Husaini!
You've had your fun with that RM100,000!
And you want to escape?
Mom.
Open this door now before I break it down!
Woman!
Can't you hear me?
Open this door now!
Mom.
I'm giving you two days.
If you don't settle this debt,
you'll die.
Arif!
WHERE'S OUR 100K
PAY IT BACK IF YOU WANT TO LIVE
All this is your fault, Mom!
You treated Radwa like an animal!
He's not even leaving us a cent!
You won't even let Dad contact Radwa!
You didn't let him do that
until he left us!
Radwa will laugh seeing us like this!
This is your fault!
You don't care about Radwa!
Shut up!
Insolent!
Is Thariq Ridzuwan really my husband?
The doctor said you can be discharged.
We'll go home to our house, okay?
Never mind, we'll go to
Mom's house if you're not ready.
- All right?
- Can I ask you something?
Will you be mad if I still don't believe
you're my husband?
No.
Why would I be mad?
Why aren't you mad?
Aren't you upset?
No.
Because the Radwa I know is intelligent.
She's not easily influenced by others.
All right, get some rest.
Let me do the work.
What work?
To continue the love story of my treasure.
If you want to trust me,
don't use this.
But use this.
How?
Sweetie, I'm here.
Go to your mom.
Sorry, sweetie.
Sorry for scaring you that night.
I'm so sorry.
Peace be upon you.
Darling, come in.
Welcome home.
Darling.
Every atom in me misses you
so much, my treasure.
Do you know
I did not change a single piece
of furniture in this house?
Especially this one.
Your favorite spot.
Why?
Because I don't want to lose
a single memory of us in this house.
Where's my room?
Your room is upstairs.
Yes, love.
I promise
she will become our Husniya Radwa again.
I promise.
Thariq?
"Radwa, please wear this outfit. Please!"
Peace be upon you.
Did anyone order a ride?
And peace be upon you.
What are you doing?
I've come to save you.
Save me from what?
To save you
from being forced to marry Adib.
- Who is Adib?
- It doesn't matter.
Okay, let's go.
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
Running away.
Running away?
What are you doing?
Do you remember that
you were once a runaway bride?
Remember?
No, I don't remember.
I don't need to wear this outfit
if you're trying to make me remember.
It's hot, you know!
Why are you wearing a uniform?
What's up with you?
Do you know what? Come on!
- Come... Slow down!
- Come.
What if I fall?
Are you afraid of falling?
I'm afraid of falling.
Then I'll catch you.
You have my word.
Your anger made me forget
how much I missed you.
Do I always get mad?
No, you get mad for a reason.
Just like now.
Why am I mad now?
Why are you mad now? Because of this.
This.
You're hungry, right?
How do you know?
I...
know you very well.
Every moment of the day.
Shall we eat?
Do you want to eat chicken?
Come on. I think we have to catch one.
Fried chicken.
Why is there so much?
What?
The chicken? These?
This is too much for you?
This isn't much for you. Do you know why?
Because there's a ghost behind you.
- Just kidding.
- Is there?
I'm just kidding.
Not funny? It was a little funny.
Darling.
Okay.
I have something serious to tell you.
You have to promise me
that you'll be open to it.
- Okay?
- Okay.
If your house is on fire
Call the fire brigade
Your angry heart is like
the fire burning the house.
The fire brigade will pour water
on the burning house.
For an angry heart
One fried chicken, please
What?
What did you just say?
Just now?
That's the most
legendary poem in Malaysia.
Your poem is so stupid.
Stupid?
But never mind, I like that.
Can I go to the toilet?
Go on.
Just a second.
This chicken is quite delicious.
Hi, Husniya Radwa. How are you?
She's drenched.
Poor thing, she's soaked.
Why did you pour water on me?
Are you a cleaner?
But you can't be cleaners,
your clothes are too nice.
What now?
- Hurry.
- Why are you panicking now?
I'm okay.
But I don't understand
why you poured water.
Darling!
Are you okay? Okay, breathe.
Follow me. T-H-A-R-I-Q.
Why must I spell your name?
Because...
Darling.
I don't want you to have
a panic attack, okay?
Breathe. Please, breathe.
Am I having a panic attack?
Do you have asthma?
Because you seem to be having one now.
Asthma?
I don't have asthma,
but I do have scoliosis.
Did you tell Ginger One and Ginger Two
to pour water on me?
Ginger One? Ginger...
Did you do all this to trigger my memory?
Right?
It wasn't me.
Haider! All this is Haider's plan!
His plan was stupid, right? You're soaked.
Here.
Whoever listened to him
is an even bigger idiot.
Where did you find those extras?
They're not extras.
They're my friends while I was studying.
You used to hate both of them back then.
I hired them to come here.
Maybe the people you hate
could've triggered your memory.
That's why I did this.
Luckily, they ran out of ice.
I told them to use iced water initially.
I wouldn't be able to handle it
with the air conditioner and all.
I'm sorry.
You're lucky you're good-looking.
But you're an idiot.
I'm good?
So...
this is where I proposed to you.
By the lake?
That's pretty cringe.
Cringe. That's why you rejected me.
Why?
Who's Rangga?
I'm Thariq Ridzuwan.
I don't know.
But the important thing is,
I didn't give up.
I ended up becoming
Husniya Radwa's husband.
Thariq, can you look at me?
Yes. Why?
I truly appreciate your effort
to trigger my memory.
Although it was idiotic
to pour water and all that.
But what if I really cannot remember?
We'll start over.
I'll win you back again.
For how long?
Forever.
I know that feeling will return.
If it doesn't?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you by saying that.
But I'm just confused now.
I feel lost.
Darling.
I...
will love you forever.
Even if you don't love me anymore,
and even if we're not together anymore,
I'll accept it.
I understand you need time.
As long as you're happy and are okay,
it's fine.
Back then,
you told me
I'm the greatest blessing
God has given you.
That you love me so much.
Very much.
More than you love yourself.
And I know you're honest.
Because you've never lied about feelings.
And what you've felt before is in here.
And I give you my word.
That feeling will return.
I will never
give up on you.
I will never give up on us.
I promise.
I may not be able to remember you yet.
Yes.
But when I look at you,
listen to you speak,
and hear these words,
it would not be hard
for someone to fall in love
with Thariq Ridzuwan, right?
The other day, I...
Go upstairs first.
- Separate rooms, right?
- Separate rooms.
Go and rest, okay?
Okay, boys.
How are we going
to restore Radwa's memory?
I've got an idea.
It's a little rough, but it might help.
- What do we need to do?
- Not us.
Kevin.
Hold on. I was just about to drink.
Kevin?
What can he do?
He can't do much,
but he needs to compliment Radwa.
But he must speak Malay.
We need you to help Radwa, okay?
Of course. I would love to help.
Okay, Kevin.
You need to memorize what we tell you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Radwa doesn't remember anything?
She asked me something earlier.
What if
she really can't remember me?
Tell her you'll woo her
until she falls in love with you again.
I told her that already.
I did.
Then she asked me...
What if she doesn't like me?
If she doesn't love me?
But what if what she said is right?
She will never love me.
Adrean.
I can't lose her again.
I've lost her before.
I don't want to lose her again.
Didn't you take her to see Fateh?
Fateh?
He's traumatized now.
I don't want Radwa's condition
to make it worse.
Dahlia?
Dahlia followed Aiman,
who was posted to Germany.
In that case,
there's no other choice, Ridz.
You have to do that one thing.
What if...
What if she gets worse?
How?
That's the only way for Radwa
to regain her memory.
You have to take her back
to the place that gives her pain.
Trust me.
Hi, love.
Love, forgive me, okay?
I've misunderstood all this time.
Even though I don't remember anything,
I know you're my child.
I'm so sorry, love. Forgive me, okay?
Forgive me.
My beautiful girl.
Darling.
Do you remember this tank?
Can I ask you something?
Do you really want to remember everything?
Or do you not mind living like this?
I'm willing to do anything
to regain my memory.
I want to remember for you.
Because you're such a good person, Thariq.
Okay. In that case,
go and get ready.
Where are we going?
Radwa, come in.
Radwa! You're alive?
My sister here just got terminated.
A true loser. And she thinks
she has mental health problems.
She's just following trends.
All she does is cry and get upset.
She gets sick all the time. What else?
Oh, yes. She's infertile.
Yes, he raped me that night!
You have to divorce Radwa
and marry Raudhah.
Radwa, what's wrong?
Mom!
As if I have done you wrong!
I will never apologize to you
until the day I die!
You want to know what I most regret?
I regret not beating you to death!
I hate you!
You should've died!
- Come here. You should've died!
- Mom, please!
- Come here.
- Mom!
Radwa.
Radwa, my child!
I thought I had lost you forever.
Praise God.
Radwa, my child!
You're an insolent child.
I hugged you nicely,
but you pushed me away!
Radwa?
Now, you come back?
Where did you go?
Do you know our house was attacked
by the loan shark?
You don't respect me as a husband at all.
You don't respect me at all!
Okay, you've been asking
all this while, right?
You've been asking all this while, right?
What are you saying?
Okay, I'll give you what you want.
Rozita Binti Ismail.
I divorce you with three talaqs!
- Q.
- Hey, darling.
Look at me. Please listen to me.
Inhale.
Exhale.
One.
Two.
Three.
We'll go home.
Okay?
Today
is the last day
Radwa will set foot in this house.
Go.
Go!
Amen.
Darling.
I now understand
why God took away my memories.
For me to forget all that pain.
Do you remember everything?
I remember now why
my mom hates me so much.
I can recall how she abused me
since I was little.
I apologized every day,
but she never forgave me.
It hurts so much, dear God.
It hurts.
I just want her to forgive me.
That's all.
For her to forgive me.
Darling.
Enough.
Dear God.
It's all right.
That's enough.
Is Radwa okay?
She still can't remember anything?
She remembers her family.
Praise God.
That's good.
But still can't remember me.
Radwa's head is empty.
He wants to fix her head.
You mean she's crazy?
- Oh my God.
- No...
Crazy, my foot.
You're the crazy ones.
Okay, serious discussion.
Does Radwa remember who you are?
Does she remember you're her husband?
I mean,
she's trying.
Okay, never mind.
We'll do it again.
Haider's silly plan.
Thariq Ridzuwan!
What's all this?
Answer her.
You asked people to pour water
over my head before and it didn't work.
Why are you doing the same thing again?
Hold on.
It was water back then.
What is it this time?
What's this?
It stinks!
This time...
It's strawberry, just like back then.
It's sticky, monkey!
This was Adrean's order.
- Yes, it was Adrean!
- Adrean!
- Over there!
- He's there.
Where's Adrean?
Adrean and Daniel!
- Yes, ma'am.
Monkey.
What did you put in there, monkey?
Glue, sir.
Oh my God, no wonder it stinks!
We're just having fun, sir.
I'm dead.
- She's coming.
- I'm dead.
Is she near?
Tell me when she's near.
Do you have Parkinson's disease?
Forgive us
Forgive me
- Forgive me
- Oh dear lady, do not pout
- Forgive us, the old bachelors
- If we are wrong, show us the way
- We'll gladly take the scolding
- Forgive me
- Come to me...
- Me...
- "Come to me"?
- "Come"?
Out.
Cute.
When you act angry like this.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm late, but I'm sorry, okay?
Remember what you said after that?
Why?
Why do you always save me?
Then, I said...
Just go home, Ridz.
Please leave me alone.
I'm used to being alone like this.
Then, you said...
"Morning."
Noon.
Day and night.
"I really love you, Radwa."
Here.
Do you remember me now?
I don't remember it here.
But I can feel it here.
I can feel that maybe it's true.
That Thariq Ridzuwan is my husband.
Do you know what happened after that?
After we fought,
I went out.
I went out and stopped there.
I was determined.
I told myself
I want to come back and see you.
I wanted to say, "Husniya Radwa,
will you marry me?"
Did you manage to do it?
What do you think?
I came from here and said,
"Husniya Radwa, will you marry me?"
But you weren't here. You know who was?
Only the chefs.
Then they said, "What was that, boss?
Husniya Radwa, marry me?"
Then I said,
"No."
I said,
"Husniya Radwa,
Maggi noodles."
- Maggi noodles?
- Maggi noodles.
- Maggi noodles? Yes.
Do you know what I said to him?
No vegetables.
I want two eggs.
If possible, I want either
chicken thighs or wings.
- Then he said, "Yes, boss."
- Right.
I got caught.
Peace be upon you.
What happened?
Loan sharks broke into the house.
Oh God...
Previously,
they've threatened many times.
Help!
Don't run!
- Move!
- Mom...
- Help me, Mom!
- Don't.
Please, don't!
Please don't hurt her!
Help me, Mom!
Raudhah!
No!
Raudhah?
All right, let's go.
Where's Raudhah?
Raudhah is gone.
I want to see Mom.
Let's go.
Mom?
I'm here, Mom.
Radwa.
Forgive your mother.
I used to
really hate you.
But I'm still your daughter.
A child should forgive her mother.
Not the other way around, right?
I mean it, Mom.
I forgive you.
Dear.
In all your life as a mother,
you've never done anything good
for our children.
Ridha ran away.
Raudhah is dead.
And our son
was kidnapped.
And to this day,
we still don't know
whether he's alive or dead.
The only one who is left
is Radwa.
Radwa is right here.
Please.
Please do good for our daughter
for the last time.
To avoid becoming a failure as a mother.
I...
won't allow
you
to forgive me.
Mom?
But...
I...
forgive...
Mom?
Mom.
Mom!
Mom...
All my life,
I've wanted only one thing.
I wanted you to forgive me.
That's all.
Uncle, we'll take our leave now.
Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
Come on.
I'm going to the car.
I'll wait for you there.
Dad.
Radwa.
You're still my daughter, right?
I'll love you for eternity.
Dad.
Let me take care of you.
- This is delicious.
- All of this
was cooked by me.
Megat, do you believe
Ridz cooked these dishes?
No, I think the baby cooked.
- What do you mean?
- What?
- What do you mean by that?
- Fried chicken...
Guys!
I've got a very big announcement
to make today.
Why? Are you getting married?
I know that as a Malaysian,
I should know how to speak Malay.
Yes, correct.
It is our national language.
- Right?
- Yes.
Thalia.
My apologies for saying this.
Haider.
He used your toothbrush
to scrub the toilet clean.
That's not all.
He placed the toothbrush back
for you to brush your teeth.
Seriously?
Boss, your little brother here.
You hung out at the mamak that day, right?
He had just eaten
five soft-boiled eggs, boss!
And ate stink beans too.
Then he farted on your cheese naan, boss!
And you ate it!
You farted on my cheese naan.
You, Megat!
You keep laughing.
You're crazy about divorced women.
- And rejected by them too!
- True.
He likes divorced women.
I know all of you
thought this whole time
that I've been quiet and clueless.
I don't know how to speak Malay.
Because I want to tell all of you
that you're idiots.
Idiots!
Enough. Megat!
Ridz, that's enough.
- Take that.
- You deceived us.
Sorry, guys!
Okay, guys.
Remember, we're the Holy Dragon.
We're all brothers.
Promise me
we'll remain like this forever.
Promise me, boys.
- Promise me.
- Yes, promise.
Come on.
- Until death.
Thank you
for being my hero.
For always protecting me.
Protecting us.
Darling.
I want you to know
that you will always be my treasure.
We know you're in the special forces.
Can you help?
What's wrong? Help with what?
I was just having a moment with my wife.
Help us, please!
A child fell into the lake.
- Oh my God!
- Why aren't you helping?
Because there's a crocodile!
I'll go now, okay?
Hurry!
Take the baby and go home.
- Go home, okay?
- Okay.
Dear.
I...
I believe
there's nothing you can't conquer.
Even if it's a crocodile.
Come back safe, Thariq Ridzuwan.
I will.
My hero.
My love.
Crocodile.
THE END
I'm coming for you.