( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 14=
Qing'e, I'll teach you how to
make small-portion stir-fries.
Do you know what that is?
It's making just one dish per wok.
Everyone in the village does that.
Save it.
Can they make sautéed pork slices
or Guo Bao Rou?
Or chicken stew with mushrooms?
They won't even know them.
Know why we use young
chickens for that stew?
Because the meat is tender.
Laidi,
go and
prepare a basket of potatoes.
What's for breakfast?
Millet and mung bean porridge.
And for the solid part?
Cornmeal steamed cake.
How many beans are used?
400 grams.
250 grams is enough.
Just boil plain water, then.
You want it tasty, but add nothing?
How am I supposed to cook it?
Laidi.
Pass me the Mo basket.
It's millet and mung bean porridge.
Not mung bean and millet porridge.
Millet is the lead. Mung beans are extras,
only adding flavor.
You think mung beans are you?
One says 250 grams, one says 400 grams.
Which one exactly?
250 grams.
Fine. 250 grams it is.
You won.
Here, kid. Take it.
In case you get hungry.
400 grams.
Master Song.
400 grams it is.
I want to sleep in the storeroom.
Why sleep in the storeroom?
Is someone picking on you?
You can't sleep there.
It's damp and cold.
It's drafty, with mice too.
That's scary.
I'm not scared.
Well, I am.
If anything happens to you,
how do I face your uncle?
Or the troupe?
What are you even thinking?
(Award)
♪On the golden mountain in Beijing♪
♪Chairman Mao is the golden sun♪
Yi Qing'e, what are you doing?
I'm asking you, dummy.
I'm not dumb.
Where's she going?
No idea.
Maybe going to the pigpen?
For what?
So she can be back home.
I'll fix this hole later.
And I'll install a bolt.
Use this to block the door for now.
Tell me if you need me.
Get some sleep.
We have work tomorrow morning.
Keep the door blocked tight.
Uncle!
Aunt Hua.
Master Song said you chose to sleep here.
I think it's a good idea.
It's better than being miserable with them.
I went to Beishan Prison today
to see your uncle.
I brought him some things.
How is he?
Like a different person.
Just like when you first arrived,
he's gone silent.
I told him all about you.
He tried to hide it,
but I could tell...
he cried.
He only said one thing to me.
He wanted you to keep practicing.
You promised him, didn't you?
Then you'd better keep your word.
Come here.
You're a kid from the mountains.
You haven't seen the world yet.
If city kids look down on you,
that's not your fault.
You did nothing wrong.
I know you're hurt, but you're tough.
Opera takes endurance.
Endure the pain and the hurt inside.
But we can't just endure it.
We have to learn to change.
You need real skill in you.
Whether others respect you or not
doesn't matter.
You must learn to respect yourself.
You get it?
I'm scared.
Don't be.
Remember what I told you.
We all
have to rely on ourselves.
It's never easy.
You can do it.
I have to leave tomorrow.
Where?
To have my baby.
When will you be back?
I don't know.
Look after yourself here.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Master Gou.
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
Sanyuan and I won't be around.
If the kid leaves this place,
please check on her.
If anything comes up,
send word to me.
No problem.
Hope all goes well for you.
Bring back a healthy baby soon.
Are we leaving or not?
I still need to train the kid later.
I'm off, then.
Be good.
Dachui, careful.
Worry about yourself.
Keep practicing.
Hua Caixiang had left too,
making a new home in a far land.
She was Yi Qing'e's pillar of strength,
yet she had lost her own support.
Ever since joining the opera troupe,
Yi Qing'e had been saying goodbyes.
To Bayi.
To Shoes Bai.
To Hu Sanyuan.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Watching her leave,
Yi Qing'e seemed to have grown stronger.
She had become used to partings.
♪A couple parted by life and death♪
♪The world's deepest pain♪
♪A month of sorrow♪
♪Weighs heavy on my heart♪
♪The moon is hazy tonight♪
♪Silence fills the fields♪
♪In the cold and desolate outskirts♪
♪I cry for my wife♪
♪Since we were wed♪
It's all static. I can't hear clearly.
Is it really him singing?
It's Zhou Ren Hui Fu!
Even with static, I'd know Gu's voice
even a hundred years from now.
Have the old plays been liberated?
If they have been liberated,
then the three of us
will finally see the light of day.
Nice.
Nice!
Nice. Nice!
Stop tapping. Can't you see it's stuck?
Director Huang, you hit hard.
Even Zhou Ren couldn't take you.
I heard it.
Zhou Ren Hui Fu, right?
Old plays can air again?
What are you trying to say?
I heard many out-of-town troupes
are restaging the old plays.
Shouldn't we provide
against a rainy day too?
Do you know where the rain's coming from?
It's already on the radio.
Isn't that a signal?
Who gave you that signal?
Which radio station
gave you that signal?
The Provincial People's Broadcasting Station.
We should tune in to the Central
People's Broadcasting Station.
Be careful. Careful.
Next one.
You still have an appetite?
What?
The radio just played the version of
Zhou Ren Hui Fu sung by Gu Cunxiao.
Old plays can be staged now?
I don't know.
That aired on the Provincial
People's Broadcasting Station.
Listen to the Central
Isn't the provincial one run by the Party?
You're a gatekeeper.
Yet your mouth has no gate at all.
Stay calm.
Be patient.
You can't rush hot tofu.
Where would we even get tofu?
Let me give you a warning.
The kids can't keep training like this.
With these showy moves for
the old plays, they're not even
fit for playing minor roles.
Planting rice when the pot's empty?
Too late.
True.
Worry about rice in your own pot first.
The ruler's calm, but the aide panics.
Shameless.
(Boiled water)
No, your waist is too loose.
Soft as tofu. Look.
Training isn't just arms. Use your waist.
Skip the waist, and you won't excel.
Come here.
Let me explain.
Tending the fire.
You can do both.
Do another one. Come on.
Please move aside.
Why is this kid so stubborn?
Laidi.
Come in and give me a hand.
Go.
You still have room for improvement.
- Okay, next.
- Next.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Straighten your arms.
Okay. Go.
Are you dumb or what?
Why are you so slow?
Get up, get up.
What did you say?
Did Director Huang scold you like that?
I think the kid is doing great.
That's what Director Huang said.
He's slow, so he needs hard training.
He said that?
Are you dumb or what?
Keep practicing!
One more try.
Train harder.
- Go.
Why aren't you eating?
We eat last.
What's the ration for kitchen workers?
No ration. Eat all you want.
I want to join you.
Can you think of a way?
Go ask your aunt.
I did. Got beaten for it.
Serves you right.
Since you left, I've become the worst one.
So lonely.
Train hard.
I do already.
They make it look easy.
I push the hardest and still lag behind.
No wonder they laugh at me.
I even hate myself for it.
When will this ever end?
Do me a favor.
What favor?
Train hard by day. Coach me at night.
We'll practice together.
Aren't you tired?
During that time,
one slow kid taught another the skills.
Three, two, one.
Yi Qing'e didn't know why she practiced,
- but she just wanted to.
- One more time.
Not only because she promised
Hu Sanyuan and Hua Caixiang
she'd never give up.
The hands.
Why was she like this?
Then...
- She couldn't explain.
- Kick back hard.
Swing back hard.
Three, two, one, go.
Up, up, up.
Why are you so dumb?
I'm not dumb!
Don't get angry.
That's how the teacher scolds me.
It's not like a teacher without that word.
Try it again.
One, two, three, go.
Listen.
Use both hands.
Tighten up and use your core.
Why did you hit me?
For your own good.
Leave me alone!
Why are you so ungrateful?
You do it wrong. Let me teach you.
No need.
Be a stoker forever?
What I do has nothing to do with you.
You're so stubborn.
Even Hu Sanyuan doesn't talk back to me.
Fine, then go back to your fire.
You're finished.
No, you're finished.
Who is it?
Master Qiu.
Come with me.
♪Your illness is fake♪
♪I'm a fake doctor too♪
♪Patients can't tell I'm fake♪
Just go in.
Go in.
Move.
Come on, lift your leg.
This one.
Straighten the other leg.
Higher.
Bend back.
Lower.
Lock your legs. Lower.
This kid...
Tight tendons, stiff bones.
Not much hope.
If she wants to get good,
she'll have to suffer.
Really suffer.
No kid could endure that.
This kid...
has a spark in the eyes.
Kid.
Do you know why I took you here?
Our troupe used to
be called the Cunjia Troupe.
Master Gou was their leading star,
performing the Dan role.
Master Zhou and I used to perform,
right here on this very stage.
Back then, Master Gou
was a star performer for miles around.
The three of us will teach you.
Work by day, and take training by night.
Kid,
do you know why I chose you?
Because you're the best
in the trainee class.
Those other teachers are blind.
None of them has my eye for talent.
You might look dumb, but you're not.
Out of everyone in the class,
no one has a spark as bright as yours.
It'd be a waste if you quit.
I'll teach you.
Work hard and follow my instructions,
and I'll make sure you make it.
If I fail,
I'll die on the stage.
Yi Qing'e remembered her promise,
so she kept practicing in secret,
never missing a single day.
Yet, she felt lost inside.
Cooking wasn't what she wanted to do,
but as for opera training...
even Ms. Hua and Ms. Mi
found it so difficult.
How could she ever succeed?
(Sealed by Ningzhou Police, May 15, 1977)
Gou Cunzhong came looking for her,
insisting she was a natural talent.
He even risked her life.
Before this,
no one had ever valued her so much.
Tears welled in her eyes.
She wanted to cry, to scream.
But she knew
she was only a girl tending the fire.
Helpless and torn.
She thought it over and over.
But she still wanted to prove herself.
You need real skill in you.
Whether others respect you
or not doesn't matter.
You must learn to respect yourself.
You must keep learning the opera.
However hard it gets,
keep going.
We all
have to rely on ourselves.
It's never easy.
You can do it.
I need to hear you promise me.
I promise you.
I'm in.
To train with me,
rather than with that trainee class,
will be much harder.
I'm not scared.
If you start, you can't leave it unfinished.
What does that mean?
It means quitting halfway.
I won't quit halfway.
This stays between the four of us.
Don't tell anyone else.
Got it?
Got it.
At Master Zhou's, train each night.
Before you help them cook breakfast,
practice one more hour on your own.
Can you do that?
Laidi.
It's late. Why are you still up?
Waiting for you.
Here.
Where did you get it?
Don't ask. Just eat.
I swiped them.
It's fine.
Chu Jiahe secretly gave
them to Feng Xiaoxiao.
A lot. I only took two.
He won't notice. Eat up.
Where did you go?
Don't ask.
Why not?
I can't tell you.
I don't keep secrets from you.
I even told you about the candy.
I promised that person.
Who?
Fine. Like I care anyway.
I got scolded again today.
When will these scoldings ever end?
Actually, somersaults aren't just legs.
You need the waist strength.
If your waist gives, you're done for.
Who taught you that?
Whoever teaches you, it takes hard work.
I'm slow.
No one can teach me.
I'm slow too.
It's not our fault we're slow.
They'd be the same if born in the hills.
Others might think we're dumb,
but we can't think of ourselves as dummies,
or we'd really be dummies.
Why do you sound like a grown-up?
Laidi, check out my new move!
I'll show you.
Be careful.
Laidi, what are you doing?
Starting the fire.
It's Sunday, so we only
eat twice.
I completely forgot.
What's wrong with you?
Don't burn a hole in the pot.
Let me flip another one!
What's with Heiwa? So diligent.
Heiwa.
Heiwa!
Heiwa! Heiwa!
What's the matter?
Heiwa, you okay?
Heiwa!
Heiwa.
Don't touch him! Leave him be.
Just watch him.
Don't touch him. I'll get help.
Heiwa!
Laidi, don't touch him!
Heiwa.
Heiwa. Heiwa.
- What's wrong with you?
- Heiwa fell down!
That didn't count.
Heiwa!
Heiwa, what's wrong?
Eat.
As much as you want.
You won't have to practice anymore.
No more staying in the dorm alone.
Since you left, I've become the worst one.
So lonely.
I got scolded again today.
When will these scoldings ever end?
Here.
Eat.
I'll eat with you.
I'm going to training.
(Men)
(Boiled water)
The forward somersault was better.
But don't practice alone yet.
During the day tomorrow,
practice the other basics.
Okay?
Go back and get some rest.
Hey, go back and sleep.
Turn it on.
Mr. He...
Chu Jiahe, save it.
Mr. He,
it's Saturday. Let us have some fun.
You wish!
Dancing like demons.
Look at yourselves.
During the training,
your rear hurts, your head hurts,
your toes hurt...
My fingernails hurt.
Feng Xiaoxiao!
What? Not hurting now?
No training, no pain.
Cut the nonsense.
Can't hit me!
Mr. He.
Saturday comes just once a week.
Let us play a little longer.
Chu Jiahe, Monday comes
just once a week too.
Why don't you rise early?
Mr. He.
Just one song.
Stop!
Save it!
Spotlight, follow me.
Three songs!
Feng Xiaoxiao,
come here!
How embarrassing.
The pants are
on backward.
But they swept the ground clean.
Those are called bell-bottoms.
And what kind of dance is that?
Having a fit?
It's in now. Young people love it.
Can it stay in for thousands of years?
Nothing outlasts the Qinqiang opera.
Feng Xiaoxiao.
Come help me.
Kids these days are really something.
They all think they're Nezha.
What are you staring at?
Push. I can't pedal anymore.
One, two.
Easy now.
Hold tight.
Hold tight. Hold tight.
Speed it up.
(The Qinqiang opera San Di Xue)
♪A plan♪
♪Send word to Shaanxi, check it through♪
This half pig I bought is really fatty.
The fat alone is two fingers thick.
That was three.
Come on, unload it.
Unload it.
Why the long face?
Someone's trying to take over.
Who?
Take over what?
The knife and ladle. He wants Head Chef.
That jerk.
Making stuff up again.
Master Liao?
Having tea?
Why are you so angry?
Can he even cook?
The twice-cooked pork was
burnt the last time.
He can't even stir-fry
shredded potatoes well.
The bun filling was way too salty.
The stuff he makes
is burnt, salty, and sticky.
Kid. Kid.
Stop moving things.
Take a break.
Go. Take a break.
A pig feeder as the head chef?
Embarrassing!
Everyone makes mistakes sometimes.
It was just a one-off for Master Song.
You can't just dismiss him.
What...
You can't just write him off,
right?
No, let's talk about me instead.
You shouldn't waste my talent, right?
- Go on.
- Using a sword to kill a flea?
When Director Huang transferred you,
didn't we agree you'd be the sous chef?
We have to be practical, right?
I was a chef at Chang'an Restaurant.
Being a sous chef for a pig feeder?
Does that seem right?
So what do you suggest?
I'm a reasonable man.
Here's my plan.
The position of
Head Chef should rotate every week.
Can you decide that?
Or should Director Huang talk to you?
Don't bother him with this.
It's no big deal.
Drink tea.
I'll talk it over with Master Song.
Just drink.
No big deal.
Master Qiu.
Drawing water?
A bully with backing.
Using his ties to Huang Zhengjing.
He's just being unreasonable.
Don't stoop to his level.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
You must stand tall.
Acting is about portraying life.
Your reach goes from
the gate to the kitchen!
Pooh!
I'll teach you a lesson.
Zhou Ren Hui Fu!
The lead Wusheng of the Cun generation.
Please, Master Gu.
A 17-year-old,
learning from a 60-year-old,
became so old-fashioned.
What do you mean by that?
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪