( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 15=
Master Qiu.
Getting water?
(Hot water)
He's throwing his weight around,
just because he's related
to Huang Zhengjing.
He's completely unreasonable.
Just don't stoop to his level.
What?
They really let him be the chef?
The guy is just bluffing.
What Chang'an Restaurant?
I asked around.
He just chops veggies in a tiny diner.
Keep your voice down.
I bet those salty steamed buns last time
were tampered with by that jerk.
Don't talk nonsense.
You can't accuse him without proof.
Fine, I'm talking nonsense.
Qiu, don't feel pressured.
I'm fine either way.
Qing'e.
Come in.
Check out my knife skills.
Don't go.
Hot pan, cold oil.
Stir-fried shredded potatoes.
Master Liao, Master Liao!
Too much, too much oil!
Scallions to bring out the aroma.
If you keep cooking like that,
we'll be broke
for the rest of the month.
Not a drop of oil left.
Here comes the shredded potatoes.
Cooking takes real skill.
Ignore that amateur's nonsense.
See how I do it.
What a mess.
How's that?
Hurry, hurry. Your waist.
Straighten up. Keep it straight.
Keep your legs tight.
Stand straight in life.
Performing opera is about people.
If your back isn't straight,
you'll look all limp onstage.
Wriggling like a snake up there.
It'll be disgusting.
Our opera stars,
such as Mi Lan and Hua Caixiang,
are not Dan roles at all.
Once they step onstage,
their bodies sag,
hips drop, and legs sink.
Such a waste of their pretty faces.
Do you think the audience
comes for faces?
They come for basic skills
and the opera.
The streets are full of faces.
Back then, among the Cun generation,
there were so many
great Northwest stars.
First, we had a great master.
Second...
Second, we could endure hardship.
Splits, backbend, and handstand.
Not to mention the carpet work.
Where were the carpets?
We tumbled on the bare yellow earth.
Do you know how we practiced
the circular walk?
Master made us balance a book
on our heads.
He stood there with a cane.
If the book fell,
we got caned.
We also got caned
for walking too slowly,
twisting our waist,
and shaking our heads.
After a day of the circular walk,
we were covered in bloody welts.
We were covered...
Qing'e.
Master Liao, you're still up?
Where have you been?
Nowhere.
You go to the theater every day.
What are you doing there?
I've been watching you for a while.
Are you learning opera
with that old gatekeeper?
What?
You want to leave the kitchen?
Lately,
you've seen it.
I work as the chef.
Everyone praises my cooking, right?
So, don't go anywhere.
Just learn cooking from me.
Here.
- Rock sugar.
- I don't want it.
You eat it.
No, I don't want it!
Keep your voice down.
Hey, slow down, kid.
Slow down.
Get to bed early, okay?
One day, I'll get you candy.
(Keep things clean)
So annoying.
(Hot water)
Where is that fool?
Still snoring and sleeping in.
Look at what he did.
He used half a month's oil in a week.
What about the rest of the month?
Don't worry.
This week: steamed buns and noodles.
Let's use less oil
and try to make it up.
That's not the point.
He took the cow and left you the stake.
The flame's too high.
The corn congee is sticking.
I'm not mad; you shouldn't be either.
Laidi, lower the heat.
(Hot water)
Harder.
Use your waist like in training.
This dough.
Come on, push harder.
Master Song.
Are you free right now?
I was looking for you.
Cover it and let it rest a bit.
Then call two from the troupe.
Have them help make steamed buns.
I need a rest. I'm heading back.
Qing'e, come here.
Add some water.
Don't burn yourself.
What did you see?
Tomatoes are almost out of season.
Make the tomato sauce, okay?
I haven't bought any.
- Too pricey.
- Why?
- Pricey.
The troupe is buying tomatoes
for tomato sauce.
I'll take you with me.
Will it be cheaper?
That's great.
I saw the sweater you knit for the kid.
That red one?
It's really nice.
Why are the edges curling?
Qing'e, we're short on wrappers.
Roll more.
Master Song, the filling's too salty.
- Too salty.
- Leave it there.
Here.
Okay, here.
I'll knit it. Bring it here.
- It's nothing.
- Really.
Stop.
It's way too salty.
What a jerk.
Honestly, Master Song.
Can't you be more careful?
I'll do it next time.
Good thing we caught it early.
Or those opera singers would yell at us.
Those jerks can't even act well.
Oh, my goodness.
They're ruining the troupe,
yet they pick on us daily.
It makes me so mad.
Why keep making them?
The filling is too salty.
(Hot water)
Laidi.
Master Song.
Say no more.
I know everything.
He's gone too far.
He's way too scheming
to tell right from wrong.
If this continues,
karma will get him.
It's okay to take a little loss.
Oh, right.
Keep this to yourself, okay?
It won't do you any good.
I'll just be more careful.
Thanks.
Where are you off to now?
Going to practice flips again?
Don't go.
The fire's banked. I'm done here.
Why can't I go?
Why can't you go?
You're always with that old man,
calling it learning opera.
That old man
put his hands all over you all day.
Who knows what he's up to?
I'm the chef here.
I'm your boss.
What if something happens to you?
I'm responsible for you.
I promised Master Gou.
I can't quit halfway.
I'll finish him off.
Laidi.
Master Gou.
What are you doing? I was waiting.
Why haven't you gone?
Master Liao.
You old fool.
You came over here yourself.
Why are you cursing at me?
Cursing? That's letting you off easy.
Your hands reached
from the gatehouse to the kitchen.
Trying to poach my people?
I'm telling you.
There are over twenty kids there.
Find apprentices over there.
If you reach my kitchen again,
I'll chop you off and feed you to pigs.
You mean the kid learning opera?
She goes after you've damped the stove.
It doesn't affect the cooking.
What can she learn from you?
Oh, my gosh.
She should learn cooking from me.
She's made for performing opera.
She might make it one day.
I fear she'll cook here all her life.
That would bury his talent.
What's wrong with cooking?
Opera singers used to be
in lower social strata.
Now, you're acting all fancy.
You're getting cocky, huh?
Food is the people's priority.
Do you think opera
matters more than food?
Fine.
You have a point.
The kid studies opera to make a living.
Let's talk this through calmly.
One more skill for the kid
can't be a bad thing, can it?
Even so, she shouldn't learn from you.
I know
what you're capable of.
As a man, you always play women.
All prissy and affected.
Not manly at all.
You'd only teach her
to be a vixen.
Oh, please.
Do you think you're really
Chef Liao now?
Shame on you.
You're a total embarrassment.
Why huff? You're driving me mad.
Back at that greasy roadside diner,
you just scrubbed pots and chopped veg.
Then you came here,
like a pig with scallions,
playing grand.
You can't even fake being refined.
You're just a bumpkin.
I'll teach you a lesson.
How could you hit me?
I... you...
Ah, it hurts. It hurts!
Showing off moves with me now?
You think you're clever, dumb hog?
I'll fight you for real!
Bring it on.
No, no. Whoa, why grab a tool?
Let go. Give it to me.
- Talk it out.
- It's okay.
Just wait. I'll go to Director Huang.
Go to anyone. It won't help.
You hit me, huh?
You want to be fired, huh?
- Keep it down.
- Remember this.
Neither of you will stay.
You only bully old men and kids.
You fool. Choke on your anger.
Just you wait.
You can't do this. You can't.
You'll ruin the child's future.
Don't be scared.
With trash like him, hit where it hurts.
Why should I care about her future?
Let the child go. I'll drop the ladle.
Master Liao! Master Liao!
What did you say?
If you let the child learn opera,
you can be the chef from now on.
I'll work under you.
I'll wash veg and dishes,
feed pigs, and tend the fire.
I'll do whatever
you tell me to do. Deal?
Master Gou, please don't be mad.
♪Expecting the bride♪
Zhou.
Bring me the staff.
What do you need it for?
Master Gou just fought Master Liao.
Did you lose?
Of course not.
Then why?
Master Liao won't let me learn opera.
That old coot.
I'll break his legs.
As if I'd need you to hit him.
I've thought it over.
Let's stage an introductory play,
Da Jiao Zan.
That's how we had our initiation.
You'll teach her
how to use the staff and spear;
I'll teach her posture, vocal style,
and dialogue.
What do you think?
Great.
Da Jiao Zan
is an opera excerpt from Yang Paifeng.
Yang Paifeng is a person's name.
She's about your age.
She was also a kitchen maid.
While she cooked by the stove,
she drilled martial arts foundation
and later led armies as a great general.
This opera excerpt has martial scenes.
It's perfect for initiation.
Martial scenes take real effort.
Be it a martial scene or a civil scene,
a martial arts foundation never hurts.
What's initiation?
Initiation
means the teacher drawing
the first stroke on a blank page.
Kid, remember this.
Not good.
Go.
Good.
Don't drift too far.
Pick up the pace.
Throw the punch.
That's even worse.
Project the singing.
(Remold, Rescue, Reform)
One, two, one.
(Education)
One, one.
Aim to reform.
Right.
Go.
Turn around. Pose.
Still not good.
♪The couple was separated by death♪
♪The deepest pain in this world♪
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
♪In the first month, sorrow was♪
♪Buried deep inside my chest♪
♪Tonight, the moon is veiled in mist♪
Sign in.
♪The land lies still and silent♪
♪The lonely wilds feel cold and bleak♪
Who are you here for?
♪Cries for my wife♪
Zhou Ren Hui Fu!
My old friend!
I thought you died and became a ghost.
On Tomb-Sweeping Day,
at Master's grave,
I nearly burned offerings for him too.
Where have you been all these years?
How did you make it through?
In the mountain gullies
of Xifu, Gansu, and Ningxia,
out in those remote, poor villages,
I went from village to village,
singing opera for meals where I could.
Then why not stay out there as a stray?
Why come back?
Don't steal our meal, okay?
We're very protective of our food.
Let's get serious.
That out-of-town troupe
is doing the old opera
with real drive and precision.
We old hands of the Cun generation
should show our voices too, right?
Pour some more.
Pour it. Pour it.
Who's this kid?
A relative's kid. He's an orphan.
His name is Situan.
He's been with me for years.
Half my apprentice, half my son.
So, he's your apprentice. Cheers.
Apprentice.
Good apprentice.
Come on. Come on.
Master Gou.
Come here, kid.
Hu Sanyuan's niece.
She's an apprentice to all three of us.
Where's Hu Sanyuan?
- He's left.
- Where to?
I'll tell you later.
I told you before.
What are the names of the Cun brothers?
Ren, Yi, Li, Zhi, Xin.
Wen, Liang, Gong, Jian, Rang.
Xiao, Ti, Jie, Shu, Yong.
Zhong, Hou, Shang, Qin, Jing.
What are the names of the living?
Zhong, Xiao, Ren, and Yi.
He's Xiao.
Call him Master Gu.
Go on. Greet Master Gu. Offer wine.
Master Gu, please have some wine.
Zhong, Xiao, Ren, and Yi are all here.
Good.
Hu Sanyuan's niece.
Let me tell you.
I spotted your uncle's gift for drums.
That's why he learned, got it?
Kid,
Master Gu is really something.
The top Wusheng role
of the Cun generation.
His civil scenes match
his martial scenes.
A big-name opera star back then.
Everyone wanted him in Chang'an Troupe.
Across the Five Northwestern Provinces,
he performed everywhere.
He's truly impressive.
- He knows hundreds of plays.
- Yes.
Do Da Jiao Zan in a bit.
Let Master Gu give you some pointers.
Come on, come on.
- Okay.
- Come on.
You hit the kid on the head.
Say something.
The truth or a nice lie?
Speak plainly.
Fine.
The kid's staff work is excellent.
You can tell at a glance
that Zhou Cunren taught her.
What about the posture and vocal style?
I spaced out for a second.
It was like seeing
you back in the day.
Kid,
Master Gu praised you. Say thanks.
Thank you, Master Gu.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
Training under someone in his sixties,
you've built real skill
and picked up his old-fashioned air.
What do you mean by that?
Kid,
how old is Yang Paifeng?
Sixteen or seventeen.
But on stage,
I didn't see a 16- or 17-year-old
lively and cute kitchen maid.
All I saw was a mature
and steady heroine.
You mean
the kid didn't act lively or cute?
Not lively or cute enough,
but way too calm.
Yang Paifeng is a kitchen maid.
Poor kids grow up fast.
She's no rich lady or princess
who never worries about food or clothes,
or gets doted on by her parents,
spending all day thinking
about how to be naughty or act cute.
Then why, back then, did you act
with your eyes darting around,
bouncing around like a little deer?
I was beaten by Master.
Master didn't hit you hard enough.
You know squat.
You don't know the Dan role.
Why ask me if you won't listen?
A leopard can't change its spots.
You only want to hear flattery.
You never have anything nice to say.
Is this really necessary?
It's been so many years.
You miss each other when apart,
but bicker every time you meet.
You didn't bicker enough in your youth?
Sorry, I didn't perform well.
You did great. Really great.
You're not wrong. It's not your fault.
Alright, stop talking.
I'm turning off the lights. Let's go.
Am I old-fashioned?
What does old-fashioned mean?
Go home and look in the mirror.
Practice being lively and cute.
You're hopeless.
You can't even do cute.
Hu Sanyuan.
Here.
Report to Captain Zhang at the office.
Yes.
(Qinqiang opera: Zhan Shan Tong)
♪With one roar, I'm bound outside♪
Captain Zhang.
Hu Sanyuan is here.
Report.
Come in.
Go on in.
How was my singing?
You're the pro here.
Give us your thoughts.
Captain Zhang, it was great.
How so? Tell me.
Even troupe pros avoid Zhan Shan Tong.
Yet you dare to sing it.
Why?
It takes serious vocal skill.
It's easy to go off-key.
Did I go off-key?
Tell me the truth.
Captain Zhang,
you sang it with your own style.
What style?
No one would recognize it.
Captain Zhang, you asked for honesty.
Go.
Yes, sir.
Come back.
Here.
Here's the thing.
Teach me a piece everyone can recognize.
I'm joining
the Provincial Prison System
Art Showcase.
Let's try to bring back
the first prize. What do you think?
What are you mumbling about?
(Education, Reform, Rescue)
Report: Hu Sanyuan is back.
- Rejoin the team.
- Yes.
Why are you back?
What's that about?
Nothing good.
It must be another
Qinqiang opera jam with you.
Notice.
(Turn over a new leaf)
A showcase is coming.
Inmates with Qinqiang opera talent
or music and singing skills
are encouraged to sign up
and take part in the auditions.
They'll join correctional officers
to form a top performance troupe
representing Beishan Prison
in the Provincial Prison System
Art Showcase.
That is all.
- Hu Sanyuan!
- Here!
Step forward.
Except for the Women's Detachment,
(Education, Reform, Rescue)
everyone who can play
or sing is here.
Select from them
and form a decent troupe
to join the showcase.
Bring me back the first prize.
Captain, what if we can't?
Then get a second prize.
At least get a third prize.
If you win, I'll record your merits.
(Turn over a new leaf;
Embrace a new life)
Hu Sanyuan!
Here!
I got all these instruments
exactly according to your list.
I did my part.
Now, it's your turn.
Yes.
Okay.
Start practicing.
(Turn over a new leaf;
Embrace a new life)
(Notice, Wang Jianmin, Letters)
Master Gou, did you call me?
Drink that bowl of chicken soup.
You have it.
Drink it when I tell you to.
What's so funny?
When you head back later, take that pot
of chicken soup to Master Gu.
Master Gu was right that night.
I made you too old-fashioned.
I didn't even realize it
until he said it.
I just didn't learn well.
That's just you being old-fashioned.
Don't take the blame for everything.
Have some soup.
You're too withdrawn, kid.
Hang out with the trainee class kids.
Have some fun with them.
Sing a little, dance a little.
Look at those roller skates.
You should try them too.
Go shopping, catch a movie with them.
Change things a bit.
All day in that ragged apron,
with greasy and grimy sleeve covers.
Buy yourself a few pretty outfits.
Learn to dress yourself up.
A young girl's face
shouldn't be dirty and messy all day.
Wash up more often.
But I have work to do.
Fine.
Forget what I said.
(She was never treated like a girl.)
(All her life,
she was taught to endure.)
(No one taught her how to be a girl.)
(Master Gou told her to make friends.)
(How could she possibly know?)
(This was harder for Yi Qing'e)
(than 1,000 vertical leg-holds
and 10,000 flips.)
Come on, kid. Have a bowl too.
I already had some.
Then have another.
It'll warm you up. Come on.
Save it for Master Zhou.
Gou's soup is really good.
Your master is wasted at the gate.
He should cook in the cafeteria.
Your uncle was a good man, too.
Such a shame.
He was
the most gifted drum master I knew.
I remember when he first learned drums.
His master only had to give him a hint,
and he'd make the drums sound magical.
Later, his master actually regretted it,
saying that by teaching him,
he put himself out of a job.
That's how awesome your uncle is.
Don't overthink it.
It's a blessing in disguise for you.
Gou is the best Dan role I've ever seen.
Back in the day,
his fame spread for hundreds of miles.
Just wait till he plays Li Huiniang.
You'll see.
His makeup, posture, movement,
and vocal style
are amazing.
You'll completely forget he's a man.
Master Gu.
How do I practice being lively and cute?
Being lively and cute comes from within.
If it's just practiced,
it's not cute at all.
(Rehearsal Hall, Weed through the old
to bring forth the new)
What are you looking at?
Who are you hitting?
Chu Jiahe.
Come on, come on.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
I'm reporting it to the county.
We'll do Bi Shang Liang Shan.
You're back.
Now, I feel a lot better.
Let's welcome our four directors.
Director?
A sweeper, a shopper, a gatekeeper.
How did they become directors?
They'll show us their best tricks.
What's there to see?
Go light the stove.
Some people say you four
can't direct a play at all.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪