( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
ظآزOnly after bloom comes fruitظآز
ظآزWho says glory must fade to the pastظآز
ظآزOnly through thunder
do you reach the cloudsظآز
ظآزWho made you the crown of every peakظآز
ظآزI stand at the center of the stageظآز
ظآزMy shadow is pinned against the wallظآز
ظآزFacing the light earns every medalظآز
ظآزLittle birds,
save your needless peckingظآز
ظآزThe open sky rises highظآز
ظآزWhen night falls,
the moon begins to shineظآز
ظآزI stand in the heart of these landsظآز
ظآزMy shadow bears no crown or robeظآز
ظآزThen I know truth needs no disguiseظآز
ظآزThe green hills see me as I amظآز
ظآزLike dew, lightning,
and moon on the riverظآز
ظآزShowing me exactly who I amظآز
=The Lead=
=Episode 16=
The troupe's old scripts are all here.
Shi Wu Guan. San Di Xue.
This one's Zhou Ren Hui Fu.
Xia He Dong.
Now some are all moldy.
Others have been chewed by mice.
We can't find one complete script.
So what if you do find one?
The old opera takes real skill.
The effort used in modern plays
isn't the same kind at all.
Among the actors,
me, the director,
and you,
is anyone an expert?
No.
If the old opera can be liberated,
shouldn't the veteran artists
be liberated too?
- Exactly.
- There's something wrong with that.
What do you mean, "liberated"?
The whole country was liberated in 1949.
So,
are you trying to say
those veteran artists still
live in the old society?
Director Huang...
Call me Troupe Leader.
The Revolutionary Committee era is over.
The title "Director Huang"
should be retired.
Do you know what I'm thinking?
This is no time for nitpicking.
Nitpicking?
Deputy Troupe Leader Zhu,
this is called political consciousness.
We must never lose
our political consciousness.
Stop looking down.
You're the director.
If you can't direct the old opera,
what good are you anyway?
Go and invite those three veteran artists
back.
Troupe Leader, let's talk about them then.
One guards the gate.
One manages the meals.
One watches the theater.
And what about the other?
Wandering around the world.
We don't even know if he's dead or alive.
Those three old guys have been
off the stage for over 20 years.
Look how old they are now.
At most,
they can do an opera excerpt.
A full-length opera is impossible.
Isn't an opera excerpt still an opera?
Better than having nothing to perform.
Right?
Besides,
I heard the Provincial
Troupe's opera excerpts
are extremely popular.
The tickets are impossible to get.
They're the Provincial Troupe.
And what are we?
Just a tiny County Troupe.
Provincial-army vs County-regiment level.
That's many ranks apart.
I don't need to spell it out.
A mere bit-part player from there
could play the lead here.
We have only two lead performers.
Hua Caixiang left to have a baby.
Mi Lan's busy getting married, right?
And let's talk about
the greenhorns in the trainee class.
Sure, they've trained for years.
But they can't carry the show.
What matters in the old opera?
It's the performer's real skill.
Troupe Leader,
I won't say anything so discouraging.
We'll do exactly as you asked.
We'll just wing it and force the show.
But I have one question for you.
Where will we get the opera costumes?
That's a serious problem.
Exactly.
Those costumes
were all burned to ashes.
Exactly.
Now, no one watches the new plays,
and we can't do the old opera.
It's been over a year since we had
any shows to perform.
In my opinion,
we should just fold and disband.
I agree.
Deputy Troupe Leader Zhu,
you draft a proposal
to disband the County Troupe,
and I'll submit it for you.
What do you think?
Now you're making me look bad.
Let me be clear with you.
The county leaders are quite unhappy with
our troupe's recent performance.
As Deputy Troupe Leader
in charge of operations,
if the troupe has no shows,
you will be held responsible.
That's not very fair to say.
I told you to provide against a rainy day.
And what did you say?
What did I say?
You said,
"How do we know which way the rain falls?"
Was I wrong?
Was I wrong to say that?
Enough, we'll do Bi Shang Liang Shan.
Get me a plan immediately.
I need to report to the county.
Take this seriously.
Keep your leg up.
Just keep going.
Good basic skills.
Come learn to cook with me later.
Why are you being so sneaky?
I have a surprise. Come.
Come on.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm tired of your games.
Think about it carefully.
The troupe's future is at stake.
Suit yourself if you won't come.
Surprised?
Are you surprised?
You're the boss this time.
You bet I am.
This way, please.
This is all we have left.
Quite a surprise?
It's all still here.
Thank you, Master Gou.
Thank you, Master Zhou.
Thank you, Master Qiu.
Hold on, hold on.
There's one more surprise.
Come on.
Please.
Master Gu?
You're back.
How did you get so old?
That's just time for you.
Surprised?
The troupe did two modern plays, but nobody
really liked them.
No one in the troupe can
perform the old opera.
People all say the troupe is failing.
Now, everyone in the troupe
is discouraged and listless,
barely hanging on.
Whose fault is that?
Your own.
We warned you to prepare early on.
How did you snap at us?
I'm just a donkey.
Wherever the whip strikes,
I just pull along.
Have you ever heard a donkey tell a whip
where to strike?
What's the situation of the troupe?
The county leaders are very unhappy.
So, Huang Zhengjing wants the old opera.
Which one exactly?
Bi Shang Liang Shan.
The Qinqiang opera has so many classics.
Why start with a difficult adapted play?
Huang Zhengjing thinks it's safe.
Aren't others as safe?
Back then,
when the troupe did Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui,
Huang Zhengjing wanted to be the best.
Fighting for first in the district.
And the result?
Hu Sanyuan's single blast
took Nail's life.
And almost took his own.
That changed Huang Zhengjing's fate, too.
Otherwise, Huang Zhengjing would have left.
If he had left,
would the troupe be in this bad situation?
That's because your leader is useless.
Why blame Hu Sanyuan?
What could Huang Zhengjing do?
Did he want to control everything?
Now he's a hands-off boss.
No one knows what he does.
He stays in his office all day long,
doing who knows what.
Now that you're back,
I feel much more at ease.
But I don't.
Why?
The excerpt Ye Ben from Bi Shang Liang Shan
is extremely challenging for male actors.
Lin Chong's singing,
acting, and recitation
are all extremely complex.
That's why
we're inviting you four
veteran artists back.
Teach the kids in the troupe.
Let me tell you.
I came back this time
hoping, while I still can,
to join my old partners and perform
a few opera excerpts.
What do you want to perform?
Zhou Ren Hui Fu.
Put that aside for now.
You Xi Hu.
You two, set those aside first.
Why?
The most urgent thing is that
the traditional opera needs successors.
Let the kids do something
for the troupe,
give it blood and keep it alive.
Or the troupe is beyond saving.
Well,
you head back first.
We'll talk it over.
About us performing opera,
maybe
we put it on hold.
On hold?
We're already neck-deep in dirt.
Wait longer, you'll sing in the underworld.
But what else can we do, given the troupe?
We have to save it first.
But how?
Call a doctor when it's in the coffin?
You think you can pull off
a miraculous cure?
I can't do it alone,
but the four of us can.
Let's give it
a shot together.
There might still be hope.
So what if there is?
Paving the way for Huang Zhengjing?
If you want to be his stepping stone,
go ahead, but leave me out of it.
He's walked all over me for 20 years,
and I've had enough.
Who said anything about helping him?
You two need to talk this out.
No need
to get all worked up.
You had tempers when you were young,
I get that.
But look how old we are now.
That fire should be long gone.
Why still so angry?
Just hot air.
- Let's go have tea.
- Sure.
You two, keep arguing.
Call us when you settle it.
Silly, get moving.
- Waiting to get scolded?
- Come on.
Let's go.
Argue, then. You're tough.
You go first.
Look at you.
I drank too much last time.
That talk about your apprentice
was just drunk talk.
Sir.
I was wrong, okay?
How could you ever be wrong?
You're always right.
Still sulking?
I'm serious.
In times like these, you still
trained such a fine apprentice.
That couldn't have been easy.
So you do know.
Of course, I know.
I also know
why you all risked it
to save these opera costumes
from the furnace.
Wasn't it so that one day someone
could wear them again?
If no one ever wears them,
won't they just turn to ash in the end?
Right?
I'm not trying to argue with you.
The troupe is in such a mess.
I'm worried you'll be left
holding the mess,
with no show, just dirt all over you.
Sorry.
I'm late. What did you need me for?
The four of us have decided.
We'll do as you said.
That's great!
I'll go start the preparations now.
But we have conditions.
What conditions?
First,
Huang Zhengjing must ask us in person.
He has to come himself?
So my word isn't good enough?
That's different.
You're just the one pulling the cart.
The donkey doesn't get to
choose the driver.
Fine, I'm the donkey.
But even a donkey has its pride.
Let's not worry about
saving face right now.
The troupe isn't an
old opera troupe anymore.
Without pride, there is no substance.
Fine.
I'll go get Huang Zhengjing now.
What is it now?
Since it's the old opera,
we decide how to rehearse it.
Everything follows the old rules.
Rest assured.
Huang Zhengjing is just a layman.
Besides, with your old opera,
he won't get a say at all.
What I fear most are so-called experts.
You mean me?
Once rehearsals begin,
there can only be one voice.
No scattered comments
from all sides.
It'll be chaos. We can't rehearse.
You sit there and watch.
Okay.
Seriously?
Can you just say it all at once?
Once this show is over,
it'll be
our turn to perform, right?
The troupe can't go on like this.
If I get to call the shots later,
those are tiny things.
What do you mean?
What do I mean? Think it over.
Why'd you stop that noise?
What? I have to go myself?
My rank isn't high enough.
Yours isn't high enough?
Then what rank are they?
All they want is respect.
We show them some respect,
and they'll return it tenfold.
Besides, you're head of the troupe.
So you should show up in person.
The way I see it,
the old opera troupe's bad habits are back.
Give them an inch,
and they'll ask for a mile.
Give them a little, and they push it.
Then they'll get cocky again.
They won't.
After all they've been through,
even the proudest tail
has been snapped by now.
Those veteran artists, in the end,
just want some dignity and respect.
Let them have it.
Troupe Leader.
Troupe Leader is truly wise.
Here they come.
We're not staging Bi Shang Liang Shan.
Why not?
I tried.
Where's Huang Zhengjing?
Calling me a donkey flatters me.
I'm just a mouse trapped
in a bellows. Getting grief
from both sides.
What's the point for me?
You two are cut from the same cloth.
The troupe isn't Huang Zhengjing's.
Why wait for him to invite us back?
So ungrateful.
My first condition is
now void.
Pushing his luck.
Really thinks he's a big shot.
Useless.
What kind of move is this?
Did you do what I asked?
Do what?
I told you to be more lively.
Show me.
What are you doing?
Dancing. Disco.
Have you lost it?
I never saw your gift for the Chou role.
Get down here.
What's that attitude?
Did you buy some new clothes?
Why not?
I'm clueless.
Can't you learn from others?
Look at what Chu Jiahe wears.
Aren't they pretty?
They are.
So you do know what beauty is.
What do audiences expect from a Dan role?
They expect your beauty.
Beauty in singing.
Beauty in acting.
Beauty in the appearance.
Miss one, and you can't play the Dan role.
Your strength is you can take hardship.
Your flaw is that's all you know.
Doesn't that make you
a blockhead?
Get what I'm saying?
You really are a blockhead.
I get it.
Then hurry up and look your best!
Kids in the back, settle down.
We haven't held a
creative meeting in a long time.
Troupe Leader Huang
has some family matters
and can't make it.
So I'll be filling in for him
to host this creative meeting.
First,
I need to announce
a major decision.
The troupe
will very soon
stage the traditional opera
Bi Shang Liang Shan.
Even new plays fail.
Why stage the old opera?
That's because
your drumming is bad.
Fine, fine.
Next,
I'll introduce our four veteran artists.
Gou Cunzhong.
Zhou Cunren.
Qiu Cunyi.
These three masters
are familiar to you,
so I won't introduce them.
Go back.
Next,
I'd like to formally introduce
Master Gu Cunxiao.
- Nice.
- Impressive.
Cool.
Master Gu Cunxiao
- was the star performer.
- Hu Hansan is back.
You kids might not know him.
Due to special circumstances,
Master Gu Cunxiao left
the troupe years ago.
But today, he's back.
Together with the other three,
he will jointly
serve as Director of Bi Shang Liang Shan.
Now, with warm applause,
let's welcome our four directors.
Directors?
Why shake the coat to speak?
No idea.
Again. There it is.
There it goes. Shaking the coat.
No idea.
Janitor. Grocery buyer. Gatekeeper.
How did they become directors?
Right? The gatekeeper, a director?
Feng Xiaoxiao!
What are you muttering?
Stand up!
Say it loud.
Master Gu's shaking the coat is impressive.
Keep your admiration to yourself.
Sit down.
Okay.
The traditional opera
and the modern play share the same goals
through different means.
The traditional opera emphasizes
singing,
reciting,
acting...
What are you humming for?
It's about singing, reciting,
acting, and combat.
I believe that
under the guidance of our four directors,
they will show their signature skills
and lead all the actors of the troupe
to make the show a success!
Great!
Slice the potatoes thinner.
They look like shoe insoles.
This is a radish.
A radish?
You don't cut them the same way?
You always have an excuse.
Wash these vegetables thoroughly.
What are you looking at?
- It's a circus.
- Look at the Dan role.
Get back to work.
During the circular walk...
Whose kid?
Leave
if you aren't supposed to be here.
When she's doing the circular walk,
she must tuck in the stomach, lift the hips,
relax the shoulders, straighten the back,
stretch the neck, lift the head,
and sink breath.
Point your toes forward.
No showing from under your skirt.
Keep your torso still and glide along.
That's how you make
the circle walk elegant.
What do the audiences see?
Your beauty.
You must not wobble or sway.
Who would watch that?
Otherwise,
you won't be the
chief military instructor's
fair lady,
and you'll just be a woman
from a Production Team.
Don't laugh.
You thief!
Watch me again.
What's there to look at?
That old man's opera singing
isn't worth watching. Go start the fire.
This is how you look charming and graceful.
Keep your upper body still.
Your feet are drifting.
- Keep your torso still.
- Stop watching.
Your feet are drifting.
Love what you do.
You thief!
Slash. Thrust.
Too high!
Kid, over here. Right here.
Remember that. Next.
One, two, three.
Slash. Move.
Where are you looking?
Ready? Pull.
One.
- Two.
- Bow like you mean it.
- This way.
- Three.
Look this way.
Go.
He Dachui!
Troupe Leader.
What are you doing here?
Rehearsing.
Go to the rehearsal room then!
The rehearsal room and the canteen
are all full of actors.
You still can't play the drums here.
We were in the courtyard,
but we scared the baby.
So, we ended up here.
Not here either. Go!
ظآزHusband and wifeظآز
ظآزTears and bloodظآز
ظآزHard to part waysظآز
Go!
My lady!
- My lord!
- Hurry up!
My lady!
Stop, stop, stop.
How many times must I tell you?
You keep slouching your back.
You're playing Lady Lin.
Don't sway like a snake,
drifting in the wind without poise.
Stay steady. You are Lady Lin.
You want this role?
Go ahead.
I've said it before. As a Dan role,
relax the shoulders
and straighten the back
for proper posture.
Also,
lift the wrist and flip the sleeve.
Lift the wrist and flip the sleeve. Got it?
That's how you show your charm.
Lift the wrist and flip the sleeve.
Now try.
I can't. Something's in my eye.
Director Gu, what should we do?
Mi Lan.
Listen to him.
Qing'e.
Stir constantly in the wok.
Or it won't cook evenly.
I used to stir-fry with a small ladle.
The food would fly up and down, you know?
Without spilling a single drop.
This is manual labor.
Song,
come here.
You take over this low-skill work.
I'm the head chef, you know?
What head chef does this all day?
Qing'e.
Come here.
Come rub my shoulders.
Thump my back. I'm so sore.
Apprentices used to massage their master.
It was perfectly normal.
Traditional rules.
Come here.
Come here!
Laidi, the fire is dying.
- Got it.
- Hurry and add some coal.
I was cooking just fine earlier.
Why did it die when you took over?
Just admit you lack the skill.
Big talkers get struck by lightning.
Speak normally to me.
I don't understand your idioms.
Gou.
Gou!
Alright, alright.
Our Security Section
is truly full of hidden talents.
All these years,
your talent has been buried.
What is it?
Your Section Chief said you work hard,
so I came to check on you.
Don't be so formal.
Master Gou, we're all
in the Security Section.
We're family, aren't we?
Exactly.
Master Gou, can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Can I play Lin Chong's wife?
That's not up to me.
Master Gou,
I've been an extra my whole life.
I've never played the lead,
or even a decent role.
If I don't do it now,
I might never get the chance.
I've learned everything you taught me.
Just watch me.
You thief!
How was that?
Not bad?
Gou.
Master Gou?
Okay?
You think?
Why not?
If we need Lin Chong's mother next time,
I'll definitely let her play the role.
What is this? What are you even doing?
Like this.
Not like this.
Go.
Small.
Walk.
Big.
Small.
Walk.
Big.
Small.
Walk properly.
(Recreate a new soul)
Won't work?
Always talking about "dear wife"...
Stop, stop.
Stop chatting.
Shoulders rounded.
Your eyes. The mood.
Okay, get ready.
(Pastries)
(Musical Feature Film:
Reverberations of Life)
Kiss you?
- Shanshan.
- Kiss whoever you want.
- I'll kiss you.
- You're taking a huge risk.
Your dad and I went to Huang Village.
With your uncle...
We went to Tian'anmen together.
Stop pushing me.
(Ningzhou Cinema)
Give me a chance.
What's wrong? Is the movie no good?
Er Laizi, she's glaring at you.
Stare at me again and
I'll gouge your eyes out.
Scared?
I'm not a monster.
Er Laizi, get her!
(Today's film: Reverberations of Life
Ticket price: 1 jiao)
It's all about singing now,
right?
This singing part has nothing to do
with my drumming.
ظآزThe north wind blows hardظآز
ظآزSharp as a knifeظآز
Stop!
What now? Was I wrong again?
Not you.
It's the orchestra.
What's wrong?
Your drumming is way too loose,
putting everyone to sleep.
Nonsense.
I was playing
with the feeling.
It had to be slow.
Slow doesn't mean loose.
Keep it slow, but with tension.
Keep the pace measured.
Keep the spirit flowing through.
What were you playing?
It's slow, but there's no tension.
Like baggy old granny pants. It doesn't
grab anyone.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Fine.
Come on. You play it.
Play those baggy pants with feeling.
I'm not the drummer.
Then keep your mouth shut.
Cut the nonsense.
Who's talking nonsense?
You.
Keep playing like that,
and you'll wreck the whole show!
Nonsense!
I've had enough of you!
That lousy coat of yours!
Flapping all over!
A dumb dog acting like a guard dog!
You're making me dizzy!
The rehearsal's a mess, who's to blame?
You blame this, blame that!
I want to knock out every tooth you have!
Do it! Knock them all out!
Acting so tough?
Screw you!
Director Gu. Find the teeth.
- No.
- His teeth fell out.
Here, here, pick them up.
The teeth are here.
Pick them up.
Come on, check.
Is it okay now?
It's fine.
Try taking a bite.
Seriously?
I couldn't bite even with good teeth.
My dear Pei,
is anything else on you fake?
It's all original, except the teeth.
You were actually right.
A real mess.
Told you.
Deal with it yourself.
Master Gu.
How are your teeth?
He Dachui was sent to the hospital.
His leg is swollen like a balloon.
Save it!
This isn't over!
Master Zhou, please calm down.
Come on, cool off. Sit down.
Sit. Sit down.
Sit.
You didn't see him.
That guy's a total mess now.
Master Zhou, you went too hard.
No idea what's with his bones.
If they hadn't stopped me,
I'd have put him on two crutches!
Then who would play the drums?
I'm not defending He Dachui.
But if he doesn't drum,
who in the troupe will?
Wouldn't that be perfect?
Just disband.
Listen to yourself, Master Zhou.
Does that sound like you?
Look how far we've rehearsed.
Cast and orchestra are in sync.
We can't just call it quits.
Let me tell you guys,
rumors are flying in the troupe.
People are saying the four of you
are only good at putting on airs,
and can't even direct a play.
What?
If we fall apart now,
what will the troupe think of you?
Is Master Gu okay?
What could be wrong?
He's old. His dentures are just loose.
Go back. Don't worry about it.
He sold steamed Mo his whole life.
He's seen it all.
Your uncle is so unreliable.
He's never around when it matters.
This is driving me crazy.
Come on, shuffle the cards.
Hurry it up.
- Sir?
- You almost set the house on fire.
You're here.
Join us?
Come on, join us.
Not now.
I need a word with Dachui.
- Leave for now.
- Let's go.
But we were about to...
- Go.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Shut the door.
Okay.
Come back later.
Later? How's your leg?
Still don't know yet.
The X-ray won't be ready for three days.
Where exactly?
This spot keeps spasming.
Right here, yeah?
It keeps aching.
Let me see.
Looks fine
to me. You can walk.
Why did you act like that?
Those four old guys
couldn't rehearse their show.
They blamed my drumming for it.
Wouldn't you be mad too?
You knew they were old guys.
Why get physical with an old man?
What if you really hurt him?
=The Lead=
(Preview)
Stop it! So annoying!
That kid was born for the stage,
and her fundamentals are rock solid.
Our trainees are nowhere near her level.
Can we pause rehearsals for
Bi Shang Liang Shan
and switch to Yang Pai Feng first?
Do you realize
what it would mean
if this show failed?
A county-level troupe's standards
end up worse than a disciple
casually trained by a few old guys?
ظآزWhen I woke up and turned backظآز
ظآزI wasn't sure where to goظآز
ظآزWe met and brushed pastظآز
ظآزYour shadow drifted out of sightظآز
ظآزThe stove fire blazed in my dreamظآز
ظآزLit up the tracks of pearly tearsظآز
ظآزIn my dream, water sleeves flewظآز
ظآزHiding a lifetime of loveظآز
ظآزThe Qinling Mountains
crossed the stageظآز
ظآزSpring water brewed strong wineظآز
ظآزSheep moved through the valleyظآز
ظآزIt felt like a promise
from another lifeظآز
ظآزWhen I woke up and turned backظآز
ظآزI wasn't sure where to goظآز
ظآزIf I chose again, I'd still roamظآز
ظآزAll over this sunlit plateauظآز
ظآزThe dream ends; the curtain fallsظآز
ظآزMoonlight washes off this stage makeupظآز
ظآزThe one in the mirror wears gray hairظآز
ظآزAlready sang all my joy and sorrowظآز
ظآزAlready shouted across Qinchuan Plainظآز