( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 13=
♪Burying sorrow deep within my chest♪
♪Tonight the moon is veiled in mist♪
♪The land lies still and silent♪
♪Cold and desolate♪
Aunt Hua, I want to go home.
No, you can't.
Your exams are in a couple of days.
I'm not taking them.
You have to.
Don't overthink it.
Just go in and do your best.
I don't want commodity grain anymore.
I want to go home.
I can't stay in the troupe anymore.
You have to stay.
For your uncle's sake, you can't go.
He's not coming back.
Shut your mouth.
Say that again, and I'll rip it open.
Your uncle is like a cat.
He's got nine lives.
Aunt Hua, I'm scared.
We've got nothing to fear.
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
♪Grandma tells♪
♪Of the brave old days♪
♪When sacrifices were made♪
♪As it turned out♪
♪I was♪
Why aren't you practicing?
They say this exam cuts the bottom two.
Don't take it lightly.
Leave me alone.
What's wrong?
♪Through the forest,
across the snowy plains♪
♪Our spirit soars to the sky♪
♪The guard's call♪
♪Like a wolf's howl♪
♪I step forward♪
♪Out through the gate♪
Stop, stop.
What are you doing?
Who taught you to sing like that?
Who taught you?
I've given it my all.
You wouldn't do any better.
Move along.
You wanted him.
Didn't you insist on it?
You said he was the greenest grass.
Well?
Green enough for you?
Director,
this kid is suited for the Chou role.
That's mainly spoken parts
and physical skills.
Yi Qing'e, the teacher is calling you.
Why aren't you going?
What's wrong?
- Yi Qing'e!
- Hurry up.
- He's calling you.
What are you doing? You're up! Hurry!
Yi Qing'e, what will you sing?
What are you going to sing?
Don't just stand there.
Have her sing
Grandma's Revolution Story.
Sing Grandma's Revolution Story for us.
I don't know it.
Then sing The North Wind Blows.
The kid's just nervous.
She's just nervous.
Not at her best today.
Don't be nervous, okay?
Just sing whatever you know.
Sing loud. Sing with confidence.
It's okay if you mess up.
I don't know any songs.
Let me say a few words.
We all know what she's been through.
Even adults would struggle with it.
Let alone a child.
I have a suggestion.
Let Yi Qing'e take it later.
I agree.
I agree too.
Same here.
That could work.
This is outrageous.
What's so outrageous?
The exam hall is a battlefield.
Everyone's already in battle.
The charge has already sounded.
And you want to charge days later?
Does that make any sense?
Why wouldn't it?
Good soldiers lead the charge.
The wounded stay in the rear.
If the wounded were to charge,
the commander must be an idiot.
Look at you.
Hua Caixiang, don't go too far.
Who exactly is going too far?
Forget about what Hu Sanyuan
did for the troupe all these years.
Just take this time.
If he won't do the stage design,
what can you do to him?
Who can condemn him?
Director, please sit. Sit down.
She's pregnant. Don't get mad at her.
Here, cool down.
To help the troupe stage a good show,
he never complained about the work.
He did his job
and stepped up
for what he shouldn't have.
What happened?
He nearly lost his life,
yet someone used it to get revenge,
saying it was
deliberate sabotage
and a long-term plot
for revenge.
Can it get any more outrageous?
What is this?
It's a frame-up! It's persecution!
Calm down. She's pregnant.
Don't get worked up.
Alright, alright.
Hu Sanyuan is in prison.
Now, you won't even spare his kid.
Even plays aren't so vicious.
- What's wrong?
- Alright.
♪Grandma tells of the brave old days
when sacrifices were made♪
♪As it turned out, I was born
in the wind and raised in the rain♪
♪Oh, Grandma♪
♪17 years of care, deep as the ocean♪
Let her learn drums with me instead.
Well done.
Keep it down.
I took all the Mo.
Where are you going?
(Ningzhou County Qinqiang Opera Troupe)
Who's there?
Stop right there.
Kid, where's your exit pass?
Don't run. You might fall.
(Picket)
Why is this truck carrying a prisoner?
Don't you know?
A prisoner means being shot.
So, he's to be executed?
Oh, my. He's a killer.
My grandma is paralyzed.
What about your parents?
My dad went to work in the mountains.
He was crushed by falling rocks.
And your mom?
She lost her mind.
She disappeared six months ago.
Grandpa.
Here, eat.
Eat. Here.
Have some solid food. It lasts.
White Mo.
Grandpa, white Mo.
Where did this Mo come from?
That girl gave it to me.
You eat it. Go on, eat.
You eat.
Quick, bring me a basin.
Hurry, hurry. Get a basin.
Quick, quick.
Good. Put it here.
♪Wang Chao♪
♪Sends word♪
What's he shouting?
It's just what he likes to sing.
My grandpa hollers when he's bored.
He says shouting out what's bottled up
makes you feel better.
♪Ma Han reports♪
♪Saying♪
♪The Princess♪
♪Has come here♪
♪Here I am♪
♪Stepping forward♪
♪Quickly kneeling♪
(What happened the night before)
(made Yi Qing'e vaguely understand)
(why people in the mountains love opera)
(and love to sing opera,)
(because it lets people)
(cry out what weighs on their hearts.)
Sis.
How did you...
Dad, Mom, Laidi's back!
What?
Why are you back?
Did you walk all the way back?
Laidi.
- Laidi.
- Laidi's back!
Where did you go?
You scared us to death.
You really scared us.
You've got too much nerve.
Where on earth did you run off to?
Do you know how worried we were?
Laidi.
I ought to give you a good smack.
Her uncle is such a deadbeat.
He never took life seriously.
As a kid, he poked a hornet's nest.
He got stung up,
and dozens in the village got stung too.
Back then, he disliked the Director,
so he peed in his pickle jar.
They caught him and beat him badly.
We paid him all our pickled vegetables,
so we had none to eat all winter.
- Recently,
- Thanks.
he sent word he'd come to perform opera.
He told us all to go.
We were so excited
that we nearly called the whole village.
And what did we see?
We were too ashamed to show our faces.
People always say
that the older you get,
the steadier you become.
Why does he only cause bigger trouble?
Now, it's turned into a serious case.
Enough, enough.
Stop going on about that.
Here's the thing, Laidi.
Because of your uncle,
your exam scores,
and your running from the troupe,
they are going to expel you.
Aunt Mi Lan, Director Glasses,
Uncle Dachui,
and everyone else spoke up for you.
Huang Zhengjing had no choice.
Now, you're moving to the kitchen.
Aunt Mi Lan and I have talked
with your parents.
We think the kitchen is fine.
Right.
You won't mix with those kids.
Back then,
your uncle got you in
just for commodity grain, right?
Right.
As long as the quota stays with you,
you'll always have a meal.
Yes. Exactly.
What are you looking at?
The teacher is right. Opera feeds you.
Stoking the fire puts you by the pot.
I won't learn opera.
I'll stay home, help you work,
help Mom cook, and watch my brother.
You...
Look at you.
If you stay home,
can your mom give you money
or grain coupons?
I have money.
I saved this myself.
Two yuan went missing.
She has so much money.
I didn't spend a cent.
Eat up, then go with your teachers.
Do you hear me?
I'm asking you.
I don't want to go back.
I can't take it.
What's so hard to take?
Do you know who these teachers are?
Even our Commune Secretary
can't meet them.
For you, they crossed mountains
and came all the way to Jiuyangou.
Don't be so ungrateful.
Eat up and leave.
Stoking fires beats staying home.
If you can't perform opera,
you can become a chef.
That'd be something to be proud of.
Exactly.
Why are you crying?
Sir, here's the thing.
She's been gone two days; she's tired.
She's been away from home for so long.
How about letting her stay
for a few days?
Is that okay?
I'm afraid Huang Zhengjing
may change his mind.
Ms. Hua, this isn't up for debate.
Take her tomorrow.
The scenery here is beautiful.
After so long in the troupe yard,
I forgot how wide the world is.
A child born here takes the sky
as their roof and the earth
as their bed.
They're used to being free.
Being locked in the troupe
is like a sheep
getting penned up.
It's really hard to adapt.
But people aren't sheep.
You know?
Sis, where are our sheep?
The state forbids keeping them,
saying we have to cut off
the tail of capitalism.
They were taken away.
- Taken where?
- Thanks.
The commune.
Can we still get them back?
No way, they're mutton with Mo now.
That's a sheep's fate.
Here.
Why do you get to wipe first?
Take it or leave it.
Your uncle said
he'd take you to the troupe.
Right.
But I never made it there.
Can you sing?
Yes.
Sing something for me.
♪Sing a folk song to the Party♪
♪I compare the Party to my mother♪
Aunt Hua,
my sister sings really well.
Please talk to my dad again.
Take my sister to the troupe.
Can you?
No.
It can't be changed now.
Your sister sings on pitch.
Your voice is fuller, more grounded.
Mom's calling you.
Actually, Laidi
isn't tone-deaf by nature.
She lacks confidence and technique.
She can still change.
Plus, she doesn't even sing properly.
I'll leave her to you from now on.
Why do you never give me the good ones?
Over the years,
I've let you down in many ways.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I wrote the letter
to Huang Zhengjing's wife.
I figured.
I've been wondering:
Do you really love opera that much?
Always fighting with me.
Writing that letter
and fighting with you
are two different things.
Besides, am I fighting for opera?
You fought me over a man?
What we fight over doesn't matter.
What matters is
that it's you I'm fighting.
Are you out of your mind?
What did I ever do to you?
Why can't you stand seeing me happy?
I want you to be happy.
Just not happier than me.
Then I must be happier than you.
I'm going to be a mom.
As long as you're happy.
Yi Qing'e is back.
That smell.
How did Yi Qing'e come back?
Yeah.
Where did Ms. Hua find her?
Exactly.
Where did she come from?
Come with me.
Right. Where did she go?
Exactly.
Master Qiu.
Master Song.
The kid is here.
Here she is.
No need to introduce her, right?
Transferred from the trainee class.
Here to help us.
From now on, she's one of us.
We're short on hands.
I asked for help, and this is it?
Isn't the kid a person?
What can she do?
Like a green walnut.
I can't peel it or eat it.
Who are you trying to fool?
She can't handle heavy work.
But she can lend a hand.
She can peel onions and garlic
and tend the fire.
Right.
Welcome to the cooking squad, kid.
Good. Welcome, welcome.
Kid,
Master Song is your teacher now.
Master Liao is new,
but he's your master too.
From now on, speak sweetly, stay sharp.
Be quick with your hands,
busy on your feet.
Got that?
Good.
Come, kiddo. Opera has costume gear.
Physical skills practice has gear too.
So, we also have gear.
We knew you were coming.
So, we prepared a set for you.
Your hand.
Good.
Look.
Let's see how it fits.
Come on, let Aunt Hua have a look.
You look great.
Laidi,
after sweeping,
remember to feed the pigs.
Sleep early when you're done.
I'm heading out.
Don't forget to turn off the lights.
Five-five seven.
Five-eight, five-nine, sixty-one.
Six-five six, six-five seven.
Six-eight, six-nine, seventy-one.
Seven-five six, seven-five seven.
Seven-eight, seven-nine, eighty-one.
Eight-five six, eight-five seven.
Eight-eight, eight-nine, ninety-one.
Nine-five...
(Keep things clean)
I'm heading out.
Feng Xiaoxiao.
Wait for me.
I waited for you last time.
I'll help you.
No need.
It's fine.
You're even feeding pigs now?
Yi Qing'e,
when will that pig be fat enough?
I'll butcher you. Move.
Does your pig eat crap?
Come on, why are you so gross?
I'm warning you.
Warning? Who are you warning?
Ow, ow, ow!
Go easy!
Let go!
Let go, let go!
Shut up.
Let go! It hurts!
My hand! My fingers!
My fingers, my fingers!
It hurts! It hurts!
Bang, bang!
Come on, guess.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Missed.
You again?
I'll go first.
Lights out again. What rotten luck.
Such a jinx.
What's that smell? It reeks.
What else? Slop, of course.
It stinks.
Like a pigsty.
Yi Qing'e,
you're with the kitchen now.
So, you're not under me.
But this dorm is my turf.
Take your clothes out
and wash off that pigsty smell
before you come back in.
Move it.
Hurry up and go.
Why are you spacing out? Go.
Hurry up, go.
Go on.
Hurry up and go.
Go wash up.
Get out.
Close the door behind you.
Laidi.
Bring over the washed vegetables.
Laidi, Laidi.
Quick, get a basin of water.
The corn gruel is too thick.
Laidi.
Come here. Come on.
- Come on.
- Come, come.
Okay, okay.
Go add some water for me.
Laidi.
Add two shovels of coal for us.
The fire's weak. Stoke it up.
Hurry up!
Okay, my kid.
You can't keep adding coal.
You can't...
It's only making smoke now.
Hurry!
Stop dawdling! Hurry!
Attention!
Right face!
Double time, march!
One, two, one! One, two, one!
Keep your distance!
Plead guilty and accept reform.
Follow the rules for an early release.
Eat up! Eat up!
Hoeing fields under the midday sun.
Every grain comes from hard work.
(Turn over a new leaf)
What is this?
The stitches are crooked.
Are you sewing pig intestines?
Can you keep the stitch straight?
Take it apart.
Sew it again.
Hu Sanyuan.
Here.
Come with me.
The correctional officer said
you're like you've gone mute now.
You don't talk all day.
The blast must've left you dazed.
A blast that big
takes time to recover from.
I don't talk much now either.
I just want to be alone
and sit quietly.
Before coming, I visited Nail.
I burned paper offerings for him
and told him I was coming to see you.
I also told him
you survived.
This is heaven's punishment for you.
It wants you to pay for life.
Heaven wants me to pay for life too.
I've sung opera half my life.
Onstage,
we worked together like magic.
Offstage,
we both lost our tune.
I'm leaving
for another place
and singing another story.
Let's both take care from here.
For the scenes still to come,
sing them well.
And Laidi...
Laidi
got dragged into this.
She left the trainee class
for the kitchen.
But I think that's for the best.
There's still a chance.
If she stays with the troupe,
she'll get another shot.
She's in the kitchen.
Then we can both relax.
Qiu Cunyi and Master Song
won't leave her with no one.
Tell her to keep practicing.
She promised me.
Then you promise me too.
Don't give up.
For all the shows ahead,
sing them well.
What do you need?
Always stewed cabbage
with tofu and vermicelli.
How can it taste good?
We make a tub; half goes to the pigs.
Without meat and oil,
how could it be good?
You don't know costs
till you run things.
Easy for you to say.
Your skills are off.
Don't blame anything else.
Listen, I've put up
with you for a long time.
You even turned shredded potatoes
into potato sticks.
Big pot dishes
don't need cuts that thin.
They'd just turn to mush.
I see. It's not your knife skills.
It's you who's off.
It's nice out there. Go wait outside.
If you're not helping, why talk so much?
I'm helping you?
At your level,
even I couldn't help.
Idiot.
You need to pull apart
the spinach roots.
Wash off all the dirt.
Clean the carrot roots too.
Is the water cold?
No, it's not.
Laidi.
Are you tired?
No.
What's your full name?
Yi Qing'e.
Which Yi is that?
The Yi from "easy".
Rare surname. Hard to remember.
Then I'll call you Qing'e.
Always honking away.
The best are opera singers;
next are pimps and pushers.
Lower still are cuckolds,
and lowest are tortoises.
Those were the old lower nine trades.
You know that?
Chefs outranked opera performers.
Listen to you.
We still make our living off them.
Oh, come on.
You always have to butt in.
Qing'e, do you know what I used to do?
Master Liao is from Chang'an Restaurant.
Top-class place in Qinchuan.
Only big shots get to eat there.
I cook for people with status.
They always pick on me.
They learned in the army cooking squad.
They only know big pot dishes.
Qing'e, I'll teach you stir-fry.
Do you know what it means?
One wok, one plate. That's it.
Every farm home does that.
Give it a rest.
Can they make sautéed pork slices,
Guo Bao Rou,
or chicken stew with mushrooms?
They've never even heard of them.
Do you know why that stew
uses young chicken?
Because young chicken is tender.
Laidi.
Go down there.
Bring me a basket of potatoes.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
Many other troupes
have started restaging the old plays.
These kids can't be trained like this.
This fancy posturing is
not even good enough to be walk-ons.
Acting is about endurance.
Endure the pain in your body
and the bitterness in your heart.
As long as you're willing to suffer
and do as I say,
I promise you'll make a name
for yourself in opera.
I have a favor to ask you.
Practice hard during the day;
at night, you come back and teach me.
Laidi, one more flip for you.
Heiwa!
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪