MALANG, EAST JAVA
WELCOME, PROSPECTIVE GRADUATES
Time's up.
The finals are over.
Hey!
- Surrender!
- Raka!
Say it!
Damn it!
You bit me.
- You had it coming.
- Damn.
So how did the test go?
Piece of cake.
We're still hiking, right?
Of course we are.
I really want to go to Welirang.
I don't feel like going back to Jakarta.
Your dad misses you, you know.
Just because he remarried
doesn't mean he abandoned you.
I don't know.
I just feel like
it's too soon.
I haven't gotten over it.
My mother died recently,
and he's already remarried.
Yes, but you still have parents.
You have a family.
Meanwhile, me?
I don't have anyone.
You still have a family too.
I'm still here, right?
If you consider me family,
does that mean
my girlfriend is family too?
I don't feel good about this.
What's happening?
- Just come with me.
- Huh?
Come with me.
Are you sure, Nita?
This is Welirang. The terrain is tough.
I'm sure, Aryo.
But you've never climbed a mountain, Nita.
I personally think that
you'd better use this holiday
to take a Javanese language course.
You've been in Malang for a long time,
but you can't speak Javanese, right?
You'd better do that.
Oh, come on, that's no fun.
I'll manage.
Babe, help me convince Aryo.
Aryo, we can take an easier route.
They won't mind.
Besides, you and I are mountain climbers.
It'll be safe.
Then what will I be doing?
Third-wheeling?
Don't you worry.
Raka and I won't let you become
a fly on the wall.
I'm asking Yuni to come.
Yuni?
Yuni.
Hi, Yun!
Hey, Nita.
Raka.
Aryo.
Hi.
Yun.
Raka, Aryo, and I are going hiking.
You're coming along, right?
Sure.
Thank you for inviting me.
Are you sure it's okay if I come?
Of course it's okay.
But…
Have you ever climbed a mountain before?
Not yet, but I want to try.
- It looks like fun.
- Yeah, it's definitely going to be fun.
Yes, definitely, now that there's Yuni.
Should we prepare?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Get ready.
- Yes.
- All right.
As for the details,
Raka knows better.
Relax, man.
So we will ride the Jeep first,
from the city to the registration point…
WELCOME TO TAMAN HUTAN RAYA
Okay.
Thank you, sir! Let's go.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Fill in the form.
Your name, ID, and an emergency number
that can be contacted.
When you're hiking, don't rush.
Most people disappear or fall
because they want
to reach the summit quickly.
Listen to him.
And one more important thing.
Don't go off the hiking trail.
Don't be arrogant.
Respect the mountain guardians.
Mountain guardians?
What does he mean?
Whether you believe it or not,
just do as he says.
Be respectful.
A mountain is no ordinary place.
There are guardians.
You mean like the unseen?
Just be respectful.
Don't underestimate nature.
- - Babe.
- Yeah?
Why are you already out of breath?
I'm not even tired yet.
Are you making fun of me?
Look, I can be faster than you.
Nita.
Hey.
Don't rush, Nita!
Yuni.
Does your mother know you're here?
No.
Why do you ask?
Just curious.
What is your relationship like
with your mother?
That's an interesting question.
I just want to get to know you
a lot better.
Get to know me?
Then what happens if you know more?
Do you want to date me?
What do you think?
I think you shouldn't.
I already told you.
My mother is weird.
She's a psychic.
And
she passed it down to me.
Do you still want to date me?
So you can see ghosts?
No, I don't want to.
Whether you can see them or not,
I don't care.
What matters is that I can see you.
Come on, how can you lose to me?
Nita.
You can't go up the mountain quickly.
Our lungs and heart
need to work effectively.
Don't tire them.
I think
climbing a mountain is like
having the opportunity
to get to know yourself.
Because we focus on the journey,
the experience,
we understand ourselves better.
Yeah.
I feel like I learned
something about myself.
Like what?
It turns out I'm better
at climbing mountains than you guys.
Be careful, Nita.
Huh?
What is this?
Careful, Nita, don't kick it.
Almost every mountain has one.
For those who occupy the space.
It's like an offering.
So that climbers won't be disturbed.
Oh, please.
That stuff's not real.
It only exists in stories.
Those who come, forget the way home.
What?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
It's like someone was speaking Javanese.
I didn't hear anything.
Yun, did you say something just now?
- Aryo?
- What?
No.
Oh, whatever.
Let's keep moving.
Okay.
Cheater.
- I'm going first.
- Nita!
Come on.
Nita, wait.
Don't leave the others behind.
Come on, hurry up.
Nita, wait a minute, okay?
Yuni, are you good?
Wait.
Shouldn't we be going to the left?
Nita is on the wrong path.
Nita!
- Nit?
- Nita!
Nit?
Nita!
Nita.
You took the wrong path.
I've been calling you for a while.
I don't want to see you running away
from the group again.
Babe, just relax.
I'm not going the wrong way,
you can see for yourself.
This is a really nice view.
Well…
Nit.
Nit, come on, something bad might happen.
Yuni, relax. Can't you see I'm doing fine?
Why are you all just staring blankly?
Come here!
- Nita!
Nita!
- Nita.
- Nit, Nita!
- No, Aryo, stop!
- Aryo!
- Nita, hold on.
- Nita.
- Help.
- Hold on, okay?
We'll help you, okay?
- Help me.
- Nita, calm down.
- Hurry.
- Nita.
Take the rope, Nit.
Come on, Nita.
Grab the rope, hurry up.
- Grab it.
- Grab it, Nit!
Hurry up, Nit.
Come on, Nita, grab it. Hurry up.
Grab the rope quickly, Nit!
- Nita!
- Nit!
Those who come, forget the way home.
Nita!
Nit!
If we can't see her,
something bad has happened.
I know.
Nita?
Aryo, Raka! Nita is over there.
Nita!
- Nit?
- Nita.
Nita?
Aryo, help her up.
Come on.
Nita? Come.
Nita.
Nita?
Nita, hey.
She's still in shock.
It could be hypothermia.
Aryo.
We'd better find a place around here
to set up a tent, okay?
Nit.
Here.
She doesn't want anything.
She's just been quiet.
Raka, put this on her.
To keep her warm.
Put these on, okay?
One, two, three.
Those who come, forget the way home.
Forget the way home.
Tell them, forget the way home!
All of you
came all the way here.
Do you think you can go home?
Don't be rude!
Nita?
- Nita!
- Nita, Nita?
- Nita?
- Nit?
- Nit…
- Nita?
Nita?
We should descend.
We've been going around in circles.
We're already near the post
with the stall. Let's go.
What do you mean?
We've been going around in circles
all this time.
Trust me, Yun,
we are not going around in circles.
Yes, just keep walking.
What if we keep walking and end up here?
You feel it too, right, Raka?
But we're on the right path, Yuni.
Right, Raka?
Yeah, we're descending.
Let's just turn here.
Come on, hurry up.
We don't have much time.
Hurry up.
Come on, Yuni.
That seems expensive.
This is already cheap.
I hear people.
Locals.
They must know the way down.
What is it?
Do you hear something?
The voices are fading.
Come on, hurry up.
Sir?
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
Sir?
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
It sounds like it's coming from there.
Let's go there.
Let's ask them for directions.
Come on, hurry up.
I've never seen a market
in the middle of a mountain.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I ask you something?
Do you know the way
to descend the mountain?
Sir?
Let's take a break.
Right here.
Help me.
Okay.
Nit. Nita?
Nit?
I'll get you some tea.
Can I order a cup of tea, sir?
Raka?
I'm going to the restrooms.
I need to go too.
RESTROOMS
Nita?
Are you okay?
Is there another way to the restrooms?
Why didn't we see her?
Nit? Yun?
Yuni! Nita!
This place is not right.
This place is not right, I saw…
Nit?
Nita?
Nita!
Nit?
What?
Come on.
Where's Nita?
Yun!
Why is the market empty?
Where did everybody go?
Why is Nita here?
Nit?
Nit.
You were just in the restrooms.
Why are you here already?
Raka!
Hey, wake up.
Let's get out of here.
Come on!
Excuse me, sir.
Where did everybody go?
Go home!
- Nita.
- Nita!
- Come on, come on.
- Help me out.
- Come on.
- Hurry, hurry.
Come on!
Those who come, forget the way home.
The market is gone.
This place is suspicious.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Those who come, forget the way home.
Aryo!
Come on!
Aryo.
There's no way out of this, Aryo.
There is no end. This is the wrong place.
But we came in through here, right?
No, we should turn.
Listen to me, Aryo.
So what now? Should we go back or what?
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's turn around.
Let's turn around.
Hey, youngsters.
You have dared to enter this forest.
Who else?
Who else will be my prey?
Who else will die by my hand?
Let's get out of here.
- Come on. Hurry.
- We should go.
Aryo.
Let's take a break.
Let's stop for now, okay?
- Help me out.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Careful.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I said,
what are you doing here?
We're sorry, sir.
We're lost.
We've been going around in circles,
but we can't get out of this field.
We can't descend.
What did you see?
A market?
Did you see a wayang performance?
This is not your place.
I'll guide you out.
Please.
You have to go up the mountain.
There's another way down from the summit.
Thank you, sir.
We should get out of here.
One, two, three.
Those who come, forget the way home.
Forget the way home.
You came all the way here.
Do you think you can go home?
Nit? Nita!
Nita?
Nit…
Sir.
Control yourself.
Drive out what hides inside you.
Nita.
Nit. Nita?
Nit.
She has calmed down.
But the mountain's hold on her
is still strong.
The mountain's hold?
You are now caught between
the realm of humans and the supernatural.
This place
is called the Village of the Dead.
Your friend has been marked by
the ruler of the mountain
to be used as a potential sacrifice.
We must remove the influence
from her body.
Otherwise, it will have full control.
How do we remove its influence?
You have to come to my house.
Later, you will witness the exorcism.
Sir.
Can't it just be done here?
My house is the safest place.
Come on.
We don't have much time.
My name is Surop.
You don't need to be afraid.
I really want to help.
He just helped Nita.
We have no other choice.
We have to go inside
before the village torches are lit.
Turn off the flashlight.
Come, quickly.
Raka.
Put Nita here.
- Help him.
- Help me, Aryo.
- Help me.
- Careful.
The incense must always burn.
It should stay lit.
That's what protects this house.
So that this place remains safe
for its residents.
So that whoever is here…
won't be detected.
This is my daughter, Amari.
She is sick.
Water.
You can't have water, my dear.
Help.
I'm thirsty.
Water.
Change Nita's into these clothes.
When the ritual is over,
put her normal clothes back on.
We will start the ritual soon.
From the first flower
to the third flower.
From light to dark.
Help me, Almighty.
Remove the power of the forest spirits.
Leave, power of the mountain.
Leave this girl's body.
You will be my servant.
Let go of this girl.
This is none of your business, old man!
This body is already mine.
I have tried
to heal Nita from
the influence of the mountain.
I hope it's fully gone.
You can leave after Nita wakes up.
But it must be after sunrise,
because at night,
the villagers wander around.
You cannot be seen.
Don't open the window.
Don't open the door.
Don't go out until the sun rises.
That is an order.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Sir.
It's Nita. She's not healed.
Yun, where is Nita?
Sir?
Sir!
Move.
Sir?
Nita is not healed yet.
She is still under the influence.
I'll go after Nita.
We're going with you.
No.
Wait here. Stay indoors.
But I want to help you find Nita, sir.
This is an order.
- Raka.
- Aryo, what about Nita?
Sir…
Nita.
Let's go home.
Nita and Mbah Surop haven't returned.
We can't just stay still like this.
But where should we go, Raka?
Do you want to just stay here?
What if something happened to them?
Are we supposed to wait?
I'm thirsty.
Water.
I am thirsty.
He won't give me water.
Dad is evil.
He is evil!
Evil!
- I just want water.
- Raka!
I am thirsty.
Dad is evil.
I just want a drink.
I want to drink.
Raka!
She needs to calm down.
Raka, Mbah Surop said not to.
It's just water. Why can't she drink?
Those who come,
forget the way home.
Let's go after her.
No, no, no.
We are not allowed to leave
Mbah Surop's house.
Let's go. Amari can't have gone far.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Raka, wait.
Amari?
- Amari?
- Amari!
Amari!
- Amari?
This is a graveyard.
Amari?
- Amari!
Amari!
Amari?
Where did she go?
Turn off the lights.
Aryo, look.
Tonight, on these grounds,
the offering ritual
for the mountain's ruler
shall begin.
Bow to the ruler of the mountain
and the giver of life.
Edwin?
Edwin, no!
Edwin!
Yuni, come on.
We need to leave.
Hurry up, Yun!
Come on!
Faster, Aryo!
Over there. Get in!
- Let's go!
- Yuni!
Go, go!
- Hurry, Yuni.
- Hurry!
Come on!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Come on, Raka!
Aryo, close the entrance.
Here.
One, two, three.
Hurry, Raka.
Come on, here.
Come on, one, two, three.
It's a dead end.
This cave is a dead end.
We're trapped here.
Until when?
And who are those people?
What are they?
Aryo.
Raka.
These are the ones chasing us.
Residents of the Village of the Dead
who come out after the torches are lit.
And they leave after sunrise.
We're going to get caught.
And we'll become sacrifices?
So,
are we supposed to wait here
until sunrise?
It feels like there's no air here.
No oxygen.
We could die here. We have to go.
We have to go back to Mbah Surop's.
Our equipment is there.
And we can be safe.
It's the safest place there now.
Mom…
I wish you were here.
Maybe you could have helped us, Mom.
We have to get out of here.
We have to see our families again.
You still want to see your dad, right?
Yuni!
Pull her!
Quick, run!
Hurry, Raka!
- Let's go, Yun.
- Be careful!
Hurry, hurry!
Open it!
- Open it!
- Come on!
One, two, three!
Hurry up, Aryo!
Hurry up! Hurry, hurry!
It's safe out here!
- Yuni, come on!
- Go.
Raka!
- Come on, Ka.
- Come on, Raka.
- Come on, Raka!
- I'm stuck, Yo!
- Come on, Ka!
- I'm stuck.
I'll pull you out.
Pull me out! Pull!
Pull!
Come on, Yun!
Let's go!
Raka?
Raka!
They got him.
- Raka!
- Yuni, no.
The incense is out.
They might enter.
We have to find the incense.
It must be in Mbah Surop's room.
Yuni, I think they're here.
Yuni.
Yun! Yun.
Here, here.
When I open the door,
you run, okay?
Yun!
Yuni.
Aryo, where are we?
Aryo. Yuni.
Over here.
- Raka?
- Here.
Raka.
Raka?
Raka…
Thank God you're alive.
Mbah Surop?
This is what the residents
of the Village of the Dead look like.
I am one of them.
Those who have been residents
for ten years…
Their face
and their skin will change.
I've been here for ten years.
Among the people who are chosen
to be potential sacrifices,
if you are strong, you can refuse,
but if you're weak,
you will immediately become a sacrifice.
I almost forgot my human side.
Until a year ago.
Amari?
My daughter became a potential sacrifice.
She was supposed to be
the twentieth sacrifice.
But I stopped it.
I hid her at home
while still pretending to be
a loyal villager,
and despite the influence
of the mountain ruler
that made her body ill.
As long as she didn't get wet,
the influence of the mountain
could still be controlled.
The final ritual requires
twenty-one people.
Now, Amari is in their hands.
And also Nita.
She's sacrifice number twenty-one.
The villagers' festival
is held every year.
And tonight is the final ritual.
The villagers intend
to fill this land with graves
as a form of worship
to the ruler of the mountain.
And we will become residents
of the Village of the Dead.
We will never be able to go home.
We're all going to die.
No, Yuni.
We're getting out of here.
We'll be safe. We'll go home.
You will also see your mom again.
I promise.
You're going home too, Aryo.
You have to see your dad.
The two of you only have each other.
Yuni, you should go home too.
You're coming home too.
We're all going home.
Where, Aryo?
To Bandung?
To an orphanage
that has forgotten about me?
The other kids my age
already have a new family.
I've always been waiting.
But no one has ever come for me.
Then…
come home for Yuni.
For me.
And for Nita.
We're your family now.
What's that?
The final ritual has begun.
Cursed land.
Collecting on a promise.
Stealing souls.
Leading them astray
into delirium.
Spirits drift above the graves.
The sound of gamelan breaks the silence,
welcoming the arrivals,
celebrating a festival of the dead.
You okay?
Aryo.
Got it.
Gosh.
Sir.
If we take Nita and Amari away,
will they stop the ritual?
Yes, for sure.
Where should we take them?
As far as possible.
What if they chase us later?
We'll look for a place to hide.
We'll stay there until sunrise.
Until they are no longer there.
Sir, do you know a place?
Yes. Go to my house and light the incense.
It will be safe there.
I'll make them chase me,
and I'll hide at Mbah Surop's house
until sunrise.
You should take Nita and Amari away
in a different direction.
As far as possible.
I'll come out when the sun rises.
When it's morning.
When they're already gone.
Okay?
Come on.
I promise.
We're all going home.
- Let's move.
- Let's go.
It's Nita's turn soon.
Now is the time.
Untie the rags first.
I need to do a little ritual
to reduce the influence
of the mountain ruler.
Raka.
Raka!
Come back here.
Let's talk about it.
You wait there, take the others.
No!
Come here!
We need a plan.
What the hell are you doing?
Come back here!
Raka!
Hey!
Come on!
Here! Come get me!
Nit?
Please break this evil bond.
Open your eyes.
See everything.
Your body is strong.
Get rid of the bad influence!
Quick, untie them!
Nit?
Their bodies are still weak.
The mountain ruler
can still influence them.
Come on, hurry up.
- Quick, help them up.
- Okay.
Come on, Nit, come on.
Come with me, my dear.
- Come on, Nita.
- Let's go.
I can't walk anymore, Dad.
Amari?
Nita? Nita!
Nita!
Nita?
Nit?
Sir.
Sir, what's wrong with them?
Their bodies are weak.
Nita, wake up.
Aryo?
Aryo…
Aryo.
Aryo, what happened to you?
Die, die, die.
Raka…
He is mine.
You have taken away
my twentieth sacrifice.
I am taking this boy…
as a replacement.
And your daughter
is the twenty-first sacrifice.
I am taking her now.
Don't take my daughter!
I will be the twenty-first sacrifice.
Take me instead!
Let them go!
I love you, my dear.
Forever.
Take Nita and Amari away from here.
Hurry!
Go on, then. Take me!
Where should we go, Yuni?
We can't get out of here.
We will become residents
of the Village of the Dead.
I'll get us out of here.
Come on, Aryo.
Come, Nita.
We can definitely get out of here.
I'm sure I can help.
I have to accept the real me, Aryo.
We will see our families again.
Come on.
That way.
Mbah Surop is no longer with us.
The ritual is complete.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Aryo?
Where's Raka?
Raka!
Where's Raka, Aryo?
Where's Raka?
Yuni.
Where's Raka, Aryo?
Dad…
Yuni?
Help! Over here!
Over here!
Here!
Yuni!
Hurry.
- Nit?
- Help them up.
- Help them.
- Please help us.
We've been searching for a week.
Please help.
Are you hurt, miss?
A FEW DAYS LATER…
RAKA PRAWIRA HAS RETURNED TO HIS
ETERNAL HOME WITH HIS MOTHER AND FATHER
"INSPIRED BY THE STORIES
OF HIKERS ON MOUNT WELIRANG"
TWO HIKERS FROM MALANG
REPORTED MISSING ON MOUNT WELIRANG
STUDENT MISSING ON MOUNT WELIRANG
STILL BEING SEARCHED FOR
TWO HIKERS MISSING ON MOUNT WELIRANG
TWO MISSING HIKERS FOUND DEAD
ON MOUNT WELIRANG
MISSING FOR TEN DAYS
FOUND DEAD ON MOUNT WELIRANG
HIKER FOUND DEAD ON MOUNT WELIRANG