( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
3C Group… Let's see how I can crush you.
If you tarnish my family's name,
you won't get a single penny.
I'll kill their members one by one
until I reach their ringleader.
It's good to finally meet you, Taiga.
- I don't know you.
- But I know you very well.
You're not actually Mr. Kenji's son.
What are you, the son
of Blazing Tiger's yakuza boss,
doing at Cosmic Central Group?
I…
used to know your real parents.
And the one who saved you is me.
If you make Taiga the leader,
I think we'll run into problems.
Because he isn't my real son?
This orphan from Thailand
has grown up perfectly as my only son.
No matter his past, Taiga's future
will never let our Blazing Tiger crumble.
Prin, your father, is a good man.
As for me and your mother,
we were friends.
Your mother chose to marry your father.
I stepped in when I learned Fire Phoenix
was after your father.
Fire Phoenix eliminates anyone in its way.
When they killed Mr. Kenji,
you had to come to Thailand,
to Cosmic Central,
the place your father built.
But a treacherous friend
like Naruban seized everything
and destroyed your family.
Pok, don't.
Prae! It's me.
Dear.
Pok, take care of your mother
and brothers.
Dad, come with us.
I'll follow shortly.
You need to take the kids to Khanin.
He'll hide you and our children.
And you?
I'm exposing Fire Phoenix.
I won't sell them the satellite.
I won't let customer data
fall into Fire Phoenix's hands
as a terrorist tool.
Let's go.
Hurry! Go!
- Hey!
- Oh no!
- Ugh!
- Dad!
- Dear!
Ugh.
Prae, I love you.
We'll wait for you, Prin.
Go, quickly.
Let's go.
Ugh.
Let's go, dear.
Go, quickly!
Pok, get out of here!
No!
Dad!
Hurry!
Get them!
Quick, Mom! They're coming!
Mom!
Ugh!
Hey.
Let's go.
I helped you first, Pok.
Then I helped your two younger brothers.
Dad. Mom!
By the time I came back,
you were already gone.
I searched for you everywhere for years.
I found out you stayed at a temple,
then a wealthy Japanese took you in.
All of you, leave!
He just came here to stay.
He can't answer questions properly
and doesn't even remember his own name.
We're trying to help him
find his relatives.
Seeing him reminds me of my son Hikaru.
If he's still alive, he'd be about
the same age as this little boy.
Do you want a home, kid?
Later, there was a police officer
handling your family's case.
He chased the four gunmen
who had fled the country
and did everything he could.
In the end, the case was called off,
without catching the mastermind
or any gunmen.
Where is he now?
Inspector Phumin died four years ago.
Fire Phoenix killed him.
I'm not sure.
He died when one of the gunmen reappeared.
It was Chok.
He had been missing for ten years.
Got the money?
Don't mess around.
Or I'll expose everything.
I know Prin's three sons are still alive.
Good.
I need to verify what you're saying.
Where is that police officer's family now?
The eldest daughter is abroad,
completely cut off from everything here.
As for the youngest…
Where's the youngest?
Drowned.
So you're saying
that everyone you mentioned,
all of them is dead.
Even the children you said was me
and my siblings. You have no proof.
Fire Phoenix never spares their enemies!
You don't have to believe me.
But I want you to know
I'm gathering all the evidence
that Inspector Phumin ever collected.
Your parents' deaths won't be in vain.
Naruban stole everything your father built
despite him being the original founder.
You know Naruban is tied to Fire Phoenix.
Since Mr. Kenji died, Cosmic Central Group
has been buying up every business
your father owned in Japan.
That's where they launder their money.
Mr. Kenji
protected you for years.
But eventually, Fire Phoenix found you.
That's why they spare no one.
Dad died because of me.
I want you to think it over for yourself.
If you believe me,
we'll hunt them together.
Even if they hide in the shadows,
Fire Phoenix must be exposed!
If there's no sun,
life would be impossible, huh?
Yeah.
You can't be without me.
If you hurt Aru, you're dead.
Aru, she's scary. Help!
Come on.
Come here!
Let's take a photo.
Come on!
- My bangs!
- Cheese!
Aw.
It's good now.
One, two, three!
So cute.
Why close your eyes?
- Let's see the other shots.
- Adorable!
Here, the other shots look fine.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Aru.
If there's no sun, I'll be your sunshine.
Lee!
You're not dead.
My name's Rin.
You look just like my best friend,
really similar.
But no fangs.
Your skin's different.
Lee is gone.
You helped me.
Yeah.
I pass by there every day.
I helped, but didn't know where to go,
so I brought you here.
Thanks.
I'm Aru. I won't trouble you for long.
I asked the building owner.
The last room down the hall is available.
Thanks, Rin.
Hungry?
For you.
Thank you.
Pol.Lt.Col. Phumin Pongrit!
Here's your medal.
What should a taekwondo champion
get as a reward?
You already got a new phone.
Spare the poor cop. My wallet's
been through a lot already.
I'm just joking!
I'll claim it all at once when I graduate
with first-class honors. How about a car?
We'll settle it later when the time comes.
I'm a bit forgetful these days.
It's the same case, right?
It's been so many years.
Whole family wiped out,
father, mother, and three sons.
They were unbelievably cruel.
I'll become a police officer
and continue your investigation.
Don't you want to be a national athlete?
I do.
I want to be both a national athlete
and a police officer.
That's the coolest!
Here.
This is for your report.
Ugh!
Why is this so hard?
In Thailand,
- Transition metals are elements or ions
- they use Debt-to-GDP
- with outermost electrons.
- to assess…
To assess…
- D-orbital.
- To assess…
- Complex compounds.
- household debt.
- Coordination compounds.
- Yet it's not
- Reactive to oxygen
- a true reflection
- in the air.
- of the economy.
What are you two doing?
Wait a minute.
Huh?
That super-hot Professor Methee
just came over and talked to you.
No way!
Yes, I saw it too.
Hey, are you going to tell us or not?
If you don't,
the whole university will know!
Hey, hit him again. I allow it.
Hey.
You're always rough
with your boyfriend, seriously.
He's hitting on you, right?
He's not!
- Nah, I'll continue reading.
- Hey.
Suspicious.
Not suspicious!
- Wow!
- Gotcha!
Come on, tell us.
Lee.
Sorry, I came to return the book.
Go wait in the garden for a bit.
I'll take a quick shower.
That's fine. I'll just leave it here.
Who are you talking to?
Oh.
This is the person you called over?
Lee, wait! It's not what you think!
Do you want to tell me anything?
I'm proud you're my daughter.
You take after your mom.
Beautiful, kind,
and easy to get along with.
If your mom were here,
she'd be just as happy as I am.
I got fooled.
Who fooled you?
It's okay. I'll only be dumb once.
I love you, Dad.
I'll study hard to become
a police officer like you.
Come on!
Ugh! Are we done?
Dad, you deserve lots of stars
on your shoulders
for all the hard work you do
helping people.
But I want all the stars in the sky
to belong to you.
My angel.
When I graduate and get a job,
I'll take care of you
and make you the happiest.
Alright.
Dad!
Dad, watch out!
Take cover!
Are you okay, my dear?
Dad!
Dad…
Do you know why your father was shot?
Please answer.
- Just answer us.
- Please tell us.
- Who let the reporters in?
- Say something.
- Please give us the information.
- Get them out.
Excuse me. Please leave.
Please step outside.
Uncle Punlop! Who shot my father?
We're tracking him down. Don't worry.
I won't let Phumin die in vain.
Is it true Inspector Phumin is linked
to a kidnapping and extortion gang?
Is he also connected
to the suspect's secret drug accounts?
That's not true!
My dad would never be involved
in something like that. He's a good man!
Lee, stay strong.
Stay strong.
Uncle.
Why are they asking things like that?
You know my dad would never take bribes.
He wasn't a corrupt cop!
Alright.
Uncle, what's Fire Phoenix?
Did Phumin tell you about this?
Dad never went into details.
But I saw him keep all the information.
Bring those things to me.
You shouldn't be involved in this.
What's it about?
You were Dad's most trusted subordinate.
Please tell me.
Fire Phoenix…
is something a kid like you
shouldn't know about
or get involved in.
But my dad's dead.
He spent his life working for others.
But everyone's criticizing him
because they believe the fake news.
I know we shouldn't think like this.
But the law can't protect
every good person.
Fire Phoenix
is a secret organization that works
to eliminate injustice in society.
That means Fire Phoenix
can find who killed my father.
Uncle, where is Fire Phoenix?
No, Lee.
It's too dangerous.
Let the law handle this.
But you said it yourself,
that the law can't always help.
How long will it take for everyone
to realize Dad wasn't a corrupt cop?
Ten years? Twenty years?
Every time someone searches his name,
they see bribe-taking cop, corrupt cop.
Just because the law
can't catch the real mastermind.
Search everywhere. She's here.
Hah!
Hey!
Go.
Yes, sir.
Got it.
Boss said to kill her like her father.
Hah!
Uncle.
Lee!
I'm going to find Fire Phoenix.
No, you can't, Lee.
This time, you might not survive.
Luckily, my people found you. Otherwise…
If you want Fire Phoenix to help…
There will be a price.
Think carefully, Lee.
Once you take this path,
there's no turning back.
You can take my life if you want.
From now on, Lee doesn't exist
in this world anymore.
Can I see my friend's face one last time?
You can't tell
what she looked like anymore.
She drowned, rotted, and was eaten
by animals. Only bones remain.
She's probably been dead for months.
The only ID we found
is under the name Ms. Lirin Pongrit.
Lee…
Sun, why did she have to die like this?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thanks.
You're working like you owe someone money.
Worse than that.
I just got out of prison.
Manslaughter case.
The tickets are ready.
The ski clothes are ready.
What's missing?
The wedding ring is ready too.
I'll propose to you in the snow.
Hey, what the hell?
Hey.
- Ouch!
- Oh!
Hey! What's your problem?
Sorry.
Nice wife you got there.
Can I borrow her for a night?
She's cute.
Sun!
- Oh!
- Ugh!
Sun, oh no!
Sun!
Let go!
Huh?
Hey! What's going on here?
- Stop!
- Hey, the cops are here!
Hurry up!
Police!
Please come with us.
Take care of your family, Sun.
I confessed.
Got a three-year sentence,
but since I was a model prisoner,
served only two.
How's that for a profile?
Perfect.
Don't overthink it.
If you need anything, just ask.
Come on, Aru.
You're Arunothai.
Time to start your new life.
Oops.
The website Rin found
is related to Fire Phoenix.
Mr. Taiga's my personal designer.
He can work here
anytime.
Fire Phoenix…
will pay with every life
for Blazing Tiger!
Subtitle translation by:
Chomchanach Yanaharn