( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
♫ ♫
♫  ♫
When you become famous one day,
I'm going to brag to everyone
that I was your very first fan.
No one will see that you're sad.
Anyway, I've already faced reality.
The whole world hates me.
No one likes me.
♫  ♫
Are you crazy?
He Xiang Yong.
Chen Hao Wei, please don't go.
- I'm begging you, don't go.
- Don't stop me.
Chen Hao Wei.
♫  ♫
♫ ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
7️⃣Shooting Stars Team @Viki.com
♫  ♫
♫ ♫
[]
Chen Hao Wei.
Chen Hao Wei. Chen Hao Wei. Wake up.
-
Wake up. Why are we here?
How did we get back yesterday?
Get up. Get up.
We were clearly on the main island yesterday.
Didn't we go out for a meal,
and then we went for a walk?
-
Then there were no boats,
so we stayed at a hotel. Did you forget?
-
We've been at the inn the whole time.
- What kind of dream talk are you blabbering?
- Wake up.
Look at me.
Wake up. Look at me.
Are you messing with me?
Is this a joke?
-
Wait a minute. You're the one messing with me.
What are you talking about, Zhong Xiao You?
Let me sleep a little longer.
What did you just call me?
Why did you call me Zhong Xiao You?
What else should I call you?
Me...
Have I changed?
I haven't changed.
I'm He Xiang Yong.
-
What time is it now?
How is this possible?
I'm not Zhong Xiao You.
I'm He Xiang Yong.
-
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down, okay?
You just had a nightmare.
Just get some rest.
Wow, is this new?
What's the plan? Looking for redemption?
What redemption?
You're the Unlucky King.
-
Do I need redemption?
Let me see.
- What's wrong?
- How did I get back yesterday?
- What are you talking about?
Yeah.
Xiao You, what are you doing?
Why are there only photos of you and Mr. Hua?
Where's the family photo?
What family photo?
You know, Mom...
Where are the photos of your wife and son?
And why are all those trophies gone?
Wait, you were married?
If I were married,
you'd be the Eddie Peng of Starry Islet.
We've known each other so long,
and you don't know if I'm married?
What are you talking about?
You're not married?
Xiao You, you've been working here
for three or four months.
How could you not know if he's married?
Take it easy! What are you doing?
There's a lot of stuff in that cabinet. Be careful!
-
I think he's in bad shape.
- Give him a checkup.
- I'm a surgeon.
-
Maybe he hit his head.
Something's wrong with his brain.
Just check him out.
This is impossible.
Xiao You. Go to the clinic.
Yeah, go get a checkup.
Good grief.
Holy crap.
Mom!
Do you want me to wash
your sheets or your pants?
- Why are you calling me?
- Mom, why am I at home?
If you weren't at home, where would you be?
No, I mean, yesterday...
I went to bail out Xiao Hai,
and by the time we were done, it was late.
There were no boats back,
so we just found a hotel to stay in.
- After we checked in, we went to sleep...
- Mr. Li!
- After we went to sleep...
What are you talking about?
It was your birthday yesterday.
We had tomahawk steak at home.
Remember? It was a huge piece!
You kept saying how delicious it was.
Did you forget?
Tomahawk steak...
This isn't a dream.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Mom, I'm taking the day off.
Hama-chan!
- Hama-chan!
- What?
Yesterday... let me tell you about yesterday.
Where's your injury?
What injury?
Weren't we on the main island yesterday?
And then I went to the police station...
- You seemed to have gotten into a fight.
- I'm very busy today.
If you need something, tell me when I'm back.
Just let me talk for a second.
Hama-chan!
Li Wan Zhe!
Where are you going?
I've been looking for you for so long.
- What do you want?
- Something's gone wrong!
What's wrong with you?
I was clearly on the main island last night.
But I woke up today back on Starry Islet!
Me, too.
I also suddenly teleported
back to Starry Islet.
You too?
What should we do?
Does this have to do with
wishing on a shooting star?
Wishing upon a shooting star?
How did you know I made a wish?
Are you an idiot?
We made it together.
I never made a wish with you.
Remember that night
we had the roadside banquet?
Your mom shoved a microphone at us,
and I told everyone I was fired.
I ran to the seaside platform,
and you came to find me.
We made some random wishes together.
Did you forget?
What are you talking about?
I've never had a roadside banquet with you.
Li Wan Zhe.
What's my name?
Zhong Xiao You.
What do you mean, Zhong Xiao You?
I'm He Xiang Yong.
He Xiang Yong?
Who's that?
Listen to me.
I don't know how you found out,
but I hope you don't go around telling people.
Li Wan Zhe!
Li Wan Zhe, you...
I'm doomed.
What exactly went wrong?
How could this happen?
You're back.
Are you okay?
Someone named Xi Xi called looking for you.
She said she's your friend.
What did she say?
She asked for He Xiang Yong at first,
but then she asked for you.
She left her number.
So, who is He Xiang Yong?
Hello, Xi Xi.
Do you still remember me?
Even if you're not the editor I remember,
you're the only one I could think of.
He Xiang Yong.
Thank goodness.
Xi Xi, listen to me.
Last night, I was clearly with Chen Hao Wei
at a hotel on the main island.
But when I woke up today,
I was back on Starry Islet.
And when I asked Chen Hao Wei,
he told me he didn't know
who He Xiang Yong was.
But he clearly recognized me last night!
Then I went to ask my dad.
But he told me he'd never been married.
And the things in my house...
my photos, my mom's photos,
our family portrait, they've all disappeared.
Then I went to find Li Wan Zhe,
but he said he didn't recognize me either.
But before this, he was clearly the only one
- who always remembered me.
- Calm down.
Listen to me.
I dreamed that I went to Starry Islet.
Outside the grocery store, I met someone
who knew I liked bitter melon black tea.
The grocery store?
Was it Hong?
He said that when a wish comes true,
it also means you'll lose something.
I think the wish is backfiring.
Time and space are becoming distorted.
The card I drew also confirms what Hong said.
So, if I get Zhong Xiao You's identity,
is He Xiang Yong destined to vanish?
Is everything I got from that wish
going to be this short-lived?
Xi Xi, what should I do?
I finally made up with my dad.
I finally got a second chance
with Chen Hao Wei.
What can I do to save all of this?
Is there anything I can do
to make things go back to normal?
Xi Xi, please help me.
He Xiang Yong.
If you give up now, the game is over.
Go find Hong first.
Why look for Hong?
I don't think he's an ordinary person.
He might be the only one who can help.
Hong!
Mr. De.
Have you seen Hong?
Isn't he sitting outside?
- No.
- He's not?
[Ask Star AI...]
[When'll wishes upon shooting stars backfire?]
[Please wait...]
[Sorry, the system doesn't have an answer.]
Even AI can't solve this.
What am I supposed to do?
Li Wan Zhe, the sweet soup is ready.
Bring it down for me.
Li Wan Zhe!
What on earth are you busy with?
Get your butt down here and work!
You put on the same act every day.
Aren't you tired of it?
Tao!
Coming!
Chief, you're here, too.
Okay.
I'll give you fewer tapioca balls
and more mung beans, okay?
- Sure.
- All right.
Zhe Ma, have you seen Hong?
Hong? Why are you looking for Hong?
Doesn't Hong live by the temple?
I have something very important to ask him.
He lives behind the temple.
No, he lives in the sixth house
from the end of Coastal Road.
But I remember him being at the grocery store.
What are you talking about?
He lives right by the pier.
He lives behind the temple.
He used to lay out his straw mat there.
He even did his laundry there.
Li Wan Zhe.
What do you want?
I know you don't believe me right now,
but I still have to tell you.
If we want to solve this problem,
Hong seems to be the key.
Are we even that close?
And how do you know so much about me?
I'm warning you, don't tell anyone.
I didn't tell anyone.
- Xiao You.
- Hao Wei, want some shaved ice?
Later. I'll eat later.
- Okay.
- Xiao You.
Come back with me now.
Mr. He is already angry.
Here, catch.
Skipping work, huh?
Go home.
What?
How did he disappear just from making a call?
I'm leaving now.
- Bye.
- Ride safely.
Okay.
Weirdo.
What was it you wanted to tell me?
In the two months you've been here,
it's the first time I've seen you so flustered.
All right.
It's okay if you don't want to say it now.
When you're ready to talk, just let me know.
I'll call Mr. He and say we'll be back late.
Where do you want to go?
Come on.
Let's get a little mushy.
Get closer.
So, you finally decided to come back.
Looking for Hong...
Everyone on Starry Islet knows about it.
Well? Did you find him?
What is wrong with you?
No matter what's going on,
you can't just run off without a word.
Who's going to do the work at the inn?
Hao Wei or me?
Mr. He.
Xiao You was looking for Hong...
- It must be because...
- He has a mouth, he can speak for himself.
You're acting very strange today.
You won't even offer an explanation.
I'm sorry.
It's my own problem, I'll find a way to fix it.
I won't let it affect the inn work again.
Forget it.
You young people have your own ideas.
But if you really run into
something you can't solve,
even if you don't want to tell me,
you can go to Mr. Hua, or go see Angela.
We're your elders, after all.
You can at least talk to us.
Xiao You.
You've had a long day. You must be hungry.
I'll go make you something to eat.
Wait here a moment.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
Let's eat.
Thank you, Mr. He.
What's wrong? Does it taste bad?
My parents also love
garlic shrimp rice noodles.
If you miss home, just go back.
You don't even need to ask for leave.
Go on, get some rest.
Over here.
Are you okay?
Si Si.
I'm here to pick up the batch
of brown sugar my mom ordered.
Wait a second. My dad's in the shower.
Okay, thanks.
Old man!
It's Wan Zhe.
Hong.
Do you know anything about
wishing upon a shooting star?
Why does Zhong Xiao You
keep saying that you're...
that you're the key?
What do you mean I'm the key?
I didn't make a wish.
You did, didn't you?
I did.
Then what did you wish for?
I didn't make a wish.
I definitely didn't make a wish.
It's all a secret.
A secret?
What do you mean?
In this world,
no wall is completely soundproof.
One day, the sea will bring you
the message it wants to tell you.
It's right here.
What sea?
Love like fireworks is burning up!
Just like a fire!
What fire? What's burning up?
Hong, what are you trying to say?
I wanted to ask you about Zhong Xiao You.
Here.
This is for you.
Don't come looking for me again.
I'm going home.
I'm going back to my home in the sea.
I can finally go home.
Wan Zhe.
My dad said to go get it yourself.
Can you even see with those sunglasses on?
You don't get it, I'm a rocker.
It's raining now.
Why don't you go inside?
I want to sit here a bit longer.
Go home if you want to.
Don't worry about the work here.
I'll handle it.
This is my home.
You don't believe me, do you?
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
Have you ever heard of déjà vu?
Déjà vu is a sense of familiarity.
It's a feeling that you've seen this before.
Lately, when I talk to you,
I often get déjà vu.
Actually, I'm curious about something.
You said He Xiang Yong and I
were high school classmates.
And you said you are He Xiang Yong.
So...
did anything happen between us before?
In your senior year,
you lost a basketball game.
I pulled your hat down over your eyes,
because I didn't want people to see you sad.
In my senior year, I was studying for exams.
I didn't play in any basketball games.
On your 18th birthday,
I drew a picture of a sea turtle for you
as a birthday present.
But I never received a sea turtle drawing.
Then do you remember
how you used to love telling bad jokes?
The necklace around your neck...
I gave that to you, too.
This necklace?
I bought this for myself
when I was on the main island.
Forget it.
There's no point in talking about it.
You don't remember anyway.
The more I say, the more disappointed I get.
I think it's very interesting.
And you can draw?
I've always admired people who can draw.
I want to follow your art.
Always, always, always...
I'll always be your number one fan.
Actually, what you just told me...
I think I have some memory of it.
Didn't you say you didn't remember?
It's just déjà vu.
The person in my dream is blurry.
I can't see his face clearly.
Then...
what else did you dream about?
If you ask me to think about it now,
I won't be able to remember.
This must be the consequence
of wishing upon a shooting star.
Everyone will forget about me.
Forget everything about He Xiang Yong.
Shooting stars? Making a wish?
I know it's hard to believe.
But it really happened to me.
I've said those exact words to you before.
Do you mind?
I kind of believe it now.
- Want a drink?
- No thanks.
No.
I wasn't asking you.
So noisy.
It's late. Your mom will scold you again.
Can you really not remember anything?
Remember what?
Those two dishes.
Chicken feet and stinky tofu.
You used to pester me all the time.
You kept following me around.
And now...
Anyway, I don't know how to explain it.
Stop playing.
Go home.
I'm almost at the next level!
Whatever.
Fine.
Don't text me later to nag me.
- See ya.
- Hey.
Are you really not staying?
Do you really want me to stay?
Get lost!
Bye.
Damn, he really left.
Those moments of déjà vu you mentioned...
One day,
will you remember them?
Or...
have I really been forgotten by everyone?
[Epilogue]
[For you]
Hong.
What are you doing?
I'm...
watching the shooting stars.
Watching shooting stars?
But it's daytime.
I know there are shooting stars in the day.
But... you shouldn't be able to see them.
Dummy.
That's because you aren't
looking with your heart.
You have to look with your heart.
With my heart?
What do you mean?
Do you want to make a wish on a shooting star?
Please.
I've heard that story since I was a kid.
Has anyone's wish ever actually come true?
Oh, that's because you're all
using the wrong method.
The wrong method?
Listen carefully.
I'm only saying this once.
Okay.
This is a meteorite fragment.
A meteorite fragment?
You have to...
When the shooting star comes,
take this meteorite fragment...
and throw it into the sea.
When this energy and your wish...
combine together...
your wish will come true!
Are you serious?
Want to give it a try?
Maybe next time. Next time.
I have to go back and help at the shop.
The tide is coming in soon.
Do you want to head back together?
Don't worry about me. Just go back.
- Go on.
- All right then.
- Take care of yourself.
- Okay, I will.
- Bye-bye.
- Okay, bye.
Are you here to check in?
Chen Hao Wei.
Sir? Are you checking in?
I like you.
Have you ever heard of cellular memory
or muscle memory?
Your brain might forget,
but your heart never does.
You remember, don't you?