( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
"Saeng Karun Foundation"
Rise and shine, everyone.
The birds are already out.
Get up.
Or Grandpa's coming to scold you.
Make a fist and spin it round
Raise your hands
and wave them side to side
Spread your arms up and down,
fold and touch your shoulders
Spread your arms up and down
Stand up straight
and spin around
Line up.
Phi Oui, get me the eggs.
(Phi, respectful honorific)
Here.
Now the zucchini, Phi Oui.
Put it down, Mom.
Leave it to the young.
Very well. You carry it over.
Then come back and help Auntie Oui
lift the rice pot.
Okay. Don't have to tell me.
Hmph.
- Hot stuff coming.
- Should I stop feeding you?
Okay. Come on in.
Here. Grab it. Okay.
- Easy now.
- Yes.
There we go. Okay.
You're welcome. Here you go.
- Alright, okay.
- Thank you.
Give them plenty now.
Hey... hey, your pants.
Suck it in a little.
There you go.
Hmph...watch out
or they'll fall right off you.
Nice job.
Stop, stop. Pik, hold on.
Here. Do not eat boogers, okay?
Hey, not yet.
Phi Pipe, leave me alone.
Pipe, don't pick on her.
Yes, Phi Save.
Grandpa, go sit down.
You could pass out
blowing that whistle.
Stop before you drop.
It's you who will drop.
See? With this.
Go on.
Stay with Mom, okay?
Yeah.
- One, two, three, four...
- Five, six, seven, eight.
One...
Hehe.
Breakfast is ready. Stop playing.
Just a little warm-up, Grandpa.
So I can eat more.
Trying this move.
It's way more fun.
People need to do things
one at a time.
Take your seat.
We're about to eat.
Kids these days always talk back.
Go on.
Mart.
Any rice left?
What's going on, Sorn?
Someone dropped off a kid, Dad.
She looks hungry.
Thank you.
Listen for the signal.
Alright, let's eat.
Yay.
- Okay, hop on in. Careful now.
- Hurry, hurry.
Serves you right.
- Pipe.
- Pipe, at it again?
Snow, hold it. Let him go.
Dad, let's go.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Grandpa.
- Bye-bye.
- Buh-bye.
- Oh...
- That was fast.
I already spoke
with the child's mother.
Just three lanes down from here.
No husband.
Just lost her job.
She really can't manage.
Girl, this place...
is your new home now.
You'll have food to eat,
a place to sleep.
Someone to look after you.
You're safe now. Okay?
Mm-hmm. Mart.
Take her to see
where she'll be sleeping.
Great. I'll show you.
Dad, we can't take in
any more children.
Why not? What's wrong?
Hello.
Good morning, Supaporn
calling from Thanarak Bank.
May I speak
with Mr. Somsak Prasitphithaya?
Speaking.
The reason for my call today
is that we have not received
a loan payment
for December 2025
through January 2026.
When would you be able
to make a payment, sir?
Very soon.
I'm dealing with
a few things right now.
I must inform you of another matter.
In February 2026,
your reduced-rate agreement is
nearing the end of its grace period,
after which your payments
will resume at the standard rate.
And if I still can't pay?
We encourage you to come in
for a consultation.
Accounts over 180 days past due
will be subject to legal action.
I'm sorry... legal action?
What happens then?
Well...
the Enforcement Department may
seize the land used as collateral
and sell it at auction
to settle the debt.
How much do I still owe?
Principal and interest
comes to 12,508,649.75 baht.
I see.
Was that the bank?
What did they say?
Hmm?
Nothing to worry yourself over.
Over not making
loan payments on time?
Dad, we barely can afford groceries
for the children.
And then there's tuition
and everything else.
Tonight they're delivering
rice and cooking gas,
and I'm afraid
I have no money for those.
It's all right. I'll sort it out.
There's always a way.
My elderly allowance just came in.
I'll transfer it over.
How much is it?
Seven hundred baht.
Hey, Mom. Sitting out here again.
Now listen.
I've told you many times,
do not bring that out here.
You could drop it.
Worth a lot, you know?
Come on. Give it to me.
Mm. It's getting hot out here.
Better go sit inside. Come on.
Come, come. Grab the cane.
There we go. Up, up.
Can you make it?
Alright, let's go.
Easy steps. Go on. Go on.
Alright, turn, turn.
Now, back up.
Back up. Easy, easy. There we go.
Good. Very good.
Huh.
Mom, I'm heading up to work now.
"Thailand Writers' Association,
Certificate, Somsak Prasitpittaya"
"Saming the Slayer, Volume 2"
"Saming the Slayer 2,
by Harn Chanprai"
Hmph.
Go, go.
Hey, hey. Watch it.
Hey.
Pheem. Pheem.
Hey, block it. Block.
- Yeah...
- Yeah.
- What the.
Hey, hey. Why aren't you in class?
Get to class. Now.
Tuck in your shirt too.
You...
Hey.
Supawit.
You're on a scholarship.
Why not show your friends how to be
studious and not skip class?
Go before they pull
your scholarship.
Too late for that, teacher.
It's my last semester.
And I already got into uni.
So why must I go to class?
If you're at school,
you go to class.
And this is no time
for soccer, right?
Besides, you two
still have final exams
just like everyone else.
Please, just this one period.
Cut us some slack.
Even if I go,
I won't pay attention anyway.
I'll just bother everyone.
You two wear me out.
Fine. But no soccer.
The other kids can see you.
Hang out somewhere else.
- Yes.
- Got it.
Okay.
Hey, all of you go to class.
Lucky for us,
Kru (teacher) Met came.
Kru Suri could've dragged us
to her office.
Well, let's bounce
before she gets here.
Yeah?
Ugh.
You think you got me?
Hey Guy, all your posts are
in Close Friends, huh?
Who else is in there?
Just you.
And some others.
Who?
Secret?
No.
Hmm?
Not telling me?
Will we still be friends
after we graduate?
Why?
Well...we'll be at different unis.
So far apart.
We won't see each other much.
Come on.
You'll make new friends in no time
and forget all about me.
An athlete like you,
I bet you'll have a girl in a week.
Hey, Save.
Yeah?
I just want to tell you...
Hmm?
Tell me what? Just say it.
We'll still be friends.
I'll make sure we hang out
all the time. Okay?
Of course. What's gotten into you?
Stuttering and spacing out.
I didn't want to
say something cheesy.
Go ahead and say it. I won't gag.
What's wrong with you?
You're being weird.
Mm.
- Phi Sorn.
- Hmm?
Is this ride far from here?
Not at all. Just two lanes over.
Good.
Don't take another job yet.
I have a new project.
What project?
Mm. Just finish the job and return.
Mm-hmm.
Be careful.
Phi Sorn, shouldn't we get
a handyman for this?
We've got everything we need.
Why waste money?
You actually know what you're doing?
Trust me.
Just need to check the drill first.
Been sitting a while.
It may be rusted.
Here.
Take this. Wait right here.
Oh, Grandma.
Just watching us work?
You just sit and watch;
no need to help.
- We've got this.
- Oh no, Grandma.
Just cheer us on from here.
That's plenty.
And why are you holding that clock?
It's worth a lot, you know?
Ugh.
- Easy now.
- Good.
What are you two doing?
What is it, Dad?
Ugh.
Watch the hand. Be careful.
Yeah, I know what I'm doing.
You sure about that?
Absolutely.
Hey, anybody kicked the plug?
I did.
Oof.
What's all the racket?
It drove me mad upstairs.
Phi Sorn is making a trellis
for the vegetable garden.
A trellis? What for?
Well, it's obvious.
So we can save money on buying them.
Oh? Is that so?
Mm-hmm.
You all know how to do that?
Can't be that hard.
Drop some seeds, water them,
wait for them to grow.
Then pick and eat. Simple as that.
Mm.
Alright. Just keep it down a little.
It's bothering me.
Yes.
Sorry, Father.
We should hurry.
Oh, Mom. Not again.
What is it with you and that clock?
Give me that.
Hmph.
Keep doing that,
and you'll pull something.
You heading straight home?
Yeah.
My mom just messaged me
to help Dad with something.
Okay. I'm heading home.
Let's go.
Hey, Save.
Yeah?
If I tell you something,
can you promise you won't hate me?
What is it? Just say it.
Well, I...
- I like...
- I'm waiting out front.
Who were you just talking to?
It's Jang, asking me to go to Siam.
What about...
going home to help your dad?
Oh, that can wait.
Scoping out girls comes first.
So...you were saying?
Nothing. Forget it.
Hey.
What is it? Tell me.
It's just...
I was going to say I...
like...
Hey, Save.
Ow.
Hey, you okay?
Ow, that hurt.
That's nothing. You're so dramatic.
Guy, you coming with us or not?
- You in?
- Yeah, I'm in.
Well, it's a mess, really.
I still don't know what to do.
Thank you, honestly.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
I won't forget this.
I really mean it.
Hey.
Mom, where's the clock?
The one you always carry around.
Where is it?
Where did you put it?
It's gone. Where did you leave it?
What are you looking for?
The clock that was always up there.
Oh, I haven't seen it at all.
No idea where Mom left it.
That clock isn't any regular one.
The former Army Commander gave it
to me as a wedding gift.
Who were you on the phone with
just now?
Me, on the phone?
Yeah, you. I saw you on the phone.
Oh...
Um, I was talking to...
- A friend.
- A friend?
An old friend.
Hadn't spoken to in a while.
Mm-hmm. So it took you
a while to answer me?
Hehe.
My, so forgetful at your age.
You'll be like my mom soon, huh?
And if you find that clock,
put it back where it belongs.
Yes, Father.
Right.
Mom, this can't keep happening.
Things keep going missing.
I can't keep up with this.
Let's kick some ball.
We're here already.
Alright, engine's off.
Everyone can get out now.
- Thank you.
- Yes, yes. Don't run. You'll fall.
- Go on, kids. Watch yourself.
- Easy, easy.
- Thank you.
Oh, oh. Careful. Here.
Slow down
or you'll trip over yourself.
Good girl.
Go wash up and do your homework.
Alright, that's everyone.
Ugh.
Pipe, you...
Hey, hey. Guys.
I'm Snow.
I'm Mabel.
I'm Yoyo. What's your name?
My name is Jingjai.
Jingjai, Auntie Oui asked us
to look after you.
Come on, we'll give you
the home tour.
She already did.
But there are rules
you need to know.
I'm sure she didn't tell you.
Bathroom rules.
Two minutes per person. That's it.
What? Only two minutes?
Yes.
If you go over, you're scrubbing
smelly toilets for a week.
It's not personal.
It just wastes water.
Right. Two minutes, no more.
This is the dining area.
We all come together
for every meal, every day.
Mealtime rules.
Finish everything on your plate.
Not a single grain left.
No food waste.
Trying to sneak it out?
You get no meal for a week.
That could starve someone to death.
We all have to be frugal.
No throwing food away.
Every plate, every dish.
Nothing goes to waste.
Food is precious.
And this is the computer room.
For homework and studying.
If you want to use a computer,
sign in right there.
But no more than thirty minutes.
If you go over,
no social media for you. Forever.
Don't linger.
It runs up the electric bill.
Last stop: the bedroom.
Everyone lights out at nine.
If anyone refuses to sleep...
- The ghost will get you.
Hey, the power's out.
Get a flashlight.
I'll check on the kids.
Hm...
The electric authority
said nothing about a blackout.
Oh, now I remember.
- Remember what?
- I forgot to pay the bill.
Sorn, it's important. How could you?
Well, Mart borrowed it that day to
get school uniforms for the kids.
She hasn't paid me back,
so it slipped my mind.
Don't blame me.
I just need more time.
And you never reminded me.
I figured paid it after all.
Why did you assume?
I've got a lot to do:
deliveries, errands, on and on.
Of course, things slip my mind.
The borrower should follow up.
Ow, I'm busy too.
My head's spinning all the time.
Alright, alright. That's enough.
Go pay it tomorrow.
Flashlight.
I'm gonna check on the kids.
Oh.
Yeah?
Uh. What's going on?
Dead batteries.
Haven't used it in ages.
What actually works in this house?
Happy birthday to you.
Whose birthday is it?
Haha. Don't mess around.
The power's out.
Your dad forgot to pay the bill.
Your mom borrowed the money.
Alright, enough. It's fine.
Save, go check on the kids.
Yes.
Oh, and fetch Auntie Oui for me.
Got it.
And... where's the cake
and candles, Grandpa?
Hmm?
Cake and candles?
Go now, or I'll push you there
with my foot.
Oh, I'd better hurry.
- Hurry with my foot?
- I'm going, I'm going.
- Auntie Oui.
- Yes.
Mom needs you.
Oh, alright.
You keep an eye on the kids.
Just watch them. That's it?
Whatever you say, Save.
This way.
Phi (honorific) Save, I'm scared.
Why? You sleep with the lights off
every night.
Hmm?
But it's a blackout.
Is the house ghost messing with us?
You mean Tiad?
He should've reincarnated ages ago.
Look...
Hey, Snow.
Hmm? You made up
a scary tale again?
I did not. I did see him
in a photo smiling.
You were paranoid.
- I wasn't.
- Hey, guys.
How about something fun?
Good idea, good idea.
Quick. Gather round. Come close.
And the final transformation.
A werewolf.
Wrruff!
Save, come here a second.
Coming.
Snow, my phone please.
- I'll be right back, yeah?
- Phi Save, keep dancing.
Hey, I'll be back.
You guys stay put.
Okay?. Be right back.
- Phi Save...
- I'll come back.
Why? It's scary.
That was terrifying.
Mom always breaks up the fun.
- Did you hurt bad?
- Ow.
Reached up and my back went out.
Oh, no.
Yeah, Mom?
Your dad just threw out his back
reaching up there.
There. Get that box from up top.
What do you need, Mom?
A lantern for the kids.
Don't want to use candles.
Something might catch fire.
We should use electric lanterns.
Nobody uses oil lanterns anymore.
Right there is a brain.
Wonder where he gets that from.
- Come on.
- Where?
- There.
- Here?
- Careful, it's high.
- Easy, easy.
- Watch out.
- Dad, a little push.
- Push him.
- Ow, hold on. Ugh.
Support him. Easy now.
Watch that stuff on top.
He's taking too long.
It's been forever.
Mom and Dad definitely
put him to work.
Mm.
Hey, Pipe.
Shh.
Awoo.
- Awoo.
Look.
Awoo.
Not even close.
Well, you think you can do better?
Awoo...woo.
- Awoo...
Werewolf or mangy mutt.
- Mangy mutt.
Hey.
Ow.
- Hey.
Pipe, look what you did.
You knocked me first.
You pushed me first.
Because you shoved me.
I did not.
Let's ask them.
They saw the whole thing.
Fire. Fire.
Hey. Fire.
- Hey.
- Hey, fire.
Fire.
- What?
- Hey.
- Go look.
Everyone, get down.
Everyone, crawl to the door.
Dad, spray it. Spray it.
What's wrong, Dad?
I don't know. Something's wrong.
Is it expired? Come on.
We're done for.
Ow. Everyone, follow me.
Snow, why are you crawling?
To get under the smoke.
Everyone get down.
There's hardly any smoke.
- Get up. Get out now.
- Get up.
Out, out, out. Quick.
Children, this way.
Go on, hurry along.
Be careful.
- You got it?
- Whoa.
Hey.
Sorn, why aren't you spraying it?
It won't come out.
Whoa.
Hack. Hack.
Oh no.
Ah, let's go.
Hurry, hurry.
Mom.
- Hey.
- What?
Good grief.
Aw.
Great-grandma,
how did you get here?
Her timing couldn't be worse.
Dad, don't. I'll handle it.
Take her outside.
Quickly.
Save, go get more buckets.
- Hurry. Give me that.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Yes.
- Water.
- Get Grandma out, Dad.
Mom, let's go.
- Please calm down.
- Ugh.
Mom, stop fighting.
- Get out now.
- Hurry.
Is our house going to be okay?
The whole place is gonna burn.
And it'll spread to the neighbors.
Stink breath.
That's not gonna happen.
It is burning.
All because of you, Pipe.
Yeah, you started it. Put it out.
Enough.
Everyone, follow me.
Ow.
How could it be broken?
I still haven't found a husband.
I'm not ready to die.
Water's here.
Mom, water.
Here, here.
Water's here.
Save, get more water.
Okay.
- We're here to help.
- Help is here.
- Yeah...
We did it.
We don't have to
sleep on the street after all.
Oh.
Why did you say that, Mabel?
Because without this house,
we'd have nowhere to go.
Huh.
Save's helping Auntie Oui
clean up now.
Tonight the kids should
be able to sleep inside.
Mm.
Phi Sorn, pay the electric bill
right now.
I looked it up for our area.
If we pay now,
they can still come out tonight.
We'll have power back right away.
- Really?
- Mm.
And we should get new bedding
and a new fire extinguisher.
Alright. I'll pull money
from the bank.
I'm afraid it's not enough
for the power bill.
Then I'll find a way.
Dad, I know you love this place.
I do too.
But we're getting
stretched too thin.
I'm working on it.
Father.
The clock on the shelf.
Grandma didn't take it anywhere.
I did.
I've been quietly pawning off
old things from the house.
Quite a few pieces by now.
What? No wonder.
The place has been looking emptier.
Mart, why didn't you
talk to us first?
Well, if I'd told you that,
would you have let me?
There might have been another way.
There wasn't another way.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be
stressed out like this.
I'm sorry, Father.
But I really had no choice.
Dad, don't be angry with Mart.
I'll find the money
to get everything out of pawn.
No need.
I'm nearly done with
the second volume of my novel.
Once it sells, we'll have cash
to work with again.
But Dad...
That's final.
Remember to pay that electric bill.
The kids need their lights back on.
Yes.
Hmm.
"The End."
Whew.
Save, give me a hand.
Yeah, Dad?
Take Grandpa to the publisher.
What? Right now?
Of course.
What?
Gas money.
Hmm.
Hmm...
Uh-mmm.
Huh?
Hmm. That's final.
Dad, this is a car, not a motorbike.
Well, just drive it easy then.
Easy how?
Look it up online.
Isn't that what you always say?
Huh.
How to save on gas.
Sure thing.
Here are the simple ways.
Start by driving smoothly.
Avoid hitting the gas too hard.
On top of that, keeping up with
regular maintenance,
like proper tire pressure
and regular air filter changes
can really save some gas.
Oy...how much is that gonna save?
Ahem.
Well. Do you have enough cash?
Yes, sir. Wait by the car.
I'll grab the keys first.
Sure.
Hmm.
Scoot in a bit
or the sun will dry you out.
I'll get going now.
Hmm...
Heh...fun, wasn't it?
Well...
See? I still got it.
And I hadn't written in ages.
The craft never left me.
Haha.
Being a writer is in my blood.
Cut me open,
I bleed words.
Your father knew that.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Sorry to say this.
But... Saming the Slayer, Volume 1,
that my father published in '97,
out of kindness,
was...
uhm...
Seeing you today
actually reminded me
of unsold stock in the warehouse.
I had someone bring it over
to donate it.
Oh, doing some good then.
Wonderful. I rejoice in your merit.
Yeah. And here...
Saming the Slayer from '97.
Why? I don't see anything strange.
Any novel, no matter who writes it,
has a few copies come back unsold.
Perfectly normal.
Hehe.
Yes.
Um...sir.
Here's the thing. All of this.
These are all yours.
What?
That can't be right.
It is, sir.
It...can't be.
"Palang Publishing"
"Guy: Whatchu up to?"
"Save: An errand with Grandpa."
"Guy: Where to after?"
"Save: Not sure. Probably home."
"Guy: I want to see you. Can we?"
I understand that...
Volume 1 may not have
hit its sales target.
But there are people out there
asking for Volume 2.
Who, exactly?
Um...
Pull up a website for me.
Someone mentioned
a site about novels.
There. Right there.
Search for my pen name,
Harn Chanprai.
Okay.
See?
Missing earth's scent, jungle hush,
the grip of danger in Harn's novels.
Anyone else waiting
for Saming the Slayer Volume 2?
Next comment. Been waiting
nearly 30 years to read it.
No one rivals Harn Chanprai.
I want to go back into that forest
one more time.
I need to know if
that Saming (were-tiger)
is truly finished.
You see?
I didn't want
to let these fans down.
So I pushed myself
to finish Volume 2.
But sir, there are only 12 comments.
Sir, I genuinely cannot
publish this for you.
I'm being honest with you.
My publishing house is
barely staying afloat.
Phuri, I need this to sell.
I need the money.
I'm afraid...you'll need to
write something the market wants.
It might be worth looking into
what people are reading these days.
"Save: You okay?"
"Guy: Something important
to talk to you today."
"Save: Just say it then."
Save, take me to a bookstore.
Hmm. Which one?
Whichever one people go to
these days.
All right.
No need. I can walk myself.
Hmph. Show-off, huh?
You fall and no one's gonna feel
sorry for you.
"Save: Going to a bookstore at Siam.
Just say what you gotta say."
"Guy: I'm at Siam too.
Come find me. Same spot."
What's with him?
Grandpa...
Stay inside the store.
Don't go anywhere.
I go see a friend. Be right back.
Mm-hmm.
I'm over here.
Guy, what's on your mind?
Been holding back since yesterday.
We're friends.
You can tell me anything.
My Close Friends account,
you asked who's in it.
It's only you.
So what? Just add other people.
No. I only want you in it.
So cute.
- Hey, let me see.
- Here.
I mean I only want you
to see what I post.
Why?
You still don't get it?
What is it? Just say it.
I've been sitting on this
for a long time.
After I say this, I don't know
if anything will be the same.
But...
Save, I like you.
"Until the Time is Right"
Hey.
If we can't hold on,
better sell the orphanage.
I won't. I'm going to write
a Boys' Love novel.
Make enough to clear the debt.
Grandpa, you don't have to hide it.
I already know.
You think your BL novel
will save this house?
Of course.
Guy, how about we give this a try?
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
Let us be real,
not dreaming away,
We'll walk in the light
of a new day.
No one can tell
what tomorrow may say.
Wherever the gentle wind blows,
let our hearts flow,
soft and slow.
And land where
our hearts both grow.
The world keeps
turning every day.
And we keep
turning in its play.
Just open up, we'll learn it in.
We just might see
the world within.
Let's walk together,
day by day.
Come take the step,
what do you say?
MkvDrama.net