( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[Episode 6]
He saved me.
I thought
he only wanted a test of skill.
So I didn't see the need to expose him.
I didn't expect him to steal the official seal.
He lost his nerve. Right at the end.
He thought he couldn't defeat you,
so he ran away in a hurry.
Let's go to Xiankong Island.
Now? It's like walking into a trap.
That's those rats' nest.
He has so many brothers there.
Maybe, this is their idea to trick you there.
If word gets out that Lord Bao's official seal
is lost,
certain will seize the chance to make trouble.
Even if I'm walking into a trap,
I must go there.
This place is really nice.
The water is clearer,
and the breeze is gentle.
My Lord, are we almost at Xiankong Island?
Yes.
Ahead of us is a field of reeds.
Xiankong Island is to the south.
Are you really going to Xiankong Island?
Yes.
I hear the island has fine views.
I want to take a look.
Don't do that.
On Xiankong Island,
there's the Five Rats' private estate.
Not a pleasure garden for idle sightseers.
The Five Rats?
Are they also known as the Five Justices?
Their leader
is Lu Fang, known as Zuantian Rat.
Exactly true.
People say the Five Justices are chivalrous
and love to make friends.
I doubt they'd refuse us a visit.
Usually,
if you talk to them nicely, it might work.
But it definitely won't work these days.
A few days ago,
I took a fruit merchant there.
He was kicked out as soon as he landed.
Lately, the docks on Xiankong Island
have been guarded.
No one is allowed to enter.
Maybe
that Jinmao Rat
got into some trouble again
and is hiding on the island.
So,
Bai Yu Tang doesn't seem to be well spoken of.
The first four of the Five Rats
are quite reasonable.
But this one,
Bai Yu Tang the Jinmao Rat,
has a strange personality.
You won't get far reasoning with him.
I heard that not long ago,
a young man was beaten by Bai Yu Tang,
simply for being better looking than him.
While beating him, Bai Yu Tang said,
"If I see you appearing around here again,
I'll ruin your face.
Best stop calling yourself handsome.
All that 'everyone loves me' is just a laugh."
Look at you.
Once you're on the island,
you'll probably get beaten up too.
A rat beating up a cat?
That's a first for me.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Still don't believe me?
I've warned you.
Go ahead if you want.
If
you truly anger Bai Yu Tang,
go to Mohua Village in Songjiang Prefecture.
Seek out Chief Ding.
His family is
on good terms with Xiankong Island.
Perhaps he can put in a good word for you.
In that case,
let's head to the Ding's first.
All right.
I heard you say earlier
that you lived in Songjiang for a while.
Don't tell me you're staying at the Ding's.
That's true.
I learned Heavenward Crane Strike
from Uncle Ding.
So,
the rumors are true?
What rumors?
That you are the Ding family's
recognized son-in-law.
And that's why Ding taught you
Heavenward Crane Strike.
How can you believe such gossip?
Our families have been friends for generations.
Uncle Ding told me that the Zhan family
once did the Ding family a favor.
So he taught me Heavenward Crane Strike
to fulfill his wish of repaying that debt.
That's how it is.
My Lord, don't you worry.
I'll do everything to put this rumor to rest.
Soon you'll be back at the top of the list
ladies in the capital most want to marry.
What list?
Forget it.
But must be careful.
Such romantic rumors
always break a young lady's heart.
It affects your ranking.
Stay away from those rumors.
Just maintain your good image.
After all, being a hero isn't easy.
You know quite a lot about how to be a hero.
Of course.
Take my word for it.
[Ding Zhao Hui, one of the Ding Twins]
Zhan!
What brings you here?
Why didn't you tell us you were coming?
I decided on the spur of the moment.
Are you heading out?
Yes. I heard Shen Zhong Yuan
is holding a gathering at his estate.
Such a big event, I have to see it.
You haven't changed at all.
Ming Zhu Er.
This is Ding Zhao Hui, one of the Ding Twins.
And this is Ming Zhu Er.
So you're the real Ding. The second brother.
The real Ding?
What do you mean?
Is someone pretending to be me?
It's a long story.
Zhao Hui.
I came all this way
to ask the Ding family for help with something.
So that's what happened.
Pretending to be me? That I can forgive.
But taking the seal? How stupid.
When the imperial court investigates,
the Five Rats will share the blame.
I have long heard of
the Five Justices of Xiankong Island.
I respect them greatly.
Though I haven't known Bai Yu Tang for long,
I know he is a chivalrous man.
That's why I'd rather not let this escalate.
I only wish to persuade him
to return the official seal
and explain to Lord Bao.
Then the matter can be settled.
My Lord, isn't that letting him off too easily?
The boatman said earlier
that he hits people just because
he's jealous of their looks.
Look, he even kicked me for no reason.
What kind of chivalrous man is he?
Don't believe those rumors.
Bai Yu Tang beat up Hua Chong,
nicknamed "Flower Butterfly".
That man harassed the Guo family's daughter.
Bai Yu Tang only acted to right a wrong.
He just didn't expect
that Hua Chong refused to admit fault.
He distorted the truth
and slandered Bai Yu Tang.
The Guo family
feared gossip about the girl.
So they didn't clarify anything.
The rumors twisted and grew worse with telling.
I see.
Zhan.
You said you needed help from the Ding family.
Do you mean going to Xiankong Island?
Exactly.
I heard that the island has been closed.
No visitors are allowed.
I have just arrived.
I'm afraid it wouldn't be proper
to barge onto the island.
So I'd like to ask the Ding family
to handle this for me.
No need to put yourself out if it's hard.
No, no, no.
Zhan, the Ding family will definitely help you.
Why don't we go there right now?
Zhao Hui.
It's getting a bit late
to be setting out for the island now.
How about this? Keep your things.
I'll go check on Zhao Lan and Yue Hua.
That sounds better.
Ding Zhao Hui didn't seem the least bit angry,
not even after that white rat stole his name.
Instead, he helped clean up the mess.
It seems
they have a good relationship.
Those two must share the same nature.
Both martial arts fanatics.
Bai Yu Tang went to the capital
and stole the official seal,
just to test his skill against mine.
When Zhao Hui was young,
to compete with Yue Hua over
who could learn Heavenward Crane Strike,
he locked himself in his room
and didn't eat for three days
just to learn the mental techniques.
So, who won? He or Lady Ding?
The hardest part of Heavenward Crane Strike
is the circulation of inner energy.
The more impatient you are, the harder it is.
But Zhao Hui and Yue Hua
are both impatient.
So the one who finally mastered it
was actually Zhao Lan, their eldest brother,
who is calm-minded.
I heard from the storytellers in Bianjing city
that the Ding Twins
look exactly alike.
My Lord, is that true?
It is indeed.
They are a pair of twins.
The only difference between them is
that Zhao Lan has a mole between his eyebrows.
[The Ding family]
Lord Zhan.
Old Ding, it has been a long time.
How is your health?
All is well, all is well.
Lord Zhan,
it's been a long time since you last came.
Our young master will be delighted
to lay eyes on you.
Please come in.
Look who's here!
Zhan.
Zhan, what brings you here?
For official business around.
I stopped by to see you and Yue Hua.
If you had arrived a bit earlier,
you would have seen Zhao Hui.
He just left not long ago.
I ran into him on the road.
Is that so? What a coincidence.
Where is Yue Hua?
I recall that no one is permitted
to touch these camellias
save for Yue Hua and that little maid.
That little maid went back home for marriage.
Yue Hua has fallen ill,
and can no longer tend to these flowers.
What illness? Is it serious?
Take your time.
Let's get inside and talk it through. This way.
Zhao Lan, what illness does Yue Hua have?
Is it truly not serious?
It's not serious.
Just dizziness and a fever this morning.
She has taken medicine
and is resting in her room now.
It's not serious.
She's grown now.
Her chambers are off limits to men now.
I'm afraid you two
won't be able to meet this time.
By the way,
you mentioned earlier
that you are here on official business.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I had a misunderstanding with Bai Yu Tang.
I want to go to the island to clear things up.
But I heard that Xiankong Island
is closed to outsiders these few days.
It might be unwise for me
to set foot on the island uninvited.
So may you write a letter
to Chief Lu
and explain my purpose for coming?
Easy. Don't worry.
I'll have the letter ready tonight.
Zhao Lan, in a little while,
I'd like to go to Tingfeng Pavilion
to pay my respects to Uncle Ding.
Okay.
Zhan, you go ahead.
I'll go check on the meal.
We haven't had guests for a long time.
They might slip.
[Virtue Casts a Long Light.]
It's decorated with such exquisite taste.
Doesn't feel like a wanderer's den,
but more like a scholar's study.
Besides practicing martial arts,
during his lifetime, Uncle Ding was
also quite knowledgeable
in calligraphy, painting, and chess.
Back then,
he taught us martial arts by day.
And at night,
he would take us to Tingfeng Pavilion
to practice calligraphy and play chess.
I remember Uncle Ding
once told me while we played chess
that blind courage alone
is not enough to master martial arts.
A battle in martial arts
is just like a game on a chessboard.
One must remain objective and steady.
Only then
can you discern your opponent's intent
and know how to counter and defeat them.
At that time,
I didn't understand his meaning.
I only remember that as we played,
the wind blew through the bamboo forest.
The sound
was truly nice.
No wonder it's called Tingfeng Pavilion.
Let me listen to it too.
My Lord,
I can't hear anything at all.
Is it because there's no wind outside?
Lord Zhan,
dinner is ready. Please follow me.
When we were young,
after father taught you
the Heavenward Crane Strike,
my younger brother often teased you about it.
Later, father told us
that the Zhan family
once saved the Ding family.
Teaching you the Heavenward Crane Strike
couldn't repay even a fraction of it.
I toast to you this time.
Our Ding family
will never forget the Zhan family's kindness.
Zhao Lan, you're being too formal.
There's no need for such talk between us.
I'm sorry, Brother Ding.
I really couldn't help myself.
I'm just too hungry.
It's fine. Eat anything you want.
Zhao Lan,
is Yue Hua feeling any better?
Much better. Ying Jie just checked on her.
She's asleep.
She has always been very healthy.
It's rare to see her so ill
that she can't even leave her room.
You know Yue Hua. She's very stubborn.
She started feeling unwell a few days ago,
but she insisted on not seeing a physician.
Now look what happened.
Her treatment was delayed.
That's why it has
become quite serious now.
Brother Ding,
didn't you say earlier
that Lady Ding only started having
a fever and dizziness this morning?
How did it become a "a few days ago"
thing?
Really? I must have misspoken then.
Let's not talk about that.
Here, Zhan.
Your official business is more important.
I'll finish writing the letter tonight.
Chief Lu never shields faults.
And Chief Han was a soldier.
They know
the gravity of stealing an official seal.
Bai Yu Tang will listen to the words
of his elder brothers.
Thank you. Zhao Lan.
You're among family here. No ceremony.
Here.
My Lord.
Do you think there's something
strange about the Ding family?
Smart guy.
What did you notice?
I didn't notice anything wrong
with the Ding family.
But I noticed something wrong with you.
You've been preoccupied since dinner.
You must think there's something strange
about the Ding family.
I feel that
Zhao Lan is hiding something from me.
Every family has secrets
they'd rather keep to themselves.
My Lord, you should just focus
on catching your "rat."
It's fine to worry less about other matters.
Oh no. I ate too much for dinner.
I need to go relieve myself.
My Lord!
- What's wrong?
- My Lord.
This Ding family
is indeed a bit strange.
I stepped out of the privy,
and ran into Ying Jie, whom we saw earlier.
In her basket, paper money and candles.
The sort for the dead.
What illness does Yue Hua have?
It's nothing serious.
Just dizziness and a fever this morning.
She has taken medicine
and is resting in her room now.
My Lord.
My Lord, wait for me! My Lord!
My Lord,
this place is too creepy.
Let's go back to our rooms.
Which way did Ying Jie go?
To the backyard.
My Lord,
can we wait till dawn?
An ice coffin?
Who died?
I didn't see anyone
wearing mourning clothes here.
My Lord, it's too scary here.
Let's go back first.
If you want to know what's strange about here,
why not just ask Ding Zhao Lan directly?
He's intent on hiding it from me.
Even if I ask,
he won't tell me the truth.
If you're scared,
go back up first.
No. No.
The Ding family is truly bizarre.
I'd feel safer staying with you, My Lord.
Hold the light.
My Lord, what are you doing?
The elders say it's bad luck
to open a coffin at night.
Lady Ding, please don't blame us.
We didn't mean to do this.
You're praying to the wrong person.
This isn't Yue Hua.
This is Yue Hua's maid,
Xiao Yun.
So why did Brother Ding say
she went back home for marriage?
That wound...
She did it to herself.
How did Xiao Yun die?
Why is she in an ice coffin?
I went to Yue Hua's room just now.
She wasn't in there at all.
Her table was covered in dust,
as if no one had lived there for a long time.
Zhan.
Regarding Yue Hua,
I did lie to you.
Please, have a seat.
I'll explain everything to you.
Ding Zhao Lan, how did you know
Zhan Zhao would come,
and have the house prepared for him in advance?
Because the person before us
isn't Zhao Lan at all.
It's Zhao Hui. We saw him at the pier.
He used his lightness skill
and got back home before us.
What are you saying?
I am Zhao Lan.
There's a messenger at our gate.
That's why I...
Zhan.
Zhan, listen to me. Zhao Hui went out.
I'll call him back now.
Zhan.
Zhan!
Step aside.
[Ding Zhao Lan, one of the Ding Twins]
Oh, my.
Every time I tried to act as my elder brother,
you always saw through me.
I should have known
that growing up wouldn't change it.
When did you notice?
During dinner.
You stopped me
from asking further about Yue Hua,
but your way of saying
Bai Yu Tang stole the official seal.
I only said it at the pier.
Zhao Hui,
what exactly happened to the Ding family?
My brother...
He's been in a coma
from serious injuries for a year.
A year ago,
Uncle Ding passed away suddenly.
Zhao Hui,
is there something about Uncle Ding's death
that's been kept from us?
Zhan,
nothing can be hidden from you.
The cuts in the bamboo forest
at Tingfeng Pavilion are very clean.
It wasn't from normal trimming,
but rather from a fight.
The new leaf buds have been out for some days.
The fight must have happened
when Uncle Ding passed away.
A year ago,
when you came for my father's funeral,
we lied to you.
My father didn't die of a sudden illness.
He was killed by the Zhanlu Sword.
My father's body
was brought back by the leader
of the Shangqing Sect,
Jing Yi Ming.
Uncle Jing.
Who did this cruel thing to my father?
Our Ding siblings
will make him pay.
[Ding Yue Hua, from the Ding family]
He was there for my birthday.
After staying at my manor for a few days,
[Jing Yi Ming, Head of the Shangqing Sect]
he bid me farewell and set off alone.
No one saw
who he fought with.
By the time I got the news and arrived,
I only saw his body.
I checked his wound.
It was clearly caused by the Zhanlu Sword.
But that sword
is now nowhere to be found.
I'm afraid the villain killed him
just to seize that precious sword.
Few in all the realm
could break Heavenward Crane Strike,
and snatch the Zhanlu Sword from my father.
Even if I have to scour every corner,
I will find this person.
The Ding siblings will make him pay.
Brother Zhao Hui.
I'm going with you.
Enough.
The most important thing now
is to arrange Father's funeral.
Uncle Jing,
thank you for your effort
in escorting my father's body
all the way back.
After the funeral ended,
to express our gratitude to Jing Yi Ming,
we invited him to stay for a few more days,
but never expected...
Lady!
Lady.
Look who's back.
Xiao Yun!
Didn't you go home to get married?
How did you end up like this?
Lady.
Jing Yi Ming!
Yue Hua, are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Xiao Yun told me
that Jing Yi Ming raped her,
and threw her into a brothel!
Absurd!
This is nonsense.
I would never do such a despicable thing.
Yue Hua,
is it possible Xiao Yun mistook him?
How could Uncle Jing...
You believe him just because he's a master?
Yue Hua,
don't be rash.
Uncle Jing's Shangqing Sect
is far away in Xiangzhou.
Xiao Yun had always been here
then returned to her hometown.
They shouldn't even know each other.
Don't forget,
the day before Xiao Yun left here,
Jing Yi Ming was here too.
The next day, when she bid father
farewell, Jing Yi Ming was also present.
He intercepted Xiao Yun after she left here.
Utter nonsense!
Where is that girl?
Bring her here.
Let her face me!
Your scandalous deeds are exposed,
yet you still dare to bluster!
Yue Hua!
You don't believe me?
Yue Hua.
Until there is solid evidence,
you must not act rashly.
Lady,
I'm afraid you'll fight him.
Let's... let's go.
Forget it.
Stay right here!
Let her make things clear
before she leaves.
Young lady,
you are young and inexperienced.
Now talking nonsense. I don't blame you.
But the Shangqing Sect
has a century-old reputation.
No one dares to slander it.
My decades of friendship with the Ding family
cannot be ruined too.
Today, before the Ding descendants,
say it once more.
Did I, or did I not,
commit those indecent acts against you?
If not, clear my name.
If I did,
they would never forgive me.
They would surely risk their lives
to seek justice for you.
Tell us.
Did I,
or did I not?
No.
I mistook him for someone else.
Xiao Yun!
Everyone said
Xiao Yun was ashamed to face anyone,
and killed herself
because her virtue was shattered.
But Yue Hua said
Xiao Yun had promised her the night
before that she wouldn't kill herself.
She was certain
Xiao Yun was killed by Jing Yi Ming.
That same day, Jing Yi Ming
went to bid my brother farewell.
He said he didn't want to cause
any more trouble between us.
When Yue Hua heard about it,
she took her sword
and rushed to Tingfeng Pavilion.
Zhao Lan!
It wasn't me.
He was fighting with Zhao Lan.
He pushed Zhao Lan onto my sword.
It wasn't me!
How could a family like Ding
ever produce a daughter like you?
You came here with a sword.
Zhao Lan was afraid you would hurt me.
That's why he stepped in.
No matter how angry you are,
you shouldn't have done this to him.
- You...
- Yue Hua!
Stop it!
Yue Hua left after that,
and she never came back.
Actually, my brother's sword wound
wasn't that serious that day.
His physical wounds
have been healing day by day.
But for some reason, he remains unconscious.
To this day, I still don't understand
what really happened that day.
I asked the butler later.
Before Jing Yi Ming bid my brother farewell,
my brother had just checked Xiao Yun's body.
My guess is that
my brother found something suspicious,
so he took a look at Xiao Yun's body.
But I don't think he ever found anything.
If someone slits their own wrist,
the force came from outside in,
and the cut runs deep above, shallow below.
But Xiao Yun's wound
was exactly the opposite.
So,
Xiao Yun was murdered.
Besides,
even if Yue Hua didn't mean it,
she couldn't have damaged Zhao Lan's meridians.
Only severed meridians
would leave him unconscious.
Yue Hua's skill is nowhere near that level.
Unless
Zhao Lan's Heavenward Crane Strike was broken.
The power he gathered never left him
when preparing Heavenward Crane Strike.
Instead, it tore through his body
crashing into his own meridians.
As you said,
before Jing went to bid Zhao Lan farewell,
Zhao Lan had just checked Xiao Yun's body.
Zhao Lan is very thorough.
He must have discovered
that Xiao Yun didn't commit suicide.
Stay back! Stay back!
- Stay back!
- No need to fear.
I'm here to set you free.
If you tell the truth,
not only will you shatter your virtue,
but you'll also drag the Ding family down.
Why bother?
You might as well
leave yourself some dignity.
Zhao Hui.
You've already done very well.
What have I done?
I even helped Jing Yi Ming.
I let him destroy the Ding family
right in front of me.
No one knows the Ding's eldest son is in a coma
from a serious injury.
That's because of you.
You pretend to be Zhao Lan in public,
which is how you fooled everyone.
Everyone covets
our Heavenward Crane Strike and Zhanlu Sword.
The chief of the Ding family has passed.
If word got out that the eldest son
was also in a coma,
the Ding family's situation
would be worse than we imagined.
Before today,
I thought you
were still that reckless and impulsive boy.
I didn't expect that overnight,
you would shoulder the family burden.
No matter what I do now,
I can't make it up to Yue Hua and Xiao Yun.
Since Yue Hua ran away from home,
she hasn't returned once.
She must hate me to death.
I really want to explain to her.
When I blocked her sword that day,
it wasn't because I believed Jing Yi Ming.
She is no match for Jing Yi Ming.
You were afraid she would get hurt.
Don't worry. Once Yue Hua calms down,
she will understand.
Xiao Yun's death was suspicious.
My brother is in a coma,
and Yue Hua is missing.
No one could confront Jing Yi Ming
about what he had done.
I had to store Xiao Yun's body
in an ice coffin.
I wanted to wait until we found Yue Hua
and we could investigate everything.
I wanted to see if we could find
any clues from Xiao Yun's body,
so we could expose it and get her justice.
Today is the anniversary of her death.
I asked her close friend, Ying Jie,
to pay her respects.
I didn't expect you to notice, Zhan.
Zhan,
you've only been here half a day
and you've already seen the truth.
Clearly,
I was too clumsy.
I could see it
because Jing Yi Ming, that grandmaster,
made me suspicious.
In Xiangzhou,
I was ambushed by Zhi Hua the Black Fox.
The moves he used
were the Great Compassion Palm
from the Shangqing Sect.
The Great Compassion Palm is only
passed on to Shangqing Sect disciples.
How did Zhi Hua learn this secret technique?
Is there more
between Zhi Hua and the Shangqing Sect
than we've been told?
About this affair.
About your father's death.
I won't rest until I've uncovered everything.
From the look of it now,
Jing Yi Ming must be the one
who killed my father.
If Jing Yi Ming really can break
Heavenward Crane Strike,
then the murderer
is very likely to be him.
What a so-called grandmaster.
I'm going to storm the Shangqing Sect
and end him with my sword!
Zhan,
I know what you want to say.
Don't worry.
I won't rush into anything.
With my current skills,
seeking revenge on Jing Yi Ming
would be like throwing an egg against a stone.
But one day,
the Ding family will make him
pay for it in blood.
Zhao Hui,
there is something I'm curious about.
Chief Lu and the other three
are of similar age and share the same ideals,
which is why they became sworn brothers.
But why did Bai Yu Tang,
at such a young age, join them?
I heard it's because Bai Yu Tang
helped Chief Lu avenge his father's death.
Chief Lu's father
was generous and charitable.
But his wealth became known,
and a band of outlaws robbed and killed him.
The authorities failed to find them for days,
but Bai Yu Tang used a clever scheme
to lure them into a trap.
Only then was Chief Lu
able to hand the bandits over to the law.
Thus, the two became sworn brothers.
From childhood, Bai Yu Tang was skilled,
chivalrous, and righteous.
Truly remarkable.
We're almost there.
Ming Zhu Er, stay here.
Lord Zhan.
Leave Ming Zhu Er with me.
Don't worry.
My Lord, old Ding and I won't go anywhere.
You two must also be careful.
Madam!
Zhen Er!
- Did you find them?
- No.
Where did everyone go?
Madam must have seen Number Five​ going crazy
and taken everyone into hiding.
[Lu Fang, Zuantian Rat][Han Zhang, Chedi Rat]
Let's keep looking.
- Brother Lu, Brother Han!
- Zhao Hui, why did you come here?
Go now! Don't throw your life away!
Chief Lu, I'm Zhan Zhao of Kaifeng Prefecture.
What has happened on the island?
Zhan Zhao?
Even you came?
Lord Bao's official seal
was stolen by Bai Yu Tang.
I'm here to persuade him to return it.
Number Five must have lost his mind.
He ignored the Chief's advice.
Went to the capital
just to fight the Imperial Cat.
Now brought the authorities here,
and caused such trouble on Xiankong Island.
Bai Yu Tang really killed those people outside?
- I...
- Bai Yu Tang won't kill the innocent.
Could there be some misunderstanding?
Zhan Zhao,
you are finally here.
Brothers, Zhan Zhao wants to kill me!
You can't watch me die right in front of you.
Brothers,
you just said Bai Yu Tang was absurd.
Why are you listening to him now?
If anyone got mad, it was those two.
Not Bai Yu Tang.
They seem to have been poisoned.
Don't move.
You've stepped on a fire mine.
Han Zhang has a military background.
While in the army,
he became an expert in gunpowder.
What are you waiting for?
Kill them!
You! Help him.
Make sure to kill them both.
[Jiang Ping, Fanjiang Rat]
[Xu Qing, Chuanshan Rat]
Big Brother!