( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
《Yulin Bell》
Those who can enter and exit this secret passage
Only He Bo and his dead soldiers
Where does this secret passage lead to?
The danger is unknown
Have you really thought about it?
Zhan Zhao once again thanked Zhangyueshi
Help
After I go in
Just leave as soon as possible
To prevent you from getting involved with Hanshui Palace
Brother Zhan
Be careful
- See He Bo - See He Bo
Get up
Haven't those people from the Yunying Sect succeeded yet?
Report to Hebo, they have returned
Tangmen and Shengyun Village
Fighting for Chang Hongbi
I thought
It's because of the years of resentment between the two factions.
turn out to be
Tang Clan was assigned by you
He Bo
You give orders to your men
Challenge each major sect one by one
All the leaders of various factions who are unwilling to be driven by you
All died by your hands
You are so deliberate
For that
Dominate the world
Since Master Jiao knows those things
The fate of stubborn people
You should understand
I'll spare your life
It's already very merciful
you
Since I dare to dream of the great dream of unifying the world,
why
Don't you dare show your true colors to others?
Jing Yiming
I heard that Master Jiao studied this sword technique
Takes several years
But I can break this sword technique
But it only took seven days
It seems that a generation of famous chateaus is in your generation.
I'm afraid it's going to decline
Stop talking nonsense
If you want to kill, then kill
Master Jiao is also a famous martial artist
Wouldn't it be a pity to kill him like this?
The birthday banquet is about to be held
I'll give you two ways
one
You will take the lead in lobbying those old people
Make them willing to join me
Two, just like them
like the walking dead
Those old stubborns who won’t surrender
Solve them one by one
How to choose between the two roads
It's all up to you
Lord Jiao
What if I don’t choose either?
you
What can you do to me?
It seems that Master Jiao has made his choice
Once you take this night sky
There is no turning back
When this poison enters the body, it will merge into the heart
invade sanity
Give you frequent illusions
From now on you can only listen to the ringtone
Even if you are asked to cut off your own meridians, you will not hesitate
This medicine is also wonderful
Its antidote is the poison itself
Only by taking this night sky again
To suppress the illusion
But doing so is tantamount to drinking poison to quench thirst
The poisoned person will become more and more stupid
A few days ago, he went to the island dressed as me.
Tricked my eldest brother and second brother into drinking poison
That poison won't kill you
But it will make people lose their minds and cause hallucinations
Where did you hide the Yicheng County Magistrate?
Are you determined to do things for Zhihua?
Bai Yutang
Don't do anything you can't look back on
Then I'll find it myself
don't talk
Jiao Chaoki
You need to think clearly
First generation owner
I really want to fall behind
An undignified end?
Zhan Zhao
I know the purpose of your trip
You did it to save her
We have heard that Nan Xia’s martial arts are unparalleled.
I'd like to try it
If you can defeat me today
people
You can take it away
Zhan Zhao
Your sword master is inherited from the swordsman Xia Yuqi
His swordsmanship is unparalleled in the martial arts world
It's a pity that there are still a few flaws
He Bo
You and I have decided the winner in sword moves.
Still better?
Zhan Zhao
My dragon chanting sword technique
How does it make it?
Even if you have stolen the skills from so many famous schools
Even if I’m afraid, I know it’s true
Don't know why
Do you think you can dominate the martial arts world like this?
How ridiculous
What kind of kung fu are you doing?
It’s my Zhanjia’s skill
Jing Yiming
Don’t you need to return to your own martial arts?
Heroes emerge in large numbers all over the world
Everyone has their own tricks
Even if you spend ten lifetimes
Nor can we take advantage of each school’s unique skills
All stolen into his own hands
Everyone, kill Zhan Zhao
Zhan Lujian
Why don't you quickly search it inside and out?
yes
- Let's go over there and have a look. - Okay
Brother Zhan, come with me
This way
Miss Huo
Is there any news about Brother Zhan?
He entered the secret passage and has not come out yet
I was afraid that you would be worried, so I came out to tell you.
How long have you been in there?
no
Don't go. Brother Zhan won't let you act rashly.
I'm afraid he's in danger
That's it
The time of a stick of incense
If he doesn't come out
I'll go with you to save him
Brother Zhan
How did you come from here?
Was that the Moon Palmist just now?
yes
Where are people?
Come on, let's go back first
Zhaohui, we have determined
Jing Yiming has been relying on running Zhongxiao Academy
Come to win over officials for King Xiangyang
Win over people in the world
He committed
It is a serious crime to subvert the imperial court
I'm coming this time
Just to catch him and bring him to justice
Show up at Jing's house tonight
We are also looking for witnesses and physical evidence.
I see
I live in Jing's house
In addition to wanting to take advantage of the birthday party to investigate
Really worried too
Yuehua will be at this time
Come to seek revenge from Jing Yiming
By the way, Brother Zhan
It’s been a few days since I stayed at Jing’s house.
some clues
I don’t know if it will be helpful to your investigation.
you say
Moved into Jing's house by myself
Jing Yiming sent people to guard a small courtyard day and night.
Whenever I'm near that yard
I can always smell a faint medicinal fragrance nearby.
how? Look at your appearance
It seems like he knows who is locked up inside.
Know
But this matter
It has little to do with your case.
What about us?
I won’t go into details.
Zhaohui
Except for the small courtyard
Is there anything suspicious in the Jing family?
have
That day I saw Jing Yiming
He took a girl with wounds all over her body into the bedroom.
This reminds me of what happened with Xiaoyun before
So I paid attention
That night I saw Jing Yiming going out
So I went to investigate.
These beasts
Thank you ma'am
I'm just applying medicine for you
lady
Although I usually
They were all locked up in that secret room
but also know
You and he are not the same person
I can often hear it
you argue with him
You will always be there for those who died at his hands
chanting sutras, burning paper
Advise him to stop
Even if he beats you for it
You never stopped
Yulian asks for his wife
Prepare a pot of poisonous wine for me
I want to kill him with my own hands
Revenge for my brother
You
Give up this idea as soon as possible
once failed
Desperately suspicious
even death
I must try it too
Let me tell you the truth
You're not the first person he's locked up
these years
i see too much
The girls who risked their lives to take his life
But in the end
It’s not just a roll of straw mat
thrown into mass grave
All lives are gone
What else are you talking about about revenge?
The time has not come yet
what you can do now
Just wait
master
I'm afraid you'll have scars
Then I asked her to apply medicine on you
You don't know why you want to kill me
release
Not the time yet?
You should talk about it
When will the time come?
ten years
You've made enough mistakes in the past ten years
Let Yulian go
Stop doing evil
Otherwise you will definitely suffer retribution
retribution?
If there is retribution, I ordered Su Yizhou ten years ago
Instigate your Bawangzhuang to fight with the Linyuan faction.
When Bawangzhuang’s entire family was slaughtered
I deserve to be punished by heaven
But now
Am I still standing here fine?
Please take it easy
I will definitely find someone to heal you properly
It was really inconvenient for me to save Mrs. Jing at that time.
And that girl named Yulian
I think
Now that he knows that she is locked up in the Jing family's secret room,
In the future, I will definitely have a chance to rescue her.
So this jade lotus
He is the witness who has seen He Bo’s true face.
It turns out that there was a fight between Bawangzhuang and Linyuan sect back then.
It came from Jing Yiming's hand
Looking at it this way, his conspiracy started as early as ten years ago
Then say so
Mrs. Jing must also know many things.
She can also be a witness
So far
Finally got a clue
Zhaohui
There's something I can't hide from you
I'm in a secret room
I saw Zhan Lujian
Jing Yiming
He should have fought against Uncle Ding
It was really Jing Yiming who killed my father
Not just Uncle Ding
I want to see the various weapons displayed in that secret room
behind every
There is a human life hidden in them all
Jing Yiming also wanted to take advantage of the birthday party
Intimidating various sects to be loyal to King Xiangyang
It's too dangerous for you to be in the Jing family
It's better to find a way to withdraw quickly.
No, Brother Zhan
I must stay at Jing's house
Firstly, I am here for the moonlight
Second
Since you are investigating the Jing family's case
There is someone staying at the Jing family
I can help you find clues
Zhaohui
Be careful when you return to the Jing family
anything wrong
Find a way to get out quickly
Don't worry, Brother Zhan
traces of moonlight
I will pay more attention
There is news
Notify you as soon as possible
good
farewell
No wonder Brother Ding
Even if you risk your life, you have to stay in the Jing family.
And he can still think of handing the person back to the government
It's really admirable
if it were me
I bear a blood feud
You must kill that enemy with your own hands.
What I'm afraid of is
Yuehua wants to leave
This is the road you mentioned
Miss Huo
You once said when you and I first met
Do you know the young master of the Tang clan?
I wonder how your relationship is?
We've known each other since we were kids and are best friends
Since they are close friends
It must be the same as you
I have a chivalrous heart.
Of course
He has a pure nature
And I will never participate in the Tang Sect’s dirty deeds.
Brother Zhan
Why are you asking about him suddenly?
I want to ask him a favor
Bai Yutang is so abnormal
It's because he learned that the poison of his two sworn brothers has not been cured yet
Think about it
It is wisdom that threatens the antidote
Bai Yutang had to do something against his will
But tonight
Jing Yiming said
There is no antidote for Ye Motian
So brother Zhan, what do you mean?
Do you want Xiao Tang to help prepare the antidote?
All I can do now is give it a try.
no problem
Tangmen's headquarters is within the jurisdiction of Xiangyang
I'll go find him tomorrow
Xiao Tang has always done research on these poisons
I think it might help
Then thank him very much
What a smart person
How dare you tease Brother Bai like this?
When it's done, I'll definitely deal with him properly
And this white mouse
This white mouse is also extremely hateful
Don't tell us such a big thing
They simply don’t consider us friends
If it weren't for Brother Zhan, you would have discovered the clues
Wouldn't that delay the two sworn brothers?
And I fell for that intellectual alienation scheme in vain.
Before cleaning up the intelligence
You and I should take care of the white mice first
you're right
But we
Don’t rush to teach this white mouse a lesson.
urgent matter
It is to rescue Yulian before the birthday banquet
Let Yulian testify against He Bo
clear
In this way, we can avoid the Hongmen Banquet.
If Brother Bai doesn't find the county magistrate,
Will definitely come back to us again
He will definitely look angry again by then
His mouth is like...
Sharper than this knife
Stab straight into the heart of the heart
Then let's prepare a fish for him
Stop his mouth that wants to curse again
It's strange to say
You two are just the opposite
Your cat doesn’t like fish
He is a mouse
On the contrary, there is no fish and no joy every day
Not talking about Zhongxiao Academy
Have additional guards been posted?
How did Zhan Zhao get in?
Intellectualization, guarding matters
Didn't you say that you are solely responsible for it?
How do you do things?
leader
I'm still investigating this matter
What else to check?
It must be your Bai Yutang
Cooperate with them inside and outside
I tried to get them to sneak in.
You are smart
Recruit Bai Yutang in
Do you think you can lead others by the nose?
In fact, you were fooled
leader
Now Zhan Zhao already knows your big plan for the birthday banquet
It will definitely cause trouble at that time
I beg for your life
Invite me before the birthday banquet
Get rid of this serious problem
You get rid of him?
I heard that Dad is going to fight him to a draw.
You said you wanted to get rid of him?
Okay, this matter
It's up to you to arrange it
yes
Must be before the birthday party
Get rid of Zhan Zhao
father
When the child comes back
I saw that boy from the Ding family
He smells of alcohol
It seems like I just came back from a restaurant
Drunk?
I don’t know
He is really drunk
Or are you pretending to be drunk?
Lost Jiao Chaogui
Those old guys won't give in so easily.
You need to hit it twice.
That's the case
I will let them see clearly what happened to the Ding family
Let them know what will happen if they go against me
Ding Zhaohui will keep it for now
I want to be at the birthday banquet
Operate on him
Use him to sacrifice the flag
-Brother Zhan-Are you awake?
Why don't you sleep more?
There's something on my mind, I can't sleep well
I want to go to Tangmen as soon as possible
With the antidote, I don’t believe Brother Bai won’t come back
Then I'll trouble you
I see that the candles in your room are not extinguished all night long
Are you also thinking about saving people?
yes
I already have a preliminary plan
But only a few of us participated
is not enough
What do you want from me?
Things in Hanshui Palace are complicated
If there's nothing important
I'll take my leave now
I want to rescue Yulian from Jingfu
and the girls from Zhongxiao Academy
I don’t know the moon messenger
Can you make a recommendation on your behalf?
Take me to see Grandma Hanshui?
Do you want grandma to help you?
Grandma won't help you
Although grandma sympathizes with the plight of the girl from Zhongxiao Academy,
But with her temper
We will never let the entire Hanshui Palace take risks
What's more, now
Zhongxiao Academy is heavily guarded
Intelligence is waiting for an opportunity to attack you
This situation
How do you save people?
Even if there is only one ten thousandth hope
I must try my best too
The heroine stops
Stop
careful…
One foot has a love Gu seedling, and one foot has a blood withered grass.
Linglong, what grudge do you have against these darlings like me?
Come out, don't step on them, be careful...
Bringing you a very novel poison
I guarantee you haven’t seen it
Spare me and read countless poisons
It’s rare to see such an exquisite poison
Wonderful
Is there an antidote?
Three months?
three days
If it takes three months
I am the young master of the Tang clan
Wouldn’t he become a person who has gained a reputation in vain?
I know you, the young master of the Tang Clan, have no problem
exquisite
Although I can prepare this antidote, I don't want to prepare it
Unless you give me an explanation
Otherwise I will never help you
What explanation?
What are you asking for?
After you escaped from marriage
Why didn't you come to me instead of looking for Xiao Zhao?
you don't know
He showed off to me in the letter
besides
You and Zhan Zhao just met by chance.
Why did you go wandering around the world with him?
You don’t even know how to come and take a look at me
Wandering around the world?
Zhan Zhao and I went to handle a case and were very busy.
You two are born and die together
Then wouldn’t he soon fall in love with me, my childhood sweetheart?
- On an equal footing? - alright
It's important to save people
Besides, I’m not here today just to show off.
It’s for Bai Yutang
Why is there still something about Bai Yutang?
Why is it so messy?
What are you thinking about?
in your heart
I do everything just for the sake of my children's love
Can't it be for fairness and justice?
Talk about business
Yoma Tenichigo
It is related to the lives of many people in the world.
Preparing an antidote is not something to be trifled with
All right
I actually want to help you
I'm just worried
My uncle will be very upset if he knows about this
Your uncle's position as head of the family
Didn't your father pass it on to him?
You, the young master of the Tang clan
Are you still afraid of him?
I actually…
Didn't you always complain to me about what he did?
Now you have grown up
It's time to have your own opinion
Prepare an antidote
It's the first step to resist him
Do I resist him?
Just me...
no…
Could it be that you can't prepare the antidote?
He said three days
boast
Three days, three days
I will never break my promise
Brother Zhan, I understand your plan.
I just thought of someone
Maybe you have the same thoughts as me
can help us
Just now
The Jing family stopped all birthday banquets
It seems that I am trying my best to get rid of you
To avoid future troubles
Brother Zhan
You have no chance to sneak in
Zhaohui, don’t worry
Be sure to protect yourself first
If danger is discovered
Be sure to evacuate in time
Okay, I'll go first then
Has Zhan Zhao gone in?
Yes, do it now?
etc.
Wait a moment
Brother Zhan
Xiao Tang has already agreed to the antidote.
There are all intellectual people out there, let’s go quickly
Brother Bai
Hand over the dog officer
Thing that threatens you with intelligence
we all know
There is no antidote for Ye Motian at all
Don’t be constrained by intelligence
Make friends