( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[Episode 8]
So you've seen the contents of this letter.
Yes.
[Ferreting Out Crime]
What was written in it?
It was sent from Western Xia to the Song court.
The writer claims to be descended
from a maid of Emperor Taizu.
It is claimed that Emperor Taizong
did not ascend the throne
through any secret legitimate pact
but through usurpation,
with solid evidence to prove it.
After you delivered this letter to the Prince,
you did not return to the capital immediately.
What were you doing?
I went to visit a friend
and handle some personal matters.
Your visits to your friends began
at the very same time those whispers appeared.
- That was...
- Chief Justice Cheng,
because I've read the letter
and because I was off duty for a few days,
you see me as the culprit?
Are you being too hasty?
Guard Zhan, you may not know.
Since I took over this case,
I have tried to trace the source
among those spreading the rumors.
But I found nothing.
I can only shift my perspective
by investigating those who handled the letter.
Prince Hui and His Majesty are related.
He will never spread such rumors.
But as for you, Guard Zhan...
Rather than me,
the one who received this letter
has far more reason to spread the rumors.
You has a point.
However, the recipient's name
is not mentioned anywhere in the letter.
After days of hard work,
the Dali Court only found the middleman
who facilitated contact between
Western Xia and the recipient.
Then if you interrogate the middleman,
you might find clues about the recipient.
Can't do that.
Why?
Don't worry.
His Lordship's subordinate, He Bo,
has already made his move.
In Xiangzhou,
is there anything he can't do?
Guard Zhan,
have you ever seen this man?
I saw him once at Yicheng court.
Just once?
The whole of Yicheng court points
to you.
This man can unlocks the whole case.
They murdered him
to shut his mouth.
And to give themselves a reason
to come after me openly.
Zhan Zhao.
How long will you feign ignorance?
Two days ago,
the Yicheng magistrate reported this evidence
and the details of the case.
He said that not long ago, he discovered
a border market official who,
while the Song was trading with Western Xia,
exchanged intelligence with Western Xia.
Upon closer investigation,
he discovered that
his own constable, Liu Hong Yi,
was also involved.
He detained them both immediately.
Just as he was about to interrogate them,
a man in white suddenly appeared.
He killed them both and took away
the evidence of treason and collusion.
Justice has a long arm.
When the man in white escaped,
the guards saw his face clearly.
This culprit is none other than
you.
I was indeed there that day.
But I did not kill anyone.
Liu Hong Yi was not an accomplice
of that border market official.
On the contrary, it was he who discovered
that the border market official was a traitor.
Then do you have a witness?
The only witness is
Liu Hong Yi.
He has already been killed.
No one can testify for you.
[Ferreting Out Crime]
But your intrusion into Yicheng court
was witnessed by everyone there.
According to them,
you, Liu Hong Yi and the border market official
were all in cahoots.
When you saw that they were detained,
you feared they would expose you,
so you killed them.
That's utter nonsense.
What proof do you have?
You once went to Liu Hong Yi's house.
You must have burned every trace
of your little alliance by now.
How did that border market official die?
Was an autopsy performed?
According to the coroner's findings,
he died from a sharp weapon.
Based on the wound,
the murder weapon had a four-inch tip
and a one-foot blade.
It doesn't match the long sword
you usually carries.
However, if you wanted to kill them,
you wouldn't be so foolish
as to use your own sword.
As you said,
if I wanted to kill them,
it would be to prevent my plans
or those of my superiors from being leaked.
Then why would I deliver the letter
to Prince Hui
and allow its contents to be spread?
Chief Justice Cheng,
don't you think your argument
is self-contradictory?
How is it contradictory?
You were pursued the whole way.
You handed the letter to Prince Hui.
For one reason only.
To shake off the men chasing you.
You killed your accomplices
to keep them from speaking.
You spread treasonous words
to build momentum for what you have planned.
If you truly intend to cause chaos
and raise an army in rebellion,
isn't this current state of rampant rumors
just a part of your plan?
Chief Justice Cheng,
you don't seem to care about the truth.
You just want to do everything you can
to prove that
I'm the mastermind behind it all.
Guard Zhan, why do you say that?
The two key figures in this case,
Liu Hong Yi and that official, were dead,
but we can look into how they lived.
By tracing the people and things
they were in contact with,
we could find the real mastermind.
I'm afraid you haven't done any of that,
Chief Justice Cheng.
Guard Zhan,
are you trying to teach me
how to investigate a case?
I wouldn't dare.
You've been on the court for years.
Of course you know how to do it.
You just don't care about the truth.
You don't care if the real culprit is caught.
You don't care
if the Song Empire's classified intelligence
is being passed to Western Xia
by that mastermind.
You only care
if you can use this case
to convict me,
and thereby topple Kaifeng Court.
How dare you!
[Impartial and Incorruptible]
Are you accusing me of personal revenge?
Over the years,
many who lost their cases at Dali Court
have come to Kaifeng Court and cried injustice.
After consulting His Majesty,
Lord Bao retried and overturned many cases.
I used to think you were incompetent.
But now, it seems
you are just good at distorting the truth.
The Chief Justice of Dali Court.
What a key post.
And it's held by a snake like you.
How ridiculous is it?
Zhan Zhao,
you've finally shown your true colors.
Based on your last words, I can conclude
that you're dissatisfied with the court
and His Majesty's appointments.
No wonder you're involved in
such a major case of treason.
- Guards!
- Yes!
Beat him.
Beat him until he confesses.
Chief Justice Cheng,
you modified the torture device for me.
I didn't expect the great Dali Court
would resort to such dirty tricks.
What a cunning trap.
While escorting the letter,
the more tight-lipped Zhan Zhao remained,
the more unfavorable it would be for him.
If Zhan Zhao was the only one
who had access to the letter,
they could insist
that Zhan Zhao was the mole.
Judging by the situation,
that corrupt official will torture him.
Xiao Zhao,
you know a lot of people in the capital.
Can you ask how far the case has progressed?
No problem.
Let's split up.
Ming Zhu and I will return to Kaifeng Court.
We'll see what Lord Bao says.
Ling Long,
gather more information with Prince Xiao Zhao.
We'll meet back here tonight.
Then plan our next move.
Alright.
See you tonight, Brother Ding.
No need to call me Brother Ding.
From now on, call me
Brother Bai.
Brother Bai?
Zhan Zhao,
confess now and put your seal on it,
and you'll be spared the pain that's coming.
Have you made up your mind?
Confess,
or not?
It seems you haven't made up your mind yet.
Keep beating him.
Beat him until he makes up his mind.
What are you doing?
Chief Justice Cheng,
you still dare claim
there's nothing amiss with this torture device?
[Impartial and Incorruptible]
Well done, Zhan Zhao.
How dare you use force in this court?
You are flouting the law!
Tomorrow, I will report this to His Majesty.
I'm not the one who flouted the laws,
but you are,
by twisting them for your own ends.
I follow
the law of justice and right,
not the law of a single man like you.
What are you all standing there for?
Take him back to prison!
I will report Zhan Zhao's actions
to His Majesty,
then schedule another hearing.
Don't bother.
I will go back myself.
About everything that happened in court today,
please report it soon.
His Majesty should hear
how Chief Justice Cheng twisted a case
with no clear facts or evidence
into what he calls a closed matter.
You corrupt officials
have delayed this case without end.
The one who suffers is
the security of the entire realm.
Now, from Xiangzhou to the capital,
everyone is treating that letter as a joke.
The government is hunting down
so-called rumor-leakers,
causing widespread public resentment.
You handled this very well.
His Lordship is very satisfied.
But there is one thing I don't understand.
I hope you can enlighten me, Si Ming.
We went to great lengths
to capture Zhan Zhao before,
fearing the letter's contents would be leaked.
But now, His Lordship
is publicizing the contents on a large scale.
Wouldn't that ruin his years of planning?
His Lordship has his own reasons
for everything he does.
As for why,
when you see him tomorrow,
you can ask him in person.
Even if we killed that border market official,
the charges against Zhan Zhao aren't ironclad.
At most, he'll be charged with
dereliction of duty
and leaking imperial secrets.
The goal was never to make the charge ironclad.
I set this trap
specifically to lure Zhan Zhao to the capital.
Now that he is in that prison,
it is enough.
Prince Xiao Zhao.
What did you find out?
Cheng did indeed torture Zhan Zhao.
Ling Long and I have discussed it.
Tomorrow I'll see the Emperor.
I'll tell him Cheng Hao
broke the law for revenge.
And I'll ask that he be removed from this case.
It will be too late.
What do you mean?
I was around the Dali Court.
I saw the Five Venoms of Xiuluo Cult
disguised as guards,
and entered the prison.
They aren't trying to prove Zhan Zhao's guilt.
They want to take advantage of his imprisonment
to pull him up by the roots.
I'm afraid
that Zhan Zhao's friends
won't just stand by while he's in danger.
Only if they go there
can Zhan Zhao's charges
of colluding with rebels
to commit murder and escape prison
be made ironclad.
That way,
Zhan Zhao can be executed immediately.
Don't worry.
They will show mercy to your future wife.
Just you alone?
Not everyone is here yet.
Should we wait a bit longer?
No need.
Didn't only two of you
from the Five Venoms show up?
You're wrong.
The others are inside.
Once the fighting starts,
they will immediately end Zhan Zhao's life.
Can you slow down a bit?
We're rushing to save people. I can't.
When did Guard Zhan make a friend like you?
You don't strike me as a righteous man.
You look more like a complete bandit leader.
They want to kill Zhan Zhao in prison.
They'll invent a crime and make it stick.
We need His Majesty's word to save Zhan Zhao.
Nothing else is safe.
How many people in this world
dare to break into the Palace at night?
You're quite bold.
Aren't you afraid of infuriating the Emperor?
I'll take full responsibility.
Who's there?
- Your turn.
- Take him!
Stop it!
It's me.
I need to speak with His Majesty.
Your skills are decent,
but you still need more practice.
No need to lose your life tonight.
Leave now.
Zhan Zhao is the only one we need to kill.
Are you all right?
Let's go.
Zhan Zhao.
Confess now,
and you might just save your life.
[Dali Court]
That such a treacherous minister
exists right under the Emperor's nose.
You again.
Even Prince Hui cannot protect you today.
Take him.
The imperial token is here.
Let's see who dares to move.
Lord Cheng,
could I borrow two more horses?
Give them.
Take a shelter from the rain.
Since we have the token,
they won't do anything to us.
Prince Xiao Zhao brought you into the Palace?
Reversed.
I was the one who brought him in.
- You broke into the Imperial Palace?
- Yes.
On this trip to the capital,
I've accomplished another great feat.
There will be another great tale of Master Bai.
When you let yourself be caught,
I thought your job had made you a fool,
waiting to die in prison.
I didn't expect that you had some guts left.
You actually managed to escape.
I told you.
I entered this game first for the people,
and second to see what they're after.
I certainly won't sit back and wait to die.
Whether the Dali Court can hold you or not
is entirely up to you, Lord Zhan.
Here, take it back.
Both of you have a sword now.
But I don't even have a proper sword of my own.
This one is for you.
What kind of junk is this?
I don't want one from those venoms.
Remember this. You owe me a big favor.
You are charged with securing a sword for me.
Young Master.
We should take a short break here.
Wait for Prince Xiao Zhao.
He has a message for you.
Guard Zhan.
This is from His Majesty.
He had Dali Temple take your case.
The situation left him no choice.
After Cheng Hao received
the report from the Yicheng County Magistrate,
he conspired with several high officials
who are usually at odds with Kaifeng Court.
They submitted a joint report
demanding you be dealt with severely.
His Majesty trusts your character.
He knows you would never commit treason.
He thought this case would go nowhere.
Just a formality in Cheng Hao's hands.
But he never expected
they would try to kill you in prison.
His Majesty is too kind.
I am fine.
These are just minor wounds.
In recent years, the Song Empire
has always been at a disadvantage
in negotiations and trade with Western Xia.
Western Xia always seems to know
our intentions in advance.
They see right through our cards.
To be honest, His Majesty has always suspected
there are Western Xia spies in the court.
The secret letter you brought back this time
confirms His Majesty's suspicions.
Regarding the person
who is corresponding with the enemy,
Guard Zhan,
what do you think?
I've been hunted
by the authorities in Xiangzhou.
And by countless swords from the wilds as well.
Even Zhong Xiong, the Flying Trident Guardian,
was involved.
He even said
the mastermind had done him a favor.
In my opinion,
the only person capable of this,
and who would directly benefit
from the spread of the letter's contents,
is one man.
The Lord of Xiangyang.
That royal uncle of mine
has been entrenched in Xiangzhou for years.
His influence is not to be trifled with.
He publicly spread the letter's contents
so brazenly this time.
It indicates
that he is not far from starting a rebellion.
[Lord of Xiangyang]
Your Highness.
Are you getting used to that sword?
Thank you for the gift, Your Highness.
This sword is incredibly sharp.
It is a rare, top-quality blade.
People says Western Xia's swords are superior.
It seems they are right.
I have heard that
this cold-forging technique
was brought there by our own craftsmen.
Yes.
But do you know
whose hands
this technique
originally came from?
It came from
that Shangui under your command.
Indeed.
It originated from the Shangui family.
Now that you have this technique,
aren't you one step closer
to your great cause?
You put in a lot of effort
in the pursuit of Zhan Zhao.
But I am still not satisfied.
I have failed you.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
He Bo's men
are mostly rogues and wanderers.
When they act,
they rely on brute force.
Why are you acting just like them?
Blindly chasing after Zhan Zhao,
with no regard for the consequences
of causing such a commotion.
Sit.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Now that the letter's contents
are known to everyone,
the emperor, my nephew,
always known for his benevolence,
won't dare to move against me.
If he were to strike now,
wouldn't that just prove
that the letter is true?
What I am worried about is He Bo.
You caused such a scene
trying to kill Zhan Zhao.
You didn't expect you to
expose yourself so much.
Si Ming already took action last night.
Zhan Zhao.
We can manage him.
I don't think so.
His plans may seem thorough,
but there are always variables.
He underestimated
the true strength of the Southern Knight.
If I had
a general like Zhan Zhao under my command,
my great cause would surely succeed.
Forget it.
Since the word is out,
stop pursuing Zhan Zhao for now.
Step up our operations immediately.
Do not slack off.
Yes.
I will keep that in mind.
Go.
Blackie.
His Majesty told me
that Western Xia has been restless lately.
He has heard about what happen in Xiangzhou.
His Majesty concerned
that the Lord of Xiangyang and Western Xia
had already reached a tacit understanding.
If we rashly move against him now,
it will only drive them to join forces.
His Majesty needs you
to return to Xiangzhou
to investigate his conspiracy,
find a weakness, and crush it.
Okay.
I understand His Majesty's intent.
His Majesty will only let Lord Bao
know your mission this time.
If you need it,
that imperial token
can be used to mobilize the army for your use.
It is currently in Brother Bai's hands.
Alright. The Emperor's message
has all been delivered.
Don't look for me again.
Please tell His Majesty
that Zhan Zhao will give his all.
However, I have one favor to ask.
The people are innocent. Please--
I know. His Majesty had already instructed me.
The matter of the rumors ends here.
No one else will be drowned in.
His Majesty is benevolent.
It is a blessing for the people.
Zhan, I'm going with you.
This journey is dangerous.
There's no need for you
to keep risking your life with me.
Go back to the capital with the Prince.
I helped you deliver that thing to the capital.
Now you won't let me participate?
Too late. I'm seeing this through to the end.
Guard Zhan,
Ling Long just has that kind of temper.
Let her join.
I still have a few words for Prince Xiao Zhao.
Alright, go ahead.
I'm fine.
Hey, genius.
I have an official errand.
Go back to the capital with the Prince.
Another errand?
Young Master, you're covered in injuries.
Can you not wait until your wounds have healed?
You can't even rest in the capital
for two days?
It's urgent.
We can't delay any longer.
Alright.
Lord Bao is truly far-sighted.
He had Gong Sun prepare medicine
for your external injuries.
There are also clothes in the carriage.
Remember to change into them.
Practice your riding then.
I'll check on you when I return.
You're coming back with Zhan Zhao later?
We'll have plenty of time
to see each other in the future.
Good luck to you.
Leave a horse for Prince Xiao Zhao.
After all the chaos last night,
I doubt he'll sit in a carriage for a while.
Right now,
I'm truly seeing you in a new light.
You seem like a real prince now.
No.
More like a hero we all admired
when we were kids.
I don't really like how I showed just now.
It's far too exhausting.
I still prefer the name Xiao Zhao,
who used to go to Tianxiang Restaurant
with Ling Long,
to eat roasted meals and drink alcohol.
People have to grow up.
We all have to grow up eventually.
You and Guard Zhan faced challenges
and have grown up a lot.
Perhaps the next time we meet,
I will have become a true heroine.
See you.
Ling Long.
Take care of yourself.
I know.
Get in the carriage, Master Zhan.
The carriage is too slow. I'll ride a horse.
With those injuries,
how fast do you think you can ride?
If you get hurt again, we'll be caring for you.
Just listen to us.
Where are we going?
Our new coachman here should know the way.
If the master doesn't speak up,
how would a coachman know where to go?
Xiangzhou.
Yicheng County.
How could Prince Xiao Zhao
have the nerve to make you do this?
He really doesn't value your life.
And you actually agreed?
Yicheng County, Xiangzhou.
Fine, fine.
Your Highness,
Ming Zhu Er has really changed after this trip.
He even knows how to ride a horse now.
What's wrong? Are you envious?
What's there to be envious of?
Eating roasted pigeons in the capital every day
is what's enviable.
But Ling Long doesn't think so.
Being a hero is exhausting.
But all the girls in this world
only admire heroes.
- Your Highness...
- No.
Ling Long wants to be a heroine herself.
Your Highness, don't be discouraged.
Your eighth marriage is failed.
But you have the ninth one.
On the wanderer list ladies in the capital
most want to marry,
you beat Guard Zhan and are ranked first.
Wait a minute.
It's already strange enough
that I'm ranked ahead of Guard Zhan.
But why am I even on this list of wanderers?
Because I use your money to create this list.
Good.
You shall be rewarded.
Your Highness.
You've been busy all night.
You must be hungry.
Let's go back to the capital
and have some roasted pigeons.
- Let's go.
Your Highness.
Will you ride a horse or take the carriage?
You take the carriage.
I prefer riding a horse now.
Fine. Take it back.
What's so great about this?
As if I really wanted it.
Those who stand in the imperial court
really aren't any good.
Who provoked you this time?
I heard Lord Bao is upright and just,
a rare and good official.
I didn't expect him to be such a cunning fox.
How would you say that about Lord Bao?
Why do you think I broke into the Palace?
It's because he kept sighing
and dropping hints.
He implied that Zhan Zhao
would be in danger at night.
The truth is, he's wagering my life.
I'm his blade. Nothing more.
And couldn't even speak plainly about it.
What a scholar-official.
Is that so?
You can ask him.
Do you want another Linglong Honey?
Where is my Linglong Honey?
Here, take it back.
I didn't take it on purpose.
- Here.
- Keep it safe.
This Linglong Honey.
You must keep it well.
- But...
- He's lying.
He's singling me out on purpose.
You blind to that?
You deserve it.
I was just curious.
I heard Linglong Honey is like a miracle.
I'll get injured one day just to try it.
This is medicine.
Why are you so eager to try it? Are you mad?
Since you said I'm mad,
I should take a few more of these.
Why should all the good stuff go to Zhan Zhao?
You smiled.
Since you smiled, stop being angry.
You'll still have to call me
Brother Bai from now on.
How old are you?
26.
Then I am older than you.
Little Bai.
Forget about calling you Brother Bai.
With your looks,
I don't believe you're older than me.
Even nonsense has its limits.
You can talk nonsense, but I can't?
If you don't like the name Little Bai,
then how about Mouse Bai, Old Bai,
Bai Yu Tang, or Rat Bai?
Take your pick.
You're still laughing?
I truly underestimated you.
I didn't expect you to have so many tricks.
Let me ask you.
When you broke into the Palace at night,
was it really just to get that imperial token?
Nothing else?
Nothing else.
Get some rest.
If discovered,
we'll all lose our heads.
What are we going to do?
It's quite cute.
Cute? At a time like this?
[Zhao Zhen, the Emperor]
Keep it.
It looks good.